<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722233547 +0000" stop="20250723021257 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Affair</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman abandoned by her mother and raised by her father has a miscarriage which derails her life. In an attempt to find support, she seeks out her married sister, only to find herself in a toxic affair.</desc>
    <date>20231219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/2d1f214a16ce14019eec4e0e82615bc6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723021257 +0000" stop="20250723052603 +0000">
    <title>Bumher</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Jalisa Church finds her fiancé Tim 24 hours after he proposes in bed with another, it leads her to find love in a very unusual way after meeting a man named Jacob Reaves.</desc>
    <date>20240220</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/plex/0ecd626e-63aa-4c4f-9377-04f3a78a46b6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723052603 +0000" stop="20250723071342 +0000">
    <title>Triangle Slave</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Orphaned brothers Keith and Kareem struggle in the world today after loosing their mother was murdered by their father to pay a debt. Through adversary and perseverance, they rose to become two of the biggest drug kingpins in Philadelphia. But when a woman named Sapphire comes between them, will their empire collapse under the weight of their greed and jealousy?</desc>
    <date>20221124</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/j8kG5Fs57NtHu8ta9G7mHA6XHuD.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723071342 +0000" stop="20250723094020 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Betrayal</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jerry, a recently unemployed accountant, and his wife Stephanie face financial struggles after Jerry loses his job. They invite Jerry's best friend and mentor, Lionel, a music producer, to stay with them. Lionel turns out to be manipulative and begins a rivalry between Jerry and his friend Shawn. Lionel also tries to seduce Stephanie by exploiting her financial vulnerability. This betrayal leads to a chain of events that ends tragically, revealing a dark side of Jerry that he never knew existed.</desc>
    <date>20231030</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/ultimate_betrayal_1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723094020 +0000" stop="20250723113408 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Ira Reid: Haverford College's Unsung Scholar Activist</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Dr. Ira De Augustine Reid, was a prominent sociologist and proficient writer who wrote on the lives of black immigrants and communities throughout the United States. Follow along his story of perseverance and relentless pursuit and how he became the first tenured African-American Faculty member of Haverford College and left a historical impact on the world of academia.</desc>
    <date>20241105</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723113408 +0000" stop="20250723132043 +0000">
    <title>Everything I Never Expected</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Opposites attract when a spoiled bachelor and a broke college grad accidentally become roommates. Forced to cohabitate in a less-than-ideal apartment, they clash, prank, and eventually fall for each other. Life challenges and misunderstandings complicate their budding romance, but true love prevails.</desc>
    <date>20241126</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzI3ZjIwN2MtODEzZS00ZGZlLTlkM2EtODZjMjlkNjdjMWNmXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723132043 +0000" stop="20250723145558 +0000">
    <title>Bad For You</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Paris McMillan works as an undercover FBI agent taking down known crime rings in the city. When she meets Liam after a one-night stand, she discovers that he is her next target. Now she has to make the difficult decision about loyalty or love.</desc>
    <date>20240903</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a3yowEoFSVGqhduH67qNihZFNSz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723145558 +0000" stop="20250723170659 +0000">
    <title>Bissonnet</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Drea gets kicked out of school, she turns to the streets to make some money. What she does not know is that fast money and life on the streets of Bissonnet come at a high price.</desc>
    <date>20230911</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/753ccd725d09bb602026b2fea4ea48f1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723170659 +0000" stop="20250723184646 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723184646 +0000" stop="20250723201031 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWVkNzQ1MjAtYmNjZS00NDc0LTg0YzktNzVlNGViODYyMmUxXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723201031 +0000" stop="20250723214549 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723214549 +0000" stop="20250723234356 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lC6QNvelSJtOzkzzEC6D6jn1Hh3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250723234356 +0000" stop="20250724010648 +0000">
    <title>Bissonnet 2: Back on the Blade</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A serial killer is prowling Bissonnet street in Houston, and is targeting prostitutes. Detective Wallace and Benjamin are on the case, and will stop at nothing to bring him to justice.</desc>
    <date>20240404</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/2757aba1bb9e8dcd0e683421d3edde8b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
