<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359">
    <display-name>Toon Goggles</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/1a85f23b-2648-4636-af3d-1d69b3721200/toongoggles_logo_light_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716010000 +0000" stop="20250716013000 +0000">
    <title>Roger</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The lively adventures of a little girl, the carefree, joyful and occasionally perky Fatou, and an alien, the clumsy Roger, on a tropical island… Throughout their adventures, they trigger small accidents that sometimes grow into major disasters, but (almost) always end on a happy note. In short, Roger and Fatou spend their time saving the island from their own mistakes and blunders.</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/roger_2048x1536_series_banner_v1_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716013000 +0000" stop="20250716020000 +0000">
    <title>Angry Birds Toons</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Check out Angry Birds Toons compilations! Each compilation has several episodes from your favorite shows including Angry Birds, Piggy Tales, and Stella!</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/ab_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716020000 +0000" stop="20250716023000 +0000">
    <title>Woodventures</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Woodventures" is an animated series for preschool children. The main characters are wooden toys: Kitty Meow, Doggy Woof-Woof, Piggy Oink, Horsey Yee-Ho-Ho and Elephant Pawoo. The toys live in a small wooden town (the prototype of a child's play room). Every toy has its own unique personality and reacts to different circumstances appropriately. With the help of the invisible narrator, the toys, along with the audience solve different tasks, play and take part in adventures. "Woodventures" is a musical series with lots of songs and dances. Some of the songs represent our characters and appear in each series, and some of the songs are related to the events in the series, so it is only found in that particular episode.Each episode presents a playful and learning environment.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/woodventures.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716023000 +0000" stop="20250716030000 +0000">
    <title>Cutie Cubies</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An animation series about the adventures of four aliens - Cubies: Captain, Boatswain, Navigator, and Doctor. Having arrived on our planet and disguised as representatives of the local flora and fauna of the cubic form: a yellow chicken, a red rabbit, a blue aquarium and a bush of green grass, they are learning the diverse phenomena of our planet Earth.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/cutie_cubies.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716030000 +0000" stop="20250716033000 +0000">
    <title>Ollie! The Boy Who Became What He Ate</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ollie is a 6-year-old with a massive imagination, often lost in his own world - flipping, sliding, climbing and rocket-blasting through the house, practicing at being the master of all things. But even masters need to stop and refuel. When meals or snack time interrupt Ollie’s play, he finds himself confronted with the real challenge of childhood; trying new food. To escape his predicament, Ollie uses his magic spoon to transport himself, along with his sister Poppy, and her stuffy Nummy, to a food planet filled with adventure and the very food Ollie stuck his spoon into.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/ollietheboywhobecamewhatheate.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716033000 +0000" stop="20250716040000 +0000">
    <title>Heroes of Envell</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Present days. Saint Petersburg. Four friends – Art, Kira, Phil and Vic are the coolest gamers in school. Eventually they find a suspicious laptop with «Heroes of Envell» game installed on it. Turns out that this very laptop is a portal to another dimension, a game realm which is full of adventures and real-life danger. The game realm is a blend of medieval, steampunk and futurism. You never know what really awaits our heroes. Just like the design of the game, the game logic is very unpredictable. You start with a quest and then it becomes a race right until it all grows into a tricky brainteaser. But be sure about one thing – there is no boring or easy way in here. The game realm is a blend of medieval, steampunk and futurism. You never know what really awaits our heroes. Just like the design of the game, the game logic is very unpredictable. You start with a quest and then it becomes a race right until it all grows into a tricky brainteaser. But be sure about one thing – there is no boring or easy way in here.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/heroes_of_envell.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716040000 +0000" stop="20250716043000 +0000">
    <title>Plum the Super Witch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Plum is a perfectly normal 6-year-old witch who lives fun adventures trying to stop Elizandra from destroying her city.</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/plum_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716043000 +0000" stop="20250716050000 +0000">
    <title>AnimaCars</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jonny and the Rescue Team work hard to maintain peace. Every day there's a new challenge, every day a new chance for adventure.</desc>
    <date>20250122</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/acat2_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716050000 +0000" stop="20250716053000 +0000">
    <title>Talking Tom and Friends</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Things get even more epic in Season 3 as Talking Tom and Friends try new ways to make their dreams come true, making more friends (and enemies) along the way!</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/media_list/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/ttf-season-3-poster-final_1920x1080_10_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716053000 +0000" stop="20250716060000 +0000">
    <title>VIP Pets</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>We are the VIP Pets! The coolest pets with a passion for hair! We are best friends and together we will discover lots of beautiful hairstyles and go on exciting adventures!</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/vertical_poster_vp_serie_sinlogoyoutube_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716060000 +0000" stop="20250716063000 +0000">
    <title>Back to Back</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Embark on an electrifying journey as they boldly leap from one heart-pounding expedition to the next, fueled by their unbreakable bond and insatiable thirst for excitement. Get ready to be swept away in a whirlwind of adrenaline-pumping quests, where danger and discovery await them at every turn.</desc>
    <date>20250427</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/1280x1800_en_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716063000 +0000" stop="20250716070000 +0000">
    <title>Bat Pat</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The series follows the comedy adventures of Bat Pat and the Silver brothers Martin, Leo and Rebecca as they unravel mysteries and cross paths with supernatural creatures of the night that lurk, haunt, shriek and dig themselves up in every dark corner of their home in Fogville, a small town that seems to be the center of all things weird in the world, a veritable magnet to ghosts, mummies, witches, creatures, werewolves and things that go bump in the night. Bat Pat will prove that the supernatural isn’t always evil but just misunderstood. Our heroes will come to understand something important: the supernatural “bad guys” are not really bad, but normal people whose actions are misunderstood by the more inhabitants of Fogville and what they really want is... just help!</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bat-pat_en_1142x1600_v1_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716070000 +0000" stop="20250716073000 +0000">
    <title>TOBOT</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ryan and Kory are twin brothers with one big secret: They’re Tobot pilots.</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/tobot_christmas_1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716073000 +0000" stop="20250716080000 +0000">
    <title>Winx Club</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Winx Club is a fantasy saga revolving around six fairies and their adventures. The protagonists Bloom, Stella, Flora, Aisha, Tecna and Musa live their daily life on Magix world, among lessons, loves, quarrels and moments of strong friendship. At any moment, when needed, they can transform into super-heroines, ready to defeat evil and save who is in danger.</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/serie1_4x3_001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716080000 +0000" stop="20250716083000 +0000">
    <title>Grojband</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The story about 12 year old Corey that emotionally torments his sister so that she will write the ultimate lyrics for his garage band.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/grojband_whitebackground.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716083000 +0000" stop="20250716090000 +0000">
    <title>Monsuno</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The series revolves around re-awakened Monster DNA, called Monsuno, that finds its way into the unsuspecting hands of adventure-seeking teenagers Chase, Jinja, and Bren. Accompanied by their Monsuno, Lock, Charger, and Quickforce, they are searching for Chase's father Jeredy Suno, the creator of the Monsuno</desc>
    <date>20240425</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/monsuno_keyart_titlecard.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716090000 +0000" stop="20250716093000 +0000">
    <title>Paper Tales</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Animation series “Paper Tales” narrate to children audience in fascinating way amusing adventures of paper animals – a moose named Aristotle and a woodpecker named Knock-Knock – in paper land where everything is made only from paper. Merry adventures come together with entertaining insets “for crafty hands” when the audience learns how to produce all cartoon characters using paper, cardboard, scissors and glue. The project is supported with the site where all flat patterns are provided with the advices how to manufacture the paper world items.This is the way spectator gets involved into a peculiar game that brings out creative work and development of many useful practical skills, distracting kids from permanent attachment to a computer. The “Paper Tales” project is a fascinating and helpful alternative to computer-oriented pastime. The whole cartoon is accompanied by off-screen narrator’s text and exuberant flow of gags. Each episode is planned to last for 5 minutes (a version without insets – 4 minutes). Technique of performance is 3D computer graphics imitating paper application work.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/paper_tales.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716093000 +0000" stop="20250716100000 +0000">
    <title>Magic Lantern</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Animation series “Magic Lantern” tells little viewers wonderful adventure stories, based on classic literature plots. Little video games fan Mike and his smart sister Kate watch and discuss each story presented as a strip film. Funny stories will help seeing classic stories from the new side and prove that world classic literature is exciting and interesting.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/magic_lantern.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716100000 +0000" stop="20250716103000 +0000">
    <title>Invent'Tom</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Meet Tom, Car City’s very own inventor! In his high-tech lab, he creates the wackiest inventions to solve his friend’s problems.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/cc2tom_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716103000 +0000" stop="20250716110000 +0000">
    <title>Pincode 105-106</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Grown up Kikoriki characters rock the world with their scientific superpowers and tell the kids scientific facts in a most entertaining way. The crew follows Captain Pin as they learn about the world we live in and share this knowledge with us.</desc>
    <date>20250426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/pincode_1400x2000.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716110000 +0000" stop="20250716110748 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>Saving the Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s Ben’s Parade in Car City. Zitron escapes from jail, planning to ruin the fun, but Robo foils his plan.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/695c5e476b174752d3f36e3d2b1b23cc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716110748 +0000" stop="20250716111240 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Aliens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rodeo and Booster merge into Robo and set a trap for a rogue UFO that's abducted baby cars from the beach.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/35620c7933587ac0122b0a990356fc82.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716111240 +0000" stop="20250716111731 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>Ghost Busting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Time to merge! A "ghost" has stolen cakes from the cake-eating competition, Rodeo and Booster get ready to stop him.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/93a2b0b69cf7eb6fca19c87d9769d18f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716111731 +0000" stop="20250716112455 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Pipes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rodeo and Booster transform into Robo to catch Zitron after he steals Billy's pipes. Matilda the Police Car helps them.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/9d26523659ca1e160d05b4e149a4e3fa.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716112455 +0000" stop="20250716113000 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Sign</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The ice cream sign's disappeared! This can only be Zitron's handy work. Rodeo, Booster and Dane merge to stop the thief.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/8ac65735e196a750161a8e33a8847c8c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716113000 +0000" stop="20250716120000 +0000">
    <title>Tiny Town</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Join the friendly vehicles of Tiny Town as they play games, go on adventures and solve problems together.</desc>
    <date>20250228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/tt_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716120000 +0000" stop="20250716123000 +0000">
    <title>Lily's Lovely Song</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Lily and Tim create beautiful clay worlds inspired by English nursery rhymes. Sing along to lovable tunes in each episode.</desc>
    <date>20250228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/lily_s1_ep001_001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716123000 +0000" stop="20250716130000 +0000">
    <title>One Zeez</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The One Zeez make music as they explore our world, learning to stomp like a dinosaur, flip like a shark and jiggle like skeletons.</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/oz_ka01_p_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716130000 +0000" stop="20250716133000 +0000">
    <title>Ted the Train</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>All aboard the learning express! Ted is a train who teaches children about colours, animals, fruits, vegetables and more.</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/troy_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716133000 +0000" stop="20250716140000 +0000">
    <title>Construction Squad</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Construction Squad builds Car City brick by brick! They're proof that everything's possible with a little help from our friends.</desc>
    <date>20250222</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/cs_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716140000 +0000" stop="20250716143000 +0000">
    <title>Babies in Car City</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Babies are curious little cars whose sense of wonder always leads them into fantastic adventures—and sometimes trouble!</desc>
    <date>20250222</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/bb_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716143000 +0000" stop="20250716150000 +0000">
    <title>MINITUNS</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>MINITUNS presents an exciting and fun selection of children's songs, perfect to enjoy, dance and sing with the family. A world full of colors and melodies, designed to teach counting, care for the planet and enjoy the game.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/media_list/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/poster_art_minituns_1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716150000 +0000" stop="20250716153000 +0000">
    <title>Ollie! The Boy Who Became What He Ate</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ollie is a 6-year-old with a massive imagination, often lost in his own world - flipping, sliding, climbing and rocket-blasting through the house, practicing at being the master of all things. But even masters need to stop and refuel. When meals or snack time interrupt Ollie’s play, he finds himself confronted with the real challenge of childhood; trying new food. To escape his predicament, Ollie uses his magic spoon to transport himself, along with his sister Poppy, and her stuffy Nummy, to a food planet filled with adventure and the very food Ollie stuck his spoon into.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/ollietheboywhobecamewhatheate.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716153000 +0000" stop="20250716160000 +0000">
    <title>Heroes of Envell</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Present days. Saint Petersburg. Four friends – Art, Kira, Phil and Vic are the coolest gamers in school. Eventually they find a suspicious laptop with «Heroes of Envell» game installed on it. Turns out that this very laptop is a portal to another dimension, a game realm which is full of adventures and real-life danger. The game realm is a blend of medieval, steampunk and futurism. You never know what really awaits our heroes. Just like the design of the game, the game logic is very unpredictable. You start with a quest and then it becomes a race right until it all grows into a tricky brainteaser. But be sure about one thing – there is no boring or easy way in here. The game realm is a blend of medieval, steampunk and futurism. You never know what really awaits our heroes. Just like the design of the game, the game logic is very unpredictable. You start with a quest and then it becomes a race right until it all grows into a tricky brainteaser. But be sure about one thing – there is no boring or easy way in here.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/heroes_of_envell.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716160000 +0000" stop="20250716163000 +0000">
    <title>Plum the Super Witch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Plum is a perfectly normal 6-year-old witch who lives fun adventures trying to stop Elizandra from destroying her city.</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/plum_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716163000 +0000" stop="20250716170000 +0000">
    <title>AnimaCars</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jonny and the Rescue Team work hard to maintain peace. Every day there's a new challenge, every day a new chance for adventure.</desc>
    <date>20250122</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/acat2_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716170000 +0000" stop="20250716173000 +0000">
    <title>Talking Tom and Friends</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Things get even more epic in Season 3 as Talking Tom and Friends try new ways to make their dreams come true, making more friends (and enemies) along the way!</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/media_list/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/ttf-season-3-poster-final_1920x1080_10_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716173000 +0000" stop="20250716180000 +0000">
    <title>VIP Pets</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>We are the VIP Pets! The coolest pets with a passion for hair! We are best friends and together we will discover lots of beautiful hairstyles and go on exciting adventures!</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/vertical_poster_vp_serie_sinlogoyoutube_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716180000 +0000" stop="20250716183000 +0000">
    <title>Back to Back</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Embark on an electrifying journey as they boldly leap from one heart-pounding expedition to the next, fueled by their unbreakable bond and insatiable thirst for excitement. Get ready to be swept away in a whirlwind of adrenaline-pumping quests, where danger and discovery await them at every turn.</desc>
    <date>20250427</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/1280x1800_en_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716183000 +0000" stop="20250716190000 +0000">
    <title>Bat Pat</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The series follows the comedy adventures of Bat Pat and the Silver brothers Martin, Leo and Rebecca as they unravel mysteries and cross paths with supernatural creatures of the night that lurk, haunt, shriek and dig themselves up in every dark corner of their home in Fogville, a small town that seems to be the center of all things weird in the world, a veritable magnet to ghosts, mummies, witches, creatures, werewolves and things that go bump in the night. Bat Pat will prove that the supernatural isn’t always evil but just misunderstood. Our heroes will come to understand something important: the supernatural “bad guys” are not really bad, but normal people whose actions are misunderstood by the more inhabitants of Fogville and what they really want is... just help!</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bat-pat_en_1142x1600_v1_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716190000 +0000" stop="20250716193000 +0000">
    <title>TOBOT</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ryan and Kory are twin brothers with one big secret: They’re Tobot pilots.</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/tobot_christmas_1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716193000 +0000" stop="20250716200000 +0000">
    <title>Winx Club</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Winx Club is a fantasy saga revolving around six fairies and their adventures. The protagonists Bloom, Stella, Flora, Aisha, Tecna and Musa live their daily life on Magix world, among lessons, loves, quarrels and moments of strong friendship. At any moment, when needed, they can transform into super-heroines, ready to defeat evil and save who is in danger.</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/serie1_4x3_001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716200000 +0000" stop="20250716203000 +0000">
    <title>Grojband</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The story about 12 year old Corey that emotionally torments his sister so that she will write the ultimate lyrics for his garage band.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/grojband_whitebackground.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716203000 +0000" stop="20250716210000 +0000">
    <title>Monsuno</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The series revolves around re-awakened Monster DNA, called Monsuno, that finds its way into the unsuspecting hands of adventure-seeking teenagers Chase, Jinja, and Bren. Accompanied by their Monsuno, Lock, Charger, and Quickforce, they are searching for Chase's father Jeredy Suno, the creator of the Monsuno</desc>
    <date>20240425</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/monsuno_keyart_titlecard.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716210000 +0000" stop="20250716213000 +0000">
    <title>Paper Tales</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Animation series “Paper Tales” narrate to children audience in fascinating way amusing adventures of paper animals – a moose named Aristotle and a woodpecker named Knock-Knock – in paper land where everything is made only from paper. Merry adventures come together with entertaining insets “for crafty hands” when the audience learns how to produce all cartoon characters using paper, cardboard, scissors and glue. The project is supported with the site where all flat patterns are provided with the advices how to manufacture the paper world items.This is the way spectator gets involved into a peculiar game that brings out creative work and development of many useful practical skills, distracting kids from permanent attachment to a computer. The “Paper Tales” project is a fascinating and helpful alternative to computer-oriented pastime. The whole cartoon is accompanied by off-screen narrator’s text and exuberant flow of gags. Each episode is planned to last for 5 minutes (a version without insets – 4 minutes). Technique of performance is 3D computer graphics imitating paper application work.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/paper_tales.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716213000 +0000" stop="20250716220000 +0000">
    <title>Magic Lantern</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Animation series “Magic Lantern” tells little viewers wonderful adventure stories, based on classic literature plots. Little video games fan Mike and his smart sister Kate watch and discuss each story presented as a strip film. Funny stories will help seeing classic stories from the new side and prove that world classic literature is exciting and interesting.</desc>
    <date>20240730</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/magic_lantern.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716220000 +0000" stop="20250716223000 +0000">
    <title>Invent'Tom</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Meet Tom, Car City’s very own inventor! In his high-tech lab, he creates the wackiest inventions to solve his friend’s problems.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/cc2tom_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716223000 +0000" stop="20250716230000 +0000">
    <title>Pincode 105-106</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Grown up Kikoriki characters rock the world with their scientific superpowers and tell the kids scientific facts in a most entertaining way. The crew follows Captain Pin as they learn about the world we live in and share this knowledge with us.</desc>
    <date>20250426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/pincode_1400x2000.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716230000 +0000" stop="20250716230748 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>Saving the Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s Ben’s Parade in Car City. Zitron escapes from jail, planning to ruin the fun, but Robo foils his plan.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/695c5e476b174752d3f36e3d2b1b23cc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716230748 +0000" stop="20250716231240 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Aliens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rodeo and Booster merge into Robo and set a trap for a rogue UFO that's abducted baby cars from the beach.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/35620c7933587ac0122b0a990356fc82.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716231240 +0000" stop="20250716231731 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>Ghost Busting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Time to merge! A "ghost" has stolen cakes from the cake-eating competition, Rodeo and Booster get ready to stop him.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/93a2b0b69cf7eb6fca19c87d9769d18f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716231731 +0000" stop="20250716232455 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Pipes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rodeo and Booster transform into Robo to catch Zitron after he steals Billy's pipes. Matilda the Police Car helps them.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/9d26523659ca1e160d05b4e149a4e3fa.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716232455 +0000" stop="20250716233000 +0000">
    <title>RoboFuse</title>
    <sub-title>The Sign</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The ice cream sign's disappeared! This can only be Zitron's handy work. Rodeo, Booster and Dane merge to stop the thief.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/8ac65735e196a750161a8e33a8847c8c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250716233000 +0000" stop="20250717000000 +0000">
    <title>Tiny Town</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Join the friendly vehicles of Tiny Town as they play games, go on adventures and solve problems together.</desc>
    <date>20250228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/tt_ka01_lg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250717000000 +0000" stop="20250717003000 +0000">
    <title>Sprinter Galore</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The good-hearted Sprinter Galore is back at his home planet, battling evil villains bent.</desc>
    <date>20240402</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/widescreen/2000x2858/sprintergalore_keyart_16x9_1920x1080px.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250717003000 +0000" stop="20250717010000 +0000">
    <title>Winx Club</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Winx Club is a fantasy saga revolving around six fairies and their adventures. The protagonists Bloom, Stella, Flora, Aisha, Tecna and Musa live their daily life on Magix world, among lessons, loves, quarrels and moments of strong friendship. At any moment, when needed, they can transform into super-heroines, ready to defeat evil and save who is in danger.</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/serie1_4x3_001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f170d60b898490041b49359" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717013000 +0000">
    <title>Roger</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The lively adventures of a little girl, the carefree, joyful and occasionally perky Fatou, and an alien, the clumsy Roger, on a tropical island… Throughout their adventures, they trigger small accidents that sometimes grow into major disasters, but (almost) always end on a happy note. In short, Roger and Fatou spend their time saving the island from their own mistakes and blunders.</desc>
    <date>20250125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/tg/show/thumbnails/standard/2000x2858/roger_2048x1536_series_banner_v1_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
