<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710000925 +0000" stop="20250710005737 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lazy &amp; Entitled Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E68</episode-num>
    <desc>Tracy says her daughter, Ashley, 22, and Ashley’s boyfriend, Andrew, 23, are freeloaders who are living rent-free in her home, while she pays all of their expenses. She says they sleep all day and have let her beautiful suburban home turn to filth. Tracy says she accepts blame for allowing the situation to spiral out of control -- learn the one mistake she says she regrets the most. Ashley and Andrew deny the accusations and say they work part-time for Tracy’s business, and they’ve earned everything she's given them. See what happens when Dr. Phil cameras enter the home. Dr. Phil gets real with Ashley and Andrew -- and Tracy. Can he get through to them? Then, Lorrie and Todd say that their 13-year-old-daughter controls their home. The parents admit that they just can't seem to say no to the teen, who they say throws tantrums and manipulates them until she gets her way. Lorrie and Todd say they prepare special meals for her and cut her food -- and it’s putting a strain on their marriage. Dr. Phil shares his insight and devises a plan to get this family back on track. Plus, tune in to find out the three tips you must know to ensure you're not spoiling your child.</desc>
    <date>20130103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11068.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710005737 +0000" stop="20250710014420 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Child Molester or Innocent Solider?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E76</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman accused her ex-husband of molesting her daughter.</desc>
    <date>20140207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710014420 +0000" stop="20250710023014 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma Won't Believe I Was Abused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Two women face the grandmother who they say did not protect them for the first time in 7 years.</desc>
    <date>20141120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710023014 +0000" stop="20250710031657 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will She Apologize for Molester Husband?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E302</episode-num>
    <desc>Two women say their grandmother refuses to believe they were sexcually abused by their step-grandfather.</desc>
    <date>20141121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13302.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710031657 +0000" stop="20250710040328 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>An Obsessed Love Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Sandie says she desperately hopes to win back her ex-husband, Chris, so they can be a family again with their adopted 11-year-old daughter, but Chris’ ex-girlfriend, Aileen, will stop at nothing to keep them apart. Sandie says Aileen is stalking and harassing her, making false reports of abuse and neglect to CPS, and even created a fake profile on Facebook to talk trash about her -- and she wants Aileen prosecuted. Sandie says she and Chris have filed a total of nine peace orders against Aileen, but only the last one filed by Chris was granted, protecting him -- but not Sandie or their daughter. Aileen admits to intentionally causing trouble but says Sandie deserves it, because she destroyed Aileen’s relationship with Chris -- and she also wants him back. Chris says he’s tired of being caught in the middle of his exes and isn’t interested in a relationship with either one, other than co-parenting with Sandie -- but is he sending mixed messages? Can this trio reach a truce and learn to respect boundaries?</desc>
    <date>20140214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710040328 +0000" stop="20250710045001 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Nanny Affair (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Affairs, fights, lies and dark secrets threaten a marriage</desc>
    <date>20070912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710045001 +0000" stop="20250710053821 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Nanny Affair (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E302</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his look into the nanny affair that shattered a marriage</desc>
    <date>20070913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6302.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710053821 +0000" stop="20250710062510 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet Success</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E102</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca says her sister, Pamela, has repeatedly betrayed her by sleeping with the important men in her life, including her ex-husband, her child's father and even her current boyfriend. Rebecca confides that she feels so scorned that she now has a difficult time trusting anyone. Pamela admits that she made mistakes but says she's tired of feeling guilty, and she feels Rebecca needs to forgive her and move on. But is Rebecca ready to leave the past behind? Can Dr. Phil help repair their relationship? Then, Steve says that over the last five years, his girlfriend, Megan, has stolen nearly a half million dollars from him. He claims she has forged his name on checks, taken out credit cards in his name and has taken more than $167,000 from his elderly mother. Megan admits to taking the money but says she did it for a good reason. Is Megan with Steve for the love or the money? And, if Steve thinks it's for the money, why does he stay? Dr. Phil explains the 16 powerful tools that the world’s most successful people use, as outlined in his book, Life Code: The New Rules for Winning in the Real World. If you’re ready to stop being used and abused and start being a star in your own life, don’t miss this show!</desc>
    <date>20130212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11102.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710062510 +0000" stop="20250710071313 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brandon Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E71</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most asked-about guests, Brandon, returns with an update.</desc>
    <date>20100209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710071313 +0000" stop="20250710080014 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Husband’s Double Life Exposed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E51</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman uncovers a secret her husband of nearly 20 years was hiding.</desc>
    <date>20191126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710080014 +0000" stop="20250710084456 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Out of the Dog House!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil's guests are trying to dig themselves out of their self-made messes. Can a two-timing womanizer change his ways for good? Or is the saying, "Once a cheater, always a cheater" the truth?</desc>
    <date>20061129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710084456 +0000" stop="20250710093202 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Starving For Perfection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Have you ever looked in the mirror and thought, "If I could lose five more pounds, I'd be perfect"? Darlene and Jennifer have been starving themselves in the name of perfection, but are they also killing themselves on their quest?</desc>
    <date>20061116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710093202 +0000" stop="20250710101921 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Hit &amp; Run or Falsely Accused?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E104</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol and Tab’s 20-year-old son, Alex, was killed by a hit and run driver. They believe that Alex’s death was no accident and they accuse Rob, 24, of being responsible. Rob, joined by his mother, Linda, and sister, Lenora, 21, says he’s being falsely accused and placed in the middle of an “unrelenting witch hunt,” and he just wants everyone to move on. See what happens when he comes face to face with Alex’s family on Dr. Phil’s stage. Why wasn’t Rob tried on vehicular homicide charges? Hear from a crime scene reconstruction expert hired by the family. Has he uncovered new evidence? Don’t miss this riveting Dr. Phil mystery as the victim’s family confronts the young man they believe deliberately killed their son.</desc>
    <date>20130218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11104.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710101921 +0000" stop="20250710110633 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mom to Blame for Babies' Death?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E136</episode-num>
    <desc>A man accuses his ex-wife and her new husband of killing his children.</desc>
    <date>20140513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12136.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710110633 +0000" stop="20250710115302 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parents Accused of Murder (Part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E323</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his interview with Tommy, who accuses his ex-wife, Julia, and her new husband, Codey, of killing his 19-month-old son, Darby, and 4-year-old stepdaughter, Kiera -- an allegation the couple vehemently deny. Dr. Phil enlists the help of forensic pathologist Dr. Cyril Wecht to examine the children’s autopsy reports -- what are his findings? And, will Julia and Codey agree to take polygraph tests?</desc>
    <date>20140506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12323.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710115302 +0000" stop="20250710123914 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate My Daughter In Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Family conflict between a woman and her daghter-in-law.</desc>
    <date>20130207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710123914 +0000" stop="20250710132512 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E132</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil is launching his parenting boot camp and teaching parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7132.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710132512 +0000" stop="20250710141206 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E217</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7217.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710141206 +0000" stop="20250710145910 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E218</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7218.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710145910 +0000" stop="20250710154747 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E219</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7219.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710154747 +0000" stop="20250710163255 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat Ban</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Children kicked off flights, prohibited from eating in restaurants and banned from vacation hot spots -- from parents to patrons, today’s guests all have an opinion about what’s being called the “brat ban” policies that many places are adopting that enforce kid-free zones. Dr. Phil's first guest, Serita, took her 14-month-old son to her local public library, but when the boy became too noisy, Serita was not only told to leave -- she was arrested! Learn how the incident escalated and got both mother and son banned. Then, it made front page headlines when a shopper slapped a stranger’s toddler at Walmart. The man at the center of the controversy speaks publicly for the first time about the incident that landed him in jail. And, Pittsburgh restaurant owner Mike Vuick caused an uproar from angry parents when he banned children under 6 from his dining room. What caused Mike to impose the ban, and has business suffered or thrived as a result? Plus, is banning kids more about banning bad parenting? It's a polarizing question that has audience members at odds. And, find out how to keep your kid from becoming a brat!</desc>
    <date>20110912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710163255 +0000" stop="20250710171913 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Explosive Anger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nichole claims her husband gets violent when he drinks which he denies. And, Theresa and Steve say their son Steven’s rage is out of control, and they fear for their lives. Plus, two victims of a road rage incident caught on tape share their story.</desc>
    <date>20130927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710171913 +0000" stop="20250710180714 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat-Proof Your Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The challenge of taming tantrums in young children is examined.</desc>
    <date>20101202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710180714 +0000" stop="20250710185045 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Torn Between Two Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E48</episode-num>
    <desc>Her husband of 30 years suffered a mid-life crisis, had an affair and filed for divorce -- but now wants her back.</desc>
    <date>20131121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12048.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710185045 +0000" stop="20250710193739 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marriage Dilemmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E48</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil's guests say they saw several red flags before they walked down the aisle, but they looked the other way and still said, "I do."</desc>
    <date>20080410</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5048.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710193739 +0000" stop="20250710202456 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Fight Over Your Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E86</episode-num>
    <desc>"Let me take a moment to read a few lines of a heartbreaking letter of a 10-year-old boy caught in the middle of an ugly, ugly custody battle between his parents" Dr. Phil says. He reads, “I'm bawling my eyes out with the tears of sadness. Dad, I never thought I would say this, but I always think that you're with another girl or sleeping with another girl. Question for dad: Mom says she still loves you and misses you. Do you still love her? Put a check in one of the boxes: yes or no.”</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8086.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710202456 +0000" stop="20250710211217 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Lazy Husbands and Cling On Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When you think of negotiations, you may think of corporate boardrooms, but negotiating happens every day " even in your own house. Learn the principles of making a deal, how to compromise to get what you want and the biggest mistakes you can make when buying a new car. Plus, learn the five things you might not realize you can bargain for!</desc>
    <date>20091110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8032.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710211217 +0000" stop="20250710215826 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Am Right!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Would you rather be right or happy? Dr. Phil talks with some right-fighters who can't settle their debate.</desc>
    <date>20051018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4036.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710215826 +0000" stop="20250710224512 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Absentee Mom,Clueless Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E65</episode-num>
    <desc>John says that when his ex-wife, Laurie, moved 1,500 miles away to be with her boyfriend, Joe, she abandoned her children, and he was left to raise the couple’s three boys -- Johnny, 14, and twins Christopher and Alexander, 12 -- on his own. The single dad proudly proclaims that being a committed father makes him “one in a million” -- but is John really in over his head? John admits the boys disrespect his authority and recently, he says Alexander punched him in the face and gave him a black eye. Laurie says her children tell her that they aren’t happy living with their father, and she denies deserting her children -- but is she willing to step up and take Dr. Phil’s advice? Then, hear from the three boys. What do they reveal about their home life? And, is this a case of clueless parenting -- or unruly kids? No parent can afford to miss this all-new Dr. Phil!</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710224512 +0000" stop="20250710233305 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In-Law Threats!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>We've all heard of in-laws who don't get along, but these guests say their problems have become scary and even life-threatening.</desc>
    <date>20061018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710233305 +0000" stop="20250711001920 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Cold Blood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E413</episode-num>
    <desc>Revisiting the 1992 murder of Shanda Sharer, her family reflects on coping and forgiveness.</desc>
    <date>20110520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9413.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250711001920 +0000" stop="20250711010642 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Cold Blood Pt. 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E414</episode-num>
    <desc>The family of Shanda Sharer who was murdered confronts one of the convicted killers.</desc>
    <date>20110523</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9414.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
