<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250721234417 +0000" stop="20250722012833 +0000">
    <title>Ultimatums</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Roman visits recently engaged Luke and his sexually frustrated fiancé Mya. Mya is forced into an internal battle between being faithful to her fiancé and sexual tension between their new house guest who has an ulterior motive of his own.</desc>
    <date>20201117</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f5d13fb6672dd1f47aed0bcc78f72536.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722012833 +0000" stop="20250722040032 +0000">
    <title>Victoria</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Victoria moves from out of town into the poor inner city of New York with her father, the neighborhood drug dealer. She goes on a journey seeking answers, justice, and revenge after her father was murdered by local competition. In the process of her revenge, Victoria realizes that she doesn't want to live the lifestyle that she is living before it becomes too late.</desc>
    <date>20210624</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTAxNzkwYTUtYzZhZS00YTc1LTk2NTAtZDdmNTc0NTc4MGRjXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722040032 +0000" stop="20250722052754 +0000">
    <title>Unfinished Business</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Local sheriff, Keith James, finds himself on a desperate hunt for vengeance after the loss of his brother. While solving the case, the truth about his past is revealed, making him and his daughter targets.</desc>
    <date>20230401</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/7688aecb2f2736457b6d32c889b65668.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722052754 +0000" stop="20250722064446 +0000">
    <title>Weapons of Warfare</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When 19 year old TJ, decides to leave the nest of his parents who are preachers of the gospel and turns to the streets for the love and support he always wanted. His life is turned upside down almost over night with gun violence, drug dealings, stolen money and countless crimes in the blink of an eye. His life becomes a tug of war between the parents that raised him and his new gang leader chief Who’s bringing him further down to the ground.</desc>
    <date>20240202</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vnLnD1e0NdgWllZp1rSzDnohieQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722064446 +0000" stop="20250722081000 +0000">
    <title>What She Wants</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Vannaleese Poole is a street smart, businesswoman who knows how to use what she has to get what she wants. In Her relentless thirst to make major moves, she hooks up with Jay, a big time street boss, who promises her the world, but only if she follows the rules that she isn’t willing to play by. She meets Brint, a business mogul, who falls hard for her and gives her everything she wants. A test of love will introduces her to something she never knew she wanted.</desc>
    <date>20220106</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b4lk5P009nJ41bo0hnJgdwdfT62.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722081000 +0000" stop="20250722101153 +0000">
    <title>Asking for a Friend</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A successful engineer struggles in the love department. In denial that his girlfriend is cheating on him, Jeff gets teased by his homeboys until they convince him to try this new dating app and get back out there prove his value to his girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>20241119</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e762414794faf066522df31e0c0cd67d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722101153 +0000" stop="20250722113541 +0000">
    <title>Make it Rain</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After struggling to find a job following graduation, Mone' is enticed by her best friend Lala to audition at a local strip club. She enters the seductive underworld of the strip club, experiencing financial success and personal challenges. As Mone' navigates the dark side of the industry, she must confront betrayal, addiction, tragedy, and ultimately find the strength to rebuild her life and pursue her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20231213</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/419c8bb9c7362ad4923fff746cdb1dec.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722113541 +0000" stop="20250722130316 +0000">
    <title>Love Inside the Drug Game</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A rent hike forces Lamar to consider transporting drugs for shady dealer Sean. A watchful detective sniffs them out, and a money shortage with Sean throws their risky plan into chaos. Can they outrun the cops and fix the mess before it's too late?</desc>
    <date>20240716</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/cbf9b24491bf7cb6d98179182eda5054.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722130316 +0000" stop="20250722144810 +0000">
    <title>Double Blended</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Two couples, once married to each other’s ex-spouses, form a double-blended family. Their seemingly harmonious coexistence is threatened when a past secret resurfaces, forcing them to confront their complicated relationships.</desc>
    <date>20240811</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/849e7c78cae87b1f2c300f63eeb1c830.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722144810 +0000" stop="20250722164533 +0000">
    <title>Curse of a Father</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A father’s horrible mistake causes a lifetime of pain for his children. His son tries his best to live a normal life, but his childhood trauma follows him into his marriage. He must face his trauma head on to break this generational curse.</desc>
    <date>20230930</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/449447a385aedbb09a609703410ff1d7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722164533 +0000" stop="20250722182312 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722182312 +0000" stop="20250722203845 +0000">
    <title>Troublesome</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Veteran homicide detective Michael reluctantly partners with rookie Derrick. Witnessing a double homicide, they survive a deadly chase, but Derrick is wounded. The suspects are linked to the kingpin, who retaliates by ordering murders across the city. As chaos erupts, the FBI joins the case, revealing the kingpin's identity. Michael finds a weak link, offering a chance to finally catch him.</desc>
    <date>20250609</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bba572182a25acd3645156c83fc0e787.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722203845 +0000" stop="20250722221402 +0000">
    <title>All the Love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman begins her journey to adulthood, navigating love and self-discovery, while being haunted by a mysterious past that she can’t fully remember. As murders and violence swirl around her, she wonders who she can trust. Will she find love or suffer the same mysterious fate as her birth parents?</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6589e799a5ad0a6e19fa52d1d64f0025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722221402 +0000" stop="20250722233547 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250722233547 +0000" stop="20250723021257 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Affair</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman abandoned by her mother and raised by her father has a miscarriage which derails her life. In an attempt to find support, she seeks out her married sister, only to find herself in a toxic affair.</desc>
    <date>20231219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/2d1f214a16ce14019eec4e0e82615bc6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
