<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712000000 +0000" stop="20250712003000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Front Suspension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s business as usual in the garage this week. We’re back at work on the Catalog Camaro and really diggin’ into the front end. You know what they say, “out with the old and in with the new,” and that’s exactly what Stacey’s doing. The old sub frame, drivetrain, and suspension are hitting the garage floor in favor of a much-needed updated suspension system that’ll keep this awesome Camaro hugging the road at high speeds—From the wheels to the sub frame, Stacey’s replacing it all. And he’s not going to break the bank while doing it, either. Follow the GearZ crew as they hit the road and visit Cornwell Tools to see their latest and greatest tool box being manufactured. From powder coat to knuckle bustin’ bolts, we’ve got you covered this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170722</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0139.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712003000 +0000" stop="20250712010001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Procharger Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>We head out of the garage to visit one of the premiere supercharger manufacturers in the world… ATI Pro Charger. Follow along for the ride as Stacey walks through the entire process of how they have raised the bar on how a supercharger is built and what it does. From bulk metal to dyno runs, we’ve got it covered. Back in the garage, a young Gearhead drops by to learn how to install an air intake and cowl induction hood on his pick-up. After the wrench turning is done, he and Stacey have enough time to hit a few licks on their guitars. From massive horsepower increases with state-of-the-art tools and machinery, to simple intake and hood installs,….. it’s all here, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170729</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0140.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712010001 +0000" stop="20250712012959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Recaps &amp; Catchups</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey is in full hot rod mode as he unveils a wicked LS engine and Tremec 6spd tranny and stuffs it into the Catalog Camaro. If 600hp and a 6spd in a Camaro doesn’t get you going, the update on the Stunt Double will! It’s old school cool as Stacey shows off the stainless light bar, side steps and cutout flairs to give the truck that “Fall Guy” vibe. After that we introduce you to the amazing world of scale R/C that is sure to have you re-thinking what you want for Christmas! Finally we roll in some updates on the Cheetah and the Junkyard Jag too. If you’re a gearhead, you’re gonna find a whole lot to love about this show!......and that’s GEARZ!!!</desc>
    <date>20170805</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0141.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712012959 +0000" stop="20250712015959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Puttin’ on the B.R.A.K.E.S.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 12 opens with bang as Stacey starts the final assembly process on the V8 Interceptor. If you’ve ever wondered how to lay out an aftermarket A/C system, wiring harness, and steering column on your project… and make them all work together, you have to see this show! After that, NHRA legend and Hall-of-Famer, Doug Herbert drops by the GearZ garage to share the shocking story that inspired him to start the B.R.A.K.E.S. driving program. Hold on tight, because this ain't your typical high school driver's Ed. Program! If you want cool tech and awesome stories… you’re gonna find that on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20180106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0142.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712015959 +0000" stop="20250712022957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Snowcat Bed Fabrication</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about fabrication and thinking outside the box, or to be more specific... outside the bed! Sure, sure, there are plenty of custom pick-up truck beds you can buy but Stacey shows you what is involved in MAKING a custom bed to fit any vehicle, even something as crazy as a Thiokol Imp snowcat! That's right… our little snowcat is back from the sand blaster and ready for a cool bed to match the cab. Stacey goes in-depth about sizing up the project, picking the right parts, and most importantly: how to cut, weld, grind and finish sheet metal to get a bed that will fit your unique vehicle like a glove. So grab a welder… it’s time to make your bed!... only on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0143.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712022957 +0000" stop="20250712025959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Fort Carson On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey takes a trip to Fort Carson, Colorado to visit the Army auto skills program during their world conference. Not only does Stacey get to meet a General, but he also meets a young Sergeant who is in the middle of a frame-off square body restoration. After a thorough walk around, Stacey decides to get LMC involved in helping out with this build. Parts for the bed of his truck can’t match the gratitude we share for our active military and all those who have served, but it’s a start. And we can’t wait to see the project when it’s finished. And speaking of new beds, with the custom bed on the Snow Cat, it’s time to address the tracks, and Right Track Systems has us covered. That little cat is going to tear it up when all is said and done! It’s going to be a lot of fun, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0144.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712025959 +0000" stop="20250712032959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Interceptor Final Assembly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about Cougars! No, not that kind of Cougar... the kind with 4 wheels and a legendary pedigree! After a short history lesson about how these cars came into existence and why they were so cool, Stacey rolls the V8 Interceptor back into the shop and digs into the final assembly of this wild ’67 Mercury Cougar. This week’s episode focuses on planning out your final assembly, and taking care of all the little details, before you put the big things in like engine and transmission. Whether it’s planning out your brake system, battery location, or running fuel lines, Stacey shows how a little extra time in the planning department will make all the difference in your build.</desc>
    <date>20180127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0145.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712032959 +0000" stop="20250712035957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Blackbird &amp; Panel Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey takes us through the history of the legendary SR-71 Blackbird. If you’re not familiar with this bird, it could fly mach 3.2, cruise at 80,000 feet and kept our country safe through its many reconnaissance missions. Never shot down, and never outrun, it was the hot rod of the sky! Stacey gets to sit down with pilot Lt. Col. Ed Yeilding and talk about his record setting transcontinental flight—Coast to Coast in 67 minutes and 54 seconds! The iconic Blackbird was such an inspiration that you know Stacey had to make a vehicle inspired by and paying tribute to it, so get ready to meet the SR-71 Rapid Tool Express!!!</desc>
    <date>20180331</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0146.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712035957 +0000" stop="20250712042959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Butt Lift and Tummy Tuck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Catalog Camaro is back in the garage and ready to go under the knife as Stacey shows how to do a butt lift and tummy tuck on a 2nd generation Camaro. What does that mean? Well, last season Stacey performed a nose job on this old ’81 Camaro to show how easy it is to get rid of the 80’s plastic front bumpers and put on the classic early 70’s split-bumper, rally sport front sheetmetal. This week he continues the makeover by losing the plastic rear bumper and wrap-around taillights and grafting in the early 70’s quarter panels, round taillights and chrome bumper. It’s more in depth than the front and definitely requires some skilled metal surgery, but Stacey shows you all the tricks on how to do it properly. So, sit back and enjoy the ride as Stacey details how to measure, cut, and weld your way to a much younger looking Camaro.</desc>
    <date>20180407</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0147.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712042959 +0000" stop="20250712045956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Big Bad Buick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in a Big Bad Buick Riviera and shows you what is possible with the right vehicle and some bolt on parts. This 1972 Riviera is a great entry-level project that won’t break the bank, and has the potential to serve some serious humble-pie to any unsuspecting hot shot that may want to mix it up at the stoplight. As it sits, the big 455 under the hood is a force to be reckoned with, but Stacey shows what a weekend in the garage and a top end rebuild can do for a car like this! Get ready to get your hands dirty and bust a few knuckles as Stacey pulls the old heads, intake, cam, and ignition off and replaces them with performance parts from companies like TA Performance, Edelbrock, and MSD. It’s a lesson in Buick and bolt-on horsepower, and you’re only gonna find it on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180414</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0148.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712045956 +0000" stop="20250712052956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Paint &amp; Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew hits the road this week and travels to the Charlotte Speed Shop to see how paint prep is going on Stacey’s Cheetah Evolution Car. With the hood and side vents glassed in and smoothed out, the first coat of primer gets sprayed and this awesome cat takes one big step closer to coming home! Stacey also stops by to visit with a fellow boat tail Riviera owner and trade tips on beefing up these classic beauties. It turns out that this guy and Stacey had both been watching this same car when it came up for sale! Come hang out with us as we visit some great folks this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180421</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0149.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712052956 +0000" stop="20250712055954 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Big Bad Buick Inside &amp; Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey gets down to business on the Big Bad Buick. With the top end engine rebuilt, the exterior and interior of the car need some serious updating. You don’t have to spend a ton of cash on simple modifications. Stacey shows what’s behind making a good clean line with your bumpers and how a simple front and rear bumper tuck can drastically change the appearance. Replacing the grille and scraping off that old vinyl top are also sure-fire ways to add attitude to this big ol’ boat tail. That old carpet has got to go! Follow along as Stacey shows the ins and outs and some tips and tricks to keep your exterior and interior redo from breaking the bank.</desc>
    <date>20180623</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0150.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712055954 +0000" stop="20250712062954 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old #7 Camaro Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Not everyone out there is wrenching on an a classic. In fact, we get tons of emails from viewers who want to upgrade brand-new vehicles but aren’t sure how to get started. Well, Stacey has the answer—and it comes with a little help from our friend and NASCAR legend Jimmie Johnson and a stunning 2018 Camaro SS. Come hang out in the garage as Stacey walks you through the top seven modifications that you can make to a car that you just drove off the lot! Everything from paint upgrades to wheels, Stacey’s got a list. Let’s get started!</desc>
    <date>20180630</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0151.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712062954 +0000" stop="20250712065954 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old #7 Camaro Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey’s hard at work on a 2018 Camaro SS. This build is super-cool, not only because he’s running down a list of the top seven mods you can make on a brand-new car, but also because seven-time NASCAR champion, Jimmie Johnson is involved with the project. We’ve covered paint mods, body mods, and interior mods. Now it’s time to go under the hood and under the car and talk powers gains and handling upgrades!</desc>
    <date>20180707</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0152.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712065954 +0000" stop="20250712072955 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Rapid Tool Express</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E12</episode-num>
    <desc>With our chassis and drivetrain out of the way, it’s time to get moving on the inside of the SR-71 Rapid Tool Express. But how do you organize a bunch of tools in and empty truck? Well, the guys from Summit Bodyworks do it every day on full size Cornwell tool trucks, so it’s only natural that they lend a hand in helping layout the inside our ’59 Panel to make it cool and serviceable. After that, Stacey addresses the issue of wooden floors and beds, and shows you an aluminum floor option that you’d swear came from the forest. Finally, the crew hits the road and gets a chance to talk with top fuel drag racer Leah Pritchett about her drive to become one of the best top fuelers in the nation. From design to drag racing, we’ve got it covered, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180804</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0153.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712072955 +0000" stop="20250712075958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Chassis &amp; Drivetrain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The SR-71 Rapid Tool Express is really taking off! We get our custom chassis from the Roadster Shop—those guys know a thing or two about quality builds. Engine Master Jon Kaase delivers a one-of-a-kind engine to power our SR-71. This build is coming together fast! With the body back on, Stacey takes you through some of the other mods that are going to tie this build in with the SR-71 Blackbird. Get ready, ya’ll, we’ve got loads of good stuff on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180811</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0154.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712075958 +0000" stop="20250712082958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 On The Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 13 is off and rumbling with Stacey showing off the new exhaust system for the SR-71 Rapid Tool Express project. From the headers to the tailpipes, this exhaust is going to scream! After that, it’s chassis details as Stacey lays out a plan for pedals, brakes and a fuel tank. Of course You can’t have an SR-71 inspired build without some killer wheels and wait ‘til you see what Stacey and our good friends at Neely Precision come up with. It’s all good, and it’s all here, this week on GearZ</desc>
    <date>20190105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0155.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712082958 +0000" stop="20250712090001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Paint &amp; Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The biggest Toy in the shop is back... HEAVY METAL! Yes... Our old junk yard International Tow Truck rolls back into the garage as the freshly painted cab returns from the Hot Rot Institute. And it’s not just any paint, It’s Razzleberry from Axalta that’s so candy, you’ll want to take a bite! But there’s no time for that because Stacey jumps right in to putting a face and interior back in this old junkyard dog. The result will make you really glad that he rescued this one from the crusher! It’s recycling at it’s best... it’s GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0156.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712090001 +0000" stop="20250712093000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Dash &amp; Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re moving full steam ahead with the Interior of the Heavy Metal cab coming together and now’s the time to get the dash set up. We’ve got new gauges, old gauges and a bunch of empty holes where switches and knobs lived in this truck’s former life. Stacey lays out the dos and donts of getting your dash updated and a layout that makes sense before it gets installed. GearZ hits the road with a special delivery for the Hot Rod Institute for all they’ve done for us and the restoration industry. Feeling a little down about your project? Well, Stacey has a tool tech that’s sure to lift you up! All this and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0157.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712093000 +0000" stop="20250712100002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The SR-71 Rapid Tool Express returns as Stacey digs into his old ’59 ford panel truck and shows how to convert it into a one-off tool delivery truck to show off a variety of Cornwell tools. From special shelves, lighting and floor, there are even a few surprises that are tucked away inside this rolling tool cart! Moving to the cab of the vehicle, Stacey addresses some of the issues people have when setting up seats and steering, and shows some simple tricks that make a huge difference in getting your seats and steering dialed in. Then it’s on the rear to lay out the gas tank, and then finally the SR-71 gets a new beak.... from a ’59 T-bird! ...What?!?.... how is that possible? Well, ya gotta watch GEARZ to find out!</desc>
    <date>20190309</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0158.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712100002 +0000" stop="20250712103004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Topping the Jeep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jeep may be the single most modified vehicle out there. From winches to lights, doors and fenders, if you’ve got a Jeep, it probably has some accessories on it. But despite all that, one of the best things about a Jeep is the removable top. It also sparks one of the biggest debates... What is best: a soft top or a hard top? Stacey takes on the challenge by comparing a factory hard top with the new Bestop Trektop. The test will include everything from ease of install to styling, overall sound decibels and of course, how watertight it is. Hopefully you won’t get wet on this ride! Then it’s back to the shop where Stacey shows you that rotisseries aren’t just for chickens, and how an automotive rotisserie can make life in the shop a lot easier. Finally, it’s on to the right and wrong way to use weatherstrip adhesive to hold your rubbers on. Sound risqué? It’s not... it’s just GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190316</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0159.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712103004 +0000" stop="20250712110005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about square body GM trucks, because The Stunt Double is back in the shop. First, we take a look back at the this awesome ‘86 Chevy 4x4 Silverado long bed build that pays tribute to the legendary Fall Guy TV truck. From its beginnings as a well-worn farm truck, you’ll see it get an upgraded suspension, interior, drivetrain, as we make it better than I was before... better... stronger... faster... wait, that was a DIFFERENT Lee Majors TV show! After that, we walk you through the paint job and show how it is similar to the Fall Guy truck, only different.... because It’s the Stunt Double!!! No hocus pocus... no movie magic... just a tough truck being built to handle the toughest stunts... only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190323</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0160.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712110005 +0000" stop="20250712113007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Frame &amp; Body Assembly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The SR-71 Rapid Tool Express is back on the block and going back together for the last time. Stacey finishes up the frame into a rolling masterpiece with the suspension and drivetrain assembled for the last time. Then the body goes back on, and the interior starts to go together. We’re talking fitting the carpet, steering column and the new dash bezel and stuffing that bezel with custom SR-71 gauges. After that, Stacey shows some tricks on how to choose the right transmission and why rechargeable power tools are giving the tried and true air tools a run for their money! It's all here and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0161.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712113007 +0000" stop="20250712120008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gas, Tops, Brushes &amp; Samurais</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the e85 market and flex fuel vehicles growing every day, Stacey dives into the myths and truths that surround ethanol and whether or not it’s a good choice for your vehicle. With a little help from Advanced Fuel Dynamics, Stacey installs a new fuel delivery system on a 2017 Mustang to show just how easy it is to up your performance and keep your engine safe at the same time. After that, Stacey and the crew head out west to tell the story of Bestop and how they’ve been making removable Jeep tops for decades. From rock-crawlers to the mall crawlers, Bestops unique past allows us to see what the future of the Jeep world will be. Finally, if you’re trying to decide between a stick or automatic transmission… hang out for a while as Stacey talks about converting your boring automatic to a lively manual transmission. We’ve got all this and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0162.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712120008 +0000" stop="20250712123007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cornwell 100</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s rare for people to reach the age of 100. It’s ever rarer for a business, but that just what Cornwell Quality Tools has done! Take a trip through the last century as Stacey tracks the development of a tool company started by a blacksmith, to the tool truck empire that stresses quality over everything else. Speaking of 100 years…trucks have been around for over a century, and for over a century, truck owners have struggled to find the best way to lift their trucks. Stacey sheds some light on picking the right kind of lift for the truck you’re driving. We’ve got all of this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190525</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0163.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712123007 +0000" stop="20250712130009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Copperhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E10</episode-num>
    <desc>There’s nothing like a good mystery. One of our favorite GearZ mysteries is the whereabouts of Copperhead, the legendary C10 that Stacey built more than a decade ago. It seemed like the truck just disappeared. Well, it’s back! And Stacey was reunited with it at the C10 Nationals in Ft. Worth, TX. Tag along as Stacey gets a chance to get behind the wheel again and boil some tires. Back in the garage, Stacey tackles a fuel injection install on a Jeep Scrambler, then checks out the new Core Doors from Bestop. There’s a lot going on and plenty of smoke on the Texas Motor Speedway on this episode of GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190713</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0164.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712130009 +0000" stop="20250712133009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Fins, Logo and Mystery Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As the SR71 Rapid Tool Express nears completion there are a couple of major things left on the plate before we can fire her up and get her down the road. First, every aircraft must have fins, and Stacey finally finds the fins he’s been looking for since the beginning of this build. Second, a cool logo design shows up at the shop. Third, what’s a stealthy tribute vehicle without stealthy paint? Believe it or not, Stacey’s got some paint that should keep the SR71 flying under the radar. Also, a slightly modified March Performance system will help Stacey get that much closer to putting some spark to this awesome build and stick around for plenty of other tech advice from America’s Gearhead… on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190720</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0165.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712133009 +0000" stop="20250712140008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road - Squarebody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E12</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re on the road, again, as Stacey visits a truck enthusiast working on his first ground up restoration. It’s a sweet, clean, square body that’s in good enough condition that it might be on the road in a couple of months. But every build can use a little push, and GearZ On the Road does just that! After that, we dig into toolboxes. Hang out as Stacey talks with two engineers about what makes the new Cornwell Platinum boxes so tough. From rollers to welds, these might be the Ultimate box! Then the Cheetah is back in the garage, but only for a day or two before it heads out to get the body work finished and get some new color. It’s all here on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190727</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0166.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712140008 +0000" stop="20250712143009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>REVIVING THE SUR-TREK 8-WHEEL DRIVE ATV</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>STACEY DIGS INTO A PROJECT THAT SHOWS YOU JUST HOW MUCH FUN YOU CAN HAVE FOR ALMOST NO MONEY. BECAUSE HE’S TAKING A DERELECT 70’S ATV, STUFFING IN A JUNKYARD ENGINE, TOSSING IN SOME GOOD OL’ AMERICAN INGENINUITY AND ENDING UP WITH A REALLY COOL RIG. IT’S CHEAP! IT’S FUN! AND YOU’LL BE SURPRISED WHAT YOU LEARN ON A PROJECT LIKE THIS!</desc>
    <date>20070301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0001.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712143009 +0000" stop="20250712150007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>What do you get when you cross the quentessential girl's car, the Mazda Miata, with the ultimate guy's car...the Shelby Cobra? Well, Gearz is the only place to find out as Stacey blows apart an innocent Miata to get it ready for its conversion into a V8 powered, screamin' machine called the "Banshee."</desc>
    <date>20070308</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0002.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712150007 +0000" stop="20250712153007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Last week he made room, this week the transplant takes place as Stacey stuffs a 400 horsepower V8 into a Mazda Miata. If you've ever wondered if it's possible to actually build a blindingly fast car on a reasonable budget...The Banshee is the project you need to see. And Gearz is the olny place to see it.</desc>
    <date>20070315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0003.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712153007 +0000" stop="20250712160007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>L.A.R.C.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on Gearz, Stacey takes you for a unique spin in one of the largest 4-wheel vehicles ever built...the LARC 60. Then it's back to the shop, where he digs into frame modifications so you can be sure the foundation is strong on your project. Then finally, he throws some cool fire-power into the back of Sgt. Rock that you are going to have to see to believe. Lock and load!</desc>
    <date>20070322</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0004.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712160007 +0000" stop="20250712163006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Superbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>This is a show for all of you restorers out there, because Stacey not only shows you how to properly drive your hotrod by flogging on a '70 Superbird, but he also shows you some tips and tricks on restoring vintage parts like exhaust manifolds and steering wheels. If you're a Gearhead, then this Gearz id for you.</desc>
    <date>20070329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0005.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712163006 +0000" stop="20250712170005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>32 Ford History and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It's anniversary time. The '32 Ford is 75 years old and we take a look back at what made this car so popular for so long. But that's not enought, no...Stacey shows you that the deuce is not dead...it's just getting started as he walks you through the assembly and building of a brand new, steel '32 roadster body at Brookville Roadsters.</desc>
    <date>20070406</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0006.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712170005 +0000" stop="20250712173004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Banshee is back on Gearz and rollin' down the final stretches as Stacey installs new suspension and brakes to help control this molten missile when he uncorks that nasty V8. Even if you are not putting a V8 in your Miata, this show is full of cool things you can do to any Miata to make it look, handle, and perform better.</desc>
    <date>20070413</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0007.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712173004 +0000" stop="20250712180002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Banshee gets a major facelift as Stacey transforms it from a Mazda Miata into a ...well...uh...the Banshee! that's right, the body parts fly and the cutting continues until slowly, from the mayhem, a car appears that really does look as good and run as fast as a cobra or a corvette...except the Banshee is actually affordable...And only on Gearz</desc>
    <date>20070420</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0008.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712180002 +0000" stop="20250712183002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cherry Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Quick...When it comes to exhaust, what is the first name that comes to your mind? If it's not Cherry Bomb, then you've missed out on a lot of years of disturbing the peace. Well, today, Stacey shows you why. Then it's a quick lesson on how to tuck your bumpers nice and tight...and a new paint product that can help you paint your car for cheap.</desc>
    <date>20070427</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0009.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712183002 +0000" stop="20250712190003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Workin' Man's Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on gearz, it’s a real world, working man’s truck on the block, and Stacey shows you how to take a late model diesel pickup and make it better, stronger, and tougher than it was before…..and it’s something that can be done in the span of one weekend without breaking the bank. Proving once again that you can have a cool truck and still use it on the job.</desc>
    <date>20070504</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0010.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712190003 +0000" stop="20250712193002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Rat Roaster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>There is no doubt that the '32 Ford is one of the most legendary cars ever built. Today, Stacey shows that you can actually build one of these cars yourself, and that hot rodding is alive and well, by jumping into a wild, late '60's style raodster project called the Rat Roaster. If you were a street-racin' hot-footed muscle car driver back in 1968, this was the car that you didn't want to see pull up next to you.</desc>
    <date>20070511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0011.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712193002 +0000" stop="20250712200003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Budget Hot Rod</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on Gearz, Stacey deals with one of the most talked about issues facing hotrodding today—Cost! The nhe shows you that it is actually possible to build a steel-bodied, '32 roadster for around 20 grand. But you've got to get back to nature to do it. So, strap on your snake boots, buddy, cause the junk yard is calling.</desc>
    <date>20070518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0012.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712200003 +0000" stop="20250712203006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hey, What is the most important part of your project? Well, if you are building a classic or nostalgic car or truck, your answer will probably be the tires...and this week, Stacey visits Coker Tire, one of the most unique tire storkes in the country. Then it's off to run a leg of the great race in the legendary Honest Charlie '32 Ford. Finally, Stacey shows you some tips and techniques on how to get some exotic wood and a show-quality finish in the bed of your classic truck.</desc>
    <date>20070525</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0013.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712203006 +0000" stop="20250712210005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Year-One Bandit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>What is the most famous car movie of all time? Bullitt?… Vanishing point?... Gone in 60 seconds? Nice guesses, but in terms of influence and sheer popularity, Smokey and the Bandit stands above them all. Stacey takes a look at not only the cultural impact of Smokey and the Bandit, but also it’s most famous character… the black Trans Am. Then, it’s off for a test drive of Year One’s new Burt Reynolds Bandit edition Trans Am to see if it lives up to the true supercar status of the original. Finally, Stacey takes a look and shows you how to use, one of the most mysterious and versatile metal working tools out there… the English Wheel</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0014.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712210005 +0000" stop="20250712213004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Rat Roaster Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The “Rat Roaster” returns and Stacey finally reveals the kind of power plant that would have made this wild deuce roadster the fastest car in the valley in 1968. And if dual carbs, a blower and about 600 horsepower don’t get you going... maybe the fact that he’s stuffing a 5-speed manual transmission behind it, will! Then, Stacey digs into the Parts Bin to take a look at some of coolest products on the market to help you build your own special ride.</desc>
    <date>00030108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0015.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712213004 +0000" stop="20250712220007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Rat Roaster Frame &amp; Exhaust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey not only brings the “Rat Roaster” ‘32 back in the shop, but he also takes it under the knife as he creates a very unique Dr Jekyll and Mr. Hyde style exhaust system and does some custom modifications to the frame to hide it all from the casual on-looker. If you are interested in taking your project and building it into something truly unique by thinking outside the box… this show will definitely encourage you to do that. Then, Stacey digs into some tips and tricks on how to set your vehicle up for storage for those times when your classic car or hot rod is going to be sitting for awhile unused.</desc>
    <date>00030808</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0016.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712220007 +0000" stop="20250712223010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Hoss Fly V8 Barstool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In the world of hot rodding, when gear heads gather around and start discussing their projects, invariably the conversation drifts into speculation of what the smallest thing is that you can successfully put a V8 engine in. Stacey pretty much puts an end to that speculation by building a V8 powered Barstool! It’s part go-cart… part garden tractor… part insane... and ALL hot rod, which of course is what Gearz is all about! If you like WILD… then you don’t want to miss this show! Then, Stacey dives into some Muffler Tech to show you what kind of mufflers there are on the market, and give you some tips that might help you make the right decision when the time comes to stick some cool mufflers on your machine.</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0017.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712223010 +0000" stop="20250712230010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building A Tri-Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to classic hot-rod components, nothing gets people going like a multi-carb setup... the Tri-power. Long admired for their stellar performance and macho attitude, the tri-power has become a hard thing to find. So why find one? Why not build your own? Stacey walks you through the process of building your own tri-power out of old derelict parts. After that, he pulls out the big Mopar guns and shows what it takes to put together a six-pack. Then, Stacey gets down and dirty and shows you how to build some simple, ultra strong axle dollies by using some old scrap metal like the kind laying around your garage. Who said gearheads aren’t into recycling?</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0018.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712230010 +0000" stop="20250712233009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Miata Banshee Paint &amp; Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Banshee is back from paint and we're ready to answer the question… does it still look like a ’95 Miata? Has Stacey shown you how to create a completely different monster? Well, all we can say is the proof is in the paint and you are not going to believe how complete and affordable this transformation really is! Then, Stacey digs into the age-old question: Is it better to restore a car original, or modify it? The answer is up to you as he features a really clean ’68 Plymouth GTX… with some not-so-subtle modifications.</desc>
    <date>20221015</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0019.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712233009 +0000" stop="20250713000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Rat Roaster - Building Floors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey pulls out the tools and starts working metal as he dives into the subject of what to do when your floors are gone… I mean literally gone…nothing there! It’s not as big of a problem as you may think! Stacey rolls in the Rat Roaster and shows you how to create solid metal floors from nothing. This show is loaded with tools and tech that will help you build anything from a small patch panel to a complete floor. While he’s at it, Stacey also covers seat selection and placement so you have a place to plant your seat when you get ready to roll down the street.</desc>
    <date>00041208</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0020.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250713000000 +0000" stop="20250713003002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ol' Smoke Corvette Twin Turbos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>What do you get when you combine Armor All, Tony Stewart and Stacey David with an iconic vehicle like the Corvette? You get a really cool car called “Ol’ Smoke” and some lucky viewer is going to own it! That’s right, Stacey takes a brand-new ‘Vette' and shows you how to create your own 180+ MPH supercar for a fraction of the cost, using some aftermarket parts. How is that possible?... turbos baby!... and on this show Stacey shows you how to slap a pair of ‘em on the Corvette to run the horsepower numbers to over 600! If you have ever wondered about turbo charging an if it’s right for your vehicle, this is a show you definitely want to see.</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0021.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
