<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714000000 +0000" stop="20250714002958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Boosting the Ford EcoBoost &amp; Buffing Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the hottest new rigs on the market is the Ford F150 with the new 6 cylinder eco-boost engine. But is it all it can be? Well, today on GEARZ Stacey takes a new eco-boost powered Ford and shows you some simple upgrades that can boost performance AND fuel economy of this great new engine…..at a price you can afford. Then Stacey rolls in the nastiest, grungiest, barn-find Mustang that you can imagine and shows you the steps and tools required to buff an old nasty paint job back to life. Did we mention that this paint is BLACK!?! All to prove the point that if it can be done with a black car...it can be done with any car…and GEARZ is the show that shows you how to do it!</desc>
    <date>20120409</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0069.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714002958 +0000" stop="20250714010001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building a Brush Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With all the makeovers going on these days, it may surprise you to find that there ARE groups out there that could REALLY use some help. The local volunteer Fire Department is a perfect example of this. Since they are volunteers, nobody gets paid the put their life on the line day in and day out, and the equipment they use is generally hand-me-down stuff from the bigger Fire Departments. Well today on GEARZ, Stacey decides to do something about that by taking a stock Chevy dually pickup, and transform it into a state-of-the-art Brush truck for the local Volunteer Fire Department. The cool thing is, he’s using a lot of aftermarket parts that YOU can use on your project…And if it’s good enough for Firemen that go into harm’s way, you KNOW it is good enough for what you will use it for. So strap in, and let’s go ride a Fire Truck!</desc>
    <date>20120702</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0070.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714010001 +0000" stop="20250714013001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Station Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Station Wagons…Love them or hate them, we all have some stories to tell about them! But most of us have never dreamed that a wagon could be a Hot rod or cool custom…but they can! Today on GEARZ, Stacey shows how much fun a wagon can be when it has an LS engine under the hood, and two four barrel carburetors sitting on it. If you ever wanted to thrash your Dad’s old Wagon, this is the show for you! After that Stacey digs into some of the most asked questions regarding shooting waterborne paint, and finally we take a trip to Texas to see how one body-man created his own business by selling tools, instead of using them. If you are looking for a new career, this could be your answer.</desc>
    <date>20120709</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0071.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714013001 +0000" stop="20250714020001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt Rock Suspension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to Cadillac’s, most people immediately think of lowering them down, and cruising with them. However, since the Cadillac Escalade is a great SUV, we thought it would be great to take the Escalade of Country artist Jason Sturgeon, and put a 3 ½” Skyjacker lift on it. Now you have no reason not to go hunting or fishing in style! After that we head to the land of the Predator, and see what it takes to be one of the most successful Monster Trucks of all time with Alan Pezo. Finally, we rub a little of that Monster Truck DNA on SGT. ROCK, as we upgrade the suspension and get it ready to do a little crushing of its own!</desc>
    <date>20120716</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0072.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714020001 +0000" stop="20250714023002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ram 1500 Longhorn/Katzkin Upholstery/ Schwartz Performance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that you can get almost anything you want on a new car or truck these days. The problem is, if you use your truck for work, “almost” just doesn’t get it. Today on GEARZ, Stacey takes a decked out new truck, and adds some key tools and equipment to make it something that you can literally take to work or play with. After that, we dig into the mysterious world of leather interiors, and show how it is possible for you to buy a top quality leather upholstery kit, and install it yourself. Finally, we roll in the SL-C and show what it takes to put twin turbos on an LS7. It’s gonna be crazy, and it’s only gonna be on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20120723</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0073.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714023002 +0000" stop="20250714030003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Project Heavy Metal Suspension &amp; Dax Shepard "Hit and Run" Lincoln Continental</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls Heavy Metal back into the shop and begins to lay out some of the incredible modifications that he is going to be doing on this old junk yard ’69 International Cab over truck. A custom four-link air suspension goes on first, and then a slick air brake system to pull this big monster to a stop. A custom exhaust is also laid out, along with numerous other modifications to make this a one of a kind rig. If you have ever wondered if a Cab over could make a cool hot rod, you need to check this out. From there it’s off to the movies as Stacey digs into the impact and influence movie cars have on our lives and culture. To prove that point, He brings in actor Dax Shepard and his cool ’67 Lincoln Continental who are both starring in the new movie “Hit and Run”. So strap in and hold on, ‘cuz we might get airborne on this ride!</desc>
    <date>20120730</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0074.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714030003 +0000" stop="20250714033004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Foxbody Mustang Stick Shift Swap &amp; V8 Interceptor Paint and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that 80’s and 90’s cars are hot right now, and one of the most desirable is the Fox bodied Mustang because it’s cheap and offers incredible bang for the buck. Today on GEARZ, Stacey rolls in a 1990 Mustang cop car and shows how easy it is to pull out an automatic tranny, and stuff in a Tremec 6spd so you can shift the gears properly. Then it’s off to the Hot Rod Institute in South Dakota to see the paint and body work that the instructors and students have been doing to the V8 Interceptor. If you thought this ’67 Cougar was wild before, wait ‘til you see this show! Here Kitty,…..Kitty……Kitty….</desc>
    <date>20120806</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0075.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714033004 +0000" stop="20250714040004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Modifying a Polaris Ranger UTV/Side-By-Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the hottest vehicles to hit the gear head world is the Side-by-Side, or Utility Vehicle. Once relegated to just farm or ranch work, the UTV is now something that you will see being used for Hunting, Fishing, Camping, Landscaping….virtually ANY kind of outdoor work or recreation. Of course that means the aftermarket is full of things to make an UTV better. Today on GEARZ, Stacey takes a Polaris Ranger and decks it out with a 3 ½” lift, bigger tires and axles, winches front and rear, and all kinds of other cool things to build an all-terrain vehicle that will really shine on the trail or off. After that he gives you a sneak peek at the new Ironworker that has everybody talking. If you work a lot with metal, you need this machine!</desc>
    <date>20121112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0076.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714040004 +0000" stop="20250714043006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Drving the Drag N Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey puts a programmer on the Drag ‘N’ Wagon to finally bring the stripped down Ram Hot Rod truck to life. If you’ve been wondering what kind of performance potential these new Ram Express trucks have, wait until you see one lit up with a supercharger! Talk about breathing fire! After that Stacey lays out how to set up a shop with custom flooring, custom cabnets, and of course a lot of tools and toolboxes. If you’ve ever wondered about the best way to lay out a shop, and utilize your space, this is the show to see… and GEARZ is the show to watch!</desc>
    <date>20130301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0077.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714043006 +0000" stop="20250714045955 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Tow Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Project Heavy Metal is back as Stacey rolls the International Cabover truck into the shop so he can outfit it with a vintage Holmes dual wrecker bed. The big truck continues to come together using parts from a junkyard wrecker, swap meet vintage beer kegs, and some new aftermarket parts. If you always thought that you had to spend big money to build a unique vehicle, this “Heavy Metal” truck will change your mind, and probably have you digging through junkyards in hopes of finding a vintage truck of your own!</desc>
    <date>20130308</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0078.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714045955 +0000" stop="20250714055957 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Inner Workings of a Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>With all the distractions out of the way, Mark returns to the machine-ship to finish the 440 4BBL for the 1970 Plum Crazy Challenger while master-assembler Dave begins working on the 1970 Lemon-Twist Roadrunner.</desc>
    <date>20171206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714055957 +0000" stop="20250714065959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Dueling Drivetrains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>With Mark out of the shop looking at a potential new location for a Mopar car-dealership, the Graveyard Ghouls begin the drivetrain assembly’s for a 1970 Lime Light Tribute Superbird and our 1970 Plum Crazy Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20171213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714065959 +0000" stop="20250714080002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Schooled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark the the Graveyard Ghouls race against the clock to finish up some last-minute tasks on their various Mopar restorations before traveling north to judge Little Creek Casino’s epic car show.</desc>
    <date>20171220</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714080002 +0000" stop="20250714090002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Roadrunner With a Twist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s another reveal day! Mark and Allysa install the graphics on the ’71 Plumb Crazy Challenger and the 1970 Lemon-Twist Roadrunner is finished and readied to be delivered to it’s owner. And Mark proposes - what he thinks is - a “brilliant” idea to the producers of the show.</desc>
    <date>20171227</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714090002 +0000" stop="20250714100001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Engines, Assemblies, and Dougie, Oh My!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With our 1970 Plum Crazy Challenger nearing completion, works shifts to our 1970 Tribute Superbird while Mark and Cousin Dougie build out a 340 engine and Will assists with metal work with George to help him stay on schedule.</desc>
    <date>20180103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714100001 +0000" stop="20250714105959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>I Love the Smell of Plum Crazy in the Morning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a special day at Graveyard Carz. The 1970 Plum Crazy Challenger that has been part of our show since its inception is finally finished and ready to be shipped to it’s new owner. But before they do that, they take it to the coast to show it off at Chinook Winds Casino Resort Car Show!</desc>
    <date>20180110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714105959 +0000" stop="20250714120001 +0000">
    <title>Gone in 60 Days</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Work ramps up on our 1970 Tribute Superbird and just when things couldn’t get more stressful, Mark has taken on a new project - a 1969 GTX owned by non other than Chris Jacobs, host of Overhaulin’. Not only does Chris want the car restored to its former glory, he wants it to be completed in time for SEMA 2017 - only sixty days away!</desc>
    <date>20180117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714120001 +0000" stop="20250714125959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Mopardy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stress is high at the shop and things don’t get any better when Mark finds out that Tony from Tony’s Mopar Parts has secretly flown out to check in on the progress of his 1970 Challenger. Knowing that the restoration hasn’t started, Mark does everything in his power to distract Tony while Cousin Dougie races to disassemble his car.</desc>
    <date>20180124</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E11_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714125959 +0000" stop="20250714135959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>A Buck Shorted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>SEMA 2017 is fast approaching and the Graveyard Ghouls are working hard on Chris Jacob’s 1969 GTX and John Buck’s 1971 Challenger with a Hellcrate Hemi. But as pressure begins to mount, Mark questions if he’ll be able to keep his promised - and ultimately - is forced to make a difficult decision.</desc>
    <date>20180131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E12_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714135959 +0000" stop="20250714150002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Phoenix 'Cuda</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Phoenix Cuda: A legendary Mopar which was incinerated and from the ashes, will be reborn at Graveyard Carz.</desc>
    <date>20180207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E13_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714150002 +0000" stop="20250714160004 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>SEMA Has Eyes On A Hellbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Graveyard Carz returns to conclude the epic builds of Chris Jacob’s 1968 GTX after it suffered a devastating fire, and the first of its kind 1970 Plymouth Superbird equipped with a Hellcat Crate Hemi.</desc>
    <date>20180307</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714160004 +0000" stop="20250714170005 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>68 GTX vs Echo Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>New Season, New Carz! With SEMA in their rear-view mirror, the ghouls begin the final assembly of a 1969 Plymouth GTX in Seafoam Turquoise. And when help comes up short-handed, Mark enlists what he likes to call his “Echo Bomber.”</desc>
    <date>20180314</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714170005 +0000" stop="20250714180007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot Takes Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s the 100th Episode! Join Mark and Royal and watch the never-before-aired Pilot featuring some of the first Mopar restorations the original ghouls tackled over ten-years ago.</desc>
    <date>20180321</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714180007 +0000" stop="20250714190006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Surveying The Will To Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a hectic day at the Graveyard. Dave jumps from car to car, installing and assembling what he can, Will struggles to keep focused on one project at a time, and Mark makes progress on his A100 build with the hopes of revealing at SEMA 2018!</desc>
    <date>20180328</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714190006 +0000" stop="20250714200003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>What's Next?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Professional wrestler, actor, and former professional football player known for his time in the WWE and WCW as Goldberg returns to the Graveyard! This time, he brings the ghouls two brand new projects - one of which includes installing a brand-new 392 Crate Hemi in his modern Dodge Truck.</desc>
    <date>20180404</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714200003 +0000" stop="20250714210005 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Performance with a Touch of Luxury</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ghouls say goodbye to the 1970 Superbird equipped with a Hellcat Crate Hemi by taking it out for one last drive. Then it’s all hands on deck to get the beautiful second-generation Plymouth GTX in Seafoam Turquoise finished in time for the owner to see it for the first time since his father drove it.</desc>
    <date>20180411</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714210005 +0000" stop="20250714220008 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Dissecting a Daytona</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>With a Plymouth GTX finished, the ghoulz refocus their efforts on the 1969 Dodge Daytona. With the owner wanting a full restoration, Mark and the Ghouls begin the tedious disassembly. Because of the car’s pristine condition, they take extra effort to document and preserve as much as they can.</desc>
    <date>20180418</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714220008 +0000" stop="20250714230009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Exorcize a Demon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The unsung heroes of the body shop begin the restoration on one of the most requested renovations ever: a 1971 Dodge Demon. With several panels needing replacement, Mark and George show the intricate process of grafting an entire front-clip from another vehicle to replace the rusted and damaged original.</desc>
    <date>20180425</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250714230009 +0000" stop="20250715000000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Frankenstein's Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s crunch time at Graveyard Carz, Mark and his cousin Dougie fire up the engine for our Turbine Bronze Charger while Dave assembles its firewall in preparation to install the drivetrain.</desc>
    <date>20180502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250715000000 +0000" stop="20250715010001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Look to the West for B5 Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Dave is ready to wrap up the 1970 Challenger R/T SE but is waiting for parts. Meanwhile, Mark’s A100 build continues, and after a long and tedious body-work and paint phase, Will is ready to deliver Dave the 1969 B5 Blue Plymouth GTX.</desc>
    <date>20180509</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S09_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
