<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709234417 +0000" stop="20250710002946 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Renew Your Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E160</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling burnt out and run down? The Doctors show you how to renew you life, body, mind and spirit. Learn the advantages to a little R&amp;R and the beauty benefits of steam. And, see what your eyes are saying about your health.</desc>
    <date>20110907</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710002946 +0000" stop="20250710011618 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Tired? Here's Why</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E42</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling tired and worn down? The Doctors reveal the top four reasons you may feel fatigued -- and none are lack of sleep! Plus, take 10 years off your face without a scalpel or filler! Could it work for you?</desc>
    <date>20121107</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/547fc29b8780c7eddaeed643f4e3991d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710011618 +0000" stop="20250710020258 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Reality TV Star Wants A New Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, Teen Mom OG star Farrah Abraham stops by for a consultation for butt implants! Then, we meet a New York City man who recently made press for being a free sperm donor with 22 children and counting! And, a weight loss plan based on your poop, does it work?</desc>
    <date>20160913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710020258 +0000" stop="20250710024850 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Most Aggravating Body Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E83</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether it’s excessive sweating, funky feet or bad skin, eliminate annoying body problems for good! Plus, can you sniff out an STD? A new study shows you may be able to.</desc>
    <date>20120112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04083.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710024850 +0000" stop="20250710032948 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Excess Skin Removal!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A 300-pound weight loss leaves a man with pounds of sagging skin…but you won’t believe what he looks like now! It’s a transformation that will leave you speechless! Plus, a massager to treat C-section pain delivers an unexpected side effect…orgasms? And, speaking of sex, what does your nose know? The surprising link between a chronic runny nose and erectile dysfunction! Then, can the secret to slimming down be found in a sandbox? Dr. Berman puts this new workout to the test! And, find out the one thing killing your diet that’s not diet or exercise!</desc>
    <date>20161003</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710032948 +0000" stop="20250710041618 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What the Health?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E88</episode-num>
    <desc>Has your health ever made you ask, “what the heck?” The Doctors tackle the H-words affecting your health. Take your hair from thinning to winning, get to the root of your heel pain and more!</desc>
    <date>20120126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710041618 +0000" stop="20250710050152 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Health Traps</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E145</episode-num>
    <desc>From hotels to nail salons, The Doctors shine a light on health dangers that lurk in the places you visit most. And, learn which room in your house is a potential fire trap. Plus, Nancy Davis and the fight against MS.</desc>
    <date>20100505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02145.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710050152 +0000" stop="20250710054840 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Live Prostate Exams &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E129</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors is giving prostate exams throughout the show and Dr. Ordon and former NBA star John Salley are taking one for the team! In an exclusive interview, The parents of a little boy whose skin blisters when you touch him share what daily life is like. See The surprise that leaves him speechless! Young Hollywood stars and artists tackle The global water crisis! Find out how you can help! Then, see the marriage proposal that involved a dramatic set up and … projectile vomiting?</desc>
    <date>20170504</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09129.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710054840 +0000" stop="20250710063534 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Sedates Children on Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E115</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom of four under fire for sedating kids on long flights! Shelby Hadden tackles pelvic pain and shares about her short film Tightly Wound. Jen Hansard shares some simple, green alternatives for your takeout favorites! We put a new personal thermostat to the test! At what point do you feel comfortable doing private things in front of your partner? Can drinking baking soda help you lose weight? Does drinking through a straw help avoid cavities? Why everyone is eating cauliflower bread!</desc>
    <date>20190509</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11115.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710063534 +0000" stop="20250710071346 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Oddities</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E51</episode-num>
    <desc>What the health?! Doctor grows new ear in the arm? Woman “impregnated” by squid? Hot headlines: sexually explicit homework? Top five things to know about hospice. #AskTheDoctors: what do i do with this gaping wound? Healthy use for pineapple skins?</desc>
    <date>20190521</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710071346 +0000" stop="20250710080038 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>600lb Health Intervention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS assembles a medical dream team to save a 600+ pound man! But first, there’s a new type of school bully with a serious health threat! THE DOCTORS takes a closer look at the wrongful death suit filed against Jim Carrey and reveals a major flaw in healthcare! Then, the hot trend in Hollywood —chlorophyll water— is it an A-List health secret or hype? And, a surprising risk to your baby and what to look for!</desc>
    <date>20161017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710080038 +0000" stop="20250710084707 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Unhealthy Lady-Like Habits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E85</episode-num>
    <desc>Women are taught to always cross their legs, never pass gas in front of anyone, and many never leave the house without makeup. The Doctors reveal why these old-fashioned expectations and other lady-like habits can harm your health!</desc>
    <date>20110121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03085.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710084707 +0000" stop="20250710093436 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Grossest Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when you think you've seen it all, The Doctors make your skin crawl in an all new episode. Meet a woman who survived a 51-pound tumor in her abdomen! And, spiders in your ears, parasites in your eyes, fungus on your face - could it happen to you?</desc>
    <date>20121017</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d0338cd40fb07a72f0bf2ea25f784298.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710093436 +0000" stop="20250710102058 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hoarder Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoarder update from social media star Glozell. Skin removal surgery shocker! Eyelid popping! Can fish oil improve your sperm count?</desc>
    <date>20200430</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710102058 +0000" stop="20250710110706 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Saved My Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman suspects she has thyroid cancer after an episode of The Doctors. Did she catch it in time? Haylie Duff dishes up family-friendly recipes that are good for you! A woman accuses a sex toy company of spying on her! The latest drug danger facing your teen could be found in the gardening store? Plus, could a vodka protect your liver?</desc>
    <date>20161011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710110706 +0000" stop="20250710115337 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fattest Woman In The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E130</episode-num>
    <desc>She was the heaviest woman in the world, tipping the scales at over 1100 pounds … can a new bariatric surgery save her life? Then, the inspiring story of a Saved by The Bell star who started going blind at age 13 and now thinks it’s the best thing to ever happen to him! A breast cancer survivor turns to The Doctors after her reconstruction goes wrong! Can she be healed? And, one of our most infamous guests - “The Sperminator” – is back with baby news!</desc>
    <date>20170329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710115337 +0000" stop="20250710124029 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Measures for Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E60</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go for beauty? A controversial surgery alters feet so women can wear heels. And, an acupuncture facelift that claims to take years off a woman's appearance. And, the latest in laser surgery that erases tattoos.</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01060.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710124029 +0000" stop="20250710132702 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Toenail Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Why does one woman have a 6th toenail? Watch as THE DOCTORS does a LIVE procedure in studio! Then, the Stool Squad is back to answer your burning questions! Want fast-food faster? A-list nutritionist Keri Glassman shares her kid-approved recipes! Next, would you change your future child’s eye color? Plus, do at-home bunion correctors really work? Then, why some people are turning to drinking vinegar for better gut health! Could it be doing more harm than good?</desc>
    <date>20181016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710132702 +0000" stop="20250710141451 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Doctors: Body Sounds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>From a grumbling stomach, to a gassy gut to ringing ears, find out which body noises are hazardous, which are harmless and how to mute them.</desc>
    <date>20091006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710141451 +0000" stop="20250710150155 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Drs: Why Does That Smell?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From foul gas to smelly ears, The Doctors answer your most pressing questions about the odors your body produces. And, editor-in-chief of Prevention, Liz Vaccariello, separates fact from fiction about a common medical myth.</desc>
    <date>20091027</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710150155 +0000" stop="20250710154855 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Body's Warning SIgns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Decipher the clues and warning signs your body is giving you. Witness a life-saving surgery that a mother and daughter underwent together! Plus, learn what kind of bruises can indicate a serious medical condition.</desc>
    <date>20091120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710154855 +0000" stop="20250710163520 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Weight Loss Extravaganza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E82</episode-num>
    <desc>The weight is over! From abuse victim to revenge body! From sickness to six packs! From bullied teen to inspirational hero! See story after story of incredible weight loss transformations without surgery that will blow your mind! Plus, meet the biggest weight loss success story in THE DOCTORS history!</desc>
    <date>20180108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710163520 +0000" stop="20250710171843 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Be Prepared</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Carbon monoxide can seep into your home while you sleep. Safeguard your family from this colorless, odorless and deadly gas. Plus, Dr. Lisa’s tips to prepare for menopause and how to lose those last 10 pounds!</desc>
    <date>20090921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710171843 +0000" stop="20250710180525 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Maureen McCormick &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, Maureen McCormick reveals new details of her shocking past! Then, one woman undergoes a live procedure for her resting “angry” face, did it work? Plus, what you need to know to protect your child from the super lice outbreak and a child abductor!</desc>
    <date>20160921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710180525 +0000" stop="20250710185135 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top Reasons People Call In Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Sore throat, upset stomach, aches and pains -- find out when you’re most contagious and when it’s safe to go back to school or the office. And, how to determine if your child is too sick for school.</desc>
    <date>20101213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710185135 +0000" stop="20250710193341 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bullied Because of My Skin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E105</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage girl is bullied because of her painful skin condition; will The Doctors be able to save her skin? Then, The Doctors discusses the latest health news. Could binge-watching your favorite shows trigger binge-drinking? Dr. Ordon reveals the latest nip-tuck trends, including a “No Downtime Neckline” procedure to help you say goodbye to your double chin! Plus, find out how you can fight wrinkles in your sleep!</desc>
    <date>20170327</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710193341 +0000" stop="20250710201951 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Can It Be Cured?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E63</episode-num>
    <desc>See a cure for chronic ear infections, a laser treatment that eliminates back pain and technology that guarantees less time in the dentist’s chair. And, at-home remedies that can cure a cold, calm a flu and quell motion sickness.</desc>
    <date>20091202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710201951 +0000" stop="20250710210546 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Miracles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E63</episode-num>
    <desc>When skin cancer destroyed one woman’s ear, see how doctors helped her grow a new one – on her arm! Then, a mom saves her child’s life with a fecal transplant. Plus, how one woman's breast milk is helping dozens of babies around the country.</desc>
    <date>20121115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710210546 +0000" stop="20250710215250 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>5 Cures in 5 Minutes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E109</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors present five-minute cures for common ailments. See a procedure that stops nasal allergy symptoms for good. And, cosmetic dentist Dr. Dorfman shares dental Dos and Don'ts, including an instant cure for canker sores.</desc>
    <date>20090223</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710215250 +0000" stop="20250710223838 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Common Medical Risks On The Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Behind the wheel, in a plane or on a train, learn how to avoid injuries and stay safe while on the go. And, Dr. Travis’ fun and safe workout tips for busy moms.</desc>
    <date>20100211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710223838 +0000" stop="20250710232659 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>A Test to Predict Cancer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>If you could take a test that would tell you whether or not you would get cancer, would you take it? And, is diet soda better for you than the than the real thing? Dr. Lisa says that everything should be consumed in moderation.</desc>
    <date>20080918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01005.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710232659 +0000" stop="20250711001327 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Vegetarian Diet Increase Strokes?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Can a vegetarian diet really increase the risk of a stroke? Are fake meat burgers the same as dog food? Should everyone be screened for Hepatitis C? Moms get help with sleepless toddlers! Are cold-pressed skin care and spray-on skin really a thing? Is your mouthwash raising your blood pressure? Plus, do emojis encourage more dates and sex?</desc>
    <date>20191008</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250711001327 +0000" stop="20250711010123 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Public Meltdowns &amp; More!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E62</episode-num>
    <desc>Caught on tape: a public meltdown at the gym! What to do when someone flies off the handle in public! Then, a 90-pound weight loss without surgery? Hear one woman’s personal tips that helped her get trim! And, The voice of beloved cartoon characters like Bugs Bunny, Ren and Stimpy, Doug and Futurama reveals his story of overcoming prostate cancer! The risk factors all men need to know! Plus, legendary Latin King of Comedy Paul Rodriguez opens up about his sister’s tragic diabetic death. Hear his heartache and his desire to improve his own personal health. Then, if you’re one of the 42 million Americans struggling with constipation, proctologist Dr. David Rosenfeld shares his top foods that can help you poop! Plus, a sweet trick for a bug-free BBQ!</desc>
    <date>20180912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
