<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716233000 +0000" stop="20250717010000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E02 - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Our five teams have been set the challenge to race across the breadth of Canada, passing through seven checkpoints, taking them from the Pacific coastline, to the edges of the Arctic and the shores of the Great Lakes, to reach their final destination on the Atlantic Ocean; St. John’s on the island of Newfoundland, the most easterly town in North America. As they experience beautiful scenery, bonds will be formed across cultural divides and relationships will be tested as never before.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303763279160536391/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717023000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E03 - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>‘Race Across the World’ is back, this time on BBC One and iPlayer, as five teams attempt to race sixteen thousand kilometres through the second largest country in the world – Canada. Without smartphones, internet access and credit cards, and armed only with the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route, our teams travel this extraordinary journey at ground level.  Their skill, ingenuity and determination will be tested to the extreme as they race through some of the world’s most remote regions, where they must also rely on the kindness of strangers in order to stand the best chance of reaching the finish line. This series takes viewers on the trip of a lifetime, following our racers as they embark on an epic and adrenaline-fueled adventure, traveling into the unknown without the trappings of modern life.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303683693704512338/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717023000 +0000" stop="20250717040000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E04 - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>‘Race Across the World’ is back, this time on BBC One and iPlayer, as five teams attempt to race sixteen thousand kilometres through the second largest country in the world – Canada. Without smartphones, internet access and credit cards, and armed only with the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route, our teams travel this extraordinary journey at ground level.  Their skill, ingenuity and determination will be tested to the extreme as they race through some of the world’s most remote regions, where they must also rely on the kindness of strangers in order to stand the best chance of reaching the finish line. This series takes viewers on the trip of a lifetime, following our racers as they embark on an epic and adrenaline-fueled adventure, traveling into the unknown without the trappings of modern life.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303825251802012717/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717040000 +0000" stop="20250717053000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E05 - Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The BAFTA-award winning third series of Race Across the World has reached the half-way point and our four teams are one leg closer to the £20,000 cash prize.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303782928279422646/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717053000 +0000" stop="20250717070000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E06 - Episode 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The BAFTA-award winning third series of Race Across the World enters the sixth leg of the race that takes our four teams a stage closer to the £20,000 cash prize.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303601485210440804/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717070000 +0000" stop="20250717083000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E07 - Episode 7</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The BAFTA-award winning third series of Race Across the World has reached its penultimate leg and the remaining pairs are just two checkpoints away from the £20,000 cash prize.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303669590892923497/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717083000 +0000" stop="20250717100000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E08 - Episode 8</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The BAFTA-award winning third series reaches its epic climax tonight as one lucky team crosses the finish line in first place, claiming the £20,000 cash prize and the title of Race Across the World Champions.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303730379840572020/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717100000 +0000" stop="20250717113000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E09 - Episode 9</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After a thrilling third series of the BAFTA award winning adventure our five pairs return to reflect on the adventure of a lifetime – across Canada.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303775370075392525/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717113000 +0000" stop="20250717130000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E01 - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The much-loved and hugely successful Bafta-winning series Race Across the World returns to BBC One and BBC iPlayer for a fourth season. Five teams of intrepid Brits will battle it out in a breath-taking 15,000 kilometres race across Eastern Asia through some of the world’s most populous regions and some of its most unexplored.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303742117790340545/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717130000 +0000" stop="20250717143000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E02 - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Bafta winning ‘Race Across the World’ is back, this time on an adrenaline fuelled adventure through Asia. Our five intrepid teams are taking on an epic 15,000 journey from Northern Japan to Lombok in Indonesia.  Armed with only the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route they will have to navigate their way through some of the world’s most populous, and most unexplored countries without smartphones, internet access or bank cards. They will need to think fast, move at breakneck speed and rely on the kindness of strangers to make it to the finish line.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303835330505502134/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717143000 +0000" stop="20250717160000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E03 - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The much-loved hit series ‘Race Across the World’ is back on BBC One as five teams attempt to race a breath-taking 15,000 kilometres through East and Southeast Asia; from northernmost Japan to the finish line in Lombok, an idyllic Indonesian paradise. Without smartphones, internet access or bank cards, and armed only with the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route, our teams must travel this extraordinary journey at ground level.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303626720221529335/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717160000 +0000" stop="20250717173000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E04 - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In the bafta-winning, much loved series ‘Race Across the World’ five teams have been set the challenge to race 15,000 kilometres across East and Southeast Asia, passing through seven checkpoints.  Without smartphones, internet access or bank cards, and armed only with the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route. Their skill, ingenuity and determination will be tested to the extreme as they navigate some of the world’s most populous regions and some of the most unexplored….</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303677651269169533/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717173000 +0000" stop="20250717190000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E05 - Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The bafta-winning hit series ‘Race Across the World’ is well underway. After journeying through Japan, South Korea, Vietnam and Cambodia and crossing the border into Thailand, the four remaining teams have reached the halfway mark in the race across Asia to the Indonesian paradise of Lombok. The leader board has been flipped on its head, and for the first time, in a dramatic turnaround retired couple Stephen and Viv are at the top and Alfie and Owen have dropped to the bottom with an 11-hour gap separating them.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303819206140467655/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717190000 +0000" stop="20250717203000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World - Episode 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Four teams remain in the race of a lifetime battling it out for pole position in the much-loved Bafta-winning series Race Across the World.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303842896810702812/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717203000 +0000" stop="20250717220000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E07 - Episode 7</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In the penultimate episode of the heart-warming BBC hit series Race Across the World, the finish line is in sight for the four remaining teams.</desc>
    <date>20250307</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303708377044754407/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717220000 +0000" stop="20250717233000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E08 - Episode 8</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After racing nearly 14,000 kilometres, over seven weeks, through 7 countries it’s all come down to…12 minutes. That’s all the separates the first two teams as they embark on the final leg of their Race Across the World from Jakarta to Lombok where a prize of £20,000 awaits the winning team.</desc>
    <date>20250307</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303614094879499462/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717233000 +0000" stop="20250718010000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S04 E09 - Episode 9</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Six months after finishing their race across the world, the five intrepid teams are reunited in London for the first time. Together, they look back at the 51-day thrilling adventure that began in northernmost Japan and covered 15,000 kilometres through seven countries, taking in some of the world’s most beautiful, populous and remote places to reach the finish line. Unseen moments will be shown, and shocking revelations made.</desc>
    <date>20250307</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303768819882556982/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
