<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721011551 +0000" stop="20250721031419 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death And Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The body of Martin Wroath is found in his home in Midsomer Worthy. From first appearances it looks as though he had committed suicide by shotgun. Evidence soon suggests that he was murdered. When a second murder takes place on the grounds of the cottage hospital, the detectives need to uncover any possible connections to link the deaths, as well as the mysteriously disappearing rope.</desc>
    <date>20030110</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l4IKOeV42Zy1AX7KJ0FWDz0Wvz2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721031419 +0000" stop="20250721051313 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Painted In Blood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Joyce joins the local watercolour society for an open-air art class, upon the village green in Midsomer Florey. Shortly before taking a break, she stumbles across the body of elderly Ruth Fairfax, a fellow artist found in the undergrowth. It turns out that she had more to her than meets the eye. When Barnaby is taken off the case by the NIS, it is left to Troy to 'apprehensively' let Barnaby in on what's going on with the investigation.</desc>
    <date>20030117</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7MJZtCCUhs3qDD8X89ygppSdRT4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721051313 +0000" stop="20250721070937 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Tale Of Two Hamlets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At the family home of actor Larry Smith in the village of Upper Warden, a crowd has gathered to watch the promotion for the sequel to his hit film 'The House of Satan', when Larry walks into a summerhouse house in the grounds, it suddenly explodes. His family quickly suggest that it was someone from the rival village of Lower Warden. When Larry's director; another member of his family is also murdered, electrocuted while using an exercise bike.</desc>
    <date>20030124</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5jygVAhMdKM9726eSXpEOilrAzu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721070937 +0000" stop="20250721090554 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Of Prey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the village of Midsomer Magna, the body of a man is found who had apparently drowned himself. It is discovered later that he was desperately seeking a way out of bankruptcy after visiting a local millionaire to get back his money from a scheme he had invested in. The post-mortem says that he was indeed murdered. Whilst DS Troy assists a pretty wildlife liaison officer with an investigation into the illegal sale of protected birds eggs.</desc>
    <date>20030131</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8D9yxp3s8Wfc87jz8bS06vtDrln.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721090554 +0000" stop="20250721110443 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Green Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>During a canal restoration project near Midsomer Worthy, on which Joyce is working as a volunteer, several skeletons are discovered shortly after a tunnel collapse. DCI Barnaby begins his investigations when it is found that one skeleton had modern dental work. Meanwhile, DS Troy, having been promoted to Inspector has his last case in Midsomer, to look into the murder of a youth, Simon Mayfield (Henry Cavill), who had caused problems for many in the village.</desc>
    <date>20031102</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nhfabQSsoGFCTT09gx1rzwm8Vq7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721110443 +0000" stop="20250721130319 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Tidings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>DS Dan Scott, a charming young man but with a bit of an urban chip on his shoulder, arrives in Midsomer as DS Troy's replacement. He is instantly involved in his first case, a woman stabbed after attending a Spanish-themed evening in Midsomer Mallow. Not long after, a retired doctor for whom she had worked is murdered during the village's annual garden open day. It quickly becomes clear that the two victims knew a secret about one of the villagers. Are both crimes connected?</desc>
    <date>20040104</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aIU38yMvh21kAjGhHwtnmp7bYCs.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721130319 +0000" stop="20250721145833 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Fisher King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Back in 1970, Roger Heldman died in what appeared to be an accident, during a dig at Midsomer Barrow. It unearthed two important Celtic pieces, a spear and chalice. In present day, Roger's son Gareth is killed with the spear, after having altercations with several villagers. At the climax of the summer solstice celebration Gareth's half brother David Heartley-Reade is killed while performing a ceremony to save his failing marriage.</desc>
    <date>20040111</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3ot5o0bSjljuuT9nDRAi8QmjoHT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721145833 +0000" stop="20250721165049 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of Commission</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>DCI Barnaby and DS Scott arrive in Midsomer St. Michael to investigate the apparently accidental death of former prize-winning author Richard Rackham. But it is discovered that he had had his neck expertly broken before his tumble down the stairs. The village's 12th annual Literary festival brings feuding writers, publishers, and editors to town. When Mr Rackham's editor is then found dead during the festival's opening ceremony, it leads police on a trail of deception, fraud, and hidden truths.</desc>
    <date>20040118</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wrBYTFkpZpSjJODMntSQqV3XVr7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721165049 +0000" stop="20250721184306 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Maid In Splendour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The village pub of Midsomer Worthy, The Maid in Splendour, is the workplace of many locals. One night, popular barman Jamie Cruickshank is found dead near an abandoned cottage in the woods. The new manager Stephen Bannerman, who is thoroughly disliked by many, wants to sell the Maid to property developers in secret. When Stephen is murdered, Barnaby and Scott have to find out whether Jamie or Stephen was the intended target of the first murder.</desc>
    <date>20040125</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y1VAyLGu8s6CG5UdQvvRAY7hE6r.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721184306 +0000" stop="20250721203530 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Straw Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Midsomer Parva have all come out one evening to see the revival of an old Pagan festival. The centrepiece is a straw effigy of a woman. When it is set alight and people look on in wonder, it soon turns to horror when the local curate screams out in pain from within the effigy. The villagers quickly turn against Liz Francis, a local teacher who had organised the event.</desc>
    <date>20040229</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nrOBSdUgTLPdvICauwBZ9dy7A9K.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721203530 +0000" stop="20250721222802 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Ghosts Of Christmas Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Nine years after Ferdy Villiers committed suicide at the family home of Draycott Hall, the extended Villiers family gather together to celebrate Christmas. When a riddle in a Christmas cracker proclaims that two members of the family will be dead by midnight on Boxing Day, everyone takes no notice, until elderly Aunt Lydia nearly dies after getting locked in the garage, after her car has restarted itself and then later in the night, falls down the stairs.</desc>
    <date>20041225</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ZtPtLMhYmIDZEDoDc5Js6z9IIl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250721222802 +0000" stop="20250722001326 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Rider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The appearance of a headless horseman at Quitewell Hall foreshadows a number of deaths amongst an aristocratic family.</desc>
    <date>20120201</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b467aebVPvYT8pRWgoFy1RgbfCW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250722001326 +0000" stop="20250722015820 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When a barrister is killed in Midsomer, suspicion falls on convicted murderer Grady Felton. Grady has just returned to the village where he committed the murder years ago amid much anger from locals.</desc>
    <date>20120321</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AoU821xt5fTC39LOACFizTzrNL2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
