<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146">
    <display-name>Runtime</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/2bad1dfc-bfda-46ae-bd0d-36b1e07ccb47/runtime-logo_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718000000 +0000" stop="20250718012228 +0000">
    <title>Elon Musk: The Real Life Iron Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Discover the meteoric rise of Elon Musk, the man who is transforming the way we think about travel techlogy through electric cars, the Hyperloop, andrevolutionary ideas on how we live through artificial intelligence and colonizing Mars.</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/elon_musk_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718012228 +0000" stop="20250718025202 +0000">
    <title>Eating Our Way to Extinction</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Narrated by Kate Winslet, this entertaining and surprising documentary will challenge the way you look at the food industry. What is the true cost of food? Who pays the price? Featuring shocking undercover footage and poignant first-hand accounts from indigenous people, this one-of-a-kind documentary will permanently change your perception of food and its connection to the future of our planet.</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/eating_our_way_to_extinction_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718025202 +0000" stop="20250718034102 +0000">
    <title>Celebrity Trawlermen: All at Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As their voyage gets under way, the terrifying reality of what they are taking on begins to hit home and they struggle to prove their worth. Shane Lynch, Ben Cohen and Antony Worrall Thompson are taken to sea on the same terms as any new crew, by skipper Alan Watt.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebrity_trawlermen_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718034102 +0000" stop="20250718043009 +0000">
    <title>Celebrity Trawlermen: All at Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After 5 days at sea, the relentless cycle of work and very little sleep starts to take its toll in unexpected ways. And the celebrities first night time haul reveals something extraordinary; a shark. When the only toilet on board becomes blocked and suspicion falls on the boat’s newest recruits – the celebrities and Rugby star Ben find himself taking the blame.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebrity_trawlermen_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718043009 +0000" stop="20250718051853 +0000">
    <title>Celebrity Trawlermen: All at Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As the wind hits gale force eight, the dangers of the job come sharply into focus. The risks are taken in the hope of a valuable catch of monkfish. But instead, the celebrities catch yet more cod, which under European legislation they’re forbidden to land, and is thrown back into the sea.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebrity_trawlermen_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718051853 +0000" stop="20250718060000 +0000">
    <title>Frame of Reference</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The series explores the vulnerable and often hectic lives of a close group knit of friends and provides a truthful evaluation of how fear and past misfortunes can define our present point of view.</desc>
    <date>20230123</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/frame_of_reference_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718060000 +0000" stop="20250718080144 +0000">
    <title>Relish</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A teenage social media influencer and four teenage outcasts escape a private treatment facility, led by a rebellious transgender young man, go on a life-changing road trip, and discover they have a lot more in common than they ever imagined.</desc>
    <date>20190906</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/39ad832eab2013dcd70a5f31b146dc2b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718080144 +0000" stop="20250718100538 +0000">
    <title>Fling</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An attractive young couple's open relationship is stretched to the breaking point when each partner finds themselves falling in love with other people.</desc>
    <date>20240808</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/fling_thumbnail_7x10_poster_en.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718100538 +0000" stop="20250718110336 +0000">
    <title>The Insider: Reggie Yates</title>
    <sub-title>Reggie Yates in A Texan Jail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>For one week Reggie Yates will eat, sleep and work alongside the inmates of Bexar County Jail, Texas to try to understand the criminal justice system from the inside. He doesn’t just meet the prisoners of this Texan jail, he becomes one. Stripped of all personal belongings, locked up at the ankles and wearing an orange jumpsuit, he enters into a world most of us will never know.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_insider_reggie_yates_s1_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718110336 +0000" stop="20250718120000 +0000">
    <title>The Insider: Reggie Yates</title>
    <sub-title>Reggie Yates in the Mexican Drug War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Acapulco was once a tourist paradise frequented by the Hollywood starlets of the 1950’s but things have dramatically changed and now it’s the 4th most dangerous city in the world. The sense of danger is constant, on the day Reggie arrives; there are nine murders in Acapulco. The civilians he encounters on the streets refuse to talk about it from fear of the omnipresent cartel.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_insider_reggie_yates_s1_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718120000 +0000" stop="20250718135436 +0000">
    <title>Bigfoot</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After his bicycle crashes into a forest, Percy Caldwell encounters a new friend, Bigfoot, an eight-foot-tall creature, who has been displaced by a recent forest fire. But when two bullies find Bigfoot, they decide to capture him, take him back to their farm, and sell him to the highest bidder. Now its up to Percy, Leonard, and Madison to rescue Bigfoot and return him to his home.</desc>
    <date>20080101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/9edcf53a754bbbe8ff53b4c55b1df324.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718135436 +0000" stop="20250718154009 +0000">
    <title>Faith, Love &amp; Chocolate</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jessica Miller is thrust into the "real" world when she graduates from college. To conquer this new world, she must discover her faith, open a box of memories and learn the simple secrets of life only a mother can share.</desc>
    <date>20180923</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jPsGNVrCC23FwM5zMEcUgQ18lf1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718154009 +0000" stop="20250718170549 +0000">
    <title>The Last Hillbilly</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the state of Kentucky, it is often said that its residents feel less American than Appalachian. Reeling from the effects of an economic downturn, mines that used to employ thousands sit empty across a wild, rolling landscape. Those remaining in the area are often referred to disparagingly as “hillbillies”. For Brian Ritchie, a gentle local worker and loving father, this term is a provocation to be proud of, regularly using it in his affirming, vulnerable poetry to outline his identity and subvert stereotypes.</desc>
    <date>20240706</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_last_hillbilly_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718170549 +0000" stop="20250718184908 +0000">
    <title>Kingdom Of Gladiators</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A king makes a pact with an ancient demon and after years of ruling his kingdom in peace, the demon has come to collect. Now a group of rival gladiators must fight for the survival of the kingdom.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/kingdom_of_gladiators_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718184908 +0000" stop="20250718204431 +0000">
    <title>Warriors Of Terra</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A headstrong animal-rights activist group plans a raid on a bio-tech company to stop the cruelty of their animal testing. They instead discover the unimaginable true nature of the experiments that are actually taking place, and when a genetically mutated human with a taste for human flesh gets released, they all struggle to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240808</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/warriors_of_terra_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718204431 +0000" stop="20250718223000 +0000">
    <title>Laal Kabootar</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Alia's husband is murdered in a brutal target killing, she seeks answers and revenge. Her luck changes when she meets the street-wise Adeel, a cab driver looking for a way out of the city. The two quickly find themselves in over their heads, and in the cross-hairs between a corrupt cop and a real estate tycoon, sinking further and further into an entrapping web.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/laal_kabootar_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250718223000 +0000" stop="20250719001244 +0000">
    <title>Clubbed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Set in the violent world of 80’s clubland, when life in Britain was tough, where run-down inner-cities were seething with drugs and crime. Danny, a lonely factory worker, is depressed, his marriage is over and the local dealers are out for blood. After a savage beating Danny decides to fight back. He gets involved with the local doormen, who take him in and teach him how to stand his ground.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/clubbed_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250719001244 +0000" stop="20250719021428 +0000">
    <title>Relish</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A teenage social media influencer and four teenage outcasts escape a private treatment facility, led by a rebellious transgender young man, go on a life-changing road trip, and discover they have a lot more in common than they ever imagined.</desc>
    <date>20190906</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/39ad832eab2013dcd70a5f31b146dc2b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
