<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722004543 +0000" stop="20250722013144 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What's Causing Your Symptoms?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Mysterious foot pains? Unexplained nosebleeds? The Doctors reveal what’s really causing your concerning symptoms. Plus, are you over or underspending on your health? Money guru Suze Orman has the answers.</desc>
    <date>20120213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722013144 +0000" stop="20250722022005 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>No Surgery Nose Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Precocious puberty affects girls as young as 5 years of age. Find out what changes to watch for in your daughters. And, always wanted to have a nose job, but afraid to go under the knife? See Dr. Ordon's no-surgery nose job!</desc>
    <date>20080923</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722022005 +0000" stop="20250722030636 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Grossest Moments Ever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E508</episode-num>
    <desc>The Embarrassing, Gross, and Wild Special brings you some of The Doctors’ most unforgettable moments! See “The Great Pop-Off”! Relive Dr. Pimple Popper’s biggest and best pops! Marvel at the courage of guests who shared Their most embarrassing problems to raise awareness! From the huge, painful keloids that isolated a school teacher to The severe birthmarks that tormented a young woman, These guests stepped out of the shadows for help. Don’t miss one man’s 315-pound transformation! Laugh and learn as Dr. Ordon and NBA star Jon Salley undergo prostate exams backstage! Score a simple fix for dry, chalky elbows.</desc>
    <date>20170908</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09508.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722030636 +0000" stop="20250722035326 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Know Your Body Signs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E159</episode-num>
    <desc>Can’t get rid of dark under-eye circles? Constantly having bad hair days? Find out what your body may be telling you! And, learn which eyebrow color may be an early indicator of diabetes.</desc>
    <date>20100715</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02159.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722035326 +0000" stop="20250722043922 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Smelly &amp; Hairy Solutions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E135</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors search for the smelliest flatulence in America. Meet the top contenders! Put a stop to offensive breath for good, get tips to fight frizz and watch a live hair transplant.</desc>
    <date>20110509</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722043922 +0000" stop="20250722052606 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Skin Removal Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E123</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors checkup, we go inside the O.R. as a guest who lost 280 pounds gets skin removal surgery! Meet the biggest weight-loss loser of the #DropTheSugar Challenge! Dr. Travis’ skills are put to the test in the Baby Daddy Challenge! Could weekend brunch be causing us to put on weight.</desc>
    <date>20200506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12123.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722052606 +0000" stop="20250722061242 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Doctors: Specialist Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E83</episode-num>
    <desc>Can a mole be removed without leaving a scar? What’s the best treatment for chronic bladder infections? Can rosacea be cured? Plus, what you can learn about your health from some of the most beautiful male doctors in America!</desc>
    <date>20130118</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05083.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722061242 +0000" stop="20250722065940 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What to Do if Disaster Strikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E56</episode-num>
    <desc>When disaster strikes, would you know what to do? Are you prepared for earthquakes, tornadoes, hurricanes, blizzards and more? Plus, five things you can do to increase your chance of surviving a plane crash.</desc>
    <date>20101108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03056.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722065940 +0000" stop="20250722074629 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Feeds Children Dog Feces?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom accused of feeding her own kids dog feces? ASMR dandruff scraping? Why some are soothed by watching people scrape their scalps! Is elderly drinking on the rise? The medical trend that could be harming your grandparents! Woman celebrates massive excess skin removal! Cauliflower chocolate smoothie? Man’s penis turns to bone? Uncovering singer Camila Cabello's mental health tip is for a stress free day!</desc>
    <date>20191016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722074629 +0000" stop="20250722083255 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Cringey Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Embarrassed by a family member? From Dad’s dancing to your cousin’s crazy clothes, learn how to combat your relative’s kookiest quirks! And, Dancing with the Stars’ Louis Van Amstel’s dance tips.</desc>
    <date>20111101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722083255 +0000" stop="20250722091950 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ashamed of My Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you your own worst critic? From sweaty armpits to thick ankles, see new solutions for your most “embarrassing” body problems. And, get simple, at-home remedies for brittle nails.</desc>
    <date>20091009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722091950 +0000" stop="20250722100642 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What The Yuck?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bothered by bad-smelling belches? Problem with pinworms? Get answers to the questions that make you go, “What the yuck?!” And, The Doctors’ Motherhood Survival Club tackles the biggest issues modern moms face.</desc>
    <date>20100924</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03021.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722100642 +0000" stop="20250722105320 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Mistakes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>People know that smoking causes cancer and continue to puff anyway, but could you be doing something you didn’t know was bad for you? The Doctors reveals some of the health mistakes you never knew you were making.</desc>
    <date>20091002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02021.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722105320 +0000" stop="20250722113850 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Best and Worst for Your Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Some tenets of good health are undisputable: vegetables are good for you, smoking is not. But some are not as obvious. The Doctors reveal the best and worst things you can do for your body.</desc>
    <date>20091022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02039.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722113850 +0000" stop="20250722122639 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Health Hazards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Did you know that brushing your teeth can actually harm your oral hygiene? And that coughing could lead to a hysterectomy? Find out seemingly-harmless situations that may be ruining your health. Plus, must-know sleeping pill info.</desc>
    <date>20121012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722122639 +0000" stop="20250722131326 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>10 Things I Hate About You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>From middle-of-the-night gas to unwanted hair loss, find out how to remedy things you may hate about your health. And, simple, healthy recipes your family will love!</desc>
    <date>20101004</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722131326 +0000" stop="20250722140016 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Body Quirk or Something Worse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E150</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedienne Niecy Nash goes on assignment to uncover mystifying body quirks and what you can do about them. And, a new, minimally invasive procedure promises to put an end to heavy periods. Plus, common sex mistakes men make.</desc>
    <date>20090422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01150.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722140016 +0000" stop="20250722144648 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E114</episode-num>
    <desc>A domestic violence survivor is nominated by her daughter for the ultimate Hollywood makeover and you won’t believe the transformation! The Dahm triplets put at-home ancestry kits to the test! The results will shock you! One yogi showcases her menstrual stain to the world … is her bold decision gross or empowering? Meet the record-breaking martial artists people are calling the modern-day Bruce Lee! Score Rosie Mercado’s must-have tips for full-figure fashion! If given the choice, would you choose a million dollars or true love? Find out why seniors are having the best sex! Plus, a simple way to move forward from emotional pain … today!</desc>
    <date>20170303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09114.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722144648 +0000" stop="20250722153246 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>20 Fast Fixes For Loads Of Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E148</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how maple syrup reduces the risk of cancer, the advantages of vinegar and treat five ailments for one dollar. Plus, if you think vodka is only good for making cosmos, think again! Discover the health benefits behind the bar.</desc>
    <date>20110510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03148.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722153246 +0000" stop="20250722161816 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Race to Erase 10 Years Makeover!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors “Race to Erase 10 Years” on a lucky audience member! Just wait until you see The jaw-dropping results! Candle explosion: could it happen to you? People are suing The major cereal companies over “nutritious” and “wholesome” claims! Guest loses 170 pounds but it isn’t enough! Find out what still is weighing her down. The Doctors discusses a new study that claims going vegan leads to depression! Product claims to whiten teeth 6 shades lighter in just 3 days? Does it work or is it 50 shades of disappointment? We’re putting it to The test! Plus, The water bottle danger you haven’t heard!</desc>
    <date>20171012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722161816 +0000" stop="20250722170439 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Spray Tanned Toddlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E76</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors discusses the wackiest health headlines! Hilarious photos of toddlers in a fake tan mess and how to safely clean up a bad tan! Which state has the most psychopaths? The best beauty buys all for under $10! The Doctors diagnoses your toilet dilemmas in a segment called, “What The Flush!” Instant treatment to reverse tremors?</desc>
    <date>20190503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722170439 +0000" stop="20250722175138 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Live In The OR</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors go Live in the OR to witness a knee replacement surgery! Woman finds out if she’s been catfished! Viral TikTok star talks about her life living with alopecia! Missouri woman fights to keep pet monkeys she claims helps her with PTSD!</desc>
    <date>20191003</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722175138 +0000" stop="20250722183823 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask The Docs: Permanent Cures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Backaches, allergies and toothaches are among the most common recurring health problems. Find out how to keep your chronic medical issues from coming back, and learn to keep body odor and bad breath at bay.</desc>
    <date>20091013</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722183823 +0000" stop="20250722192458 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Best Treatments From Head To Toe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E135</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share treatments from head to toe. Brooke Burke reveals how to regain your pre-pregnancy figure. And, Olympic champion Steve Holcomb shares how eye surgery helped him win gold.</desc>
    <date>20100426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722192458 +0000" stop="20250722201148 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Uncooked Pasta Addiction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman addicted to eating uncooked pasta for 30 years writes in to THE DOCTORS to save her life! Could her obsession with macaroni noodles be cured? Then, a body builder dies … from a protein overdose? And, why the internet has everyone cringing over the callus removal videos? Plus, could the hormones in fast food be to blame for one boy’s “A” cup breast? THE DOCTORS discusses the startling links between hormones and your health. And, caught on tape: a crazy calf cramp that seems to have a mind of its own! Then, see what happens when the “Yum Yuck Crew” kids give their critiques on avocado ice cream … will they like it? And, breast surgeon Dr. Kristi Funk gives you the “Breast Case Scenario” on your most embarrassing nipple issues.</desc>
    <date>20250324</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722201148 +0000" stop="20250722205829 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Frustrating Body Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Plagued by persistent and frustrating body problems like dandruff, blackheads or excessive sweating? The latest installment of Ask Our Doctors shows you how to get rid of pesky ailments for good!</desc>
    <date>20090128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722205829 +0000" stop="20250722214518 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eat, Sleep, Poop at Every Age</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Eat, sleep, poop; we all do it! The Doctors answers your questions about the three most common bodily functions! Get clear on food allergy rumors, discover the risks of snoring and learn how to combat the dangers of constipation.</desc>
    <date>20110125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722214518 +0000" stop="20250722223226 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Transplants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E59</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother hears her son’s voice for the very first time. See the cutting edge procedure that restored her hearing after 15 years of silence. Then, should your child take a break from ADHD medicines? Plus, are you overtreating your skin and hair?</desc>
    <date>20121203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722223226 +0000" stop="20250722231431 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E73</episode-num>
    <desc>A celebrity hairstylist that’s groomed some of the hottest men in Hollywood changes the lives of homeless people with a haircut! The Doctors first wedding for a couple whose story went viral! What’s The Real Deal with a wearable device that relieves headaches? Does it work? Infant sleeping dangers every parent must hear! Simple trick for a perfect burger!</desc>
    <date>20181127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11073.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250722231431 +0000" stop="20250723000122 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. G Medical Examiner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E78</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. G: Medical Examiner says that the dead don’t keep secrets. Watch a simulated autopsy, and learn ways to keep premature death and disease from your doorstep. And, a procedure that can shrink you six sizes in less than six hours.</desc>
    <date>20090119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250723000122 +0000" stop="20250723004805 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Health A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Improve your health from A to Z! From anti-aging to zits, The Doctors tackle common health concerns and share the latest medical treatments, simple cures and surprising tips to keep you in tip-top shape.</desc>
    <date>20091113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250723004805 +0000" stop="20250723013630 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Singer's Spine Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E58</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors Exclusive: Gloria Gaynor’s major spine surgery. Gloria and her surgeon, Dr. Hooman Melamed explains the risky procedure. Tips to protect your family this flu season! Testing new non-surgical procedure to rid you of saggy skin and those dreaded jowls. The man behind some of Hollywood’s biggest superheroes shares his top workout moves anyone can do at home. The surprising germy spots in your kitchen!</desc>
    <date>20191213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
