<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726000000 +0000" stop="20250726002959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old Trucks and Other Junk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in an old ’67 Ford pickup that has been hacked on over the years, and shows how to get rid of the old afterthought floor shifter, and convert it to a column shift that will actually shift gears! After that, Stacey digs into one of the newest fuel injection units on the market and shows how easy it is to install, and then demonstrates how to shave the drip rail off of your muscle car. Finally, we answer the question: Is it possible to put chrome plating on aluminum or stainless steel? We take a trip to Advance plating in Nashville to find out. There’s so much stuff going on, you’re gonna need to watch this show twice!</desc>
    <date>20110813</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0064.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726002959 +0000" stop="20250726005959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Breathing Fire into the Drag’N’Wagon – The New Face of Slot Cars/Carrera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on GEARZ, Stacey brings back the Drag’N’Wagon to see if he can get the beast to breathe some fire! The first thing he puts on is an ATI supercharger system to get some air sucking in. Then adds some hotter coils to help light the flame…and finally slaps on a bigger exhaust system to help blow the air out. If you are wondering how to make a street beast out of an entry level truck, this show spells it out. Then it’s on to the world of slot cars, as Stacey explores the past, present, and future of the little motorized miniatures that helped shape the gearhead world as we know it and introduces you to Carrera slot cars.</desc>
    <date>20120310</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0065.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726005959 +0000" stop="20250726013001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Super Cars, Kit Cars, and the SL-C</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on GEARZ, Stacey jumps into a project that’s bound to get everybody talking…a SUPERCAR that will run with the Ferraris and Lamborghinis that are out there. But, before he can show you HOW to build one, he has to show you how the whole supercar thing came into existence, and what it takes to build something that will run over 200mph…safely! If you’ve ever dreamed of owning a super car, and thought you couldn’t afford it…… this is a show you can’t afford to miss!</desc>
    <date>20120319</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0066.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726013001 +0000" stop="20250726020001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Body Building the SL-C</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Quick…what is the first thing that comes to mine when I say, “kit Car”? Well, if It’s images of cheap poorly fitting bodies, bad engineering, and goofy looking cars, you are about to have your mind changed as Stacey continues building a true supercar, from a Kit, that’ll run over 200Mph! From assembling the chassis to installing the body, this show goes into the nuts and bolts of what it takes to hand-build a car in your garage, that will rival the best that the European Exotics have to offer. Only in America, and only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20120326</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0067.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726020001 +0000" stop="20250726023000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Build Your Own LS7 &amp; Setting Up a Mid-Engine Drivetrain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>If you have ever dreamed of walking into a place like GM, and building your own engine using all their tools and equipment, you have to catch this episode of GEARZ, because that is exactly what Stacey does! With GM’s new build-your-own-crate-engine program, you are able to follow Stacey thru the process of building your own LS7 engine. Not only does it give you a great look at how these engines are built and manufactured, but it’ll also give you great incentive to get to GM and build your own! After that, Stacey goes thru the mysterious world of the transaxle, and how to set up a mid-engine car for mind-blowing performance. If you are not watching GEARZ, you’re missing out on a lot of things you haven’t seen before!</desc>
    <date>20120402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0068.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726023000 +0000" stop="20250726025958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Boosting the Ford EcoBoost &amp; Buffing Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the hottest new rigs on the market is the Ford F150 with the new 6 cylinder eco-boost engine. But is it all it can be? Well, today on GEARZ Stacey takes a new eco-boost powered Ford and shows you some simple upgrades that can boost performance AND fuel economy of this great new engine…..at a price you can afford. Then Stacey rolls in the nastiest, grungiest, barn-find Mustang that you can imagine and shows you the steps and tools required to buff an old nasty paint job back to life. Did we mention that this paint is BLACK!?! All to prove the point that if it can be done with a black car...it can be done with any car…and GEARZ is the show that shows you how to do it!</desc>
    <date>20120409</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0069.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726025958 +0000" stop="20250726033001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building a Brush Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With all the makeovers going on these days, it may surprise you to find that there ARE groups out there that could REALLY use some help. The local volunteer Fire Department is a perfect example of this. Since they are volunteers, nobody gets paid the put their life on the line day in and day out, and the equipment they use is generally hand-me-down stuff from the bigger Fire Departments. Well today on GEARZ, Stacey decides to do something about that by taking a stock Chevy dually pickup, and transform it into a state-of-the-art Brush truck for the local Volunteer Fire Department. The cool thing is, he’s using a lot of aftermarket parts that YOU can use on your project…And if it’s good enough for Firemen that go into harm’s way, you KNOW it is good enough for what you will use it for. So strap in, and let’s go ride a Fire Truck!</desc>
    <date>20120702</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0070.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726033001 +0000" stop="20250726040001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Station Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Station Wagons…Love them or hate them, we all have some stories to tell about them! But most of us have never dreamed that a wagon could be a Hot rod or cool custom…but they can! Today on GEARZ, Stacey shows how much fun a wagon can be when it has an LS engine under the hood, and two four barrel carburetors sitting on it. If you ever wanted to thrash your Dad’s old Wagon, this is the show for you! After that Stacey digs into some of the most asked questions regarding shooting waterborne paint, and finally we take a trip to Texas to see how one body-man created his own business by selling tools, instead of using them. If you are looking for a new career, this could be your answer.</desc>
    <date>20120709</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0071.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726040001 +0000" stop="20250726043002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt Rock Suspension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to Cadillac’s, most people immediately think of lowering them down, and cruising with them. However, since the Cadillac Escalade is a great SUV, we thought it would be great to take the Escalade of Country artist Jason Sturgeon, and put a 3 ½” Skyjacker lift on it. Now you have no reason not to go hunting or fishing in style! After that we head to the land of the Predator, and see what it takes to be one of the most successful Monster Trucks of all time with Alan Pezo. Finally, we rub a little of that Monster Truck DNA on SGT. ROCK, as we upgrade the suspension and get it ready to do a little crushing of its own!</desc>
    <date>20120716</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0072.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726043002 +0000" stop="20250726050002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ram 1500 Longhorn/Katzkin Upholstery/ Schwartz Performance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that you can get almost anything you want on a new car or truck these days. The problem is, if you use your truck for work, “almost” just doesn’t get it. Today on GEARZ, Stacey takes a decked out new truck, and adds some key tools and equipment to make it something that you can literally take to work or play with. After that, we dig into the mysterious world of leather interiors, and show how it is possible for you to buy a top quality leather upholstery kit, and install it yourself. Finally, we roll in the SL-C and show what it takes to put twin turbos on an LS7. It’s gonna be crazy, and it’s only gonna be on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20120723</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0073.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726050002 +0000" stop="20250726053004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Project Heavy Metal Suspension &amp; Dax Shepard "Hit and Run" Lincoln Continental</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls Heavy Metal back into the shop and begins to lay out some of the incredible modifications that he is going to be doing on this old junk yard ’69 International Cab over truck. A custom four-link air suspension goes on first, and then a slick air brake system to pull this big monster to a stop. A custom exhaust is also laid out, along with numerous other modifications to make this a one of a kind rig. If you have ever wondered if a Cab over could make a cool hot rod, you need to check this out. From there it’s off to the movies as Stacey digs into the impact and influence movie cars have on our lives and culture. To prove that point, He brings in actor Dax Shepard and his cool ’67 Lincoln Continental who are both starring in the new movie “Hit and Run”. So strap in and hold on, ‘cuz we might get airborne on this ride!</desc>
    <date>20120730</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0074.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726053004 +0000" stop="20250726060005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Foxbody Mustang Stick Shift Swap &amp; V8 Interceptor Paint and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that 80’s and 90’s cars are hot right now, and one of the most desirable is the Fox bodied Mustang because it’s cheap and offers incredible bang for the buck. Today on GEARZ, Stacey rolls in a 1990 Mustang cop car and shows how easy it is to pull out an automatic tranny, and stuff in a Tremec 6spd so you can shift the gears properly. Then it’s off to the Hot Rod Institute in South Dakota to see the paint and body work that the instructors and students have been doing to the V8 Interceptor. If you thought this ’67 Cougar was wild before, wait ‘til you see this show! Here Kitty,…..Kitty……Kitty….</desc>
    <date>20120806</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0075.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726060005 +0000" stop="20250726063004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Modifying a Polaris Ranger UTV/Side-By-Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the hottest vehicles to hit the gear head world is the Side-by-Side, or Utility Vehicle. Once relegated to just farm or ranch work, the UTV is now something that you will see being used for Hunting, Fishing, Camping, Landscaping….virtually ANY kind of outdoor work or recreation. Of course that means the aftermarket is full of things to make an UTV better. Today on GEARZ, Stacey takes a Polaris Ranger and decks it out with a 3 ½” lift, bigger tires and axles, winches front and rear, and all kinds of other cool things to build an all-terrain vehicle that will really shine on the trail or off. After that he gives you a sneak peek at the new Ironworker that has everybody talking. If you work a lot with metal, you need this machine!</desc>
    <date>20121112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0076.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726063004 +0000" stop="20250726070007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Drving the Drag N Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey puts a programmer on the Drag ‘N’ Wagon to finally bring the stripped down Ram Hot Rod truck to life. If you’ve been wondering what kind of performance potential these new Ram Express trucks have, wait until you see one lit up with a supercharger! Talk about breathing fire! After that Stacey lays out how to set up a shop with custom flooring, custom cabnets, and of course a lot of tools and toolboxes. If you’ve ever wondered about the best way to lay out a shop, and utilize your space, this is the show to see… and GEARZ is the show to watch!</desc>
    <date>20130301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0077.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726070007 +0000" stop="20250726072956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Tow Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Project Heavy Metal is back as Stacey rolls the International Cabover truck into the shop so he can outfit it with a vintage Holmes dual wrecker bed. The big truck continues to come together using parts from a junkyard wrecker, swap meet vintage beer kegs, and some new aftermarket parts. If you always thought that you had to spend big money to build a unique vehicle, this “Heavy Metal” truck will change your mind, and probably have you digging through junkyards in hopes of finding a vintage truck of your own!</desc>
    <date>20130308</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0078.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726072956 +0000" stop="20250726075957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Long Bed Into Short Bed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody wants a classic short bed pickup. Unfortunately, short beds are hard to find for a good price… but long beds are a dime-a-dozen, and cheap! The solution?... chop a long bed down! That is exactly what Stacey does on this episode of GEARZ. He takes a classic 67 Chevy long bed, and walks you through the way to cut the frame properly, so you have a safe and reliable truck when you are done. If you’ve heard about this kind of modification, but always thought it was too difficult or involved for you to do, you need to watch this episode of GEARZ and let the cutting begin!</desc>
    <date>20130315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0079.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726075957 +0000" stop="20250726082955 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Monn Buggy Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Who put men on the moon? If you answered “Gearheads” then you are right… of course, we call them engineers and rocket scientists now. But that doesn’t change the fact that a bunch of hot rodders figured out how to get America into Space, and Stacey takes a look at the roots of the Space Program, and the invention of the moon buggy. Then it’s out to the NASA testing grounds to see the annual Moon buggy race. If you think you’ve seen some weird projects, wait until you see what some of these young minds have dreamed up. You may think you’re on another planet, but you’re not… you’re watching GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20130322</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0080.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726082955 +0000" stop="20250726085956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Short Bed Classic Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey picks up right where he left off a few weeks ago and proceeds to install a brand new short bed, on the chassis of a truck that was born a LONG BED. That’s right, with the cutting done, the next step is to assemble a new short bed using all new aftermarket parts. You hear people say, “if it was that easy, everybody would be doing it!” Well, it IS that easy, and a lot of people ARE doing it… and YOU need to be one of them! Now… chop to it!</desc>
    <date>20130329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0081.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726085956 +0000" stop="20250726092957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>P38 Lightning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It was one of the most lethal airplanes of WWII… the P-38 Lightning. Stacey takes a look at what made it so unique and why the German army nicknamed it the “Forked tailed devil”. But the legend didn’t end in the 1940’s… it continues on as Stacey showcases the new P-38 engine parts from Jon Kaase that you can put on your small block Ford to make it run like greased lightning! After that, Stacey sits down with Rock and Roll legend and certified car nut, James Burton, to dig into the unique connection between cars, guitars, and Rock and roll. Turn it on… crank it up… and hold on!</desc>
    <date>20130405</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0082.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726092957 +0000" stop="20250726095956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Lawn &amp; Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Some of the most neglected tools around the house are lawn and garden tools. Mowers, weed-eaters, chain saws, etc. all usually get thrown in a garage in the fall, never to be touched again until spring. Stacey walks through the simple steps on how to care for those tools, so they give you years of trouble free service. After that, He goes through the many parts you will need to put a manual transmission into a project, with Transmission Tech. Finally, if you’re looking for a simple project to do over the weekend, how about a muffler swap? You say “no”?... Stacey says “yes.”</desc>
    <date>20130412</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0083.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726095956 +0000" stop="20250726102958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Interceptor Paint and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The V8 Interceptor is BACK and wearing a striking coat of glossy black paint! How did it happen? Well, Stacey walks you through the process and shows off the incredible paint and body work that was done by the Hot Rod Institute. From the subtle body nips and tucks, to the major fabrication of a new roof, this classic Cougar now has a straighter body than anything that may have rolled off the assembly line in 1967! But the paint is only half the story, as Stacey starts to re-assemble the car with bumpers, lights and engine, you start to get a good look at what is rapidly becoming the ultimate street predator!</desc>
    <date>20130419</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0084.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726102958 +0000" stop="20250726110001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Winches</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>What is cooler than a vintage tow truck? … Nothing! Stacey proves that point by rolling Heavy Metal back into the GEARZ shop to outfit it with new electric winches, and an amazing custom tool box and light bar. This ’69 International cabover truck may have been rescued from a junkyard, but it won’t be long before this truck starts pulling off rescues of its own! This is recycling at it’s best! Then ride along with Stacey and crew as they travel to Minnesota and get the story on Edwards Manufacturing and how they have managed to stay in business for over a hundred years building simple tools. It’s all good, and it’s all GEARZ!!</desc>
    <date>20130426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0085.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726110001 +0000" stop="20250726113002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ray Barton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When you say “HEMI”, you get people’s attention! But when you say “Ray Barton HEMI” you win races. Stacey and crew take you to Ray Barton Racing Engines to show you the amazing engines and parts they build, and why they go so fast. After that, Stacey digs into the interior of the V8 Interceptor and shows what kind of options you have when you are restoring or customizing the interior of your project. You’ll love the custom PRS guitar and matching wood dash and steering wheel! There is no doubt that this Cougar is the perfect blend of brutal power, and sophisticated elegance.</desc>
    <date>20130503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0086.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726113002 +0000" stop="20250726120002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt. Rock Exhaust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in SGT. ROCK to take care of steering, brakes, and the exhaust system. With a quick trip to Stainless Works for a custom set of headers and exhaust system, and with the layout of the four-wheel hydraulic steering, it won’t be long before this big military beast is rolling under its own power. After that, he takes on the seat in Heavy Metal tow truck. Just because a project may have come out of a junkyard, doesn’t mean it has to look like junk. Stacey proves that by adding a custom bomber-style seat to this already VERY unique vehicle… this episode of GEARZ is the one to see!</desc>
    <date>20130510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0087.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726120002 +0000" stop="20250726123003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Moby Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey sets out to build a nice hunting rig out of a 2012 GMC 4x4 truck. But this rig belongs to John Godwin of Duck Commander, which means the truck will be spending some serious time on the road… and off… hunting for ducks. On goes a 6” lift, 35” tall tires, and massive bumpers and winch to pull this big white beast out of any mud holes it may end up in. And since it IS such a big white beast, it is only fitting that Stacey name this project “Moby Duck”! If you’ve ever wondered if it’s possible to have a daily driver, that can also be a nice hunting, fishing, or outdoor rig. This episode of GEARZ will show you how to do it.</desc>
    <date>20130517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0088.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726123003 +0000" stop="20250726130004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Super Car, Hot Rods, Go Carts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls the SL-C back into the shop to show off the twin turbo system Schwartz Performance installed. If you thought 1000hp out of an LS-7 was impossible, THINK AGAIN! Even wilder is the fact that this engine is pulling that kind of horsepower on pump gas! If supercars and twin turbos are your thing, you have to see this! After that, Stacey goes through some of the problem areas that you will face when you are building a vehicle and how to pick the right project. Finally He digs into the 1st motorized vehicle that most of us had…the Go-Kart. There's something for everybody in this show. That’s why they call it GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20130524</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0089.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726130004 +0000" stop="20250726133005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building A Shop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>We dig into the ultimate how-to project… building a shop! It’s an incredible transformation as Stacey and Crew take a huge open warehouse and build it into the new GEARZ shop. Along the way you’ll pick up all kinds of tips and tricks that Stacey uses when he’s setting up a useable work space. With today’s economy, there are more and more people thinking about opening a shop, or converting their existing garage space into a more useable area. This show can help you do that. After that, Stacey shows how to stop rust dead in its tracks by using the simplest tool in the box… a paint brush! It’s all here on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140407</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0090.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726133005 +0000" stop="20250726140005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Gearz Express</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey makes a house call… to Pennsylvania! Why?... to pick up an old fire truck to use as a project truck to make even more house calls with! If this sounds confusing, then you NEED to see this show, because Stacey shows you how to take a vehicle that nobody really has a use for anymore, and convert it into something you can use for your home or business. Sound deadening, tool boxes, and an on-board air system are all things that you’ll see go on as the big green fire truck, begins the conversion into a rolling tool truck</desc>
    <date>20140414</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0091.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726140005 +0000" stop="20250726143007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>100th Episode Pt. 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s anniversary time…the 100th episode of GEARZ! And we have put together a one-hour special of the history and making of GEARZ, in two episodes! Stacey takes a look back at how the show came about. Then he digs into some of the project vehicles, and looks at the ideas and reasoning that shaped these trend-setting vehicles. If you’re new to GEARZ or wondered how the show was put together, this episode will shed some light on that</desc>
    <date>20140421</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0092.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726143007 +0000" stop="20250726150003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>100th Episode Pt. 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Part two of the 100th Episode special starts with a bang and a lot of tire smoke, as Stacey looks back at some of the wild test drives and feature vehicles that have been on GEARZ over the years. After that, they go behind the scenes and show you some of the funny and potentially dangerous situations that can happen when you work on a show like GEARZ. Finally, we showcase some of the incredible guests that have been on the show, to give you an idea of what to expect in the future. It’s all here and only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140428</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0093.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726150003 +0000" stop="20250726153003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Wrapping The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in the big green fire truck, with every intention of changing the color and look. But he’s not using paint… he’s using a vinyl wrap! If you’ve ever wondered what the deal is with vinyl wraps and if it is a good thing to do to your project, you need to see this show! But that’s not all, as the wrap is going on, Stacey also takes the time to show how to restore and bring back to life your accessories and trim without spending a lot of money.</desc>
    <date>20140505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0094.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726153003 +0000" stop="20250726160004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Richard Petty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>If you’ve been around cars very much, you’ve heard the term “barn find”. It depicts that “diamond in the rough” vehicle that everybody wants to find. Stacey delves into the barn find phenomenon and unveils what could be the ultimate barn find… the lost Richard Petty Car! Follow the incredible story of the car that Richard and Maurice Petty built in their early days, that was then sold and disappeared for decades... only to be found by Stacey and returned to Richard Petty so it could take its rightful place in the Petty Museum. It’s gearhead archeology at its best, and you’ll only see it on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0095.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726160004 +0000" stop="20250726163005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey hits the road to visit a GEARZNation member to see if he can lend a hand on his project. The owner is a 16-year-old kid and the subject is his ’96 Dodge pickup that’s looking a little rough from years of use and abuse. That quickly changes as Stacey jumps in to help give the truck a new face, and at the same time offers tips and tricks to breathe a breath of fresh air into the project. See what a difference some time, expertise, and a few parts can make on a beat up old truck! After that, Stacey takes a look at the amazing Moduline Cabinets, and digs into what makes them so great.</desc>
    <date>20140519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0096.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726163005 +0000" stop="20250726170002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>LMC Casey James Bronco</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey shows you how to tackle the one restoration project that everybody dreams of doing one day... the frame off restoration! You’ll be surprised how simple a job like this can be if you follow his simple tips and tricks and plan the project out properly. In the world of high dollar builds, a simple frame off restoration can get you back on the road enjoying your car or truck and at a fraction of the price. But to get a grasp on how to do it, you have to see this show. After that, Stacey swaps some licks with recording artist Casey James who just happens to be a gearhead at heart… all here… all Gearz!</desc>
    <date>20140526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0097.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726170002 +0000" stop="20250726173003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Custom Bumper Mounts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>So, you think you want some custom bumpers for your big ol’ truck? Stacey shows you how to find what you’re looking for in the aftermarket, and also how to fabricate and build your own custom mounts to make ‘em sit exactly where you want them. After that he digs into the history of the Sgt. Rock truck and how it is permanently connected to “the greatest generation”. But this truck isn’t just about WWII, as a special tailgate airbrushed by Mickey Harris reveals, It’s about the men and women that have sacrificed for the freedoms we enjoy today. This is one show that will have you waving the flag!</desc>
    <date>20140602</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0098.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726173003 +0000" stop="20250726180004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey hits the road to help out a Gearz Nation member with his ‘56 Corvette project. Since the guy really wants to drive the car, putting in a modern 5 or 6spd tranny would be really nice. But which one? Well, we not only answer that question, but also give the guy a little helping hand with the transmission too. If you’ve ever wished Stacey made house calls, this is the show to see. After that we take a look at some serious questions that people ask about becoming a tool dealer and if it’s really worth it. You wanted to know… we got the answers for you!</desc>
    <date>20140609</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0099.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726180004 +0000" stop="20250726183004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Street Sweeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey dives into the world of the sleeper, by taking a non-descript ’73 Plymouth Satellite, and begins transforming it into a street pounding monster under the skin. Gone is the lethargic 318 engine and front suspension, and in its place Stacey begins fitting a new state of the art performance suspension. It you are into surprising people at stop lights and run-what-you-brung race nights, then a “Street Sweeper” just might be the sort of approach you want to take on your next project.</desc>
    <date>20140616</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0100.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726183004 +0000" stop="20250726190004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Street Sweeper E3 Testing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Street Sweeper is back! Stacey delves into just how many parts it takes to completely change the drivetrain and suspension on a classic muscle car. Accessories, transmission, overdrive, headers, the list may seem to go on forever, but it’s all about finding the right parts in the aftermarket, to build the car that YOU want. After that it’s off to the races to see if E3’s new top fuel spark plug can handle the pressure of competition. If you want to see the ins and outs of building a car, GEARZ is the show to see!</desc>
    <date>20140623</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0101.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726190004 +0000" stop="20250726193001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Street Sweeper Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>If you could only do one upgrade on your vehicle, that would make the biggest impact on the looks and drivability, what would it be? Stacey answers that question by installing a Katzkin leather interior into a Jeep Compass, and showing that if you’ve got an open weekend and a few hundred bucks, you can do the same thing on your car or truck. After that, he jumps back onto the Street Sweeper project to lay out the interior and the rearend, and finally drop that huge Hemi into place. If you’ve ever thought it would be fun to build a sleeper car, this is one ’73 Plymouth Satellite that shows how it can be done!</desc>
    <date>20140630</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0102.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726193001 +0000" stop="20250726200003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>NAPA Perfect Additions Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey Preps the bed of the NAPA Perfect additions truck. From rolling out Herculiner to installing transfer tank, truck boxes, and even a combination generator/compressor, this big Ford begins its Perfect Additions transformation. He also throws in a wiring tech that will keep you from getting your wires crossed.</desc>
    <date>20150306</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0103.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726200003 +0000" stop="20250726203003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>NAPA Perfect Additions Truck 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey tackles power gains at the air intake, modifies the computer and replaces the stock exhaust before addressing a 2” front-end suspension lift kit. He moves on to give the truck some extra height and support in the rear of the truck where payload weight can be a serious issue. After the suspension is in place, new wheels and tires bring the truck back down to the ground. Stacey also covers several tools that will help you get that old exhaust out from under your vehicle.</desc>
    <date>20150313</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0104.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726203003 +0000" stop="20250726210004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Junkyard Jag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey leads the crew on a hunt for a junkyard Jaguar with a rare engine. Pin-striping legend Von Hot Rod comes to the GearZ studio and lays down some lines on a hot rod guitar. Need to repair or replace the door on your pick up? Stacey’s got a handle on that. A bed lifter system turns a four-man operation into a one-man show. And Stacey’s got a steering column that will keep Falcon owners between the lines. All this and more!</desc>
    <date>20150320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0105.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726210004 +0000" stop="20250726213003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Evolution Worlds Fastest Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey tells the story of the legendary Cheetah and how that car was designed to beat Shelby’s famed Cobra. The GEARZ hunt for this iconic race car features the original ’63 Cheetah that Budd Clusserath drove 215 mph at Daytona in ‘64. But the story doesn’t end there, because Stacey gets his hands on a Cheetah Evolution and shows you how to build your own version of this tire shredding cat! After that, you’ll see Steering wheel options from Grant, a serpentine belt system from LMC Truck, and Wizard products to make your vehicle come alive, as well as a quick tip to get things rolling in your shop. All this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150403</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0107.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726213003 +0000" stop="20250726220004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Put A Heart In The Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Moving deeper into the build of the Cheetah Evolution, Stacey and the crew pull the skin off this cat and start putting in the guts. Overviews of suspension, steering, and brakes get this project up and running. Moving into the heart of this beast, Stacey shows us that good things do come in small packages—the LSX 454 small block is sure to get your pulse rate up. And once the transmission is mounted, look out! Headers follow, and this cat is almost ready to run. Stacey’s tool tech will give you a lift… all this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150410</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0108.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726220004 +0000" stop="20250726223004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Paws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A road trip, an overview of the Cheetah interior including seat and dash installation, rear lights and a tool tech. The GearZ crew heads out on the prowl to visit a budding young mechanic with a passion for 4X4’s. Back in the garage, Stacey gets in tight with the Cheetah, installing seats and the dash. Selecting gauges and placement are discussed, an AC unit will help keep this cat cool, taillights are fitted, and the side pipes will give this Cheetah some growl! Stacey’s tool tech will keep your project on time and on budget. And Fast Orange cleans more than your hands. All this on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150417</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0109.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726223004 +0000" stop="20250726230003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Beaten &amp; Downtrodden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Auction cars and what you might really find out once the car is in your garage: suspension, brakes and electrical concerns. In the current fad of “flipping” cars for cash, Stacey takes on the good, bad, and ugly of a ’66 Biscayne that was bought at auction. Nice looking paint can’t hide the safety issues that are found once this car is put on the lift. From suspension, to brakes, to battery cables… and even down to the lug nuts, this auction beauty turns out to be more of a beast. Safety and sport-style handling are only a few repairs away this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0110.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726230003 +0000" stop="20250726233005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Automotive Icon Turns 40</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the crew head north to celebrate 40 years of Heartthrob Exhaust and see just how far this company has come since its modest beginnings in a garage. After that we dig into a cracked dash and show how easy it is to replace one yourself with some aftermarket parts from LMC Truck, and then we look at a painless solution will help clean up years of spliced wires and old electrical tape that might be lurking under your hood. It’s simple gearhead stuff that everybody needs to know and it’s only on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150501</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0111.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726233005 +0000" stop="20250727000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Gets Her Growl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey digs back into the Cheetah project by finishing up the stance with custom wheels and tires, and then goes through the ins and outs of putting a classic Hilborn fuel injection on a modern LS engine… and the dyno numbers show that the engine likes it as much as you will! After that Stacey sits down with a budding car designer that is making a big impact everywhere he goes and there’s also a tip on the importance of seals and gaskets. It’s all about getting out and turning wrenches, and you’re only gonna find it on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20150508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0112.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250727000000 +0000" stop="20250727003001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Curves On Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey explores the history of the legendary Jaguar D-type racecar and introduces a D-type Jag from Race Car Replicas that is sure to become a legend of its own. From race wheels to classic spoke wheels with true knock-offs, Stacey looks at options for getting the best look and most rubber on the road with this Jag. A tip might keep you from losing your mind when dealing with lug nuts that don’t want to budge and we talk shop about performance parts for your own cars. So, come hang out while we take on a legendary cat of a different color this week on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20150515</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0113.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
