<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250719230000 +0000" stop="20250720000000 +0000">
    <title>Chasing The Sun: Asia</title>
    <sub-title>Chasing The Sun: Asia - Taiwan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>From urban bustle to tranquil beaches, Taiwan has a soul and culture all its own.  Creativity abounds in its people, not to mention the greatest vegan food in the world.</desc>
    <date>20201103</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/vzxmqzkmnsdd1orffq0zza5yc/original/vzxmqzkmnsdd1orffq0zza5yc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720000000 +0000" stop="20250720010000 +0000">
    <title>Chasing The Sun: Asia</title>
    <sub-title>Chasing The Sun: Asia - South Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Explore a place where it’s illegal to be a tattoo artist and the people living in a rapidly changing culture.  A place where GPS limitations mean the possibilities to get lost in music and art are endless.</desc>
    <date>20201103</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1n4elz3vbbzyl1sgphpdiobm9/original/1n4elz3vbbzyl1sgphpdiobm9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720010000 +0000" stop="20250720020000 +0000">
    <title>Chasing The Sun: Asia</title>
    <sub-title>Chasing The Sun: Asia - Japan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Land of the rising sun and the fastest trains in the world that takes us from skateboarders to drag queens and one of the last remaining old-world jazz bars. We meet a chalk artist and a sculptor who makes art with a bite (aka: real teeth).</desc>
    <date>20201105</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/12u92iuugeytb1fjw3ebk9rzb/original/12u92iuugeytb1fjw3ebk9rzb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720020000 +0000" stop="20250720023000 +0000">
    <title>On the Record With Mick Rock</title>
    <sub-title>On the Record with Mick Rock - Josh Groban in Los Angeles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Native Angeleno and multi-platinum recording artist Josh Groban takes Mick on an inspiring tour of Los Angeles, paying homage to the high school teacher who gave him the confidence to succeed, stopping by the after-school Shakespeare program he personally supports and treating Mick to a moving performance of his song, “Hidden Away.”</desc>
    <date>20220902</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/q6dizyrbwktu1t7tqlf9o7g1p/original/q6dizyrbwktu1t7tqlf9o7g1p.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720023000 +0000" stop="20250720030000 +0000">
    <title>On the Record With Mick Rock</title>
    <sub-title>On the Record with Mick Rock - Kings of Leon in Nashville</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mick discovers how the Grammy Award-winning rock stars, Kings of Leon, escaped their Pentecostal roots to find a home in Nashville’s evolving music scene. The band dishes on its rocky past and gives Mick a tour of country music’s hometown, ending the day in the Kings’ private studio for an exclusive jam session.</desc>
    <date>20220902</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/6v629xiee6b412lcfojvw0u9b/original/6v629xiee6b412lcfojvw0u9b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720030000 +0000" stop="20250720033000 +0000">
    <title>On the Record With Mick Rock</title>
    <sub-title>On the Record with Mick Rock S01 E03 - The Flaming Lips in Oklahoma City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mick touches down in Oklahoma City to hang with the Flaming Lips and uncovers how these masters of psychedelic rock have become the surprising hometown heroes. Lead singer Wayne Coyne shows off his wacky art gallery, fills Mick in on his all-night parties with Miley Cyrus and ends the day with a performance of the group’s hit song, “Do You Realize??”</desc>
    <date>20220902</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/16o9glferhnbv1ftwyyn5rd53/original/16o9glferhnbv1ftwyyn5rd53.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720033000 +0000" stop="20250720040000 +0000">
    <title>On the Record With Mick Rock</title>
    <sub-title>On the Record with Mick Rock - Patti Labelle in Philadelphia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Grammy Hall of Fame artist Patti LaBelle takes Mick on a personal tour of Philadelphia, visiting the theater that launched her career and stopping by her childhood home where she first found her voice with a broomstick microphone. After grabbing a bite at her favorite soul food spot in the City of Brotherly Love, Patti invites Mick into her living room for an intimate performance of What Can I Do For You?</desc>
    <date>20220902</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/32n7ltnz93lg1bab3kjd9yxpy/original/32n7ltnz93lg1bab3kjd9yxpy.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720040000 +0000" stop="20250720043000 +0000">
    <title>On the Record With Mick Rock</title>
    <sub-title>On the Record with Mick Rock - Mark Ronson in New York</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mick Rocks visits with English musician and DJ Mark Ronson in New York City.</desc>
    <date>20220902</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/tzmxuyl0pkku1hnv29gbwefca/original/tzmxuyl0pkku1hnv29gbwefca.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720043000 +0000" stop="20250720050000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E01 - Heart of New Zealand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we head straight into the heart of New Zealand! We begin back in time, in an era of proud warriors and ancient traditions with Tamaki Maori Village, the most award-winning cultural attraction in New Zealand. Then we step through Hell's Gate and experience the country's most unique geothermal occurrence. Eager to catch our breath, we lose it walking amongst the breathing majestic giants at Redwood Tree Walk. And finally, arrive in Hobbiton. Yes, that Hobbiton of lore!</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1qhvin0p9sgx3z5nbkf7fjd9m/original/1qhvin0p9sgx3z5nbkf7fjd9m.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720050000 +0000" stop="20250720053000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E02 - Waiheke Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we seek refuge in Waiheke, New Zealand. Stonyridge Vineyards, a farm that is less about cropping and all about farming flavor- proves to be a fine locality from which to begin this episodic excursion into paradise. Unsurprisingly, our appetite for ingesting the best of this region leads us to the nutrient-rich, Te Matuku Marine Reserve- where we learn the value of a keystone species of the ecosystem... OYSTERS! Bellyful and bound to take a dip, we meander to Waiheke Island Resor</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/r8wonjuawnny1opjwkkae1f41/original/r8wonjuawnny1opjwkkae1f41.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720053000 +0000" stop="20250720060000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E03 - Great Ocean Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we admire history from up high while visiting the oldest surviving lighthouse on mainland Australia. Then, we enter into a passionate relationship between an unordinary couple that involves alpacas. Next, our own expectations are blown away by retreating at the 12 Apostles/Alkina Lodge! Following that, we find a soulmate to our fellow animals at Great Ocean Road Wildlife Park. And finally, take a seat at the comfortable whiskey bar at Timboon Distillery before walking on top of</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/kvj8ulf13qelzsc419i9clmf/original/kvj8ulf13qelzsc419i9clmf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720060000 +0000" stop="20250720063000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E04 - New South Wales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we arrive in Sydney by departing into the Ken Done realm of artistry. Set a spin, we then roam the regions of Coffs Harbour and Urunga! Partaking in a happiness revolution in the shape of a grocery store (The Happy Frog) to paddle-boarding with direct descendants of the world's first stand up paddlers down a historical stream- this episode highlights the aim of being open to diversity in epic forms!</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/q7z4istcp67x1ud7w1nq6ao1x/original/q7z4istcp67x1ud7w1nq6ao1x.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720063000 +0000" stop="20250720070000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E05 - Brisbane</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we "hang" with some friends abseiling over Southbank Parklands! Then we gather our courage and ascend the Story Bridge. Next, we mount some horses and find ourselves prospecting for gemstones at Thunderbird Park. Finally, we pull over and unwind in koala territory up on Mount Tambourine.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1jpiq2m1iu5li1pllmepcdnw7/original/1jpiq2m1iu5li1pllmepcdnw7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720070000 +0000" stop="20250720073000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E06 - Cairns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we discover where Australia begins by embarking down the Mulgrave River on an exclusive day tour out to the Frankland Islands. Next, we explore a bit of cultural history by spearfishing alongside the Daintree Rainforest. Then we go full eco-touristic while visiting a revered sanctuary of wildlife, Hartley's Crocodile Adventure! Ultimately, we arrive at Fitzroy Island Retreat. Enough said!</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/vrbkhwvbt3mb1156zs9llzvyq/original/vrbkhwvbt3mb1156zs9llzvyq.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720073000 +0000" stop="20250720080000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E07 - Hawaii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we pursue the spirit of ambition while discovering Hawaii's immortal culture! From walking the hallowed grounds of Hilo Coffee Mill to witnessing the reinvention of traditions at Old Lahaina Luau- this episode represents the best of what is to be expected while traveling wide-eyed through paradise!</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1dv3g0kzhz0jt1lh3r55eozsr/original/1dv3g0kzhz0jt1lh3r55eozsr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720080000 +0000" stop="20250720083000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E08 - The Island Hawaii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we visit The Island of Hawaii better known as “The Big Island.” Here, we explore the history and geography of the islands, learn how to Hula Dance, visit a tranquil secluded retreat, learn the art of lei-making, and have some sea and land adventures!</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1lgpye3jiu8uh1tvhc4zq0sgx/original/1lgpye3jiu8uh1tvhc4zq0sgx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720083000 +0000" stop="20250720090000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E09 - Pacific Cuisine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we explore the taste of pacific cuisine. From Hawaiian fusion and the beloved coffee bean to New Zealand oysters and tropical fish, Didiayer shares a variety of tastes around the pacific rim.</desc>
    <date>20231016</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/17ziiw5nf848619jrad8ze49f/original/17ziiw5nf848619jrad8ze49f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720090000 +0000" stop="20250720093000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E10 - Pacific Culture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we explore culture old and new through a variety of unique destinations. Whether it be doing the Haka with a Maori tribe, weaving alpaca hair, or getting the real story behind the Hawaiian Luau, this episode dives in to the customs that bring people together.</desc>
    <date>20231016</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/18hrtroyl74gx190uhqdks1pa/original/18hrtroyl74gx190uhqdks1pa.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720093000 +0000" stop="20250720100000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E11 - Pacific Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we step out and in to nature to explore what adventure awaits. Amongst rappelling, zip-lining, horseback riding, snorkeling with dolphins and feeding crocodiles there is hardly a moment to catch your breath!</desc>
    <date>20231016</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1d0fnfhxeqmiq18fd50aec7nb/original/1d0fnfhxeqmiq18fd50aec7nb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720100000 +0000" stop="20250720103000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E12 - Pacific Stays</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we share some of the best places from our journey where we chose to rest our heads. High-class or just like home, these lovely accommodations are sure to fit anyone’s budget and style.</desc>
    <date>20231016</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1k6tay2r9a2231x6m2v9apfi7/original/1k6tay2r9a2231x6m2v9apfi7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720103000 +0000" stop="20250720110000 +0000">
    <title>Travel with Didiayer</title>
    <sub-title>Travel with Didiayer S03 E13 - Memorable Moments</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we revisit this season's best moments in art, cuisine, culture, and adventure. These are cherished memories we hope will inspire you to head out and find your wanderlust.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1celgbgf5m7dv1vmyc64y2gn7/original/1celgbgf5m7dv1vmyc64y2gn7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720110000 +0000" stop="20250720123000 +0000">
    <title>Kyle Supley’s Out There</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Supley's Out There!  - People come to New York City to discover creative culture and characters - but not everyone knows where find them.</desc>
    <date>20200701</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/esotsbgxzjf1wz9aqx4r2ku9/original/esotsbgxzjf1wz9aqx4r2ku9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720123000 +0000" stop="20250720130000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - Charleston, SC</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee show off the best bites and sights in their hometown of Charleston, South Carolina, from Lowcountry oyster roasts to an undersea winery.</desc>
    <date>20150614</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049d60c/c85858ba-771d-4e50-a5b2-86e80d06ab3bthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720130000 +0000" stop="20250720133000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - Atlanta, GA</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee discover the international flavors of Atlanta, from Southern meets Asian “Seoul” food to globally inspired ice pops and redefined airport dining.</desc>
    <date>20150621</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049e14a/41a29878-3160-490e-a98f-a4f3b291abd2thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720133000 +0000" stop="20250720140000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - Asheville, NC</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee forage for wild ramps, throw down some local clay with a renowned ceramic artist and sample an unexpected pairing of yoga and beer in Asheville, North Carolina.</desc>
    <date>20150628</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049d9c3/e880004c-bef4-4627-818c-1a067d14c125thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720140000 +0000" stop="20250720143000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - Louisville, KY</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee descend on Louisville, Kentucky, to brew soy sauce in bourbon barrels, explore Mayan-meets-Southern cuisine and get a new taste of the traditional Hot Brown sandwich.</desc>
    <date>20150705</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049e96c/aa8f2836-c9f5-403b-807b-d9d1abc5dfb4thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720143000 +0000" stop="20250720150000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - Dallas, TX</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee land in Dallas for a taste of barbecue that’s smoking the competition before sampling the best of Tex Mex, Mex-Mex and Czech-Mex flavors.</desc>
    <date>20150712</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049dd8a/f6ebc168-c6d5-4b29-a534-89dc3fa95352thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720150000 +0000" stop="20250720153000 +0000">
    <title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Uncovered with the Lee Brothers - New Orleans, LA</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Ted Lee head to New Orleans where Creole and Vietnamese flavors merge, modern Israeli food finds a home and a historic cocktail culture gives rise to tasty hangover cures.</desc>
    <date>20150719</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/62be0d7f5e5872e95049d198/9136a523-82d5-4846-8ed4-26d2c913e6a7thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720153000 +0000" stop="20250720160000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Special Guest Florence Henderson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke meets up with Florence Henderson ("The Brady Bunch") at her neighborhood Italian restaurant where they enjoy a sumptuous pasta dinner and share stories of Florence's on-and-off-screen families.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1u7ssvdsft66t128juvk991by/original/1u7ssvdsft66t128juvk991by.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720160000 +0000" stop="20250720163000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Special Guest Jane Seymour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke visits Jane Seymour ("Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman") at her Malibu home to explore her seaside garden, prepare baked salmon and mushroom risotto, and remember how her mother's wartime struggles influence her life to this day.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/e2p2gc5wh4ph14wjaggpykpah/original/e2p2gc5wh4ph14wjaggpykpah.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720163000 +0000" stop="20250720170000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Special Guest Carnie Wilson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke goes into the kitchen with Carnie Wilson of the musical group Wilson Phillips to talk about Carnie's famous family and mix up a pot of her grandmother's chicken matzah ball soup.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/i44iuaq5eket10654xladtvsi/original/i44iuaq5eket10654xladtvsi.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720170000 +0000" stop="20250720173000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Special Guests Nicole Ari Parker and Boris Kodjoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke joins married couple Nicole Ari Parker and Boris Kodjoe ("Soul Food") at their favorite restaurant to learn to make Brazilian chicken pot pie and chat about the role food plays in keeping their family happy and healthy.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/3shpado2ozil150b2sd45keou/original/3shpado2ozil150b2sd45keou.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720173000 +0000" stop="20250720180000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Special Guests Ali Landry and Alejandro Gomez Monteverde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke drops in on her good friend Ali Landry (TV's "Eve"), where they reminisce about how cooking played a part in finding love, and they prepare some traditional Mexican fare with Ali's husband, director Alejandro Gomez Monteverde.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/qunmh8q2fi9r13seoamnalgcj/original/qunmh8q2fi9r13seoamnalgcj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720180000 +0000" stop="20250720183000 +0000">
    <title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bread with Brooke Burke - Holiday Special With Roma Downey and Mark Burnett</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Brooke and her husband David Charvet invite their close friends Roma Downey ("Touched by an Angel") and Mark Burnett (producer of "The Voice") into their home to fix Brooke's country roasted chicken and share some family holiday traditions.</desc>
    <date>20220713</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/bbrcl6dy9qrj1fo2r8snty9ri/original/bbrcl6dy9qrj1fo2r8snty9ri.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720183000 +0000" stop="20250720193000 +0000">
    <title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In 2016, newlyweds Jade and Alice (aged 34 and 26 at the time) decide to turn their backs on successful careers in London to relocate 500 miles north to the stunning Scottish Highlands. They plough the proceeds from selling their flat in Croydon and all their savings into buying and restoring a 200 year old rundown and remote small hotel, in order to start new lives being their own boss as hoteliers and restaurateurs.</desc>
    <date>20200211</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1rjgivo668zloza2yoh8une4z/original/1rjgivo668zloza2yoh8une4z.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720193000 +0000" stop="20250720203000 +0000">
    <title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Fogle travels to the small town of Ulverston in the beautiful Cumbrian countryside beside the Lake District to meet Kat and Gwill and explore their dream of owning and running their own café-restaurant.  Kat left a high-powered legal career in the City of London, trading her flat by the Thames for a 300 year old warehouse in Ulverston which she wants to convert into a café-pizzeria.</desc>
    <date>20200218</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/alo012tassru1kkg087cb87j3/original/alo012tassru1kkg087cb87j3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720203000 +0000" stop="20250720213000 +0000">
    <title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Fogle travels to John O’Groats, the most northerly point of mainland Britain, to meet former nanny Cara.  She’s left her life and career in London and followed her childhood dream of owning her own small farm.</desc>
    <date>20200225</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/c2sqi6ewwrv41kcncjzhi4vug/original/c2sqi6ewwrv41kcncjzhi4vug.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720213000 +0000" stop="20250720223000 +0000">
    <title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Fogle travels to the Malvern Hills area of Worcestershire to meet Hani and Sarah and explore their dream of owning and running their own beer brewery.</desc>
    <date>20200303</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/fluuu5holquw1un66wt7kgj6s/original/fluuu5holquw1un66wt7kgj6s.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250720223000 +0000" stop="20250720233000 +0000">
    <title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Fogle: Starting Up Starting Over - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Fogle spends a year following Paul, Toni and daughter Harriet as they risk everything to buy a rundown pub in a remote village in the beautiful wilds of Scotland, with no experience of working in a pub, in a place they have only ever visited on holiday, and as the hospitality industry faces the greatest challenge in its history, Covid lockdown.</desc>
    <date>20220705</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/asqlia4kib681tcisboxj0ns8/original/asqlia4kib681tcisboxj0ns8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
