<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146">
    <display-name>Runtime</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/2bad1dfc-bfda-46ae-bd0d-36b1e07ccb47/runtime-logo_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704011057 +0000" stop="20250704025813 +0000">
    <title>Truth or Die</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of college friends celebrate the end of term with a party to end all parties. During a drink and drug-fuelled evening an innocent game of ‘Truth or Dare’ has a very sore loser, sparking a terrifying sequence of events and a whole new twist on the game - where the truth can kill you.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/truth_or_die_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704025813 +0000" stop="20250704044257 +0000">
    <title>Clubbed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Set in the violent world of 80’s clubland, when life in Britain was tough, where run-down inner-cities were seething with drugs and crime. Danny, a lonely factory worker, is depressed, his marriage is over and the local dealers are out for blood. After a savage beating Danny decides to fight back. He gets involved with the local doormen, who take him in and teach him how to stand his ground.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/clubbed_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704044257 +0000" stop="20250704060000 +0000">
    <title>Bon Voyage</title>
    <sub-title>Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A married couple decide to take their children on a camping holiday trip to France but they soon find out another couple is stalking them.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/bon_voyage_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_uk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704060000 +0000" stop="20250704065046 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Dates</title>
    <sub-title>Nicole White</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When young mother Nicole White met Jonathan Harris online, he seemed to be just the rugged type of man she found attractive. CCTV footage from their second date at Jeepers Bar showed their evening getting off to a great start, but over the course of the next few hours, Harris’ mood changed. At the end of the evening, the pair drove off in Nicole’s car but she never made it home.</desc>
    <date>20240621</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/deadly_dates_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704065046 +0000" stop="20250704074330 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Dates</title>
    <sub-title>Ashley Pegram</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>28-year-old Ashley Pegram was a mum to three young children. Her world fell apart when her partner, and the father to her youngest son, was killed in a car accident returning home from work. Lonely and depressed, Ashley began to use dating apps to meet guys. On Friday 3rd April 2015, Ashley hastily arranged to meet a guy she’d met online just a few hours earlier.</desc>
    <date>20240621</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/deadly_dates_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704074330 +0000" stop="20250704083423 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Dates</title>
    <sub-title>Sharon Siermans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>29 year old Ballarat mum Sharon Siermans was looking for love when she began chatting online to a man named Jason Godfrey, in January 2013. They arranged their first date but when Sharon met him at Ballarat train station, he looked nothing like he did online. Sharon was so embarrassed to be seen with him in public that she made a catastrophic decision: she invited him to her house.</desc>
    <date>20240621</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/deadly_dates_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704083423 +0000" stop="20250704101336 +0000">
    <title>Exit Speed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ten strangers aboard a bus are forced off the road by a nomadic biker gang. Taking refuge in an abandoned scrap yard, they use improvised weapons, adrenaline and sheer guts to mount a defense against the murderous bikers. As their numbers dwindle, they realize that their survival depends on doing the unthinkable - fighting for their lives!</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/exit_speed_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704101336 +0000" stop="20250704120000 +0000">
    <title>Contract Killers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Double-crossed by those he trusted the most, a newbie government hit man discovers that he's the target for the world's most dangerous assassin and so begins a ruthless game of kill first or be killed.</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/contract_killers_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704120000 +0000" stop="20250704133050 +0000">
    <title>A Gift Horse</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Torn apart by the loss of her mother, young Amanda spends time at a ranch owned by a business tycoon. When his spoiled daughter rejects their new horse, Amanda proves that Misty is a true champion and restores her happiness in the process.</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/gift_horse_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704133050 +0000" stop="20250704153245 +0000">
    <title>The 5th Quarter</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Driven by the tragic and fatal car crash that took the life of his fifteen year old brother Luke, and wearing Luke's number 5 jersey, Jon Abbate helps to lead the Wake Forest Demon Deacons to the most successful season in school history.</desc>
    <date>20100408</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a0ee5ae672880e817c83a7bbf90aabbc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704153245 +0000" stop="20250704171558 +0000">
    <title>Women Talking Dirty</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A lively, outspoken single mother in Edinburgh, Scotland, develops an unlikely friendship with a shy cartoonist.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/women_talking_dirty_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704171558 +0000" stop="20250704190422 +0000">
    <title>Caged No More</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Aggie Prejean is a godmother on a desperate search to find her two goddaughters, Skye and Elle, who have been kidnapped by their sinister father. As the details behind the girls' disappearance unfold, it's discovered he has taken them overseas to be sold into slavery to settle his drug debt. Aggie enlists the help of the girls' uncle, a well-respected local philanthropist, and his son Wil, who is former Special Forces. A global hunt ensues, and the team will stop at nothing to see the girls safely returned home. "Caged No More" is a drama meant to engage and educate audiences on the realities of human trafficking. The film releases January 22, 2016 nationwide. Inspired by real events.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/caged_no_more_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704190422 +0000" stop="20250704210005 +0000">
    <title>Good Posture</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Set in current day Brooklyn, Good Posture is the gentle comedy story of a lazy but charming and beautiful young woman who has got used to using men to make her life easier, but after finally pushing one man too far, is forced to discover that she can live a happier life by taking responsibility for herself and not rely on those around her as easy props.</desc>
    <date>20191004</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c96e56371ba33c2262136981ac45345e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704210005 +0000" stop="20250704221902 +0000">
    <title>Little Bi Peep</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Directionless, Emma is going nowhere. The men and women she has been sleeping with think she's a waitress, an artist, or a teacher. In reality, she works in a porn shop, dressing up as sexy characters. One night, Emma meets Mason, a transgender IT guy who seems to have it all. Soon, Emma finds her web of lies unraveling when she encounters something new: sincere feelings for another person.</desc>
    <date>20240711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/little_bi_peep_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250704221902 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title>Ravers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a contaminated energy drink turns an illegal rave into a nightmare, a germaphobic journalist has to overcome her deepest fears to get her friends out alive. Starring Georgia Hirst (Vikings), and Natasha Henstridge (Species), Olivier "the Dutch Giant" Richters. Featuring original beats by Maceo Plex.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/ravers_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250705000000 +0000" stop="20250705014113 +0000">
    <title>Exit Speed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ten strangers aboard a bus are forced off the road by a nomadic biker gang. Taking refuge in an abandoned scrap yard, they use improvised weapons, adrenaline and sheer guts to mount a defense against the murderous bikers. As their numbers dwindle, they realize that their survival depends on doing the unthinkable - fighting for their lives!</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/exit_speed_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
