<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b">
    <display-name>OnDemandChina</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/ondemandchina_logo_dark.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250725234046 +0000" stop="20250726002737 +0000">
    <title>Qing Luo</title>
    <sub-title>Qing Luo E04</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ye Xiudu and Qingluo share a room together.</desc>
    <date>20190514</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425081/124331379-0.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726002737 +0000" stop="20250726022149 +0000">
    <title>The Demon Suppressors: West Barbarian Beast</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The movie tells the story of the 40th years of Wangzhao Dynasty, the west barbarian beast Lord was born bringing chaos to the world again. The Demon Suppressors of the town bravely wen to the expedition to the West and fight the devil.</desc>
    <date>20210828</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726022149 +0000" stop="20250726042104 +0000">
    <title>Buddha Mountain</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young pub singer leaves her family and the megacity of Chengdu behind to start a new life of freedom with her friends.</desc>
    <date>20110101</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726042104 +0000" stop="20250726062119 +0000">
    <title>Tiger Robbers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Based on a novel 'A Cheerful Gang Turns the Earth' by Isaka Kotaro. It tells the adventure story of four strange youths forming a group of "robbers".</desc>
    <date>20210430</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726062119 +0000" stop="20250726075441 +0000">
    <title>The Brocade Mouse Royal Cat Nine Deep Blood Wolf</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The film tells the story of the "Royal Cat" Zhan Zhao, and "Brocaded Mouse" Bai Yutang, the two work together, and invest the series of strange death events in Bianliang city, and protect people's normal life.</desc>
    <date>20210605</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726075441 +0000" stop="20250726095436 +0000">
    <title>Ever Since We love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ever Since We Love revolves around a medical school student whose ego constantly gets hurt by three disparate women he’s attracted to.</desc>
    <date>20150416</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726095436 +0000" stop="20250726112753 +0000">
    <title>Buddha Palm</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Long Jianbei wanted to raise money to save his sick little sister, and met the mysterious organization Black Feather Gang. They are doing human body experiment ceaselessly, attempting to makes the transformation person that has super ability. For money, dragon sword north accepts super power. As a result, Long Jianbei participated in the experiment and cannot control the power inside his body, he followed an old man to be his teacher, learn to drive the power,and masted the palm of god, got acquainted with a decent fellow, and they set out the adventure...</desc>
    <date>20200509</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726112753 +0000" stop="20250726125303 +0000">
    <title>The Underground War</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In 2248, Fang Yi of dormant C40 team captain and his team member were waken up by artificial intelligence control system "the light of long night", and will execute a top secret mission -- dive into gene medicine research center, destroy all medicine and test data. And the research center has suffered Mr.Dee the Black Feather's invasion, to obtain the authority that extends dormancy, C40 team must accept this life and death mission...</desc>
    <date>20210730</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726125303 +0000" stop="20250726141625 +0000">
    <title>Drunken Master Su Qier</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This martial arts action movie tells the story of Su Can, born in a family of officers and had a love for martial arts since he was a child. When he went to the capital to get the martial arts exam, he was framed with banned drugs. Su Gui was also accused of favoritism and fraud, leading to the destruction of Su Can's family. After that, his master in the beggars' group, Liu Jiang helped him recover from his injury, and taught him Drunken Fists martial arts.</desc>
    <date>20210930</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726141625 +0000" stop="20250726155545 +0000">
    <title>A First Farewell</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Isa is not at school or working on his parents' farmyard, he spends carefree days with his friends - until the outside world starts forcing him to say one goodbye after another.</desc>
    <date>20200719</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726155545 +0000" stop="20250726171913 +0000">
    <title>The Mask of Shura of Fire Cloud</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>18 years ago, the extremely evil forces Black Feather Group fleed into old the territory of Xi Chengyong the old ahriman, and stoled The Shura Mask, releasing fiend by it. Old ahriman decided to destroy the mask and fiend in order to protect the city, but found that the fiend was just a baby, he adopted a baby, because absorbed some power of the mask the baby has the power of the divine power and become a little ahriman. The little ahriman eventually took control of the mask and became the old ahriman's successor, continuing to guard the city.</desc>
    <date>20191231</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726171913 +0000" stop="20250726185948 +0000">
    <title>Longmen Town Inn</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tired of rivalries and feuds in jianghu world, the great master Wolong Jianxian founded town of Dragon Gate deep in the desert. For people who have washed their hands and ready to begin new life, only the Dragon Gate Inn welcomes guests from outside.</desc>
    <date>20210723</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726185948 +0000" stop="20250726202311 +0000">
    <title>The Mermaid</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Marine biology researcher Yang Fan falls into the sea when chasing a mermaid, and he gets rescued by a beautiful mermaid named Xiaoyu. Yang Fan falls in love with the half-fish and half-human lady, but Xiaoyu decides to leave him to find a half-fish half-human boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>20210906</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726202311 +0000" stop="20250726213827 +0000">
    <title>Detective Dee: Tongtian Hierarch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The famous detective Dee Renjie in Tang Dynasty. This time the story starts from a political rumor that Wu Meiniang was going to stage a coup and become the empress. At that time, many ministers were against Wu Meiniang to be the queen. The emperor didn't have a choice but to search her.</desc>
    <date>20210627</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726213827 +0000" stop="20250726230143 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of Mermaid</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The film tells the story of the Ming Dynasty, east factory supervisor Gao Dehai and Yan Lie the leader of The Imperial Guards led the fleet to travel secretly in the East China Sea. They met storm, flood and dragon attack, but fortunately were rescued by mermaid Xi yin. They accidentally hit onto the dreamlike Penglai Fairy Island, and Gao Dehai lost himself in the treasures of the island, while Yan Lie and innocent Xi yin begin to like each other.</desc>
    <date>20200220</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd7b2fdec002c14112b" start="20250726230143 +0000" stop="20250727002959 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of Mermaid 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After Penglai island’s sinking, Xiyin gave her Pearl to Yan Lie in order to save him, while she sank into the sea and disappeared, chimaren clan also disappeared. When the imperia's loved wife Shen Mei covets the pearl of inside the body of the mermaid, Yan Lie went to the Peach Flower island looking for the mermaid with him. Yan Lian accidently met his loved Xiyin who lost her memory. While Shen Mei is brewing a plot, what would the two people do in the danger...</desc>
    <date>20210101</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/staging/62b19030-da9d-4d06-8b08-748212fc4b24/Jason_Hwang_-_Fallback_Poster_2000x3000_ver3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
