<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250725010000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>How to Cook a Barracuda</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>See the complete 3-year restoration of Kimberly Cook's 1970 Barracuda Convertible: the body, paint, engine, and convertible top, culminating in Graveyard Carz' most emotional reveal to date.</desc>
    <date>20150806</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S04_E14_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725010000 +0000" stop="20250725020004 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Commando Cuda vs. Magnum Force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>New shop. New crew. An All-new Graveyard Carz! The ghouls tackle a 1970 Cuda.</desc>
    <date>20151007</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725020004 +0000" stop="20250725030004 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Rallye Red Restored</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark paints a Hemi Charger in his favorite Mopar color, burnt orange. AMD delivers the Phantom Cuda, and the ghouls finish the Dailey's 1970 Cuda 383, a project four years in the making.</desc>
    <date>20151014</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725030004 +0000" stop="20250725040003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Hell Hath No '58 Fury</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls wrap up the 340 Cuda and install panels on the Hemi Charger. Mark trains Allysa on O.E.M. assembly line markings. The legendary red Plymouth Fury "Christine" visits the shop.</desc>
    <date>20151021</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725040003 +0000" stop="20250725050002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>400 Magnum Misfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls have problems with after-market parts for the 400 Magnum V8. Allysa begins working in the shop, and two rare Mopars are disassembled</desc>
    <date>20151028</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725050002 +0000" stop="20250725060000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Return of the '70 Sunroof Challenger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's coffee addiction is spotlighted, and the ghouls work on a 1970 Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20151125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725060000 +0000" stop="20250725070002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>70 'Cuda Grace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Work on a 1970 Cuda 340 is featured.</desc>
    <date>20151202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725070002 +0000" stop="20250725080002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Hemi Orange is the New Corporate Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls work on a 1968 GTX for Bill Goldberg, and Mark repairs a Challenger deck lid. Will paints a 1967 Hemi GTX and challenges Mark to a paint-off.</desc>
    <date>20151209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725080002 +0000" stop="20250725083000 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Detailing an Electric Vehicle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter walks you through step-by-step on how to detail the exterior as well as the interior of an electric vehicle, including vegan leather cleaning and conditioning.</desc>
    <date>20230802</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/DN230107H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725083000 +0000" stop="20250725090000 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Detailing Tips &amp; Techniques</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter walks you through the best tools, chemicals, and accessories for performing a myriad of detailing tasks, including cleaning buffing pads, selecting the best tire shine, as well as quick interior maintenance.</desc>
    <date>20230802</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/DN230108H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725090000 +0000" stop="20250725093005 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Jeep Build-Off Day 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jeep Build-Off continues as the guys get a chance to finish their Jeeps and take them on a Geocaching race for all of the marbles.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725093005 +0000" stop="20250725100006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Jeep Build-Off Day 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jeep Build-Off continues as the guys get a chance to finish their Jeeps and take them on a Geocaching race for all of the marbles.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725100006 +0000" stop="20250725103005 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Commander vs Razor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>What UTV should you buy? Should it be a Can Am Commander or a Razor RZR? Matt and Bruno show you what kind of upgrades you can do to each of them, and then they have some fun on the trails!</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725103005 +0000" stop="20250725110004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Shop Misinformation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Bruno show you what a car dealership is going to look for when your truck hits a 100-thousand miles to determine its trade in value. Matt and Bruno show you what kind of repairs you can do yourself to get the most value on your truck.</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725110004 +0000" stop="20250725113004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Diesel Track Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The gloves are off….so is the exhaust, DPF, and anything else that makes our diesel track truck street legal. Today a King Ranch is getting ready for a date with the drag strip.</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725113004 +0000" stop="20250725120004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Wish List Project</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A final wish list from a customer gets completed on a 1985 C-10 project truck, and we cure a slipping transmission problem on a Dodge.</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725120004 +0000" stop="20250725123004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Wrecked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When your work truck gets wrecked, your ability to work stops. Matt and Bruno take on a project to get a work truck back on the road with some body work and repair.</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725123004 +0000" stop="20250725130007 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Jeep Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Bruno ‘s Jeep project is going to be a beast when they get finished with it. The guys install a supercharger and a long arm suspension to give it some life, and they finish it up with a new exhaust and a mean front bumper that will provide the “bite.” Then, the beast is unleashed!</desc>
    <date>00010112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725130007 +0000" stop="20250725133008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Speed Racer Story and the Real Mach 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey digs into one of the most influential cars and cartoons in our history -- Speed Racer and the Mach 5. This show not only takes you thru the history of the cartoon, but also its cultural impact on multi-generations as well. But that’s not all, Stacey manages to “borrow” the real Mach 5 and put it thru the paces against Racer X and other challengers. If you’ve never crossed the line between fact and fiction, real and imagined, we invite you to do it now with Stacey. Go…Speed Racer…Go!</desc>
    <date>00030610</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0042.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725133008 +0000" stop="20250725140009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cash for Clunkers &amp; Easy Upgrades for Fuel Economy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most controversial things to come along recently was the “Cash for Clunkers” program, but do you really know the whole story? Well after this show of GEARZ you will! But Stacey doesn’t just reveal the problems with the Cash for Clunker program, he also demonstrates real solutions available in the aftermarket to address the fuel mileage problem with simple upgrades that ANYBODY can do. If you are tired of feeling like a victim and are ready to do something about your vehicles performance and fuel economy…this is the show to see!</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0043.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725140009 +0000" stop="20250725143009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Aftermarket vs. OEM Parts – Welding Techniques for Replacing Sheet Metal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey answers some top questions from viewers as he compares OEM parts to their Aftermarket replacements. Which is the best quality? Which is the best deal? After you see this show, you will know the answer to those questions and a lot more. Then Stacey reveals the tips and techniques involved in welding in replacement sheet metal. If you never thought you could do this kind of major surgery yourself, this show will change your mind and encourage you to get out there and try it! So what are you waiting for? Get movin’!</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0044.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725143009 +0000" stop="20250725150007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>’67 Mercury Cougar disassembly – GMP Diecast story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>So you’ve got a new project and you are dying to dig into it huh?..... Well, before you touch it, there are some tips and trick you ought to know before you blow it all apart and end up getting lost in a project you can’t ever finish. Stacey shows you those tips and tricks as he rolls in a Classic ’67 Mercury Cougar and starts methodically taking it apart to prepare it for some wild modifications down the road. If you are considering a project, or are already deep into one, you have got to see this show. Then we take an in depth look at the world of die cast models, as we put the spotlight on GMP and check out their incredible models. So whether you are into toy cars, miniature cars, or the real thing, this episode of GEARZ has something for everybody!</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0045.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725150007 +0000" stop="20250725153006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Herobox ’59 Ford Stepside Pickup - Welding Table</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in a ’59 Ford Stepside Truck that is being built by the Herobox organization to help raise awareness for their goal of sending Heroboxes to all of our men and women serving in the Military. It’s a great cause and a great truck and both need to be seen! The truck has already received a lot of modifications, but Stacey adds his special touch by installing custom wood in the bed, trying out a new roll-on bedliner, and sinking some cool 60’s Corvette taillights into the rear fenders. If you’ve got an old truck and have been wondering how to bring the bed and fenders up a notch… this show will definitely give you some ideas! After that, Stacey shows you just how important having the proper work table is, and the kind of things you can do if you have one. It’s all about the tools… it’s all about the techniques… it’s all about GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0046.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725153006 +0000" stop="20250725160008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Blue Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>If you ask any Gearhead what they dream about doing, being a Blue Angels Jet pilot or an Astronaut will be right at the top of the list. But what is really involved in being a pilot for the Blue Angels? Well today Stacey takes a look at the incredible history of the Blue Angels, and where they are today. Then as only GEARZ can do, Stacey takes you into the cockpit and allows you to experience first hand the incredible experience of flying with the Blue Angels. If sitting on top of thousands of horsepower and flipping inverted at the speed of sound sounds like fun to you… then hold on, because you are in for the ride of your life! If you’ve ever wondered what it was like to be a part of the Blue Angels, and wondered if YOU could ever be a part of the team… this is one show you can’t miss!</desc>
    <date>00060510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0047.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725160008 +0000" stop="20250725163008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Project Heavy Metal &amp; Duramax Diesel Engine Install/Drivetrain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in that old International Cab over Truck, and starts a project called Heavy Metal. The project not only showcases people that work with their hands for a living, but also represents the Navy’s Blue Angels precision flying team. The first order up for business is to get some serious power into the truck and that involves Stacey stuffing a hot-rodded Duramax Diesel engine and Allison transmission into the old beast. If you have ever wondered what it takes to retro-fit a big diesel engine into a project, and if there are parts available to make it happen… this show will not only answer those questions, but also encourage you to do it!</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0048.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725163008 +0000" stop="20250725170006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Return of the Rat Roaster/Paint and Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>IT’S BACK!!! The Rat Roaster ’32 Ford roadster rolls back into the GEARZ shop wearing a new coat of green paint and sporting a custom interior… but how did it get that way? Simple, It went for a visit to the Hot Rod Institute in South Dakota, and Stacey takes you there too, as he shows you what makes this tech school so much different than all the others out there. Then Stacey continues putting the finishing touches on this hot ’32 Ford roadster as it makes its way down the final stretch to completion. The baddest car in the valley in 1969 is about to come to life!</desc>
    <date>00070310</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0049.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725170006 +0000" stop="20250725173006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The V8 Interceptor – Front suspension on a ’67 Mercury Cougar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most popular cars of the Muscle car era… the Mercury Cougar has been one of the most overlooked cars in recent decades. All of that changes as Stacey rolls in a solid ’67 Cougar, dubs it the “V8 Interceptor”… and begins to completely change the front suspension to get rid of the stock shock towers and turn this little old lady’s car into a corner-carving, road-gripping beast. But wait!... you can’t cut out the shock towers can you!?! Yes you can!... and Stacey goes in-depth on not only how to do it, but also the installation of a complete TCI independent front suspension. If you own or want to own a classic Mustang, Cougar, Fairlane, or other 60’s Ford and have always wished you could get rid of those stock shock towers to get more room in the engine compartment, this is the show for you.</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0050.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725173006 +0000" stop="20250725180012 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 interceptor – Boss 429 History - Boss Nine Engine and 6spd Transmission Install</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey takes a look at one of the most incredible engines that Ford ever built, the boss 429. But instead of leaving you WISHING you could have one, he shows you where you can actually GET one…. the legendary Jon Kaase. After that he rolls the V8 Interceptor, Cougar back into the shop and gives you 780 reasons why this car is called the Interceptor. With all that new-found room under the hood. Stacey stuffs in a 520ci, 780 horsepower, Boss Nine engine and a 6speed manual transmission to back it up. If you didn’t think modern performance parts would fit in a classic muscle car, this show proves they can! But there’s more to it than that, it’s the rebirth of Ford’s hemi and finally an answer to all those Ford fans who have wondered what could have been if the Boss engine had continued. The Boss V8 Interceptor is in the house!!!</desc>
    <date>00080710</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0051.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725180012 +0000" stop="20250725183014 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Interceptor Rear Suspension - West Coast Classic Cougar - Michigan Tech</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls the V8 Interceptor/Cougar back into the shop and begins upgrading the rear end and rear suspension to handle all the massive power that has been stuffed under the hood. The parts are flyin’ as in goes a custom 3-link torque arm suspension, a 9” Ford rear end, and a tubular sub-frame to prevent the car from flexing. If you have a classic Mustang or Cougar, you’re gonna want to see this! Then Stacey shows you where to get parts for your Mustang or Cougar project by paying a visit to a special salvage yard that specializes only in…you guessed it…Classic Cougars! If you’ve ever wondered where to get those special parts….now you know. After that we take a trip to Michigan Tech to check out their amazing testing facilities and put some actual products to the test. It’s all here…. and it’s all GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0052.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725183014 +0000" stop="20250725190015 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Jeep Wrangler JK Lift/ Custom Bumpers/ Mickey Thompson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that the Jeep is an amazing vehicle, and people use them for everything from daily drivers to hard-core off-roaders. The question is, can you do both with the same vehicle? Stacey shows you that it’s possible, as he takes a very stock Jeep JK and slaps on a lift, wheels and tires, and other essential parts and begins to create a rig that is just as comfortable on the road as it is on the trail. With today’s economy, it’s all about getting the best bang for the buck and this show will show you how to do that. Then we dig into the unique world of Mickey Thompson, and see not only his influence in the creation of off-road racing, but also how he continues to influence the off-road and racing tire markets today.</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0053.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725190015 +0000" stop="20250725193016 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Rat Roaster Top &amp; Exhaust, Jeep JK Wrangler Upgrades, &amp; V8 Interceptor Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey brings the Rat Roaster two steps closer to completion as he installs a custom exhaust system underneath the car to quiet it down and then lays out the 3” chopped top that is going to cover the top of the car when it’s raining. If you’ve ever wondered how they do convertible tops, this is the show to see. After that, he rolls back the Trail Boss Jeep. Last week was about increasing off-road performance… this week is about street performance, as he continues to transform it into a rig that is Boss on the trail…and on the street! Stacey continues with the V8 Interceptor project, as he throws on wheels and tires, to give it a real mean stance! GRRRR! Stacey also introduces the gauge cluster for the ‘67 Cougar project!</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0054.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725193016 +0000" stop="20250725200018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Rat Roaster final assembly – Cornwell tools history – Exhaust tips/ Bends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most exciting and time consuming parts of any project is the final assembly. This is where you bring it all together into a finished vehicle, and where attention to detail is so important. Today on GEARZ Stacey walks thru some of the things that need to be done on a project before you can actually call it “done”. Fuel system, electrical, driveshaft, these are all things that are easy to overlook and have a way of rearing their head to bite you at the end of a project. But with a little pre-planning and the right products, Stacey shows you how you can easily breeze downhill and to the finish line on a project, instead of crashing and burning so close to the finish line! After that we take a look at the amazing 90 year history of Cornwell tools and why they are considered the best kept secret in the tool world. Only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20110305</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0055.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725200018 +0000" stop="20250725203014 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Of The Air: The Stearman PT-17/ Buffing headlights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>We all know what a Hot Rod is right? Well today on GEARZ, Stacey pushes the boundaries of traditional Hot Rod thinking by showing you a vintage Hot Rod that FLIES! We don’t mean down the road! If you’ve ever wondered what it’s like to build, restore, and fly a vintage biplane, then this is the show to see. It’s exposed engine, open cockpit, wind-in-your-face cruising at its best! Then it’s back to the shop where Stacey deals with the classic problem facing drivers all across the country…..dull hazy head light lenses. With a few simple tools and techniques, He quickly shows you how to make them as good as new, and save some serious cash…… and that’ll have you singing “I can see clearly now, the haze is gone” Only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20110319</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0056.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725203014 +0000" stop="20250725210018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Discovering Bigfoot / Installing Smooth Door Handles / Using a Bead Roller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on GEARZ, Stacey finally puts an end to the controversy on all the Bigfoot sightings, and offers proof that Bigfoot does exist! And he lives in St. Louis! Sound crazy? Not really, because St. Louis is the home of Bob Chandler… the mad genius behind the Bigfoot Monster Truck. On this special episode of GEARZ, Stacey rolls through the unique history of not only Bigfoot, but the whole Monster Truck genre. If you’ve ever wondered how these big, smoking, monstrous beasts came to roam the planet, then this is one history lesson you don’t want to miss! After that, Stacey shows you how to get the best of both worlds by shaving the original door handles on a classic muscle car, and installing some smooth modern handles… WITH A VINTAGE LOOK!! A perfect combination? WE think it is, but before YOU can vote, you have to see the show!!</desc>
    <date>20110326</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0057.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725210018 +0000" stop="20250725213018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The V8 Interceptor: Nips, Tucks and 8 Stack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The V8 Interceptor is back! Stacey answers your questions by walking you through the fitment of that massive Boss 9, 520ci engine in the ‘67 Cougar. Headers, oil pan, master cylinders, are addressed, but the big surprise is what is going on top. It’s an incredible 8-stack injection with the look and feel of a vintage Hilborne system, and the function and drive-ability of a modern electronic fuel injection. You have to see it to believe it, and when you do see it, you won’t believe it! Then Stacey goes through some tips and tricks for your fuel system that will keep you running down the road, and not sitting on the side of it! It’s all GEARZ…and it’s all here!</desc>
    <date>20110402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0058.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725213018 +0000" stop="20250725220018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Setting up the Ultimate Trailer – Towing Tech</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>If there’s one thing that every gearhead needs, it’s a trailer so you can drag more junk home! The problem is, most of us don’t really put much thought into the set up of a trailer, and that can add up to some serious problems when you go to retrieve your prize. Today on GEARZ, Stacey walks you thru how to set up a simple trailer, so you’ll be ready to pull a rusted hulk out of a field, or pull a restoration from coast to coast. Compressed air, Winch, and auxiliary electric power are all things that you CAN take with you if you take the time to plan ahead and select the right equipment so it all works together. If you like to hunt for those forgotten treasures, a trailer is one tool you’ve got to have!</desc>
    <date>20110604</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0059.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725220018 +0000" stop="20250725223018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Ram 1500 Express</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Two of the biggest complaints that people have about the new Car manufacturers today, is that they don’t build the cars and trucks people want, and what they do build is too expensive. Well, never fear because today on GEARZ, Stacey introduces the new Ram 1500 Express that has a 390 horsepower 5.7 Hemi in a short bed, regular cab truck, and an price tag that will have you rubbing your eyes and pinching yourself to see if it is true. Better yet, there is a huge aftermarket out there to help you build a one of a kind vehicle. In 1968, Plymouth stood the muscle car world on its ear with the incredible Road Runner. In 2011,Mopar has done it again with the Ram 1500 Express…and GEARZ has the very first one… BEEP…BEEP!!!</desc>
    <date>20110618</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0060.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725223018 +0000" stop="20250725230014 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Speedway Motors/ Cherry Bomb Camaro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to America, we all know who the founding Fathers are, and what their vision was for this Nation. When it comes to Hot Rodding, a lot of people have no idea who the founders are, and how this all got started. Today on GEARZ, Stacey gives you an up-close and personal look at the legendary, “Speedy” Bill Smith and the incredible world of Speedway Motors. Not only were they there from the beginning in the early ‘50’s, but they are still on the cutting edge and pulse of the Hot Rodding world. How do they do it???? You’ll have to watch and find out! After that, Stacey takes a look at the wild ’68 Camaro that Cherry Bomb has put together, to serve as their new way to disturb the Peace. CRANK IT UP!!!!</desc>
    <date>20110702</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0061.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725230014 +0000" stop="20250725233015 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Miata Banshee Payoff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s back! It’s done!! AND it’s WILD! The Banshee comes full circle as Stacey walks you thru the complete buildup of this incredible V8 powered Miata, and then takes it out for a good flogging! If you’ve ever dreamed of owning a Cobra or Corvette, but you needed something more reliable and affordable, this is one project you have to check out! If you’ve always considered the Mazda Miata a girl’s car…you HAVE to check this out! If you think that it’s impossible to have a reliable car with power windows, Air conditioning, and a real working top, that is ALSO blisteringly FAST…YOU HAVE TO CHECK THIS OUT! The best part is this is a car you can actually build and afford…and that’s what real Hot Rodding is all about!</desc>
    <date>20110716</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0062.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250725233015 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Drag’N’ Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls the Ram 1500 Express back in the shop and starts to transform it into the Drag’N’ Wagon. Pulling on the legacy of the iconic Superbee, the Little Red Wagon wheelstander, and the current popularity of Dragon folklore, Stacey sets out to create a modern street machine from a lowly base pickup that anybody can afford. To get the rig to handle, a state-of-the-art air suspension is installed, along with massive brakes, and cool performance wheels and tires. One thing about this wagon…..it’s going to handle!!!! After that, it’s off to the dyno to see what kind of difference a spark plug can make in the performance of your engine.</desc>
    <date>20110806</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0063.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250726000000 +0000" stop="20250726002959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old Trucks and Other Junk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in an old ’67 Ford pickup that has been hacked on over the years, and shows how to get rid of the old afterthought floor shifter, and convert it to a column shift that will actually shift gears! After that, Stacey digs into one of the newest fuel injection units on the market and shows how easy it is to install, and then demonstrates how to shave the drip rail off of your muscle car. Finally, we answer the question: Is it possible to put chrome plating on aluminum or stainless steel? We take a trip to Advance plating in Nashville to find out. There’s so much stuff going on, you’re gonna need to watch this show twice!</desc>
    <date>20110813</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0064.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
