<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724005831 +0000" stop="20250724012942 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prodigal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank robber hides at the McCain Ranch and takes Lucas and Mark hostage. Problems arise when the gunman's mother shows up, believing he owns the ranch and Mark is her grandson. The truth comes out when more gunmen arrive.</desc>
    <date>19600426</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72425.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724012942 +0000" stop="20250724015929 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Fourflusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharecropper Gabe Fenway enters his horse, Sapphire, in a race. His landlord, Jake Preston, bets Fenway that Mark's horse, Blueboy, will win. Preston wants Fenway's farm and bets $1000 against his whole year of crops. He will stop at nothing to win.</desc>
    <date>19600503</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72426.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724015929 +0000" stop="20250724025649 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Mr. Grimm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>During an arrest, Cheyenne shoots and kills the lawless son of Nathanael Grimm, a wealthy man who controls the town. Cheyenne faces a murder charge, and the townspeople are out of work when Grimm closes his mine in revenge.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724025649 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Beholden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne arrives in Winslow with a letter recommending him for the marshal's job. As he delivers it to the banker the next morning, Elijah McGuire and his men rob the bank, and Cheyenne finds himself caught in the middle.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>On this episode of The Cowboy Way, the road trip concludes as the cowboys learn how to round up cattle Louisiana-style. The guys jump into airboats and dodge gators to move a herd out of a marsh.   Back home, Cody brings the boys to the Montgomery History Museum to do some family research, and discovers Bubba shares the same last name as Booger's mother!  Are Booger and Bubba...related? When Jaclyn signs Matthew up for tee-ball, Booger jumps in to coach - and discovers it's probably easier herding cattle than 4-year olds. Kaley and Bubba get the whole gang together for a much-needed day of family fun at the lake.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's a high-flying episode of The Cowboy Way. Misty surprises Cody with the gift of a thrilling ride on an aerobatic glider - only problem is, Cody is terrified of heights! Back on solid ground, some of the herd escapes into a neighboring trailer park. Can the guys wrangle them in before they do any real damage? Jaclyn starts the search for a new family home, but a rough dirt-road stands between them and their dream house. And it's down to the wire for the cowboys' cattle deal as the guys try to find a buyer before their million-dollar herd runs out of grass.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724063015 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun from Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A killer, John Holliver, and his followers come to North Fork looking for revenge. All of the residents are terrified since they ran him out of town five years earlier. Lucas, now acting marshal, realizes that he must face Holliver and his men alone.</desc>
    <date>19611211</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72475.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724063015 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The High Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Two mountain men, Ambrose and Gorwin, come to the McCain Ranch. Ambrose is captivated by Lucas' rifle but Lucas won't trade it. After Gorwin is killed trying to steal it, the family holds Lucas accountable.</desc>
    <date>19611218</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72476.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724072945 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>The Spirit of Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After his fur trapping expedition is surprised by a Crow war party, legendary mountain man Jim Bridger suddenly finds himself in a desperate struggle to rescue his fellow trappers when one of them goes missing, and another is on the brink of madness.</desc>
    <date>20240215</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/dd94ae4b1a978566a19e44664b618bde.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724072945 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>The Fossil Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When bloodthirsty Canadian trappers try to kill him, mountain man Jim Bridger takes cover in an unexplored valley. There, he runs headlong into a family of escaped slaves who show him the huge footprints and fossilized bones of long-dead monsters.</desc>
    <date>20240307</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b53cf81178284d0ba6fcfff0c3a55f5f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724083015 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Bill Hickok &amp; the First Quick-Draw Duel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Wild Bill Hickok and his buddy, Davis Tutt, see their friendship fall apart over gambling debts and the affections of a beautiful woman. After Tutt swipes Wild Bill's prized timepiece as payback for a disputed debt, things begin to heat up. Then, when Tutt parades through town with the watch in one hand and Hickok's former girlfriend in the other, Wild Bill's blood begins to boil. Tutt refuses to return the watch, and he continues to flaunt the beautiful woman on his arm. The two men meet in the middle of town to settle their differences once and for all in what will become the very first quick-draw duel of the Old West. Both men reach for their pistols at the same time and fire! In an attempt to separate the truth from the fiction, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews George Ward Nichols, the journalist who immortalized the duel and created the legend of Wild Bill Hickok.</desc>
    <date>20210411</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/v4/episode/8320789/screencap/6085e52eebc37.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724083015 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Susan Anderson: Frontier Medicine Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Freshly-graduated from medical school, Dr. Susan Anderson sets up a practice in Cripple Creek, Colorado, a rough-and-tumble mining town. At a time when only ten percent of physicians are female, Dr. Anderson faces her share of doubters and has a difficult time attracting patients in the frontier town. When miners suddenly rush into her office with an injured boy, she defies prevailing wisdom and decides to save his mangled arm instead of amputating the limb. The risks are enormous. If the boy's arm becomes infected, and he dies, she will lose everything. Years later, Dr. Anderson relives the story while treating Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, who comes down with fever while passing through Cripple Creek.</desc>
    <date>20210502</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c0da2fc3fadb4999833/f1b313ea-4ed8-4367-885e-13101a5fc4fcthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>John Mullan: Roadbuilder of the West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Army officer John Mullan heads west to help establish an important wagon route through the Northern Rockies. But, before he can build his road, Mullan must survive the hardships of the frontier and a dangerous encounter with Yakima warriors.</desc>
    <date>20240505</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/66e868c60340f39f5e729e83/cfe684c1-952f-4f9b-bbbb-7f9fdd64f4c6/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Steered Off Course</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The remaining six contestants battle it out for the immunity belt buckle with an oldfashioned horse race. Two-by-two, they race over rough terrain, ravines, and a pond until the three winners go up against each other to win safety from elimination. Two cowboys bond over their rodeo experience and confide in each other about their past. The elimination challenge tests the cowboys' ability to drive cattle out of hazardous and rugged terrain. Using only the map provided, each team has to locate three stray steers and drive them back to a trailer. The blue team comes up with a smart strategy, but one member grabs the wrong steer, sending the rest of the team searching for a steer they'll never find. The green team works together and creates a streamlined plan that they execute with ease. During elimination, one cowboy doesn't fret throwing their teammate under the bus if the result means staying in the game. Trace sends the cowboy, who acts too much on impulse, packing.</desc>
    <date>20210407</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/951462a43cb02a1797e2e8f1b6e6973e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>The Littlest Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ike struggles with his handicap and is bitter after being beaten by men who take advantage of him. But, when he meets Arthur, a terminally ill boy, his outlook begins to change. Despite his circumstances, Arthur has an undeniable lust for life.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724123044 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas receives several mysterious threatening notes. He discovers they are being sent from ex-convict, John Beaumont, who is bent on revenge. Beaumont wants Lucas dead since he is the one responsible for his imprisonment.</desc>
    <date>19600412</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72423.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724123044 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins of the Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy Moon and his young son, Bobby, take shelter at the McCain Ranch. Andy killed a man in a gunfight in self-defense. Now, the man's brothers are after Moon. Complications arise when Bobby discovers the truth about their running from town to town.</desc>
    <date>19600419</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72424.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724133041 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prodigal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank robber hides at the McCain Ranch and takes Lucas and Mark hostage. Problems arise when the gunman's mother shows up, believing he owns the ranch and Mark is her grandson. The truth comes out when more gunmen arrive.</desc>
    <date>19600426</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72425.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724133041 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Fourflusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharecropper Gabe Fenway enters his horse, Sapphire, in a race. His landlord, Jake Preston, bets Fenway that Mark's horse, Blueboy, will win. Preston wants Fenway's farm and bets $1000 against his whole year of crops. He will stop at nothing to win.</desc>
    <date>19600503</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72426.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Mr. Grimm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>During an arrest, Cheyenne shoots and kills the lawless son of Nathanael Grimm, a wealthy man who controls the town. Cheyenne faces a murder charge, and the townspeople are out of work when Grimm closes his mine in revenge.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Beholden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne arrives in Winslow with a letter recommending him for the marshal's job. As he delivers it to the banker the next morning, Elijah McGuire and his men rob the bank, and Cheyenne finds himself caught in the middle.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <sub-title>Done Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba, Cody and Booger close their biggest cattle deal ever on The Cowboy Way! The million-dollar herd is ready to ship, but moving all that cattle into trucks becomes a race against the clock for their much-needed final paycheck. The cowboys help a woman remove cattle from her family's land when she is forced to sell the property after the passing of her parents. Having been through a similar situation, Booger is inspired to fix-up his family's old homestead as a special surprise for his grandma. Cody's book is finally finished, but as Misty plans the book-signing event, a missed shipment could derail the whole party. The Cattlemen's Association invites the guys to their annual ball, with a very special honor in store.</desc>
    <date>20181020</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8d006b576ac85bf3699caee16e52ac98.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's a special Christmas Episode of The Cowboy Way. The holidays are always hectic, but for cowboys it's especially busy because it's also calving season. Time for the birth of new baby calves to join the herd. Bubba, Cody, and Booger must monitor their heifers around the clock and still find time to shop for gifts, decorate for Christmas, and enjoy time with their families. Booger helps Matthew pick out an extra-special gift to top Grandma's Christmas tree. Cody looks to buy Carter the perfect cute new puppy. Kaley enlists the wives to help prepare for the Thompson's annual holiday party. But, when a heifer who's in labor goes missing one night, the cowboys frantically search for her while trying to keep from missing the big event.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724182943 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend in Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man named Carl Avery kidnaps Mark and demands a $5,000 ransom for his safe return. Lucas mortgages his ranch to a longtime friend for the money. When Lucas delivers the ransom, he discovers his friend is part of the disturbing kidnapping plot.</desc>
    <date>19611225</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72477.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724182943 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Skull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are separated on a hunting trip. During his search, Lucas enters Skull Ranch, a headquarters for outlaws. The gang forces him to help break out two members from jail. Lucas has no choice after he learns they've captured Mark as well.</desc>
    <date>19620101</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72478.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724192945 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>Fool's Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After discovering a river filled with gold, Jim Bridger and his fellow trappers believe they are near El Dorado, the mythical Spanish city of gold. But their insatiable greed turns friends into enemies and puts Bridger at risk of a gruesome fate.</desc>
    <date>20240125</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b118c43375625ae72d9b1b71466134e3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724192945 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>A Prince on the Prairie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While guiding a hunting expedition, Jim Bridger must deal with an arrogant foreign prince who is abusing his servant boy. But the tables soon turn, when it's the prince who needs rescuing, and his only hope is the long-suffering servant boy.</desc>
    <date>20240201</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8a82711ced8cdd6f3b20a6928ea55402.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724203015 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Elfego Baca &amp; the Frisco Shootout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Just days on the job and brandishing a homemade badge, nineteen-year-old Deputy Elfego Baca's courage is immediately put to the test. After arresting a drunken cowboy for shooting up a saloon, Baca faces down the cowboy's friends, who are hired guns for a wealthy rancher. He wins the first skirmish, but the cowboys return with reinforcements and the stage is set for the biggest and longest gunfight in Old West history. Baca seeks shelter in a small adobe house and makes his stand against a small army of men who shoot up the house with thousands of rounds of ammunition over the course of 33 hours. Years later, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman Bat Masterson gets the real story of what comes to be known as the Frisco Shootout from the former sheriff who deputized Baca just prior to the legendary gun battle.</desc>
    <date>20210523</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmEyZTU5ODktMWJlNC00YzA1LWJlNTItMjgxODFlMTY5NDgyXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724203015 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunt for Outlaw Bill Doolin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When notorious outlaw Bill Doolin escapes from jail, the U.S. Marshals Service springs into action to end his four-year crime spree. Known as the Three Guardsmen, Deputy U.S. Marshals Heck Thomas, Bill Tilghman, and Chris Madsen have a reputation for always getting their man, but they know it won't be easy with Doolin. Doolin is no ordinary outlaw: as a former member of The Dalton Gang and the mastermind of The Wild Bunch, he has successfully robbed banks, trains, and stagecoaches. After months of tracking Doolin, Heck Thomas is so close he barely stops to eat or sleep. When Thomas and his posse finally corner Doolin, he refuses to surrender, and gunfire is the only way out. Some years later, Bat Masterson, former-gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, catches up with Bill Tilghman to hear the real story behind the hunt for the outlaw Bill Doolin.</desc>
    <date>20210613</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGM2N2U2ZDUtMGZmNy00MmY5LThmZDQtYjllODZkMzZlYmFhXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>Daniel Boone: Hero of Kentucky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After frontiersman Daniel Boone forges paths across the Appalachian Mountains and into the newly discovered lands of Kentucky, he founds the settlement of Boonesborough, which quickly becomes one of the most important outposts on colonial America's frontier. But this westward expansion comes at a price. Despite agreements made with the powerful Cherokee nation, conflict between the settlers and natives soon rages like wildfire. For Boone, the strife becomes intensely personal when his daughter and two other young women are abducted by Hanging Maw, a fearsome Cherokee chief. In a desperate chase, Boone pursues Hanging Maw's warriors and their captives through untamed wilderness, with his daughter's life hanging in the balance.</desc>
    <date>20220331</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bf5ddb4374d99146ad436f3c96646877.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>A Bull’s Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>It's now down to the top five cowboys. In the last immunity challenge of the season, Trace tests the competitors' cattle IQ with a trivia challenge - the cowboy way. For every true or false question, the cowboys must rope a steer wearing a sign with the correct answer to earn a point, and the cowboy with the most points wins. One cowboy's strategy to hang back and let the other contestants take themselves out backfires. In the elimination challenge, Trace gets rid of the teams! It may be every cowboy for themself, but they still have to work together to separate two bulls from a herd of cattle. The cowboys debate over how to get the job done, but they eventually reach an agreement. When their plan quickly goes south and puts them all in danger, two cowboys lock horns, and the arena heats up during elimination. The judges make a major revelation about the challenge, and the cowboy with a bossy attitude gets the boot.</desc>
    <date>20210414</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4534057fdb2fd0bc090414ed688793dc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250724235748 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kid captures a murder suspect and brings him back to town. However, suspicions arise when the man hangs himself while in the custody of a corrupt marshal. The riders and family of the dead man are determined to find out the truth.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250724235748 +0000" stop="20250725002909 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Bessie Steel Weaver welcomes her husband, Farley, home after his release from prison. Lucas hires him as a hand believing he has changed his ways. However, when a murder occurs during a local robbery, suspicions are aroused.</desc>
    <date>19600510</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72427.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250725002909 +0000" stop="20250725005829 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Meeting at Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas' old Army buddy, Tom Benton, comes to North Fork raising a ruckus. Micah arrests him and Lucas bails him out. Benton, an undercover federal agent, wants to stay in jail to hopefully infiltrate a gang of bank robbers.</desc>
    <date>19600517</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72428.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250725005829 +0000" stop="20250725012927 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Nora</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>An old flame of Lucas' comes to North Fork. After Lucas learns she is sick and her deceased husband spent all her money, he goes to help. However, all is not as it seems as she didn't come alone, and Lucas' good deed involves him in a murder.</desc>
    <date>19600524</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72429.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
