<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250704235300 +0000" stop="20250705004150 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>01 Tilll I Met You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassandra forms an unlikely friendship with Val and Agnes when they find out they’re being cheated on by the same man. Then, Cassandra is deceived again by a man who leaves her pregnant with Iris. Iris grows up helping her mother until Cassandra meets and marries Oliver, whom she explains to Iris as the man guaranteed by certain signs. Years later, Iris experiences these signs with her best friend, Ali.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705004150 +0000" stop="20250705011717 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After clearing her head in Barrio Santo Francisco, Rhian returns to Command Camp to continue her mission. Tiago then tasks her to investigate if the military has any knowledge about Pascal's return. Meanwhile, Marcial convinces Corazon not to push through with her business partnership with Tiago.</desc>
    <date>20190220</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705011717 +0000" stop="20250705014857 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ethan and Rhian head to Aurora for their respective missions. Later, Rhian meets up with Franco to inform him about the military's latest intelligence report on David Pascal's return. Much to his dismay, Marcial learns that Corazon pushed through with her business partnership with Tiago.</desc>
    <date>20190221</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s2_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705014857 +0000" stop="20250705022504 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep her dark secrets from being exposed, Daniela resolves to get rid of Alvin as soon as possible and goes out of her way to prevent Alvin from getting near her family. Cassie, on the other hand, has something different in mind and insists on inviting the janitor to her 16th birthday party. Later, Cassie and Robert try to settle their misunderstanding. Romina, meanwhile, cannot help but suspect that her husband is hiding something from her.</desc>
    <date>20190118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705022504 +0000" stop="20250705030138 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It is Cassie's long-awaited 16th birthday party, but despite everyone's excitement, she continues to spend the day with a long face. Witnessing this, Marga grows even more annoyed over how the other Mondragon keeps takinge verything for granted. Seeing that his efforts to cheer up his daughter is not effective, Robert decides to focus on securing the safety of the party's venue. However, no matter how much he tries to be cautious, danger continues to lurk around the corner.</desc>
    <date>20190121</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705030138 +0000" stop="20250705033010 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Following Roman’s advice, Gabriel asks Rigor about his mother, but Rigor gives a fabricated story. Gabriel shares it with Roman and receives a kind offer in return. Meanwhile, Carlos informs Victoria of Roman’s sudden interest in Gabriel’s mother. Elsewhere, Steph invites Jay-Jay over.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705033010 +0000" stop="20250705035750 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>24 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabriel asks Rigor about his mother, but doubts his father’s honesty. Later, Carlos invites him for a drink. Isabel is hopeful about rekindling her friendship with Carlos, but faces constant disagreement with her mother. Meanwhile, Roman discovers that Maila is investigating Rigor as well.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_24_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705035750 +0000" stop="20250705070000 +0000">
    <title>The Last Five Years</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Having been together for almost five years, Joan expects William to pop the question. They love each other. They live together. Marriage is the only thing that's missing. But for William, it's the hardest to give.</desc>
    <date>20220304</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_last_five_years_2x3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705070000 +0000" stop="20250705073408 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gen. Maximillano tasks Ethan to start a close investigation on the De Leons. Meanwhile, Jessie catches Isabelle in contact with Rhian. This causes Isabelle to start a commotion to distract Jessie. Elsewhere, Franco questions Tiago's love for Rhian. Later, Adalina gets a chance to close in on Rhian.</desc>
    <date>20190529</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s4_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705073408 +0000" stop="20250705080742 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Santi learns that Rhian betrayed Tiago. He confirms it from his father who also revealed his sister's real identity. Tiago finds a way to salvage his organization's financial problem with Vera's help. Meanwhile, Jessie starts to feel guilty about going against Marcial. Corazon welcomes Isabelle and Elai to her family's home.</desc>
    <date>20190530</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s4_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705080742 +0000" stop="20250705084238 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Corazon manages to escape from the military supervision on her way to see Rhian. Unknown to Corazon, Jessie and Ethan are on her tail. Convinced that she got away, Rhian immediately confronts Franco regarding Tiago's whereabouts. However, Rhian discovers that Jessie and Ethan caught up to her. Meanwhile, Amelia refuses to let Tiago drag Santi into a world of violence.</desc>
    <date>20190531</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_ctgs3fwd/version/0/vid_sec/539/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705084238 +0000" stop="20250705091851 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Jessie's hatred of Rhian leads to a heartbreaking confrontation. In the aftermath, she and Ethan both try to drown their sorrows. Tired of Franco's constant screw-ups, Tiago continues to doubt the young leader's abilities. Meanwhile, Gloria airs out her concern over Santi's welfare. Elsewhere, Gen. Maximillano remains relentless in his pursuit of Rhian.</desc>
    <date>20190603</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_w2ufuk5x/version/0/vid_sec/564/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705091851 +0000" stop="20250705095316 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian's hunt for evidence against Tiago continues as she follows Franco to Vera's drug den. Meanwhile, Alex carries on with her task to tail Rhian and updates Gen. Maximillano on her whereabouts. He then sends Ethan and his unit to raid the drug den. Despite her argument with Jessie, Corazon's resolve to help Rhian remains strong. Elsewhere, Amelia grows worried of Tiago's influence on Santi.</desc>
    <date>20190604</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_x6qc20da/version/0/vid_sec/528/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705095316 +0000" stop="20250705102711 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>As her drug shipment draws near, Vera rebukes Tiago and his underlings for botching their last operation. Rhian, on the other hand, uncovers a vital piece of information from Vera's drug den. She then decides to reach out to Ethan despite their troubled history. Meanwhile, Isabelle and Corazon gain a trump card against Tiago. Elsewhere, Jessie asks to stay over at Ethan's place to avoid facing Corazon.</desc>
    <date>20190605</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_135uj3rk/version/0/vid_sec/518/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705102711 +0000" stop="20250705110111 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian gets into a heated confrontation with Amelia during the latter's charity event. In the aftermath, Santi becomes conflicted with his feelings for his elder sister. As Tiago further influences Santi's mindset, Gloria decides to intervene. Meanwhile, Isabelle and Corazon file another case against Tiago after Elai's revelation. Elsewhere, Ethan hands in to Gen. Maximillano the information he received from Rhian regarding Vera's drug shipment.</desc>
    <date>20190606</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_brua15jd/version/0/vid_sec/520/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705110111 +0000" stop="20250705113721 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An intense confrontation ensues between Corazon and Isabelle, and Amelia as the former two file a kidnapping case against Tiago. Upon sensing that Ivan is losing focus, Franco scolds him and pushes him to do better on their mission. Tiago breaks a tragic news to Santi and implies that Rhian is the reason behind the gruesome crime. Rhian resolves to move forward and targets one of Tiago's partners to avenge the death of a loved one.</desc>
    <date>20190607</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_jgo8e063/version/0/vid_sec/563/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705113721 +0000" stop="20250705121132 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg grows more and more impatient as the search for Rhian and Tiago drags on. While the pressure from his superiors increases, his obsession to surpass Marcial and prove his skills also intensifies. Meanwhile, Jessie goes on a surveillance mission at the port. Tiago's business partners, on the other hand, begin to fret about the drug shipments. Elsewhere, Rhian decides to contact Corazon.</desc>
    <date>20190610</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_57zhx0xk/version/0/vid_sec/524/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705121132 +0000" stop="20250705124418 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiago's drug shipments finally reach the country's shores. Wanting to prevent the contraband from proliferating, Ethan and his unit keep a close watch on the ports. Unknown to them, Tiago manages to sneak the goods right under their noses. Rhian, on the other hand, quietly monitors Tiago's activities. Meanwhile, Corazon tries her best to reveal Amelia's true nature to the public.</desc>
    <date>20190611</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_ao5vxkmt/version/0/vid_sec/495/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705124418 +0000" stop="20250705132008 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Aryann and Tristan help to clear Waldo's name after Gomez drags his name into a scandal. Jenna forms another devious plot as she digs deeper into Waldo and Aryann's past.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705132008 +0000" stop="20250705135513 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A heated confrontation erupts after Tristan learns about Waldo and Aryann's past. With Aryann's life crumbling before her, Jenna is a step closer to taking back her family.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705135513 +0000" stop="20250705142634 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aryann and Waldo tie up loose ends as they decide to let go of their failed love. However, fate finds a way to bring them together again when Aryann's former client goes berserk.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705142634 +0000" stop="20250705145848 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on keeping Aryann for himself, Tristan resorts to desperate measures to marry her. Armand, under Jenna's orders, works on eliminating Aryann and Waldo's family.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705145848 +0000" stop="20250705153156 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While Aryann remains unconscious at the hospital, Waldo decides to cut their ties for good. Tristan finds himself in hot water as he gets blamed for the attempt on Waldo's life.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705153156 +0000" stop="20250705160320 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Aryann is thrown into a vortex of emotions when she learns that she is pregnant with Tristan's child. Unaware of Jenna's plans, Tristan resolves to rebuild his relationship with Aryann.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705160320 +0000" stop="20250705163832 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>As Waldo struggles to find a new job, he meets a lady who he butts heads with. Aryann and Tristan move in together upon learning of their son's condition, while Jenna seeks revenge.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705163832 +0000" stop="20250705171257 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Waldo's hard work pays off when he receives a job offer. Tristan, Aryann, and Rosing fly to the U.S. where their worst fears about the unborn child is confirmed.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705171257 +0000" stop="20250705190000 +0000">
    <title>Sa Haba ng Gabi</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a zombie outbreak happens, two housemaids and a driver will need to survive their longest night ever as they get trapped inside the mansion.</desc>
    <date>20211029</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/sahabanggabi2x3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705190000 +0000" stop="20250705193436 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Mondragons decide to push through with their plan to move abroad. Later, Romina and Robert learn that the authorities will soon release the result of Alvin’s DNA test. Little do they know, Daniela and Hector are pulling some strings to shift the odds in their favor. Roxy, on the other hand, tries to convince Cassie to help Alvin regain his freedom.</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705193436 +0000" stop="20250705201041 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert decides to bring his family on a vacation to take a break from the stressful case of Romina. Robert then cherishes the moment of seeing his whole family complete and happy. However, he makes a shocking discovery about Daniela. Meanwhile, Cassie and Marga agree to be civil with each other. Later, Tope makes a revelation that catches Marga off-guard.</desc>
    <date>20190219</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705201041 +0000" stop="20250705204619 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After confessing her involvement in Romina's assault, Daniela begs Robert not to turn her in to the police. Despite his outrage, Robert chooses to protect his daughter. To make matters worse, Romina discovers Daniela's sworn statement to police and confronts her. Meanwhile, Hector finds out about the Mondragons' plan to move abroad and makes a desperate move.</desc>
    <date>20190220</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705204619 +0000" stop="20250705211854 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Romina becomes indignant upon learning that her rape case is dismissed. She later discovers that Robert kept mum about Daniela and Hector's connection. Filled with rage and disappointment, Romina leaves the Mondragon mansion. After Alvin’s release from jail, Hector carries out a plan to get rid of Robert immediately. Soon, a shocking news about Robert reaches Romina.</desc>
    <date>20190221</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705211854 +0000" stop="20250705215420 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Carlos tries to talk to Romina about her accusation against Daniela and gets into a heated confrontation with his wife after seeing Romina’s proof that she is involved with Hector. Meanwhile, Robert is convinced that someone is attempting to take his life. Because of this, Robert confronts Alvin over his suspicion that the latter has something to do with the car accident.</desc>
    <date>20190222</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705215420 +0000" stop="20250705222831 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert resolves to admit the truth once and for all which does not sit well with Daniela, who worries that her father will reveal her crimes against Romina. Robert informs his wife of his decision and asks her to meet him at the police station. Unknown to them, Hector is pulling some strings to thwart the Mondragon patriarch’s plans.</desc>
    <date>20190225</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705222831 +0000" stop="20250705230138 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert’s loved ones are frantic with worry as they wait for updates from the search and rescue operation. An emotional Marga finds herself in another clash with Cassie, who is trying her best to keep calm amid the horrendous tragedy. Meanwhile, Romina refuses to accept the possibility of Robert's death. Soon after, Romina passes out upon learning that foul play was involved in the incident.</desc>
    <date>20190226</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705230138 +0000" stop="20250705233221 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's disappearance takes its toll on Romina. After a fruitless search and rescue operation, Romina's fear worsens as the authorities presume her husband dead. Seeing how depressed her mother is over Robert's disappearance, Cassie tries to stay strong for Romina. Meanwhile, Daniela sets aside her differences with Romina for Robert's funeral.</desc>
    <date>20190227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250705233221 +0000" stop="20250706000525 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniela confronts Alvin about his involvement in Robert's death and is caught off guard when Alvin presents a piece of evidence on Romina's real rapist. Meanwhile, Romina tries her best to move on without Robert, but is determined to seek justice for her husband's untimely passing. In her quest to find out the truth, Romina makes a shocking discovery about Robert's last moments.</desc>
    <date>20190228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706000525 +0000" stop="20250706004517 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After her emotional testimony and revelation, Sonya is left with no choice but to await the judge's verdict. On the day of Sonya's sentencing, Judge Tortuga gives both sides a chance to present a final argument. Atty. Vega and Atty. Balmaceda close their respective cases by appealing to the sympathies of the court. Meanwhile, Anna uncovers a vital piece of evidence against Jacob. After sharing her discovery with Paco, Anna immediately takes action against her treacherous stepfather.</desc>
    <date>20180222</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s3_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
