<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726000503 +0000" stop="20250726005144 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Weighs 6yo Daily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A mom is under fire for weighing her 6-year-old daughter every single day after she’s bullied for her weight! Is this mom doing the right thing the wrong way? Plus, the controversy over using marijuana for pain relief in the NFL continues! Do you think the drug should be allowed for players? Then, kids are so stressed out doing their homework they now need therapists? We discuss the new alarming trend! And, using oregano oil to stop a cold in its tracks – is it a buzz or a bust?</desc>
    <date>20181102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726005144 +0000" stop="20250726013805 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eye Whitener Scars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A company is accused of pushing opioids on patients for profit! One patient shares her story, and a whistleblower speaks out! A popular TV actress gets a procedure to reverse her scarred eyes, but does it work? Then, our kid taste testers taste favorite foods made healthy! Why some doctors are treating patients with hydrogen peroxide injections! Then, a man has the world’s largest bladder stone removed! And, a secret beauty tip from Molly Sims.</desc>
    <date>20171010</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726013805 +0000" stop="20250726022452 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Post Surgery Skin Removal &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Massive skin removal reveal post weight loss! Break up battle plan with Dr. Ish. Does beer make men more fertile? “Morgue Mom” Mysteries! The ABC’s of cancer and what you need to know today! Viral superstar “Sancho” the therapy dog! Fridge hacks you must have!</desc>
    <date>20180927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726022452 +0000" stop="20250726031022 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>DIY Baby Delivery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom’s at-home delivery story you won’t believe! Could fruit flies be the key to figuring out the male sex drive? Treating face shingles. Newly engaged couple in need of serious weight loss help. The shocking new dating trend! DIY shoe polish hack you need to know! The new “String Test” to determine if you’re obese!</desc>
    <date>20180928</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726031022 +0000" stop="20250726035702 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Stool Squad Answers Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Stool Squad is back to answer your most embarrassing poop-related questions! Disturbing Kim Kardashian look-a-like plastic surgery! Shocking celebrity beauty trend! Toddler hospitalized after using a toy makeup kit!</desc>
    <date>20181009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11004.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726035702 +0000" stop="20250726044358 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fix It or Live With It?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E78</episode-num>
    <desc>Embarrassing conditions, annoying problem areas, unsightly body parts … everyone has at least one or two. But you don’t have to be stuck with them! Get solutions for painful heartburn, frequent urination, stuttering and more.</desc>
    <date>20110113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726044358 +0000" stop="20250726052959 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Let It Happen to You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E108</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors are joined by home improvement guru and safety expert, Eric Stromer, to share important tips about home, flood and fire safety. Learn what to do if you find yourself in a dangerous situation. And, kitchen safety rules to live by.</desc>
    <date>20100224</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02108.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726052959 +0000" stop="20250726061636 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Insta-Famous "Peach Booty"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E109</episode-num>
    <desc>Insta-famous fitness star Abby Pollock is known for her “peach booty” that’s so perfect some say it’s fake! A live glute ultrasound reveals the truth, while Abby shares a shocking admission about her past. When a bad habit becomes debilitating, a woman turns to The Doctors for help! Special correspondent Rosie Mercado joins The Doctors and is shocked to hear that people are putting apple cider vinegar… down where? Is there any truth to the internet rumor urging women to try DIY “tightening”? Could a contraceptive gel for men change birth control forever? Should you stay friends with your ex? Hear what The Doctors has to say! Then, Dr. Travis tears up as he talks about his beloved dog, Nala, and her health struggles. A 97-year-old record-breaking sprinter … how does he do it? And, the easiest way to peel garlic, ever!</desc>
    <date>20170315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726061636 +0000" stop="20250726070229 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Gross Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn why IBS can wreak havoc on your stomach and your sex life! Gunk in your eyes? Find out how to get rid of it. Plus, how to heal hemorrhoids. And, surprising ways to increase your man’s sperm count.</desc>
    <date>20121113</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d5527404ae5a786aa4d62b74df5c2239.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726070229 +0000" stop="20250726074905 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>"Teen Mom" Mental Misdiagnosis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E49</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, a Teen Mom star who thinks she was misdiagnosed with a mental health disorder comes to the show for a second opinion! Plus, the shocking story of a baby born with two noses! Then, Dr. Pimple Popper returns to discuss two gross viral videos: the “grandmother of all blackheads” and a popped blister you have to see to believe! And can you be too fat for fitness? A fitness teacher called out for her weight is here to set the record straight!</desc>
    <date>20151125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D08049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726074905 +0000" stop="20250726083506 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Addicted to Exercise Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A previous guest who was addicted to exercise and referred to as the “sickest person ever on The show” returns with an unexpected update. Then, can cold medicine be used as a murder defense? The Doctors discusses the much buzzed about court case. Plus, our Stool Squad spins The “Wheel of Poop” and answers all your questions about… “Number Two”! And, The Doctors tackles the new research that points to the root cause of ADHD being sleep issues?</desc>
    <date>20171018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726083506 +0000" stop="20250726092040 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pimple Popper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Pimple Popper returns with her latest, greatest and grossest pops! Empire’s Ta’Rhonda Jones wants to gain a better smile without losing character…can it happen? Plus, a fertility doctor is accused of secretly impregnating patients with his own sperm? And, cocktails with health benefits – win!</desc>
    <date>20161005</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726092040 +0000" stop="20250726100729 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Get It Out of Your Body Now</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E126</episode-num>
    <desc>While you pay close attention to what goes into your body, are you aware of what needs to come out? From stomach parasites to blackheads and mercury poisoning, The Doctors explains our body’s most unwelcome occupants.</desc>
    <date>20110330</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03126.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726100729 +0000" stop="20250726105258 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Pregnant Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Three years ago, Thomas Beatie made headlines as the first legal man in history to give birth. After years under the radar, The Doctors uncover everything you didn’t know about the controversial pregnancy and delivery.</desc>
    <date>20111031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726105258 +0000" stop="20250726113954 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Scare Experiment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E80</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors takes drastic measures to save the lives of three people before it’s too late. Will they change their destructive ways? And, easy steps to avoid becoming a health statistic!</desc>
    <date>20110117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726113954 +0000" stop="20250726122524 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>TV Star's Cancer Battle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a THE DOCTORS exclusive, Growing Pains star Joanna Kerns talks for the first time about her secret breast cancer battle and the double mastectomy surgery she had one week before co-star Alan Thicke’s death! Then, our cameras go “inside the OR”’ as a young woman undergoes cervical artificial disc replacement surgery after years of chronic shoulder and neck pain! Plus, Bar Rescue star Jon Taffer returns to give us some of his grossest dirty bar and restaurant secrets! And, are you hitting a roadblock with your diet? A THE DOCTORS prescription that could help knock off those unwanted pounds.</desc>
    <date>20171005</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726122524 +0000" stop="20250726131054 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Race to Erase 10 Years Makeover!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors “Race to Erase 10 Years” on a lucky audience member! Just wait until you see The jaw-dropping results! Candle explosion: could it happen to you? People are suing The major cereal companies over “nutritious” and “wholesome” claims! Guest loses 170 pounds but it isn’t enough! Find out what still is weighing her down. The Doctors discusses a new study that claims going vegan leads to depression! Product claims to whiten teeth 6 shades lighter in just 3 days? Does it work or is it 50 shades of disappointment? We’re putting it to The test! Plus, The water bottle danger you haven’t heard!</desc>
    <date>20171012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726131054 +0000" stop="20250726135752 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Live In The OR</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors go Live in the OR to witness a knee replacement surgery! Woman finds out if she’s been catfished! Viral TikTok star talks about her life living with alopecia! Missouri woman fights to keep pet monkeys she claims helps her with PTSD!</desc>
    <date>20191003</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726135752 +0000" stop="20250726143956 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E73</episode-num>
    <desc>A celebrity hairstylist that’s groomed some of the hottest men in Hollywood changes the lives of homeless people with a haircut! The Doctors first wedding for a couple whose story went viral! What’s The Real Deal with a wearable device that relieves headaches? Does it work? Infant sleeping dangers every parent must hear! Simple trick for a perfect burger!</desc>
    <date>20181127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11073.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726143956 +0000" stop="20250726152645 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eat, Sleep, Poop at Every Age</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Eat, sleep, poop; we all do it! The Doctors answers your questions about the three most common bodily functions! Get clear on food allergy rumors, discover the risks of snoring and learn how to combat the dangers of constipation.</desc>
    <date>20110125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726152645 +0000" stop="20250726161337 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. G Medical Examiner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E78</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. G: Medical Examiner says that the dead don’t keep secrets. Watch a simulated autopsy, and learn ways to keep premature death and disease from your doorstep. And, a procedure that can shrink you six sizes in less than six hours.</desc>
    <date>20090119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726161337 +0000" stop="20250726170026 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Uncooked Pasta Addiction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman addicted to eating uncooked pasta for 30 years writes in to THE DOCTORS to save her life! Could her obsession with macaroni noodles be cured? Then, a body builder dies … from a protein overdose? And, why the internet has everyone cringing over the callus removal videos? Plus, could the hormones in fast food be to blame for one boy’s “A” cup breast? THE DOCTORS discusses the startling links between hormones and your health. And, caught on tape: a crazy calf cramp that seems to have a mind of its own! Then, see what happens when the “Yum Yuck Crew” kids give their critiques on avocado ice cream … will they like it? And, breast surgeon Dr. Kristi Funk gives you the “Breast Case Scenario” on your most embarrassing nipple issues.</desc>
    <date>20250324</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726170026 +0000" stop="20250726174701 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Best Treatments From Head To Toe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E135</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share treatments from head to toe. Brooke Burke reveals how to regain your pre-pregnancy figure. And, Olympic champion Steve Holcomb shares how eye surgery helped him win gold.</desc>
    <date>20100426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726174701 +0000" stop="20250726183526 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Singer's Spine Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E58</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors Exclusive: Gloria Gaynor’s major spine surgery. Gloria and her surgeon, Dr. Hooman Melamed explains the risky procedure. Tips to protect your family this flu season! Testing new non-surgical procedure to rid you of saggy skin and those dreaded jowls. The man behind some of Hollywood’s biggest superheroes shares his top workout moves anyone can do at home. The surprising germy spots in your kitchen!</desc>
    <date>20191213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726183526 +0000" stop="20250726192124 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>20 Fast Fixes For Loads Of Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E148</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how maple syrup reduces the risk of cancer, the advantages of vinegar and treat five ailments for one dollar. Plus, if you think vodka is only good for making cosmos, think again! Discover the health benefits behind the bar.</desc>
    <date>20110510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03148.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726192124 +0000" stop="20250726200832 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Transplants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E59</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother hears her son’s voice for the very first time. See the cutting edge procedure that restored her hearing after 15 years of silence. Then, should your child take a break from ADHD medicines? Plus, are you overtreating your skin and hair?</desc>
    <date>20121203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726200832 +0000" stop="20250726205535 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>50 Ways to Improve Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you want to better your health, but can’t seem to find the time? The Doctors reveal 50 ways to improve your health, and each takes just five minutes or less! And, learn simple housecleaning tips that don’t cost a dime.</desc>
    <date>20090918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726205535 +0000" stop="20250726214158 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Spray Tanned Toddlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E76</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors discusses the wackiest health headlines! Hilarious photos of toddlers in a fake tan mess and how to safely clean up a bad tan! Which state has the most psychopaths? The best beauty buys all for under $10! The Doctors diagnoses your toilet dilemmas in a segment called, “What The Flush!” Instant treatment to reverse tremors?</desc>
    <date>20190503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726214158 +0000" stop="20250726222831 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E114</episode-num>
    <desc>A domestic violence survivor is nominated by her daughter for the ultimate Hollywood makeover and you won’t believe the transformation! The Dahm triplets put at-home ancestry kits to the test! The results will shock you! One yogi showcases her menstrual stain to the world … is her bold decision gross or empowering? Meet the record-breaking martial artists people are calling the modern-day Bruce Lee! Score Rosie Mercado’s must-have tips for full-figure fashion! If given the choice, would you choose a million dollars or true love? Find out why seniors are having the best sex! Plus, a simple way to move forward from emotional pain … today!</desc>
    <date>20170303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09114.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726222831 +0000" stop="20250726231513 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Health A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Improve your health from A to Z! From anti-aging to zits, The Doctors tackle common health concerns and share the latest medical treatments, simple cures and surprising tips to keep you in tip-top shape.</desc>
    <date>20091113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250726231513 +0000" stop="20250727000155 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Frustrating Body Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Plagued by persistent and frustrating body problems like dandruff, blackheads or excessive sweating? The latest installment of Ask Our Doctors shows you how to get rid of pesky ailments for good!</desc>
    <date>20090128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250727000155 +0000" stop="20250727004840 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask The Docs: Permanent Cures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Backaches, allergies and toothaches are among the most common recurring health problems. Find out how to keep your chronic medical issues from coming back, and learn to keep body odor and bad breath at bay.</desc>
    <date>20091013</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
