<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250725235444 +0000" stop="20250726002323 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ali decides to give Nico a chance and agrees to go on a date with him, opening the door for them to get to know each other better.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s2_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726002323 +0000" stop="20250726005702 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After finding out about Tiago's arrest, Amelia orders her staff to leave and resolves to burn down the mansion to wipe out evidence that can be used against them. She then heads to the hospital and gets into a tense confrontation with Marcial. Meanwhile, Rhian sneaks past tight security to visit her father. Sensing the soldier's presence, Amelia orders Ramon to surround the building.</desc>
    <date>20190403</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s3_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726005702 +0000" stop="20250726013140 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With Franco's help, Rhian manages to escape Marcial's troop and Tiago's henchmen. Upon finding out about Roman's failure, Amelia fumes and lashes out on the man. Armando, on the other hand, begins to speculate Rhian's involvement in Tiago's arrest. Meanwhile, Jessie decides that it is time for Corazon to be informed of the Armed Forces' ongoing investigation on Rhian, and reminds her not to trust anyone.</desc>
    <date>20190404</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s3_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726013140 +0000" stop="20250726020514 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Romina confronts Daniela about her and Robert's last phone conversation. Carlos becomes worried and tries to settle things with Romina. During an interrogation, Daniela recalls the time when Romina had a serious fight with her father. Later, Bernard reads Robert's last will and testament where Daniela protests upon learning how much Romina and Cassie will inherit.</desc>
    <date>20190301</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726020514 +0000" stop="20250726023819 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Due to Daniela's incriminating statements, the investigators zoom in on Romina and invite her to the police station for further questioning. Realizing that she is being framed, Romina changes gears to reclaim her inheritance to properly fight back. Daniela rushes to find ways to clear her name and to take back what she believes is rightfully hers, and discovers a horrifying truth about her father.</desc>
    <date>20190304</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726023819 +0000" stop="20250726031327 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Paco discovers a new lead about the Lamost murder case.  Jean's guests celebrate her birthday party, unaware of a brewing evil plot against the Alipios.</desc>
    <date>20171205</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726031327 +0000" stop="20250726034554 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The mood at Jean's birthday party turns sour when Domeng is accused of a crime he did not commit.  Soon, Paco and Sonya race against time to prove Domeng's innocence.</desc>
    <date>20171206</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726034554 +0000" stop="20250726055531 +0000">
    <title>Born to Love You</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Despite their differences and issues, a part-time tourist guide and a photographer find solace and comfort in each other, amid the struggles they are both facing.</desc>
    <date>20120530</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/borntoloveyou_portrait_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726055531 +0000" stop="20250726062514 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Unimpressed with Carlos's presentation, Roman urges him to find a better way to boost Tiger Shark's sales without harming finances. Gabriel travels to Manila to find his employer, but an unexpected circumstance prevents him from seeing Bianca.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s1_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726062514 +0000" stop="20250726070000 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabriel apologizes to Bianca for missing her but is troubled to learn that Carlos took her home. With the farmers facing foreclosure on the mango farm, Gabriel takes on more odd jobs. An accident then compels him to test his luck in Manila.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s1_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726070000 +0000" stop="20250726073524 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcial and Rhian find themselves in grave danger after realizing that the fishing boat that they are in is about to explode. After witnessing an explosion at sea, the Armed Forces hold a search and rescue operations for the two fugitives. Upon arriving at the scene, Corazon pleads with the authorities to do everything in their power to find her family. As soon as the news reaches him, Tiago refuses to believe that the battle is over. Franco asks for Ivan's help in his plan against Tiago.</desc>
    <date>20190710</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726073524 +0000" stop="20250726081005 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping Tiago's henchmen, Marcial and Rhian try to survive in the wilderness. The general finds a way later on to contact his wife while tending to his wounded daughter. Corazon, on the other hand, struggles to cope with her family's disappearance. Meanwhile, Greg delegates some tasks to his subordinates about the ongoing search and rescue operations on the high-ranking general and the wanted spy. Elsewhere, Tiago meets with his new campaign manager to strategize for his senatorial bid.</desc>
    <date>20190711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726081005 +0000" stop="20250726084418 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After helping Rhian and Marcial, Corazon makes it a point not to let Jessie know about what happened. Gen. Maximillano receives an update on the search and rescue operations for the former military members. Rhian and Marcial strategize on how they can take down Tiago. As they carry out their plan, the father and daughter are forced to seek protection against the authorities from a group of civilians. Tiago strives hard to secure a seat in the Senate.</desc>
    <date>20190712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726084418 +0000" stop="20250726092008 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Convinced that Rhian and Marcial mean no harm, Tomas and his family welcome them to their humble abode. Tomas and Jack then assist the two in gathering the materials needed for their plan against Tiago. Meanwhile, due to her seemingly calm demeanor amidst the disappearance of her daughter and her husband, Corazon raises doubts in Gen. Maximillano's mind. Elsewhere, Tiago gets threatened by a rising opponent.</desc>
    <date>20190715</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726092008 +0000" stop="20250726095402 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian and Marcial infiltrate Tiago's house to plant surveillance devices around the place. Unbeknownst to them, Franco also breaks into the mansion to carry out his plan against their common enemy. Arriving home from his campaign sortie, Tiago senses something amiss. Meanwhile, Isabelle asks Corazon to be wary of her actions so as not to arouse suspicions.</desc>
    <date>20190716</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726095402 +0000" stop="20250726102748 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian urges Franco to work with Marcial despite their mutual distrust. Meanwhile, Tiago pays Corazon a visit at her restaurant on a pretense of checking up on her. Despite her initial reaction, Corazon realizes that this could be an opportunity to play mind games with her husband's nemesis. Amelia confronts her husband later on about the reason behind his bizarre plan. Meanwhile, Armando confronts Ivan about Franco's whereabouts</desc>
    <date>20190717</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726102748 +0000" stop="20250726110052 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Tension arises between Tiago and Cong. Sta. Ana as they throw shade at each other during the filing of their candidacies. The ex-general later explains to Amelia why he is not bothered by his rival's feisty attitude. Trying to earn back Armando's trust, Ivan carries out his plan during his meeting with Franco. Meanwhile, Jessie lashes out at Ethan over his feelings toward Rhian. Elsewhere, Marcial continues to keep a close eye on his enemy.</desc>
    <date>20190718</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726110052 +0000" stop="20250726113052 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>With his election campaign going into full blast, Tiago becomes more confident that he can secure a Senate seat. Unknown to the aspiring senator, Rhian and Marcial are roaming around his sortie to obtain a strong evidence against him. Later, Rhian and Marcial monitor Tiago's moves through the CCTVs they installed in his home. Meanwhile, Jessie fails to notice that she bumped into his father at Tiago's event. Elsewhere, Corazon organizes a mass offered to her missing husband and daughter.</desc>
    <date>20190719</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726113052 +0000" stop="20250726120458 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Despite not being invited, Tiago and Amelia barge in the mass organized by Corazon for her missing husband and daughter. Unknown to them, Franco deems the event an opportune time to carry out his plan against the senatorial candidate. However, Rhian arrives at the last minute to stop him. As panic ensues after Franco's failed attack, Tiago comes up with another scheme to win the public's sympathy. Meanwhile, Jessie finds herself in a predicament that can turn her life around.</desc>
    <date>20190722</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726120458 +0000" stop="20250726123922 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Corazon heaves a sigh of relief when she finds out that her family is safe. After learning about Marcial's plan to steal Tiago's phone, she later takes her chance at the office of her husband's nemesis. Meanwhile, Jessie reveals her secret to Adalina but tries to hide it from Ethan. Elsewhere, Rhian, Franco, and Marcial strategize for their next mission on their enemy's big event.</desc>
    <date>20190723</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726123922 +0000" stop="20250726130904 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Together with Basti, Ali and Iris spend a day in Mykonos. However, their getaway takes an unexpected turn when Ali confesses his feelings for Basti to Iris.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726130904 +0000" stop="20250726133825 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Though still in pain, Iris forgives Ali. Just as Ali finally finds the courage to tell Basti the truth, Basti confesses his feelings for Iris.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726133825 +0000" stop="20250726141011 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Agnes has an eventful time in Greece as Ali reveals the truth about himself to her. Later, she unexpectedly finds Valerie. Meanwhile, Iris decides to start anew, away from Ali.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726141011 +0000" stop="20250726144235 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Iris, Basti, and Ali put aside their differences and work together to make Ali’s event a success. Soon, the three get the chance to talk and resolve their issues.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726144235 +0000" stop="20250726151033 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Iris and Basti go on a trip to Santorini for a project. While there, Basti takes Iris to the place where he spent his childhood and to a spot with the most beautiful sunset view.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726151033 +0000" stop="20250726154027 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Nestor recalls his memories with Cassandra when Basti accuses him of trying to reconnect with his ex-girlfriend in Manila. Meanwhile, Iris begins to appreciate Basti as she sees his softer side.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726154027 +0000" stop="20250726161413 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Valerie is haunted by her past when she learns that Basti's friends are coincidentally named Iris and Ali. Meanwhile, Basti admits he still loves Iris as he defends himself against her malicious accusations.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726161413 +0000" stop="20250726190000 +0000">
    <title>The Mistress</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An architect, used to getting any woman he wants, meets a seamstress who challenges him and refuses his charms. As he falls more in love with her, he uncovers her dark secret.</desc>
    <date>20240620</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/gbl_themistress_portrait.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726190000 +0000" stop="20250726193406 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>28 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassie inadvertently infuriates Marga again after accidentally slitting her dress. Wanting to get even, Marga comes up with a plan to get back at her but gets the shock of her life when her prank goes horribly wrong. Meanwhile, Romina prepares to be reunited with her family as she waits for her release papers. Elsewhere, Kulas and his sons are surprised to find out about Myrna's condition.</desc>
    <date>20190327</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_28_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726193406 +0000" stop="20250726200836 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>29 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hell breaks loose among the Mondragons after Cassie gets into an accident. An enraged Romina confront her step-daughter who, unbeknownst to her, has already prepared counter measures to keep her out of the mansion. Marga, on the other hand, is bothered by the outcome of her prank. Hector fumes upon learning that Daniela endangered their only key to get a hold of Robert’s riches.</desc>
    <date>20190328</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_29_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726200836 +0000" stop="20250726204207 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>30 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Romina and Cassie are warmly welcomed into their new home. When Romina hears of Daniela's continued mistreatment of their workers, she decides to fight back leading to the two Mondragons facing off as Romina passionately defends the company's employees. Meanwhile, Cassie adamantly refuses to be a victim against Marga's continuous abuse. Finally, Alvin urges Roxanne to make a confession.</desc>
    <date>20190329</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_30_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726204207 +0000" stop="20250726211641 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>31 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Another fight ensues between Daniela and Romina as they battle over Camila’s leadership. Determined to stop her stepdaughter from taking over Camila, Romina does everything to gain the board of directors' favors. Meanwhile, Cassie confronts Marga about her accident. However, the young Bartolome vehemently denies Cassie’s accusations. Elsewhere, Carlos receives good news.</desc>
    <date>20190401</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_31_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726211641 +0000" stop="20250726215104 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>32 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to prevent Romina from attending the court hearing, Daniela concocts a vile plan. She then wastes no time in informing Hector about it. Romina, meanwhile, becomes determined to find crucial evidence against Daniela. However, she gets the information she needs straight from the horse’s mouth. Meanwhile, Marga finds herself in a humiliating situation.</desc>
    <date>20190402</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_32_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726215104 +0000" stop="20250726222507 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>33 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniela executes her wicked plan against Romina, but her efforts go down the drain when Romina outsmarts her. Later, the widowed Mondragon makes her statement before unleashing her wrath on Daniela. Meanwhile, Marga and Cassie learn that they will go head-to-head for a chance to claim the lone spot in Maxwell Prime.</desc>
    <date>20190403</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_33_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726222507 +0000" stop="20250726225912 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>34 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Determined to prevent Cassie from leaving the country, Alvin sabotages her final interview for Maxwell Prime. Marga gives her best shot as she is interviewed by the selection committee of Maxwell International School. Meanwhile, Romina seeks the help of an ally in sneaking into Robert’s mansion to search for crucial evidence against Daniela. Elsewhere, Carlos asks a favor from Daniela.</desc>
    <date>20190404</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_34_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726225912 +0000" stop="20250726233245 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>35 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Alvin finds himself in jail once again for assaulting Tope. This prompts Hector to give Cassie an offer in exchange for her help to clear his brother's name. Elsewhere, Daniela is forced to make a difficult decision regarding Esther. Romina, meanwhile, gets her investigation against Daniela rolling upon obtaining crucial evidence and speaks with Alvin to try to talk him into revealing his connivance with Daniela.</desc>
    <date>20190405</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_35_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250726233245 +0000" stop="20250727000520 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Atty. Vega starts off with a plan of her own to stop Jacob from running away from his crimes. The entire camp, however, remains puzzled as to who tipped them of his plan to escape. Eventually, a series of developments points to Jacob as the mastermind behind the information the feisty lawyer received. The entire camp concludes that their enemy is using his wicked ways to their disadvantage.</desc>
    <date>20180328</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s5_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250727000520 +0000" stop="20250727003907 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning where she and Jacob are heading to, Jean tries to contact Sonya to inform her of their destination. Jacob, however, finds a way to cut off his and Jean's communication with everyone. Meanwhile, Anna and Paco get help from Atty. Vega in pursuing Jacob. Anna later breathes a sigh of relief as she and Paco accidentally locate Jean and Jacob. Soon, Paco and Anna are shocked upon discovering something about their mothers.</desc>
    <date>20180402</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s5_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
