<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708010022 +0000" stop="20250708013031 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show | Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E16</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029665_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708013031 +0000" stop="20250708020030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Shrinking Blankey | Things I Can Do</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bops blankey seems to be getting smaller; shes convinced its shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, she is growing. | Baby Bop isnt satisfied with her skills. She wants to play keyboard like Riff and wants to skate like Barney.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029666_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708020030 +0000" stop="20250708023029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose | Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help! | BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029667_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708023029 +0000" stop="20250708030028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Blame Game | Airplanes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. BJ brings his new toy plane to the park. Riff borrows it and takes it apart out of curiosity. When BJ finds out, he isn't mad and shows Riff how to put it back together.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029668_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708030028 +0000" stop="20250708033027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid | The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029669_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708033027 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All Aboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends transform the task of collecting litter pieces scattered across the park into an engaging game. Among them is Kami, the youngest of Barney's companions, who finds it challenging to keep pace with the other kids, leaving her feeling disheartened. Barney steps in and proves to each friend that their uniqueness makes them extraordinary.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029530_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708043007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708043007 +0000" stop="20250708050008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708050008 +0000" stop="20250708053008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708053008 +0000" stop="20250708060005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708060005 +0000" stop="20250708063007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708063007 +0000" stop="20250708070011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708070011 +0000" stop="20250708073008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708073008 +0000" stop="20250708080010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708080010 +0000" stop="20250708083008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708083008 +0000" stop="20250708090007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708090007 +0000" stop="20250708093014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708093014 +0000" stop="20250708095833 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708095833 +0000" stop="20250708102815 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708102815 +0000" stop="20250708105827 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708105827 +0000" stop="20250708113016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Fountain of Fun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd excitedly tells Barney and the kids about the upcoming arrival of a brand-new fountain for the park! While they eagerly await the special delivery, Barney and the children make the most of their time by enjoying the park's delights. They swing on the swings, admire the beautiful flowers, and create wonderful memories together, all while looking forward to the fountain's grand entrance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029550_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708113016 +0000" stop="20250708120015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>On Again, Off Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The children gather for an exciting game of on and off, which turns into a learning adventure for Barney, Baby Bop, and their friends. They explore all the different ways things can be turned on and off, discovering new ideas along the way. Later, Barney and his friends join forces to help Baby Bop find adorable costumes for her beloved teddy bear, making it a delightful day full of play and discovery!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029551_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708120015 +0000" stop="20250708123016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sharing Is Caring!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the park, Mr. Boyd is organizing a special toy drive to help children in need. When Baby Bop feels unsure about donating her toys, Barney and his friends come together to show her the joy of sharing and how it can make a difference, particularly in someone else's life.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029552_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708123016 +0000" stop="20250708130018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Here Kitty, Kitty!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Whitney introduces Angela to the concept of an animal shelter as she shares an adorable picture of kittens. When Miss Jo misplaces her beloved cat, Cody, she decides to place a lost cat sign in the park to notify anyone who passes by. Barney and the children eagerly join the search. Throughout the search, the kids learn all about cats and the responsibilities of pet care.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029553_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708130018 +0000" stop="20250708133016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon a Fairy Tale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gianna and Kami have a delightful dress-up session, followed by a charming tea party with Barney as their special guest. Meanwhile, Mario announces hed like to write his own fairy tale. In their eagerness to help Mario, the children enthusiastically act out some of their most cherished fairy tales, offering him ideas and inspiration.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029554_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708133016 +0000" stop="20250708140020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Hot! It's Cold!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The children discuss the various ways to cool off on a hot day, especially with a nice cold drink of water or some ice cream. Throughout the day, Barney and the children learn about hot and cold, but the fun really begins when Barney turns the playground into a winter/summer wonderland!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029555_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708140020 +0000" stop="20250708143019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Perfectly Purple Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sarah accidentally spills red paint into the blue paint, a mess turns into a perfectly purple day. The kids use this opportunity to explore the creation of different colors by mixing them together. Inspired by this delightful turn of events, Barney and the kids organize a surprise party for Colleen, entirely centered around her most beloved color: purple.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029556_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708143019 +0000" stop="20250708150018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Day and Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Excitedly recounting her recent sleepover, Beth shares the fun moments she had with her friends at night. After the kids wish to see nighttime, so Barney uses this opportunity to transform the park, and explain the differences between day and night!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029557_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708150018 +0000" stop="20250708153018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play Piano With Me!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stumbling upon Mr. Boyd and Bingo repairing a player piano, Barney recognizes a wonderful chance for learning and exploration with the kids. Excitedly, the children engage in playful games, immersing themselves in the delightful sounds of real pianos and even play a few notes themselves. Through this experience, they gain great knowledge about the piano, all with the guidance and encouragement of Barney and their newfound curiosity.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029558_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708153018 +0000" stop="20250708160018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Picture of Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Together, the kids use their creativity to create a drawing depicting Barney and themselves having a blast playing baseball. After playing a game of imaginary baseball, they bring Barney into the fun. After accidentally hurting BJ's feelings by forgetting to add him to the drawing, Barney and the children learn what it takes to be a good friend. BJ realizes he has many friends and enjoys a day playing with Barney and the children.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029559_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708160018 +0000" stop="20250708163017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A-Counting We Will Go!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids explore the wonderful world of counting by playing a variety of fun games, like Barney may I? Barney and the kids help Baby Bop learn how to count to 10 by including her in games, and by taking her on a make-believe shopping trip in the caboose.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029560_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708163017 +0000" stop="20250708170021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Big Little Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps Baby Bop and the children discover big and little things in the world around them. When Nick expresses his concern about being the smallest among the kids, Barney steps in to demonstrate how each person's unique size holds its own usefulness. When the group heads out to the park, they begin a creative retelling of Jack and the Beanstalk. Barney and his friends discover everyone is special, regardless of size.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029561_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708170021 +0000" stop="20250708173020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A World of Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are excited to show Barney all the international flags they are hanging throughout the Caboose, in preparation for the International Fair in the playground later that day. The children learn all about many different countries, including Brazil and Kenya. They learn about the clothing worn by local people, the fascinating animals that live in each land and they also partake in various activities they might join in other countries around the world.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029562_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708173020 +0000" stop="20250708180016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Your Neighbor?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A make-believe neighborhood in the caboose prompts Barney to teach the kids all about different community helpers. The kids explore all the different roles people have in the community that help them live safely and happily, including doctors, police officers, and teachers. The kids realize its great to celebrate the different ways people help others!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029563_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708180016 +0000" stop="20250708183017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Squares, Squares Everywhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick announces to the group that he has a workbook assignment for school to fill out, which involves finding as many squares as he can around the park. Barney decided this is a great opportunity for him and the other kids to join in, and its great fun when Barney and the kids can help a friend!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029564_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708183017 +0000" stop="20250708190018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Go For A Ride!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the children have fun playing with toy cars. They take this opportunity to learn about buses and cars, including all the mechanics inside that make them similar. After learning about different kinds of vehicles they may see on the roads, the kids build a bus to take them to their favorite neighborhood spots.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029565_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708190018 +0000" stop="20250708193015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Up, Down, and Around!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Tony excitedly takes his kite to the park to share with his friends, an unexpected gust of wind sends it soaring into the branches of a tree! Barney and the kids revel in the beauty of nature's gifts and sing heartwarming tunes that celebrate all that trees provide. Together, they work to determine how they will rescue Tony's kite from its leafy perch.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029531_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708193015 +0000" stop="20250708200017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Tea-riffic Manners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather in the park for an exciting tea party they had planned, which begins with each of them showing each other the various ways they've contributed, from cookies to decorations. As the day progresses, the tea party proves to be a fun opportunity to reinforce lessons about good manners!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029532_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708200017 +0000" stop="20250708203018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Puppy Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd wanders around the park searching for his dog Bingo, who playfully hides in different areas of the park. Barney and the kids help find Bingo, and subsequently help Mr. Boyd prepare Bingo for a trip to the veterinarian for a checkup. This eventful day gives the kids an opportunity to learn lessons about how to care for a dog.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029533_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708203018 +0000" stop="20250708210018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bunches of Boxes!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are so excited for a day of play and fun! When a bunch of empty boxes arrived from the Enjoy-Your-Toys Company, their adventure begins. They use their imagination to have the best time ever by transforming the boxes into special toys.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029534_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708210018 +0000" stop="20250708213026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Stop! Go!”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After playing with Stop and Go signs with Angela, Baby Bop leaves to direct some traffic of her own. Barney and his friends think of other ways to stop and go and discuss reading, especially traffic signs!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029535_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708213026 +0000" stop="20250708220021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Red, Yellow and Blue!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps his friends put together a Caboose Color Collection which showcases the primary colorsred, yellow and blue. This activity sparks Barney and the kids' imagination, and along with Baby Bop, they realize just how colorful the world can be!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029536_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708220021 +0000" stop="20250708223022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play for Exercise!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are amazed to find out that playing games and having fun in the park is a great way to exercise. When the rain starts to fall, they use their imagination to come up with clever ways to stay active and have fun indoors.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029537_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708223022 +0000" stop="20250708230022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Come Blow Your Horn!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids are full of excitement as five of Mr. Boyd's brass-playing friends are planning a special show in the park tonight! Angela is determined to learn the trumpet, but she finds it challenging. To help them get ready for the band's practice, Mr. Boyd introduces the children to various types of horns, making it a fun learning experience!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029538_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708230022 +0000" stop="20250708233023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A New Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Meet Colleen, Mr. Boyd's niece! Barney and the kids love having fun together every day but making a brand NEW friend is something extra special! With Barney's help, they all learn how to get to know new friends.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029539_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250708233023 +0000" stop="20250709000022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Numbers! Numbers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony has a box filled with numbers that he made with his dad and is proudly showing them to everyone. Suddenly, a strong gust of wind scatters the numbers all around! Barney and his friends team up to go on an exciting number hunt, helping Tony find and collect his homemade numbers again.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029540_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709000022 +0000" stop="20250709003024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>This Way In! This Way Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Angela is in the park to release her turtle, Terry, after observing him with her classmates in school. Barney, Nick, and Sarah are delighted to see Terry come out of his shell, which leads to a discussion about the meanings of in and out. Baby Bop arrives with her chrysalis, and together with Angela's turtle, Barney and his friends are inspired to do In and Out activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029541_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709003024 +0000" stop="20250709010025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Into Fun!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a rainy spring day, and the children can be found inside painting and creating. The weather becomes an exciting opportunity for the kids to learn all about the season of Spring and discuss all the fun activities they can partake in this season. This includes flying a kite, riding a bike, and enjoying the rainbows in the sky.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029542_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709010025 +0000" stop="20250709013024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play It Safe!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After feeling tired of being told to be careful, BJ learns that saying be careful is a way of showing love and concern. This important lesson prompts Barney to teach his friends essential safety rules. Spending time with Barney is always enjoyable, but it's also crucial to learn how to play it safe to stay protected and happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029543_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
