<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714000027 +0000" stop="20250714003026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose | Arts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. Barney and the little dinosaurs enjoy an Art Festival. BJ and Riff share some musical art and Baby Bop shares a painting of a very special friendBarney!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029652_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714003026 +0000" stop="20250714010034 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movement | Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When some of the children invite Barney to join them for a race, BJ and Baby Bop decide hell need their help. By the end of the day, everyone finds out that there are many fun ways to exercise. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers that as more time that goes by, the more she misses them!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029653_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714010034 +0000" stop="20250714012853 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio | BJ's Snack Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ has a dream after eating too many sweets, where he eats as many sweets as he wants and ends up with a big stomachache. When he wakes up, hes happy to find out it was only a dream. When he asks for a healthy snack, his friends are happy to oblige.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029654_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714012853 +0000" stop="20250714020033 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop Til You Drop | Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029655_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714020033 +0000" stop="20250714023032 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin' Hood | Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029656_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714023032 +0000" stop="20250714030032 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Butterflies | The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is sad because she lost her pet caterpillar, Monty. Barney and the others try to help her find it. Baby Bop is surprised to discover Monty inside a chrysalis. Everyone is excited to find Monty now a beautiful butterfly! Rachel carelessly litters in the park then later has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029657_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714030032 +0000" stop="20250714033032 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China | Welcome, Cousin Riff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ receives a letter from his pen pal in China revealing that his pen pal will be coming to visit. With the help of friends, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives. Barney has a tee-rific surprise for BJ and Baby Bop. Cousin Riff is moving to town!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029658_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714033032 +0000" stop="20250714040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits | Listen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective and a case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is a pet rabbit. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029659_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714040000 +0000" stop="20250714043009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden | Get Happy!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants everyone to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029660_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714043009 +0000" stop="20250714050009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big As Barney | The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029661_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714050009 +0000" stop="20250714053007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Games | No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Riff help Baby Bop learn how to follow the rules and learn that rules make games fun for everyone! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029662_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714053007 +0000" stop="20250714060006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Emperor's Contest | The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E14</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029663_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714060006 +0000" stop="20250714063004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Seeing | Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An ordinary game of hide and seek takes a not-so-ordinary turn when Baby Bop claims that an elephant is hiding in the park! BJ thinks that his sister may be seeing things but Barney takes this opportunity to help the young dinos learn about their sense of sight. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029664_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714063004 +0000" stop="20250714070003 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show | Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E16</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029665_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714070003 +0000" stop="20250714073012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Shrinking Blankey | Things I Can Do</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bops blankey seems to be getting smaller; shes convinced its shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, she is growing. | Baby Bop isnt satisfied with her skills. She wants to play keyboard like Riff and wants to skate like Barney.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029666_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714073012 +0000" stop="20250714080011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose | Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help! | BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029667_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714080011 +0000" stop="20250714083010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Blame Game | Airplanes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. BJ brings his new toy plane to the park. Riff borrows it and takes it apart out of curiosity. When BJ finds out, he isn't mad and shows Riff how to put it back together.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029668_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714083010 +0000" stop="20250714090009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid | The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029669_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714090009 +0000" stop="20250714093012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All Aboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends transform the task of collecting litter pieces scattered across the park into an engaging game. Among them is Kami, the youngest of Barney's companions, who finds it challenging to keep pace with the other kids, leaving her feeling disheartened. Barney steps in and proves to each friend that their uniqueness makes them extraordinary.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029530_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714093012 +0000" stop="20250714100013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Up, Down, and Around!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Tony excitedly takes his kite to the park to share with his friends, an unexpected gust of wind sends it soaring into the branches of a tree! Barney and the kids revel in the beauty of nature's gifts and sing heartwarming tunes that celebrate all that trees provide. Together, they work to determine how they will rescue Tony's kite from its leafy perch.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029531_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714100013 +0000" stop="20250714103016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Tea-riffic Manners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather in the park for an exciting tea party they had planned, which begins with each of them showing each other the various ways they've contributed, from cookies to decorations. As the day progresses, the tea party proves to be a fun opportunity to reinforce lessons about good manners!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029532_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714103016 +0000" stop="20250714110017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Puppy Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd wanders around the park searching for his dog Bingo, who playfully hides in different areas of the park. Barney and the kids help find Bingo, and subsequently help Mr. Boyd prepare Bingo for a trip to the veterinarian for a checkup. This eventful day gives the kids an opportunity to learn lessons about how to care for a dog.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029533_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714110017 +0000" stop="20250714113019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714113019 +0000" stop="20250714115838 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714115838 +0000" stop="20250714122830 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714122830 +0000" stop="20250714125837 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714125837 +0000" stop="20250714132832 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714132832 +0000" stop="20250714140015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714140015 +0000" stop="20250714143017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big as Barney - No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029620_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714143017 +0000" stop="20250714150018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Emperor's Contest - Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029621_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714150018 +0000" stop="20250714153019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who - Sweet Treats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for Halloween tonight! Everyone knows what they're going to be for Halloween. BJ is going to be a pirate, Melanie is going to be a cat, David will be a superhero, and Baby Bop is going to be a ballerina princess. Everyone has decided on a costume all except for Riff. Barney tries to give Riff ideas on a costume like a sailor, a firefighter, or a dancer. Riff surprises everyone in the end by wearing a one-man band costume. Then, it's time for the Halloween party to begin! Barney and his friends have fun Trick-or-Treating in the park at night. But when Ramon loses all his Halloween candies, BJ shares his Halloween candies with him.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029622_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714153019 +0000" stop="20250714160024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show - The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029623_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714160024 +0000" stop="20250714162830 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dream Big - Thats What A Mommy Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching birds fly overhead, Riff begins to daydream of flying. He decides to build his very own rocket ship and fly to Mars. The flight is not exactly a success, but Barney encourages Riff to never give up on his dream. After seeing many moms playing with their kids in the park, Baby Bop is curious as to what makes somebody a mommy. With Barney's help, Baby Bop learns all about what makes mommies so special.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029624_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714162830 +0000" stop="20250714170022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shrinking Blankey - The Awful Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's blankey seems to be getting smaller; she's convinced it's shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, Baby Bop is growing. When Riff takes a bite of ice cream, he realizes has a very sore tooth. Afraid of going to the dentist, Barney and his friends put on a show to help Riff see there is nothing to be afraid of - the dentist is his friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029625_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714170022 +0000" stop="20250714173024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Blame Game - What's Your Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. Meanwhile, Myra, has decided she doesn't like her name. After learning about many names and what they mean, Barney helps Myra see how special her name truly is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029626_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714173024 +0000" stop="20250714180026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose - BJ the Great</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. When they were in a pretend country of India, they saw a real elephant and in the end, Melanie gets a email from her friend in India (who has also seen a real elephant in India!). BJ wants to be a great magician, but he doesn't want to spend any time practicing. He convinces Baby Bop to help him do a trick, and makes her disappear. When BJ thought she is gone forever, he realizes the importance of practice. Luckily, Baby Bop hasn't disappeared after all!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029627_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714180026 +0000" stop="20250714183020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos - A Visit to Santa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn. Melanie misses the mailman, so Barney takes her to Santa's workshop at the North Pole to deliver her wish list in person.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029628_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714183020 +0000" stop="20250714190023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714190023 +0000" stop="20250714192842 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Days of the Week - Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ, Baby Bop and Riff can hardly wait for the petting zoo that is coming to the park. Barney helps them pass the time while teaching them about the days of the week. When the animals finally do arrive, everyone realizes that it was all worth the wait! Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029603_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714192842 +0000" stop="20250714200025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714200025 +0000" stop="20250714203031 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714203031 +0000" stop="20250714210026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714210026 +0000" stop="20250714213033 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714213033 +0000" stop="20250714220030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714220030 +0000" stop="20250714223024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714223024 +0000" stop="20250714230026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714230026 +0000" stop="20250714233028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250714233028 +0000" stop="20250715000030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715000030 +0000" stop="20250715003030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
