<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716230535 +0000" stop="20250717004053 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717004053 +0000" stop="20250717020606 +0000">
    <title>Finders Keepers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jaylin is a struggling single father trying to support his children and make ends meet. One day he comes upon a box of pills and tries to sell them for the cash. Until thugs approach him, and now a simple gamble, becomes life threatening.</desc>
    <date>20231129</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/plex/a62bcd6d-f7d3-49f5-8206-4646804e0e67.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717020606 +0000" stop="20250717040244 +0000">
    <title>Finding Boaz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Church administrator, Torrey, attempts to put the pieces of her life together after a failed engagement. With fears of becoming a lonely cat lady, Torrey solicits the help of her worldly cousin Nell who puts Torrey in a How to Catch a Man School. Class includes, makeovers, shopping sprees, club hopping and tactics of deceit to help Torrey find the man of her dreams. Within the twists and turns of How to Catch a Man School, Torrey catches far more than she bargained for!</desc>
    <date>20230501</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/210eb19d4e7f4f58b50ac59213ab37f0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717040244 +0000" stop="20250717060357 +0000">
    <title>Fair Play</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters, Freedom and Sasha, learn that when it comes to love, everything has a price...that's just FAIR PLAY.</desc>
    <date>20230928</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0114162e3ddcc1812a763a9060b22d44.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717060357 +0000" stop="20250717075745 +0000">
    <title>Ebony Hustle 2: Ballistic Protection</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Local detective and icon Ebony Hustle returns to help the community and solve cases. This time around she meets local up-and-coming basketball star Mac Pendleton and begins to kindle a romance with him. The two seem to be going strong, till one day Mac starts to become unruly and angry. All the while she encounters an old rival and seeks to make amends and start fresh, to much difficulty. Will Ebony be able to save her new relationship, as well as heal old wounds and continue to thrive?</desc>
    <date>20240312</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c71df44ef3fcf6036d8b63696b7736f4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717075745 +0000" stop="20250717094743 +0000">
    <title>Double Standards</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A upstanding perfect couple of their community church 'First Lady Trezjiir Jonez a devoted wife, of Pastor Noble Jonez, that lives a unknown double life, decides to engage in pre-marital counseling sessions in their unstable home, where sexual desires of hidden thirsty passion enter as a fatal demise' will the sin be forgiven or will it be the ultimate judgment day</desc>
    <date>20240314</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/plex/80a30248-adc5-4819-a286-c75e8a379071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717094743 +0000" stop="20250717114134 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Derek “Dirt” Roberts is the top lieutenant for Big Boss, a criminal mastermind who rose through the ranks from a “corner boy” to become the city’s most powerful organized criminal. When the two grow apart, Dirt hatches an elaborate plan to leave the organization. This plan is interrupted when he comes face to face with Clutch, a rogue detective on a mission to find and rescue his partner and clear his name.</desc>
    <date>20241231</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4e2530d5ad43ece51904d1dd48d5c00c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717114134 +0000" stop="20250717135942 +0000">
    <title>Conflict of Interest</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Gabrielle Winters is a successful Deputy Attorney, married to an adoring husband and mother to a beautiful college age daughter (Asia). Yet, underneath this picture perfect life, Gabrielle is haunted by a ghost of her past. Her life unravels when she prosecutes Donte, a man who could possibly be the son she gave up for adoption when she was 17. Matters only get more complicated once Donte sets his eyes on Gabrielle’s daughter. Can Gabrielle maintain this heavy secret and protect her family?</desc>
    <date>20240212</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/46dc53f8011ce8777d92292843683659.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717135942 +0000" stop="20250717152844 +0000">
    <title>Caught in a Trapp</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The story of a young teen who was abused by his father. Following the tragic death of his parents, he grew up on the streets and is forced into a life of running from D Slug, a known drug lord, after selling drugs from his opps!</desc>
    <date>20240402</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8d7b6cfc7c1407e1b48abba4b100abef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717152844 +0000" stop="20250717174123 +0000">
    <title>Busted and Disgusted</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Two sisters, Faith and Promise, overcome their difficult childhood following the death of their mother to cancer. Faith has it all, a successful career and a loving husband, but Promise feels threatened by her older sister’s success, and seeks to claim her happiness for herself.</desc>
    <date>20240407</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6037ee20ae6a1b07e61561770d9547af.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717174123 +0000" stop="20250717193930 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lC6QNvelSJtOzkzzEC6D6jn1Hh3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717193930 +0000" stop="20250717212519 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Score</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After starting their new record label, Donica Blair and Shequell Harris have entered a dangerous arena full of guns, lies, and deceit. Now they are racing against time to right their wrongs and save their own lives before they are next in a string of murders. Meanwhile their partner Seven, has fallen victim to the deadliest of them all; the Black widow.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717212519 +0000" stop="20250717231011 +0000">
    <title>Runway of Shadows</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters Ivy and Zara are separated at a very young age due to their father’s deceit. When Ivy and Zara unexpectedly cross paths at a prestigious runway show, the stage it set for a series of mysterious and unsettling events.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717231011 +0000" stop="20250718004440 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
