<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719001654 +0000" stop="20250719030325 +0000">
    <title>More Than Friends</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Angela, a heterosexual, learns her friend, Tennille, loves her, she is surprised to find that she may feel the same.</desc>
    <date>20220725</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719030325 +0000" stop="20250719042014 +0000">
    <title>Saved By Grace</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After being fired from her job, Grace Hightower applies for a position to work at the local church. Full of insecurity and self-doubt, her faith is tested when the church unexpectedly goes into foreclosure, forcing herself to find the courage to save it.</desc>
    <date>20200120</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vqLNVNQWEy3tUOi3sBjlM0lB3Ap.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719042014 +0000" stop="20250719072215 +0000">
    <title>Don't Ever Get Married</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jay, a cynical womanizer, bets his friend he can make his fiancée cheat before their wedding. Confident in his charm, he sets out to seduce her, unaware of the emotional turmoil he'll cause. As his plan spirals, Jay faces the consequences of his actions and the possibility of redemption.</desc>
    <date>20240815</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d4a16cdef88c759d5f618a98b3f649ee.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719072215 +0000" stop="20250719092821 +0000">
    <title>Through Sickness and Hell</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a police officer is trapped in a toxic marriage, he must find the strength to break free from his abusive wife, risking his career, reputation, but also his life as he battles the damaging stigma surrounding domestic violence against men.</desc>
    <date>20250318</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tM9dNTbDD2d4YxcnHL854INubQW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719092821 +0000" stop="20250719113019 +0000">
    <title>Bruised</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Young and beautiful Kayla Brown discovers that her perfect husband is not who she thought he was. Fearing for her life, she must do the unthinkable to end her nightmarish marriage, SHE MUST KILL HIM.</desc>
    <date>20230321</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b5db04bb821ab55c233b6197bdb59014.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719113019 +0000" stop="20250719131025 +0000">
    <title>Bruised 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Two years after the death of her husband, Kayla Brown has rebuilt her life following the launch of her successful memoir. she is then visited by a stalker, who is hell-bent on making her pay for what she has done in order to escape her husband.</desc>
    <date>20250218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fnKsOexczmIU62rfGnX2chMvc2T.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719131025 +0000" stop="20250719144756 +0000">
    <title>Glistening in the Snow</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When struggling club owner Anaja finds out that her co-owner, Donovan, is coming to town for the holiday, she expects him to help keep the doors open. However, his fiancé Addie wants him to sell the club. When the owners and staff are trapped in the club during a snow storm, they will have to work together to resolve their issues with each other.</desc>
    <date>20241031</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a025b429cb191a0593d693e652e529d6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719144756 +0000" stop="20250719162408 +0000">
    <title>Missing You This Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Carmen’s family has an annual Christmas tradition that supports her neighborhood. When her mother dies suddenly, she looses the holiday spirit, and no longer wants to continue, until she’s visited by her late father’s spirit who encourages her to keep hope alive.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/missing_you_this_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719162408 +0000" stop="20250719175929 +0000">
    <title>A Holiday for Harmony</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jaxon Moore is a struggling arcade bar owner with debt and facing a possible shutdown before the holiday season. When his sister dies unexpectedly in a car crash, he becomes the guardian of his young niece Harmony, who inherited a trust fund from her late mother. Jaxon hopes he can use the trust to save his struggling business, but faces obstacles when Harmony‚Äôs father decides to come back into her life.</desc>
    <date>20240822</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/a_holiday_for_harmony.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719175929 +0000" stop="20250719194823 +0000">
    <title>Rain for Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malik decides to bring his girlfriend home to Houston for Christmas. When she meets his family, they think he is all wrong for her. He meets his grandpa‚Äôs nurse, Rain, and soon realizes the true meaning of love and what he really wants for Christmas.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/rain_for_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719194823 +0000" stop="20250719214038 +0000">
    <title>Naughty or Nice</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Melody, an exotic dancer, and her doctor boyfriend, Patrick, prepare to spend the holidays with Patrick’s family. When they arrive, they are met by Patrick’s overprotective judgmental mother, and she unleashes her wrath on Melody, as she’s not good enough for her son. Will Melody become part of the family? Or succumb to Patrick’s mother’s insecurities.</desc>
    <date>20241101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/1151185c7d0ec1c457cb2415be74c0e2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719214038 +0000" stop="20250719232721 +0000">
    <title>Christmas with da Fam</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malcom proposes to Serenity, she takes him home to meet her family for the holidays. The spirit is alive, until they discover that Serenity’s ex Denzel is living with her family after a house fire. A rivalry develops between Malcolm and Denzel that ends up in a hilarious battle of wits over the holiday weekend.</desc>
    <date>20241105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/Christmas_with_da_fam.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719232721 +0000" stop="20250720013914 +0000">
    <title>Mixed Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aurora wants to enjoy the holidays this year in some warmth and sunshine, and invites her three best friends to Miami for a Christmas trip to remember. When they arrive at their AirBnb, they discover it’s been double booked…by Aurora’s ex-girlfriend and her new partner Axel. They have no choice but to combine their plans, and celebrate the holiday together.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/mixed_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
