<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725001500 +0000" stop="20250725013000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America - The Place Where Time Began</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Jago Cooper explores the ancient civilization of Teotihuacan that exploded into a position of dominance in the ancient Americas almost 2000-years ago.</desc>
    <date>20141006</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oaVLFoYJBg9NXBqQUcvPpjwhZg9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725013000 +0000" stop="20250725024500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - The Stone at the Centre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Deep in the Bolivian Andes at the breathtaking height of 13000ft stands Tiwanaku, the awe inspiring ruins of a monolithic temple city.  Built by a civilisation who dominated a vast swathe of South America, it was abandoned 1000 years ago.  For centuries it has been a mystery: how did a civilisation flourish at such an altitude and why did they vanish?  Archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper journeys through Bolivia's spectacular landscape to investigate the origins of Tiwanaku and finds evidence of an ancient people with amazing understanding of their environment whose religion was based on collective effort and ritual beer drinking.</desc>
    <date>20130114</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cFGhImYsngUFg0R5gJib4Ut1aaG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725024500 +0000" stop="20250725040000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - Kingdom of the Desert, Peru</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In the spectacular deserts of coastal Peru, archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper explores the dramatic rise and fall of Chimor, the first empire of South America.  His journey begins among the ruins of a vast lost city once home to an all-powerful monarchy, whose subjects transformed the desert landscape, created gold and silver treasures, and believed so strongly in the power of their gods that they made the most shocking of sacrifices.  Chimor thrived despite facing some of the most extreme climate conditions in the world – but not even this powerful empire could withstand the forces that eventually destroyed it.</desc>
    <date>20130121</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vWvxRx1CVnazn4FDg4a9mLJ8Ybh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725040000 +0000" stop="20250725051500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - People of the Clouds, Peru</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper embarks on an epic journey into the remote Peruvian Andes in search of the mysterious Chachapoya people.  Once numbering half a million, they were known as 'The People of the Clouds'.  Dr Cooper reveals how they developed sophisticated methods of recording stories, traded in exotic goods found hundreds of miles from their territory, and had funeral traditions that challenge assumptions about ancient human behaviour.  His search for evidence takes him to astonishing cliff tombs untouched for 500 years, and one of the most spectacular fortresses in South America, where the fate of the Chachapoya is revealed.</desc>
    <date>20130128</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g3pvdK7NoLk5r1EtHxOu3FsZJIg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725051500 +0000" stop="20250725063000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America S01 E04 - Lands of Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Through the mountains and jungles of Colombia, archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper goes in search of the truth behind one of the greatest stories ever told: the legend of El Dorado.  His journey takes him from Bogota to the Caribbean coast, through territories once dominated by two cultures, the Muisca and Tairona, who flourished for centuries before the arrival of the Spanish in the 16th century.  Dr Cooper reveals forgotten peoples who valued gold in a way the Western world still struggles to understand, travelling to an astonishing lost city and meeting the last survivors of an ancient civilisation.</desc>
    <date>20130204</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQGtqLSrbWqHjobNjowdehAfcRb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725063000 +0000" stop="20250725070000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E01 - New River Gorge National River</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are exploring one of the oldest rivers in North America and one of the biggest bridges in the country. After that, they hit the crazy whitewater of the New River.</desc>
    <date>20171007</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6339081.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725070000 +0000" stop="20250725073000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E02 - NYC: National Parks Of New York Harbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack visit the parks of New York Harbor to learn about immigration and their own family history. Stops include Ellis Island and kayaking to the Statue of Liberty.</desc>
    <date>20171014</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6353244.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725073000 +0000" stop="20250725080000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E03 - Biscayne National Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton check out the underwater world of Biscayne and help the park fight a dangerous invasive species.</desc>
    <date>20171021</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6353245.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725080000 +0000" stop="20250725083000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E04 - Glacier: Back In Big Sky Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack are back in one of their favorite parks and bringing along their buddy, Joe Stone. Joe introduces them to a new way of biking Going-to-the-Sun Road and then it’s a trip into the backcountry to camp.</desc>
    <date>20171028</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6365385.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725083000 +0000" stop="20250725090000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E05 - Jasper National Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton travel through the heart of the Canadian Rockies while exploring the famous Icefields Parkway. Then they try a new adventure… canyoneering.</desc>
    <date>20171104</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6376210.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725090000 +0000" stop="20250725093000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E06 - Churchill, Canada</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head north to Manitoba, Canada hoping to spot their first ever polar bear in the wild. Then After a night of camping in a historic fort on Hudson Bay, they kayak with beluga whales.</desc>
    <date>20171111</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407235.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725093000 +0000" stop="20250725100000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E07 - Coconino National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton take on a section of the Arizona Trail as they bike-pack their way through ancient lava fields in the Coconino National Forest. They’ll also explore a lava tube cave that’s hundreds of thousands of years old.</desc>
    <date>20171118</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407242.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725100000 +0000" stop="20250725103000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E08 - San Juan National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack are heading deep into the San Juan National Forest in Colorado to climb their first 14,000-foot mountain.</desc>
    <date>20171125</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407243.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725103000 +0000" stop="20250725110000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E09 - Katmai: Return To The Valley Of 10,000 Smokes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton return to Katmai National Park in Alaska to find one of the last remaining known volcanic steam vents in the Valley of 10,000 Smokes.</desc>
    <date>20180120</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6516886.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725110000 +0000" stop="20250725113000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E10 - White Mountain National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack set out to hike the nine peaks of the Presidential Traverse in White Mountain National Forest in New Hampshire. It’s a place known for the worst weather in the world, and this trip proves to be no exception.</desc>
    <date>20180127</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6523656.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725113000 +0000" stop="20250725120000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E11 - Devils Tower National Monument</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are in Wyoming to take on the biggest rock climb challenge of their lives... Devils Tower.</desc>
    <date>20180203</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6524929.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725120000 +0000" stop="20250725123000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E12 - Bears Ears National Monument</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore how Native American Tribes of the past lived in the vast, desolate high desert of Utah thousands of years ago. They’ll route find their way to hidden ancient cliff dwellings deep in the canyons of Bears of Ears.</desc>
    <date>20180210</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6539827.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725123000 +0000" stop="20250725130000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E13 - Santa Fe National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton meet up with up with friend and Forest Ranger Rourke McDermott to learn the skills necessary to survive in the New Mexico desert.</desc>
    <date>20180217</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6551267.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725130000 +0000" stop="20250725133000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E14 - Florida Parks: Hurricane Recovery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head back to Biscayne National Park and the Everglades to see the effects of hurricanes on the parks ecosystems and wildlife. They also lend a hand to help with debris clean-up.</desc>
    <date>20180224</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6567212.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725133000 +0000" stop="20250725140000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E15 - Best Of Caves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Caves come in all shapes, sizes, and locations. Jack and Colton look back on their most epic cave adventures on the water, underground, and under ice.</desc>
    <date>20180303</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6583281.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725140000 +0000" stop="20250725143000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E16 - Cayman Islands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are in the Cayman Islands to swim with stingrays and scuba dive a sunken Russian Frigate called the Captain Keith Tibbets. They also caving on the Island of Cayman Brac.</desc>
    <date>20180310</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6593721.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725143000 +0000" stop="20250725150000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E17 - Jean Lafitte National Historical Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head south to New Orleans, Louisiana to travel in the footsteps of well-known pirate turned patriot Jean Lafitte. Stops include: The French Quarter, Chalmette Battlefield and boating through the bayou of this national historic park.</desc>
    <date>20180317</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6605503.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725150000 +0000" stop="20250725153000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E18 - Best of Rivers and Waterfalls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>From waterfall meditation in Japan to rafting Class V rapids in New River Gorge, Jack and Colton are looking back on waterfalls that challenged them, and rivers that earned their respect.</desc>
    <date>20180407</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6631437.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725153000 +0000" stop="20250725160000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E19 - Best of Conservation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton pitch in to protect the places we all love, and the creatures who live in them.  Included: Endangered sea turtles of Padre Island, the bats of Mammoth Cave, and sorting visitor trash in Yellowstone.</desc>
    <date>20180414</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6652264.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725160000 +0000" stop="20250725163000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E20 - Best of the Rockies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether they’re cycling up, hiking down, or canyoneering into the Rocky Mountains, Jack and Colton prove there are endless ways to explore the national parks, forests, and monuments of the Rockies.</desc>
    <date>20180421</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6652265.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725163000 +0000" stop="20250725170000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E21 - Northern California</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore Northern California. Stops include Point Reyes National Seashore, the Golden Gate Bridge, and Alcatraz Island.</desc>
    <date>20180428</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6662998.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725170000 +0000" stop="20250725173000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E22 - Grand Canyon National Park: Rim to Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>For the 100th episode of Rock the Park, Jack and Colton experience the Grand Canyon in a way less than 1% of visitors do: They’re hiking rim-to-rim.</desc>
    <date>20180505</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6676906.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725173000 +0000" stop="20250725180000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E23 - Denali: Dog Sledding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Sophia Bush joins Jack and Colton as the guys head back to Denali National Park in Alaska. This trip is going to the dogs as the three immerse themselves in all things dog mushing.</desc>
    <date>20180512</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6687286.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725180000 +0000" stop="20250725183000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E24 - Nevada: The Loneliest Road in America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are traveling the “The Loneliest Road in America” and discovering the natural history of Nevada.</desc>
    <date>20180519</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6694160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725183000 +0000" stop="20250725190000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E25 - Santa Catalina Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore this island paradise off California’s coast. They check out the island by bike, search for free-roaming bison that inhabit the island and attempt their first solo shore dive.</desc>
    <date>20180526</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6703098.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725190000 +0000" stop="20250725193000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E26 - Superior National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are back in their home state to experience a true Minnesota winter. Adventures include fat biking, and cross-country skiing to frozen waterfalls.</desc>
    <date>20180602</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6711304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725193000 +0000" stop="20250725210000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E01 - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>If you were tasked to race across the world with limited cash and nothing in the way of modern technology, how do you think you’d fare?  This Spring, BBC2’s Race Across the World returns, as five teams attempt just that.  This series takes viewers on the trip of a lifetime, following our contestants as they embark on an epic and adrenaline-fuelled adventure, travelling into the unknown without the trappings of modern life.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303796533459208627/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725210000 +0000" stop="20250725223000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E02 - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Five teams have been set the challenge to travel from the top to the bottom of Latin America - leaving behind smartphones, internet access and credit cards and armed with only the cash equivalent of a one-way airfare from Mexico City to Ushuaia.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303718448085622934/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250725223000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E03 - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this next leg on the race to Ushuaia, Argentina - the most Southerly city in the world- there are just four teams left to battle it out for the £20,000 prize.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303753706154528841/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250726000000 +0000" stop="20250726013000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E04 - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>As the 25,000 km race to Ushuaia approaches the half-way mark, the four teams compete not just with each other, but with the extreme altitudes of Peru.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303691754044875836/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
