<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719000000 +0000" stop="20250719002959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Street Sweeper E3 Testing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Street Sweeper is back! Stacey delves into just how many parts it takes to completely change the drivetrain and suspension on a classic muscle car. Accessories, transmission, overdrive, headers, the list may seem to go on forever, but it’s all about finding the right parts in the aftermarket, to build the car that YOU want. After that it’s off to the races to see if E3’s new top fuel spark plug can handle the pressure of competition. If you want to see the ins and outs of building a car, GEARZ is the show to see!</desc>
    <date>20140623</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0101.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719002959 +0000" stop="20250719005957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Street Sweeper Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>If you could only do one upgrade on your vehicle, that would make the biggest impact on the looks and drivability, what would it be? Stacey answers that question by installing a Katzkin leather interior into a Jeep Compass, and showing that if you’ve got an open weekend and a few hundred bucks, you can do the same thing on your car or truck. After that, he jumps back onto the Street Sweeper project to lay out the interior and the rearend, and finally drop that huge Hemi into place. If you’ve ever thought it would be fun to build a sleeper car, this is one ’73 Plymouth Satellite that shows how it can be done!</desc>
    <date>20140630</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0102.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719005957 +0000" stop="20250719012959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>NAPA Perfect Additions Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey Preps the bed of the NAPA Perfect additions truck. From rolling out Herculiner to installing transfer tank, truck boxes, and even a combination generator/compressor, this big Ford begins its Perfect Additions transformation. He also throws in a wiring tech that will keep you from getting your wires crossed.</desc>
    <date>20150306</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0103.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719012959 +0000" stop="20250719015958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>NAPA Perfect Additions Truck 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey tackles power gains at the air intake, modifies the computer and replaces the stock exhaust before addressing a 2” front-end suspension lift kit. He moves on to give the truck some extra height and support in the rear of the truck where payload weight can be a serious issue. After the suspension is in place, new wheels and tires bring the truck back down to the ground. Stacey also covers several tools that will help you get that old exhaust out from under your vehicle.</desc>
    <date>20150313</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0104.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719015958 +0000" stop="20250719023000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Junkyard Jag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey leads the crew on a hunt for a junkyard Jaguar with a rare engine. Pin-striping legend Von Hot Rod comes to the GearZ studio and lays down some lines on a hot rod guitar. Need to repair or replace the door on your pick up? Stacey’s got a handle on that. A bed lifter system turns a four-man operation into a one-man show. And Stacey’s got a steering column that will keep Falcon owners between the lines. All this and more!</desc>
    <date>20150320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0105.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719023000 +0000" stop="20250719025959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Evolution Worlds Fastest Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey tells the story of the legendary Cheetah and how that car was designed to beat Shelby’s famed Cobra. The GEARZ hunt for this iconic race car features the original ’63 Cheetah that Budd Clusserath drove 215 mph at Daytona in ‘64. But the story doesn’t end there, because Stacey gets his hands on a Cheetah Evolution and shows you how to build your own version of this tire shredding cat! After that, you’ll see Steering wheel options from Grant, a serpentine belt system from LMC Truck, and Wizard products to make your vehicle come alive, as well as a quick tip to get things rolling in your shop. All this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150403</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0107.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719025959 +0000" stop="20250719032959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Put A Heart In The Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Moving deeper into the build of the Cheetah Evolution, Stacey and the crew pull the skin off this cat and start putting in the guts. Overviews of suspension, steering, and brakes get this project up and running. Moving into the heart of this beast, Stacey shows us that good things do come in small packages—the LSX 454 small block is sure to get your pulse rate up. And once the transmission is mounted, look out! Headers follow, and this cat is almost ready to run. Stacey’s tool tech will give you a lift… all this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150410</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0108.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719032959 +0000" stop="20250719040000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Paws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A road trip, an overview of the Cheetah interior including seat and dash installation, rear lights and a tool tech. The GearZ crew heads out on the prowl to visit a budding young mechanic with a passion for 4X4’s. Back in the garage, Stacey gets in tight with the Cheetah, installing seats and the dash. Selecting gauges and placement are discussed, an AC unit will help keep this cat cool, taillights are fitted, and the side pipes will give this Cheetah some growl! Stacey’s tool tech will keep your project on time and on budget. And Fast Orange cleans more than your hands. All this on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150417</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0109.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719040000 +0000" stop="20250719042958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Beaten &amp; Downtrodden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Auction cars and what you might really find out once the car is in your garage: suspension, brakes and electrical concerns. In the current fad of “flipping” cars for cash, Stacey takes on the good, bad, and ugly of a ’66 Biscayne that was bought at auction. Nice looking paint can’t hide the safety issues that are found once this car is put on the lift. From suspension, to brakes, to battery cables… and even down to the lug nuts, this auction beauty turns out to be more of a beast. Safety and sport-style handling are only a few repairs away this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0110.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719042958 +0000" stop="20250719050000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Automotive Icon Turns 40</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the crew head north to celebrate 40 years of Heartthrob Exhaust and see just how far this company has come since its modest beginnings in a garage. After that we dig into a cracked dash and show how easy it is to replace one yourself with some aftermarket parts from LMC Truck, and then we look at a painless solution will help clean up years of spliced wires and old electrical tape that might be lurking under your hood. It’s simple gearhead stuff that everybody needs to know and it’s only on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150501</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0111.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719050000 +0000" stop="20250719052959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Gets Her Growl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey digs back into the Cheetah project by finishing up the stance with custom wheels and tires, and then goes through the ins and outs of putting a classic Hilborn fuel injection on a modern LS engine… and the dyno numbers show that the engine likes it as much as you will! After that Stacey sits down with a budding car designer that is making a big impact everywhere he goes and there’s also a tip on the importance of seals and gaskets. It’s all about getting out and turning wrenches, and you’re only gonna find it on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20150508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0112.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719052959 +0000" stop="20250719060000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Curves On Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey explores the history of the legendary Jaguar D-type racecar and introduces a D-type Jag from Race Car Replicas that is sure to become a legend of its own. From race wheels to classic spoke wheels with true knock-offs, Stacey looks at options for getting the best look and most rubber on the road with this Jag. A tip might keep you from losing your mind when dealing with lug nuts that don’t want to budge and we talk shop about performance parts for your own cars. So, come hang out while we take on a legendary cat of a different color this week on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20150515</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0113.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719060000 +0000" stop="20250719063000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>New Bed Old Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the crew hit the ground running with a late model replacement bed from LMC that’s sure to revive and old Ford farm truck and get it out of the pastures and back on the highway. Then it’s off to show budding Jeep enthusiasts a couple of entry level options they can use when it comes to modifying their vehicle. We get a visit from a couple who learn how to install new seat upholstery. Stacey’s found something cool for all you second generation Camaro owners. And we’re just getting started! So get ready to turn some wrenches on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150522</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0114.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719063000 +0000" stop="20250719070002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gearz On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew and Cornwell Tools team up to help a new shop in Arkansas get some much-needed tools to help them take they’re shop the next level. Then Stacey puts together the final pieces of the Sgt. Rock project by making a trip to France and the beaches of Normandy. Then it’s back to the shop to show you how easy it is to put fuel injection on your muscle car. It’s all here… and only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20150529</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0115.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719070002 +0000" stop="20250719073001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Nuts Bolts Building Sgt Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 10 Starts off with America’s favorite military tribute truck! Sgt. Rock is back and ready for final assembly! Garage Guru, Stacey David, takes us on a tour de force of custom fabrication as he covers all the nuts and bolts of what it’s taken to get Sgt. Rock ready to rumble. Builders of all levels are in for a great show as Stacey tackles one of a kind steering columns, gas pedals and designing a console that not only fits form, but also function. Gauge techs will keep your instrument panels in line. And a quick tip will keep your wires from fraying and your hoses from splitting. All this and more as Sgt. Rock and Season 10 hit the road full throttle.</desc>
    <date>20160304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0116.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719073001 +0000" stop="20250719080001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt Rock Interior Other Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A custom build can lose some power if the theme doesn’t stay consistent. Stacey shows how to do that by taking you through the process of how to make door and kick panels that keep the rugged military WWII bomber vibe flowing throughout the interior of Sgt. Rock. After that, its some tips on how to fit a radiator and that all-important cooling fan in a place where space is limited. Finally, the gas tank and battery placement are critical on a custom vehicle and Stacey goes through the steps in doing that as well. If you’ve always wanted to build a custom vehicle, this episode is sure to get your fabrication gearZ turning.</desc>
    <date>20160311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0117.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719080001 +0000" stop="20250719082959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Asessing Unfinished Project</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Two things are certain in life: death and taxes. We all know what to do with taxes, but what happens when a loved one passes and leaves behind an unfinished project vehicle? How do you know what’s sitting in your garage? And how can you find out? Stacey tackles these questions and takes you on a thorough inventory of an almost finished restoration that was left to a widow when her husband suddenly died. A new dash going into your vehicle? A gauge tech should keep you from crossing your wires. And we’ve got tips that should help with battery relocation and lining up your vehicle’s body panels.</desc>
    <date>20160318</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0118.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719082959 +0000" stop="20250719090000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gearz On The Road - Basic Tools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew mount up and head out to visit a young gear-head whose love of wrenching started with 4-wheelers and has grown to include 4-wheel drive pick ups. Young Adam has a few surprises in store as Stacey visits him in his Dad’s garage and discusses tools, storage and tearing apart things to see how they work. Then, it’s back in the shop as Stacey takes on the big question every gear-head has: What OTHER tools should I have in my box? A look beyond the typical wrenches, hammers and clamps will show you what you may need and what you may not, depending on your project.</desc>
    <date>20160325</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0119.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719090000 +0000" stop="20250719093003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Body Work Latches Custom Exhaust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The son of legendary car builder, Bill Thomas, talks shop about wrenching, racing and his father’s Cobra Killer…the Cheetah. Then Stacey heads over to Stainless Works to check out how the Cheetah’s custom side pipes, headers and mufflers came together. A Gauge Tech explains the pros and cons of mechanical vs. electric gauges. After that, a Quick Tip explains the proper way to use some of those mystery tools laying around in your tool box.</desc>
    <date>20160401</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0120.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719093003 +0000" stop="20250719100002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old Dog New Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ever wonder why your wife or best buddy won’t step foot in your late model truck? It could be that crusty interior. Tag along as Stacey takes on the sights and smells of an ’83 Chevy in dire need of some attention. From new dash to leather on the bench seat and new carpet in the floor, Stacey shows you what a difference a weekend and some parts from LMC can make. Speaking of trucks, Stacey raises the bar with a bed lifter that will make you the most popular guy in your neighborhood. A new buffer is going to help add some shine to your vehicle and a creeper that’s simply “Magic” is sure to raise an eyebrow or two. Big things are happening in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160408</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0121.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719100002 +0000" stop="20250719103002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Reviving An Old Snowcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Through the years, we’ve had some amazing vehicles featured on GearZ—from elite racecars to the insanity of a V-8 barstool. Well, here we go again! Stacey hauls in a Thiokol Imp that needs some…attention. First things first with this crazy snowcatmobile; we’ve got to see if we can make it run. Follow along as Stacey takes you through the ins and outs of getting a neglected vehicle up and running again. For you performance BMW guys, a tuner from Dinan is going add the horses you’ve been looking for. We’ve got sparks flying, fuel splashing and all kinds of garage mayhem this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160415</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0122.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719103002 +0000" stop="20250719110000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Wiring Sgt Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>In the world of car building there are few things more ominous than missing titles or VIN numbers. But there is one task that stands out, one that brings grown men to tears, one that is usually lurking behind 100 yards of electrical tape…WIRING. Well hold on tight as Stacey dives head first into wiring Sergeant Rock. That’s right; see how painless Stacey can make wiring the big old truck. Follow along as Stacey moves front to back and gets the Rock one step closer to hitting the road!</desc>
    <date>20160422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0123.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719110000 +0000" stop="20250719113002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>New AC Old Chevy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>With summer in full swing, it’s time to cool down that classic truck of yours. That’s right, roll those windows up and feel the cool breeze as Stacey shows just how easy it is to install this complete AC system from LMC Truck. Now that you’re done sweatin’, let’s take a look at headers and intakes and get that motor performing the way it should. And don’t miss out on the ins and outs of turbos and super-chargers…which one fits your needs? All this and plenty of sparks in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0124.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719113002 +0000" stop="20250719120002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building A Better Tool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the GearZ crew heat things up as they head to the Cornwell forges to watch molten steel be expertly transformed into America’s best ratchet. Get ready to see sparks fly. But the trip doesn’t stop there. Tag along as the crew follows what it takes for a ratchet to end up on a Cornwell truck. Back in the garage, Stacey talks maximizing boost and the role of intercoolers when it comes to super-chargers and turbos. The wheels keep turning and the rubber keeps burning, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0125.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719120002 +0000" stop="20250719123005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road - 67 Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheetah lovers will be excited to see Stacey’s solution to keeping the headers both cool and looking red hot. Want to keep using your stock tank after converting to fuel injection? Get psyched, because Holley has a new fuel pump that’s going to make your life a whole lot easier. Think your car is buttoned up tight? Stacey and some friends from Redline Detection blow smoke at the old soap and water test and show you how to really test for leaks in your vehicle. It’s a world of problems out there, but Stacey’s got you covered in the garage. All this and more, this week, on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0126.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719123005 +0000" stop="20250719130007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Novas BBQ</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>This week Stacey and crew head to Memphis, TN to help out a local BBQ pitmaster who’s deep into a ground up rebuild of a ’72 Nova. The big challenge here?...Can you swap out an automatic transmission with a manual without losing your mind? Well, Stacey is always up for a good challenge and he’ll show you just how simple this swap can be. A new tuner from Super chips will make your Jeep life easier, and replacement dashes for Chevy owners are going to light up their eyes. There’s a lot going on in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0127.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719130007 +0000" stop="20250719133006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheap Fuel Injection Snow Cat Bed TN Electric Guitar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re winding up the tenth season of GearZ, and what a season it’s been! But we’ve got some business to take care of before we move onto season eleven. First things first…Holley just made an EFI even easier to install on your carbureted vehicle, and Stacey will show you just how on target the Sniper is. The Thiokol Imp gets a suspension upgrade to keep it on track. And there’s a new kind of off-roading that’s sweeping the nation…see what RC4WD has going on. And what season would be complete without guitars? Check out Tennessee Electric Company as Stacey introduces a new guitar-maker whose custom guitars are hotter than the asphalt at the drag strip.</desc>
    <date>20160527</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0128.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719133006 +0000" stop="20250719140008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The SL-C’s Hit the Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re back and taking it to the streets! Season 11 comes roaring back with a look at Super Lite Cars on the road and the track! Stacey recalls and earlier SLC build and introduces two SLC builders who took a very hands-on approach to putting their cars together. These street/race cars are sure to catch your eye and get your racing blood flowing. If there’s one thing Stacey preaches on every episode, it’s paying attention to the details. His quick tip is no exception, getting rid of those sharp edges and nasty welds to give your project the small details that people will notice. Side mirrors for a muscle car, building a better battery, and keeping your air flowing through carbon fiber vents fill out the parts bin. We’ve got all this and more as Stacey kicks of his 11th season of GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20170107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0129.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719140008 +0000" stop="20250719143007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt. Rock Lives!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>This is the moment you’ve been waiting for! Master car builder, Stacey David, shows off the truck that’s had the nation talking for ten years! Take a look back at the kid with the dream. Follow the design and fabrication. See what happens when the military tribute vehicle rolls out and conquers the road! This episode is gonna be epic. It’s been a long road, but anything worth doing well is worth the wait. This week, the wait is over. Sergeant Rock Lives!</desc>
    <date>20170114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0130.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719143007 +0000" stop="20250719150008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road &amp; Unicure Spray Booths</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Things are rockin’ and rollin’ in and out of the GearZ garage. Stacey hits the road to find a project build that will get gear heads buzzing. He ends up with an ’81 Camaro and some awesome stories from the seller. If you’re talking project vehicles, you’ve got to talk paint! And Stacey does just that with folks from Unicure, who specialize in paint booths and helping you get set up for that all important paint job. The V-8 Interceptor is back from a trip to Stainless works, where a custom exhaust system was made for the big Boss Nine engine. Things are about to get loud, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0131.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719150008 +0000" stop="20250719153009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Heavy Metal &amp; Snowcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the GearZ crew roll in an old favorite: Heavy Metal. The coolest hotrod tow truck is back in the garage and ready for a facelift. Our good friends at the Hot Rod Institute drop by and talk shop with Stacey about his plans for the paint and fab work needed to get this bad boy looking good and back on the road. Fresh from the sandblaster, the snowcat reveals the scars that were under the skin. And with the drive train out, Stacey walks through the importance of replacing gaskets, seals and checking for wear and tear before stuffing that engine, transmission and skid steer rear end back into the cat. There’s a whole lot going on this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0132.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719153009 +0000" stop="20250719160008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Every gear head has a secret: they all want to drive like McQueen in Bullitt, or Vin Diesel in The Fast And The Furious. But when the heat gets turned up, even some really good drivers can’t keep up. That’s when you bring in the Stunt Double! This week Stacey sits down with legendary Hollywood stunt man Ian Quinn to talk crashing cars and keeping actors out of harms way. There’s also a new project in the garage: The Stunt Double, a build inspired by the 80’s tv show The Fall Guy, and sure to get all four wheels off the ground before Stacey’s done with it. Sparks are going to fly and you know we’re gonna have a good time this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170401</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0133.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719160008 +0000" stop="20250719163011 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Nose Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Seems like you can’t go more than a block these days without running into someone whose had some work done on their face. Well, here at the GearZ garage, Stacey believes in facelifts too. Just to prove it, he’s taken on a 1981 Camaro and sharpened his scalpel to perform an automotive nose job. Just wait till you see him whack of the old rubber nose and replace it with a 71’ rally sport front end! Now that’s what we call a facelift. Plenty of people said it couldn’t be done, but that’s just the kind of challenge Stacey is up for. Plenty of sparks are gonna fly, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170408</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0134.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719163011 +0000" stop="20250719170010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>They say that true change comes from within… Well, this week Stacey turns his attention to the interior of the Stunt Double. The old, crusty junk hits the floor and our Fall Guy inspired build gets a new look: from painting trim and door panels, to a new bench seat. Man o’ man, this truck is starting to look completely different. A shower of sparks lights up the garage as Stacey demonstrates how to make a bracket that mounts our new bench seat to the truck while using the stock seat adjustment. It’s a tour de force of aftermarket parts and salvaging what we’ve got, this week on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20170415</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0135.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719170010 +0000" stop="20250719173010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Gets a Lift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When you’re putting together a project that’s inspired by a high-flying stunt truck, you know you’ve got to add some lift, and our Stunt Double gets the goods this week. The front and rear suspension get treated to a 6” lift to get that rig up in the air. But a good lift won’t do any good if the steering and frame can’t hold up, so Stacey shows you how Offroad Design has fixed some serious issues that many late model four-wheel drives encounter. Bed need to come off your truck, but the carriage bolts are rusted and spinning? Stacey’s got a fix for that too. There’s a lot going on, and we’ve got you covered, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0136.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719173010 +0000" stop="20250719180008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ram Gets a Procharger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone needs a little boost here and there. For some people, coffee does the trick. But here in the GearZ Garage we take our boost seriously. And we like ours packing 160 HP. Hang on to your seat as Stacey adds a bolt on Supercharger to a Ram 1500 breathes a little excitement into a daily driver. And speaking of things going on in the garage, you’ll definitely want to stick around as Stacey talks shop with the guys at Rebuilding Generations. Learn all about how this mentoring program is teaching the next generation about working on cars and sharing plenty of life lessons. We’ve got a lot going on this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0137.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719180008 +0000" stop="20250719183006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Drivetrain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re running full steam ahead as the Stunt Double rolls back into the shop this week! First, Stacey reveals the wheels and tires that are going to accentuate that 6” lift, then He dives headlong into the drivetrain of this beast and comes up with a hot crate engine and a high-performance transmission to get the Stunt Double ready for the road. But that’s not all…. We also take some time out for a visit with the guys from American Powertrain and so much more. Check out the sparks flying in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170715</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0138.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719183006 +0000" stop="20250719190006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Front Suspension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s business as usual in the garage this week. We’re back at work on the Catalog Camaro and really diggin’ into the front end. You know what they say, “out with the old and in with the new,” and that’s exactly what Stacey’s doing. The old sub frame, drivetrain, and suspension are hitting the garage floor in favor of a much-needed updated suspension system that’ll keep this awesome Camaro hugging the road at high speeds—From the wheels to the sub frame, Stacey’s replacing it all. And he’s not going to break the bank while doing it, either. Follow the GearZ crew as they hit the road and visit Cornwell Tools to see their latest and greatest tool box being manufactured. From powder coat to knuckle bustin’ bolts, we’ve got you covered this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170722</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0139.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719190006 +0000" stop="20250719193008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Procharger Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>We head out of the garage to visit one of the premiere supercharger manufacturers in the world… ATI Pro Charger. Follow along for the ride as Stacey walks through the entire process of how they have raised the bar on how a supercharger is built and what it does. From bulk metal to dyno runs, we’ve got it covered. Back in the garage, a young Gearhead drops by to learn how to install an air intake and cowl induction hood on his pick-up. After the wrench turning is done, he and Stacey have enough time to hit a few licks on their guitars. From massive horsepower increases with state-of-the-art tools and machinery, to simple intake and hood installs,….. it’s all here, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170729</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0140.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719193008 +0000" stop="20250719200006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Recaps &amp; Catchups</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey is in full hot rod mode as he unveils a wicked LS engine and Tremec 6spd tranny and stuffs it into the Catalog Camaro. If 600hp and a 6spd in a Camaro doesn’t get you going, the update on the Stunt Double will! It’s old school cool as Stacey shows off the stainless light bar, side steps and cutout flairs to give the truck that “Fall Guy” vibe. After that we introduce you to the amazing world of scale R/C that is sure to have you re-thinking what you want for Christmas! Finally we roll in some updates on the Cheetah and the Junkyard Jag too. If you’re a gearhead, you’re gonna find a whole lot to love about this show!......and that’s GEARZ!!!</desc>
    <date>20170805</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0141.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719200006 +0000" stop="20250719203005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Puttin’ on the B.R.A.K.E.S.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 12 opens with bang as Stacey starts the final assembly process on the V8 Interceptor. If you’ve ever wondered how to lay out an aftermarket A/C system, wiring harness, and steering column on your project… and make them all work together, you have to see this show! After that, NHRA legend and Hall-of-Famer, Doug Herbert drops by the GearZ garage to share the shocking story that inspired him to start the B.R.A.K.E.S. driving program. Hold on tight, because this ain't your typical high school driver's Ed. Program! If you want cool tech and awesome stories… you’re gonna find that on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20180106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0142.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719203005 +0000" stop="20250719210004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Snowcat Bed Fabrication</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about fabrication and thinking outside the box, or to be more specific... outside the bed! Sure, sure, there are plenty of custom pick-up truck beds you can buy but Stacey shows you what is involved in MAKING a custom bed to fit any vehicle, even something as crazy as a Thiokol Imp snowcat! That's right… our little snowcat is back from the sand blaster and ready for a cool bed to match the cab. Stacey goes in-depth about sizing up the project, picking the right parts, and most importantly: how to cut, weld, grind and finish sheet metal to get a bed that will fit your unique vehicle like a glove. So grab a welder… it’s time to make your bed!... only on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0143.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719210004 +0000" stop="20250719213005 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Fort Carson On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey takes a trip to Fort Carson, Colorado to visit the Army auto skills program during their world conference. Not only does Stacey get to meet a General, but he also meets a young Sergeant who is in the middle of a frame-off square body restoration. After a thorough walk around, Stacey decides to get LMC involved in helping out with this build. Parts for the bed of his truck can’t match the gratitude we share for our active military and all those who have served, but it’s a start. And we can’t wait to see the project when it’s finished. And speaking of new beds, with the custom bed on the Snow Cat, it’s time to address the tracks, and Right Track Systems has us covered. That little cat is going to tear it up when all is said and done! It’s going to be a lot of fun, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0144.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719213005 +0000" stop="20250719220006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Interceptor Final Assembly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about Cougars! No, not that kind of Cougar... the kind with 4 wheels and a legendary pedigree! After a short history lesson about how these cars came into existence and why they were so cool, Stacey rolls the V8 Interceptor back into the shop and digs into the final assembly of this wild ’67 Mercury Cougar. This week’s episode focuses on planning out your final assembly, and taking care of all the little details, before you put the big things in like engine and transmission. Whether it’s planning out your brake system, battery location, or running fuel lines, Stacey shows how a little extra time in the planning department will make all the difference in your build.</desc>
    <date>20180127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0145.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719220006 +0000" stop="20250719223004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Blackbird &amp; Panel Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey takes us through the history of the legendary SR-71 Blackbird. If you’re not familiar with this bird, it could fly mach 3.2, cruise at 80,000 feet and kept our country safe through its many reconnaissance missions. Never shot down, and never outrun, it was the hot rod of the sky! Stacey gets to sit down with pilot Lt. Col. Ed Yeilding and talk about his record setting transcontinental flight—Coast to Coast in 67 minutes and 54 seconds! The iconic Blackbird was such an inspiration that you know Stacey had to make a vehicle inspired by and paying tribute to it, so get ready to meet the SR-71 Rapid Tool Express!!!</desc>
    <date>20180331</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0146.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719223004 +0000" stop="20250719230006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Butt Lift and Tummy Tuck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Catalog Camaro is back in the garage and ready to go under the knife as Stacey shows how to do a butt lift and tummy tuck on a 2nd generation Camaro. What does that mean? Well, last season Stacey performed a nose job on this old ’81 Camaro to show how easy it is to get rid of the 80’s plastic front bumpers and put on the classic early 70’s split-bumper, rally sport front sheetmetal. This week he continues the makeover by losing the plastic rear bumper and wrap-around taillights and grafting in the early 70’s quarter panels, round taillights and chrome bumper. It’s more in depth than the front and definitely requires some skilled metal surgery, but Stacey shows you all the tricks on how to do it properly. So, sit back and enjoy the ride as Stacey details how to measure, cut, and weld your way to a much younger looking Camaro.</desc>
    <date>20180407</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0147.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719230006 +0000" stop="20250719233003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Big Bad Buick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in a Big Bad Buick Riviera and shows you what is possible with the right vehicle and some bolt on parts. This 1972 Riviera is a great entry-level project that won’t break the bank, and has the potential to serve some serious humble-pie to any unsuspecting hot shot that may want to mix it up at the stoplight. As it sits, the big 455 under the hood is a force to be reckoned with, but Stacey shows what a weekend in the garage and a top end rebuild can do for a car like this! Get ready to get your hands dirty and bust a few knuckles as Stacey pulls the old heads, intake, cam, and ignition off and replaces them with performance parts from companies like TA Performance, Edelbrock, and MSD. It’s a lesson in Buick and bolt-on horsepower, and you’re only gonna find it on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180414</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0148.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719233003 +0000" stop="20250720000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Paint &amp; Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew hits the road this week and travels to the Charlotte Speed Shop to see how paint prep is going on Stacey’s Cheetah Evolution Car. With the hood and side vents glassed in and smoothed out, the first coat of primer gets sprayed and this awesome cat takes one big step closer to coming home! Stacey also stops by to visit with a fellow boat tail Riviera owner and trade tips on beefing up these classic beauties. It turns out that this guy and Stacey had both been watching this same car when it came up for sale! Come hang out with us as we visit some great folks this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20180421</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0149.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250720000000 +0000" stop="20250720002958 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Big Bad Buick Inside &amp; Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey gets down to business on the Big Bad Buick. With the top end engine rebuilt, the exterior and interior of the car need some serious updating. You don’t have to spend a ton of cash on simple modifications. Stacey shows what’s behind making a good clean line with your bumpers and how a simple front and rear bumper tuck can drastically change the appearance. Replacing the grille and scraping off that old vinyl top are also sure-fire ways to add attitude to this big ol’ boat tail. That old carpet has got to go! Follow along as Stacey shows the ins and outs and some tips and tricks to keep your exterior and interior redo from breaking the bank.</desc>
    <date>20180623</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0150.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
