<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719230440 +0000" stop="20250719235050 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Can It Be Cured?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E63</episode-num>
    <desc>See a cure for chronic ear infections, a laser treatment that eliminates back pain and technology that guarantees less time in the dentist’s chair. And, at-home remedies that can cure a cold, calm a flu and quell motion sickness.</desc>
    <date>20091202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719235050 +0000" stop="20250720003840 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Doctors: Body Sounds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>From a grumbling stomach, to a gassy gut to ringing ears, find out which body noises are hazardous, which are harmless and how to mute them.</desc>
    <date>20091006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720003840 +0000" stop="20250720012303 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Desperate to Save A Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E97</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go to save your life or the life of someone you love? Meet a family who has taken drastic steps to prevent the cancer that runs rampant in their genes. And, Survivor star Ethan Zohn in the battle of his life.</desc>
    <date>20100201</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720012303 +0000" stop="20250720020817 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>More Embarrassing Problems, Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedian Tom Green speaks candidly about his battle with testicular cancer. Find out what he wants every man to know. Plus, dryness down there? Uncontrollable bowels? Excess fat in your pelvic region? The Doctors tackles your most embarrassing body problems.</desc>
    <date>20121210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720020817 +0000" stop="20250720025451 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Better Teeth, Breasts &amp; Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E81</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors reveal the latest non-surgical ways to improve your cleavage, and get prettier teeth, luscious lashes and sexier feet in minutes. And, feeling fatigued after sex? Try The Doctors’ After-Sex Sandwich.</desc>
    <date>20120120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04081.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720025451 +0000" stop="20250720034044 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Gross Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn why IBS can wreak havoc on your stomach and your sex life! Gunk in your eyes? Find out how to get rid of it. Plus, how to heal hemorrhoids. And, surprising ways to increase your man’s sperm count.</desc>
    <date>20121113</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d5527404ae5a786aa4d62b74df5c2239.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720034044 +0000" stop="20250720042722 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bizarre in the E.R.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E64</episode-num>
    <desc>Bizarre in The E.R. - strange but true emergency room stories you won’t believe! Plus, “The Doctors Court” discusses how an ex-inmate is suing a jail for $5 million after he claims They ignored his 91-hour surprise erection! And, a brand new dad was arrested for selling heroin in the hospital’s maternity ward! Then, should high school students be segregated at lunchtime by their GPAs? And, don’t look now ladies, but pimple-popping nails are in vogue! Would you try them?</desc>
    <date>20180119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10064.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720042722 +0000" stop="20250720051253 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>DIY Baby Delivery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom’s at-home delivery story you won’t believe! Could fruit flies be the key to figuring out the male sex drive? Treating face shingles. Newly engaged couple in need of serious weight loss help. The shocking new dating trend! DIY shoe polish hack you need to know! The new “String Test” to determine if you’re obese!</desc>
    <date>20180928</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720051253 +0000" stop="20250720055939 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Post Surgery Skin Removal &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Massive skin removal reveal post weight loss! Break up battle plan with Dr. Ish. Does beer make men more fertile? “Morgue Mom” Mysteries! The ABC’s of cancer and what you need to know today! Viral superstar “Sancho” the therapy dog! Fridge hacks you must have!</desc>
    <date>20180927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720055939 +0000" stop="20250720064619 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Stool Squad Answers Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Stool Squad is back to answer your most embarrassing poop-related questions! Disturbing Kim Kardashian look-a-like plastic surgery! Shocking celebrity beauty trend! Toddler hospitalized after using a toy makeup kit!</desc>
    <date>20181009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11004.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720064619 +0000" stop="20250720073302 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>My Ex Threw Acid In My Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E44</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman’s fight to put her ex-boyfriend behind bars after he throws acid on her face and lies about it to police? Plus, one couple’s late-night drive to the hospital for the birth of their daughter turns into a nightmare when they’re stopped by the police! Plus, our daytime exclusive with the amazing dog who fought off three bears!</desc>
    <date>20151117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D08044.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720073302 +0000" stop="20250720081822 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What Is That Bump?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether it’s a wart, cyst, pimple or boil, learn what your body bumps say about your health. And, tips to keep bed bugs from biting.</desc>
    <date>20100930</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720081822 +0000" stop="20250720090350 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Body Fluids: Explained</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E95</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors reveals the health secrets behind your bodily fluids. Find out how to keep acne breakouts at bay and how to stop excessive perspiration!</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720090350 +0000" stop="20250720094332 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Worst Problem Cures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E155</episode-num>
    <desc>Bad sex, ugly scars, excess fat? The Doctors reveal the best cures for your worst problems. Plus, baby news for the McGraw family, and the Sears family of pediatricians answers your most pressing parenting questions.</desc>
    <date>20110525</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03155.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720094332 +0000" stop="20250720103026 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>My Breast Implants Made Me Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E136</episode-num>
    <desc>In an exclusive interview, a former Playboy Playmate claims her implants made her sick and says she’s not the only one! Derek Hough reveals how he stays fit and gives the inside scoop on his new show! Find out why some parents are potty training their kids … in public! A young man with a family history of early-onset Alzheimer’s turns to The Doctors! What will be revealed? Get the warning signs you need to know! Plus, a hoarder finally finds freedom … how did she do it?</desc>
    <date>20170412</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09136.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720103026 +0000" stop="20250720111806 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The United States of Addiction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E45</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors highlights the other side of addiction: recovery. Witness the powerful life transformation of a man who lost his legs to heroin. Then, can a breakthrough brain treatment for pain and addiction offer hope to so many sufferers? Then, The Doctors investigates drug addicted healthcare workers who put the patients they are treating at risk. Hear a harrowing story of a mother who contracted a deadly disease at the hands of a drug-addicted hospital worker. Plus, find out how you can protect yourself from becoming a victim of a medical mistake at the hands of a drug-addicted provider. And, learn the key to harnessing hope when things feel hopeless.</desc>
    <date>20171121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720111806 +0000" stop="20250720120448 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Health A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Improve your health from A to Z! From anti-aging to zits, The Doctors tackle common health concerns and share the latest medical treatments, simple cures and surprising tips to keep you in tip-top shape.</desc>
    <date>20091113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720120448 +0000" stop="20250720125228 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Docs: Should I Worry?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E72</episode-num>
    <desc>Is someone you love showing symptoms of a sickness? The Doctors explore the biggest health concerns that often go unchecked. From vomiting to high fevers, learn when it’s time to visit the E.R. Does sitting cause breast cancer? Can cold sores lead to Alzheimer’s? The Doctors weigh in on your biggest health worries. Plus, how a stroke turned a straight man gay, when to take your child to The ER and more.</desc>
    <date>20111213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04072.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720125228 +0000" stop="20250720133649 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Accident Risks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E50</episode-num>
    <desc>Electrocutions! Brain trauma! Natural disasters! Accidents can strike at any moment – are you prepared? The Doctors reveal simple tips and tools to stay safe. Plus, there are items in your home that could suddenly explode! Do you know what they are?</desc>
    <date>20121119</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/043e7b969d2f682875b227f4311e4f94.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720133649 +0000" stop="20250720142342 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Stop It Before It Starts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E139</episode-num>
    <desc>Actress and widow of John Ritter, Amy Yasbek, shares her family’s heartbreak surrounding her husband's sudden and tragic death. Learn how to prevent this tragedy from striking your family. And, age and sun spot dangers.</desc>
    <date>20100414</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02139.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720142342 +0000" stop="20250720151023 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Miraculous Brain Stroke Recovery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E105</episode-num>
    <desc>See the unbelievable recovery of a woman who was diagnosed with a rare and aggressive brain stroke. Did her family’s love turn around her dire prognosis? Do big feet mean big love in the bedroom? And, why are some farts squeaky and others silent? Then, the controversial plan one ER doctor has to combat the opioid epidemic. Could her “Death Diaries” save lives? The best foods for a better brain. And, the perfect bed time story to get you sleeping faster.</desc>
    <date>20180215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720151023 +0000" stop="20250720155742 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Stool Squad and More!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E91</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re tackling everything from your common questions to your most embarrassing questions in our medical confessional! Then, The “Stool Squad” is back to answer all your bathroom-related questions! And, fixes for a chubby face without going under the knife! And, The surprising reason why one woman’s nose is constantly running for 7 years. Then, Dr. Nita reveals the everyday habit that could lead to a yeast infection! Next, new research says sparkling water is making you fat. But is true? And, we’re revealing the top hacks to ease your winter driving woes!</desc>
    <date>20180202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10091.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720155742 +0000" stop="20250720164547 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top 'C' Words Everyone Hates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors count down the top C words that cause consternation. And, new treatments for corns, calluses and constipation!</desc>
    <date>20091012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720164547 +0000" stop="20250720173045 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Imagine Dragons Singer's Struggle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Exclusive: Imagine Dragons frontman Dan Reynolds reveals the health struggle he’s been fighting for years! A man goes from obese to a body builder! A nurse and mother is accused of “meth mouth” because her teeth are so bad! Can The Doctors and celebrity dentist Bill Dorfman give her a new smile? Can you have your cake and eat it, too? You can with Chef Jimmy’s no-guilt, no-bake cheesecake! Plus, high-end jewelry that doubles up as sex toys? A neurosurgeon gets life in prison for malpractice! And, The easiest way to clean your makeup brushes!</desc>
    <date>20170308</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720173045 +0000" stop="20250720181734 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mind-Blowing Makeovers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E148</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a makeover spectacular! A woman loses six feet of excess skin! A man tormented by large keloids that ballooned across his face undergoes a medical makeover! A child born with an extra set of limbs receives a life-changing surgery! Rapper Siya reveals her new smile and surprises fans with a fresh new look! A mother covered in tiny tumors returns to the show for an update on her healing! Rosie Mercado puts Dr. Travis’ Lose Your Belly Diet to the test! The fitness star who made headlines for her six-pack abs during pregnancy shows off her tummy just nine days after giving birth! Plus, the surprising reason you should be saving your child’s baby teeth and the new medical guidelines that could put the tooth fairy out of business!</desc>
    <date>20170516</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09148.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720181734 +0000" stop="20250720190523 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Health Hazards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Did you know that brushing your teeth can actually harm your oral hygiene? And that coughing could lead to a hysterectomy? Find out seemingly-harmless situations that may be ruining your health. Plus, must-know sleeping pill info.</desc>
    <date>20121012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720190523 +0000" stop="20250720194751 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Potluck Poop Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E90</episode-num>
    <desc>Party crashed by unwelcome visitor – poop bacteria? New study may lead way to offset Alzheimer’s. Bizarre in the ER – you won’t believe what one patient got tangled up in and how another patient’s throat became rotted. Could trauma be healed through sex work? One survivor shares her story. Why woman was denied a manicure? When you’re under the knife, do you know what’s going on in the OR? The secret ingredient to take your smoothies to the next level!</desc>
    <date>20190225</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11090.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720194751 +0000" stop="20250720203434 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What to Tell Your Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to your health, being honest with your doctor is vital to maintaining your wellbeing. Whether it’s a nagging pain or your family’s medical history, find out all the information you must tell your physician.</desc>
    <date>20091008</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02014.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720203434 +0000" stop="20250720212126 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Scary Symptoms That Are Harmless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E61</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you constantly surfing the net trying to self-diagnose a mysterious pain? The Doctors reveal what symptoms are safe to ignore and when you need to pay closer attention. Learn the safe and scary causes of numbness, heart palpitations, easy bruising and more</desc>
    <date>20101129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03061.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720212126 +0000" stop="20250720220733 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What To Do When It Won’t Go Away!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E96</episode-num>
    <desc>Persistent pains, incessant itching, endless ear-ringing – fix your most relentless ailments today! Whiten bloodshot eyes for good, relieve the itch you can’t stop scratching and more. And, the secret to getting in and out of public bathrooms germ-free!</desc>
    <date>20120131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04096.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720220733 +0000" stop="20250720225539 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Total Body Lift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E73</episode-num>
    <desc>A cervical cancer test in the doctor's office is saving lives. See it performed live. And, Amanda lost 180 pounds, but excess skin and fat hung from her body. See The Total Body Lift surgery that allowed her to reclaim her life!</desc>
    <date>20090119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01073.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250720225539 +0000" stop="20250720234026 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E168</episode-num>
    <desc>Sometimes bigger is better! Learn when excess can lead to success. Do bigger butts indicate good health? Find out. The Doctors race through an oversized obstacle course. See who wins! Plus, meet the world’s largest dog.</desc>
    <date>20110527</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03168.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
