<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709010003 +0000" stop="20250709023301 +0000">
    <title>Pinch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A talented MC uses larceny to fund his dreams of becoming a rap star, but his life changes when he meets Allie, now the once self-centered thief is transformed into the Robin Hood for the hood.</desc>
    <date>20201221</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c0529ac93daca7b4601ad78f657f4503.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709023301 +0000" stop="20250709054842 +0000">
    <title>Promise Chronicles: Manifestation</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A despairing group of Christians and non-believer's band together during the biblical period, known as Tribulation, not only to survive death, but to escape America, and uncover a sinister globalist plot designed by an overreaching government.</desc>
    <date>20220611</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/39032113ce37ac06c48cb900103e2a1c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709054842 +0000" stop="20250709074936 +0000">
    <title>Queen of the Trap House</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Kionna is asked to step in and take control of her jailed boyfriend, Tyreek's, drug empire, she reluctantly agrees, but her new position as Queen of the Trap House suits her more than expected.</desc>
    <date>20201209</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/049a7edf7cb48796eaa41f73bed06b9d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709074936 +0000" stop="20250709092910 +0000">
    <title>Queen of the Trap House 2: Taking the Throne</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Kionna has taken full control of her dead boyfriend's drug empire. She has taken the throne to become the official Queen of the Trap House. However, a new man steps into her life causing her to shift focus away from the criminal enterprise. Kionna also begins dealing with new enemies from rival drug gangs to law enforcement. Kionna will now need to show everyone what a true Queen does to maintain power.</desc>
    <date>20220719</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/ab33578e3e704e6b3a326b5e03ff1bce.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709092910 +0000" stop="20250709113759 +0000">
    <title>Promiscuously Toxic</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Marcus had everything he wanted, money , freedom, a beautiful woman, but he had one problem: He just couldn't be faithful. In his past, he had trouble with being with just one woman, until a wonderful woman came in and changed his life, but the thing with Karma, is that it has no heart.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/015d70e8b48b9e8fd30b2caf5ac7095a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709113759 +0000" stop="20250709141106 +0000">
    <title>Men Pray Too</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An ex-con tries to rebuild a life with his girlfriend. Can he start anew through the power of prayer?</desc>
    <date>20240315</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709141106 +0000" stop="20250709155718 +0000">
    <title>Dangerous Affair</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Erika and Ryan are a happily married couple living in a high rise Apartment in Atlanta, Ga. everything is going great until Erika meets a handsome, mysterious man in her building and they start having an affair. Once Ryan finds out about the affair Erika ends it. But the mystery man has other plans. Will the married couple survive the Dangerous Affair?</desc>
    <date>20240326</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/2a9b5b5f853e4ad5ab64963dff012190.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709155718 +0000" stop="20250709184940 +0000">
    <title>Deeper</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The story of Chasity, King, and Gotti is a tale of love, betrayal, and power. Gotti returns with a vengeance, seeking to reclaim his Dallas Kingpin status and Chasity's love. Despite their challenges, Chasity and King remain determined. As they plan their future, Gotti's secrets and power grab threaten their love. Will they triumph over his schemes or will he steal her heart? Follow their journey in the dangerous world of the hustle.</desc>
    <date>20241217</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/97cfbb8a3a704aa9f1c507cf5fbe9503.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709184940 +0000" stop="20250709202457 +0000">
    <title>All the Love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman begins her journey to adulthood, navigating love and self-discovery, while being haunted by a mysterious past that she can’t fully remember. As murders and violence swirl around her, she wonders who she can trust. Will she find love or suffer the same mysterious fate as her birth parents?</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6589e799a5ad0a6e19fa52d1d64f0025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709202457 +0000" stop="20250709214642 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709214642 +0000" stop="20250709232629 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709232629 +0000" stop="20250710015829 +0000">
    <title>BARS</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Kobe lives a picture-perfect life. A devoted wife and mother, she has everything she's ever wanted. But her idyllic world shatters when she's abruptly arrested and sentenced to life in prison for a crime she didn't commit. Desperate for survival, Kobe finds solace and strength in a tight-knit group of inmates known as The Pretty Girls. Unaware of Kobe's ordeal, her twin sister Shaq returns home only to discover the shocking truth.</desc>
    <date>20241112</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
