<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709005808 +0000" stop="20250709014257 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Shot My Millionaire Cheater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E140</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who shot her fiancé in the leg after he cheated wants to marry him.</desc>
    <date>20180426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16140.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709014257 +0000" stop="20250709022637 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beaten and Bruised: #WHYISTAY</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil shines the spotlight on domestic violence, speaking with Kaitlyn, who defends her professional fighter husband, Josh, even though he's being held in jail without bail stemming from an August incident. Plus, hear from Trichelle, who faces 20 years in prison after she says she shot and killed her husband in self-defense after years of alleged domestic abuse. Will her words of warning make an impact on Kaitlyn?</desc>
    <date>20140918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709022637 +0000" stop="20250709031320 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Husband’s Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E98</episode-num>
    <desc>Danielle says that her husband of nearly 10 years, John, has been living a secret life -- reaching out to men on Craigslist for sex and looking at child pornography. John insists that the child porn was accidentally downloaded, and while he admits to exchanging emails with men online, he maintains that he never met up with anyone in person. How does he explain his actions? And, what will the results of a polygraph test reveal?</desc>
    <date>20140221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12098.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709031320 +0000" stop="20250709040005 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen writes: Dear Dr. Phil, My husband mentally abuses me. I've never, in my life, had a guy tell me how fat I am, how terrible I look, or criticize how I put my makeup on. He constantly calls me names and makes fat jokes. Sometimes I have to hide in the bathroom when I eat something just so we won't fight about it. Any time I try to get close to him, he literally pushes me away and says, "Don't even touch me until you're under 200 pounds".</desc>
    <date>20250531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709040005 +0000" stop="20250709044626 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Twisted Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E91</episode-num>
    <desc>Can a man convince his wife to accept a polyfidelic relationship with his mistress?</desc>
    <date>20060202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4091.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709044626 +0000" stop="20250709053401 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins (Part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E209</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother faces tough questions from Dr. Phil as they race to get her two daughters off the streets and into rehab.</desc>
    <date>20061120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5209.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709053401 +0000" stop="20250709060902 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins (Part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E210</episode-num>
    <desc>Two sisters struggles to detox and remain clean from drugs. Dr. Phil shows them a scary glimpse of their future.</desc>
    <date>20240605</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5210.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709060902 +0000" stop="20250709065516 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins PT 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E211</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil addresses Cindy's impact on Tecoa's sobriety and reunites Sarah and Tecoa with their estranged father.</desc>
    <date>20061204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5211.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709065516 +0000" stop="20250709074136 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Maggots, Mold and Rotten Milk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E116</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman says her daughter has a history of drug abuse, and she fears that her grandchildren are being neglected.</desc>
    <date>20110506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709074136 +0000" stop="20250709083041 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s 1000 Affairs?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E94</episode-num>
    <desc>Deb says a year ago, she discovered her husband, David’s, tangled web of lies and sexual affairs that spanned more than a decade -- and she believes he’s cheated on her at least 1,000 times. David admits he had several inappropriate relationships with other women, but claims he only had two physical affairs, and he’s ended it all. He says Deb’s obsession with proving he’s still unfaithful is destroying their marriage. Can this relationship be saved?</desc>
    <date>20140228</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12094.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709083041 +0000" stop="20250709091833 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lover, My Abuser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah is a pretty, intelligent, successful woman with everything going for her — so why won't she leave her abusive boyfriend, Robert? She says he punches her, chokes her, spits in her face, and has even threatened to kill her, but she believes he can be rehabilitated. Is she in over her head? If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic violence, don’t miss Dr. Phil's exit action plan for safely leaving an abusive partner</desc>
    <date>20120221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709091833 +0000" stop="20250709100512 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Toxic Family Love Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E103</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband cheated on his wife with her sister.</desc>
    <date>20150219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709100512 +0000" stop="20250709105222 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Spies, Suspicions &amp; Sex Accusations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E54</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman says her husband has wrongly accused her of cheating.</desc>
    <date>20131107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12054.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709105222 +0000" stop="20250709113715 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband Obsessed: A Wife Accused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E311</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues as Dr. Phil examines Mike's alleged evidence that his wife cheated.</desc>
    <date>20131108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12311.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709113715 +0000" stop="20250709122206 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>17 And Out Of Control</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you struggling to tame your rebellious teen? Chris and Barbara say their 17-year-old daughter, Courtney, is out of control! The teen proudly admits she bullies, steals, drinks and does drugs and is consumed with anger. Can Dr. Phil set her straight? Parents: If you know a teen who’s heading down a dangerous path, this is one show you can't afford to miss!</desc>
    <date>20120125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709122206 +0000" stop="20250709130744 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Where'd The Money Go?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E50</episode-num>
    <desc>Is compulsive spending ruining your life? According to a recent Gallup poll, the average American owes $29,000 in credit card debt, and last year, 1.6 million U.S. households filed for bankruptcy. Dr. Phil has advice for avoiding credit card catastrophes this holiday season.</desc>
    <date>20041112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3050.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709130744 +0000" stop="20250709135412 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Teen Can’t Stand My Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E93</episode-num>
    <desc>Marriages with blended families have a higher rate of divorce than the first trip down the aisle, and today’s guests say they know exactly why. When Kip married Vicky, he says he knew that her daughter, Tory, was part of the package. Now, he struggles to get along with the 17-year- old, and they often engage in jaw-dropping screaming matches followed by a month without speaking. Hear the scathing remarks that Dr. Phil describes as the most inappropriate comments that he’s ever heard a stepparent say about a child. What led someone to fear for Tory’s safety and make a worried call to authorities? What, if any, ownership do this teen and her mother have in this family dynamic? And, Joe, 34, became an instant father to two teenage daughters, one of whom has run away. Can this family finally have a happy ending?</desc>
    <date>20110502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709135412 +0000" stop="20250709144146 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Was Our Marriage a Mistake?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>More couples get divorced in the first year of marriage than any other. Dr. Phil talks with newlyweds in crisis about having realistic expectancies and re-negotiating within the relationship.</desc>
    <date>20031211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L2013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709144146 +0000" stop="20250709153109 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>First Year Marriage Survival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The honeymoon is over! Dr. Phil talks with newlyweds about their troubles, and he and Robin share some stories of how they make their marriage work.</desc>
    <date>20031014</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L2022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709153109 +0000" stop="20250709161717 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Affairs of the Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Can married people be friends with someone of the opposite sex without sex getting in the way? At what point does a friendly relationship become an affair of the heart or emotional infidelity? Meet Randy, who says his wife, Amanda, has crossed that line.</desc>
    <date>20090304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709161717 +0000" stop="20250709170342 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Living on a Prayer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E65</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents who force their children to live an extreme, harsh existence.</desc>
    <date>20080215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709170342 +0000" stop="20250709175313 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Mate’s Not Hot Enough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E115</episode-num>
    <desc>How much should looking good factor into your relationship? Today’s guests say appearance matters, and their mate is not up to their standards! Sandi says after six years of marriage, she misses her husband, Otto’s, six-pack. He says working -- not working out -- is a priority for him, and nothing will satisfy his wife, who rates herself a 20 out of 10. But the couple does agree on one thing: whatever Sandi wants, Sandi gets. Will Otto agree to hit the gym? Then, Dawn worked hard to shed 150 pounds, and when the new svelte Dawn met Paul, sparks flew! He thought she was hot -- until she undressed. What is she hiding? Plus, discover why Dr. Phil wrestles with his decision to help Dawn and Paul. And, Cynthia says she’s embarrassed by her boyfriend’s outdated wardrobe, and refuses to be seen with him in public! Can a professional makeover change her opinion?</desc>
    <date>20110526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9115.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709175313 +0000" stop="20250709183904 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Grandson in a Filthy Death Trap!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents say their daughter's home is unsafe for grandson.</desc>
    <date>20201006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709183904 +0000" stop="20250709192504 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Get Rid Of It!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E93</episode-num>
    <desc>Is there something you’ve been hanging on to for just a little too long? Clothes you haven’t fit into since high school? Boxes of stuff you haven’t looked at in years? Dr. Phil’s guests say their loved ones need to call the junk yard and “Get rid of it!” Kim says her husband, Paul’s, Star Warshobby has to go. With over 6,000 pieces in his collection, Paul spends 30 hours a week playing with his action figures, building models and talking to friends about Star Wars. He even had a light saber sword fight at their wedding, so shouldn’t Kim have known what she was getting into? Next, Larry and Sheila married four months ago, but Sheila says she had no idea she was getting hitched to a hoarder. Larry says she’s got it all wrong -– she’s the pack rat! With some of their favorite collections rolled out on stage, can Dr. Phil help them negotiate what goes and what stays? Plus, meet Terri, who has four storage units and two garages full of sentimental memories -– like a rubber chicken and her father’s spine X-rays! She spends so much money storing her stuff, that she can’t even afford health insurance. What’s at the heart of her hoarding? Don’t miss this hilarious look at how collections can get out of control!</desc>
    <date>20080130</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709192504 +0000" stop="20250709201253 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>More In-Laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E129</episode-num>
    <desc>It's the invasion of the in-laws! Despite an intervention by Dr. Phil, a couple and their respective mothers still struggle to get along. See how Ernie and Kerry are doing, and what happens when their moms agree to set their differences aside and meet for coffee. Since the last show, Kerry says her relationship with her mother-in-law has never been better! Unfortunately, her relationship with her mother has never been worse. Then, Alaina and Ray are married with two children, and they all live with Ray’s mother, Eda. The two women are constantly at each other’s throats and it's threatening the entire family. Is this household too close for comfort, and will they be able to find a solution?</desc>
    <date>20050908</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3129.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709201253 +0000" stop="20250709210059 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Old Flames</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E70</episode-num>
    <desc>What happens when you can't let go of a meaningful relationship from the past? What are the boundaries when getting in touch with an old flame while you're married? Although toying with old flames can get you burned, it can also be the spark that rekindles lost love.</desc>
    <date>20060113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4070.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709210059 +0000" stop="20250709214907 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>How To Spot A Scammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E52</episode-num>
    <desc>With the economy in trouble, a lot of people are under pressure and getting desperate. Learn the tools to protect yourself from liars, cheats and scammers who are trying to take advantage.</desc>
    <date>20091125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8052.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709214907 +0000" stop="20250709223628 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Nasty Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Feuds between neighbors are examined.</desc>
    <date>20070919</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709223628 +0000" stop="20250709232153 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>16 and on the Path of Destruction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E314</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother describes her daughter's self-destructive behaviors.</desc>
    <date>20131211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12314.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709232153 +0000" stop="20250710000925 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E93</episode-num>
    <desc>From “I do” to “I don’t” want to be in this marriage and feel trapped.</desc>
    <date>20060130</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710000925 +0000" stop="20250710005737 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lazy &amp; Entitled Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E68</episode-num>
    <desc>Tracy says her daughter, Ashley, 22, and Ashley’s boyfriend, Andrew, 23, are freeloaders who are living rent-free in her home, while she pays all of their expenses. She says they sleep all day and have let her beautiful suburban home turn to filth. Tracy says she accepts blame for allowing the situation to spiral out of control -- learn the one mistake she says she regrets the most. Ashley and Andrew deny the accusations and say they work part-time for Tracy’s business, and they’ve earned everything she's given them. See what happens when Dr. Phil cameras enter the home. Dr. Phil gets real with Ashley and Andrew -- and Tracy. Can he get through to them? Then, Lorrie and Todd say that their 13-year-old-daughter controls their home. The parents admit that they just can't seem to say no to the teen, who they say throws tantrums and manipulates them until she gets her way. Lorrie and Todd say they prepare special meals for her and cut her food -- and it’s putting a strain on their marriage. Dr. Phil shares his insight and devises a plan to get this family back on track. Plus, tune in to find out the three tips you must know to ensure you're not spoiling your child.</desc>
    <date>20130103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11068.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250710005737 +0000" stop="20250710014420 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Child Molester or Innocent Solider?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E76</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman accused her ex-husband of molesting her daughter.</desc>
    <date>20140207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
