<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722235623 +0000" stop="20250723002709 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded Army deserter shows up at the McCain Ranch desperate for a horse. Lucas takes him in just as the Army Cavalry unit appears to take the deserter into custody. In town, the harsh commanding officer demands he be executed for desertion.</desc>
    <date>19600315</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72419.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723002709 +0000" stop="20250723005559 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark drinks some tainted water from a barrel and contracts typhoid fever. Lucas is forced to use an eccentric old doctor. During bouts of a continuous intense fever, Mark becomes delirious and has a vision of his deceased mother, who he never knew.</desc>
    <date>19600322</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723005559 +0000" stop="20250723012631 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lariat Jones, an old friend of Lucas', comes to North Fork to open up a new gambling casino. Jones has an excellent reputation as an honest gambler. But when two strangers become his partners, accusations of cheating become deadly for Jones.</desc>
    <date>19600329</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72421.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723012631 +0000" stop="20250723015520 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful headstrong young woman named Marge Crandell doesn't like to be told what to do by anyone. Several men vie for her attention and when Lucas finds her dead, one of the men becomes a prime suspect due to a simple clue, a half-smoked cigar.</desc>
    <date>19600405</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72422.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723015520 +0000" stop="20250723025214 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Incident at Dawson Flats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne comes to town to be in Johnny McIntyre's wedding. Johnny and Lafe, his bride's brother, are celebrating. As Cheyenne arrives, Lafe shoots at him, thinking he's wanted. Tragedy occurs when Johnny accidentally shoots and kills Lafe.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723025214 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Duel at Judas Basin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne, Bronco Layne, and Tom Sugarfoot Brewster battle an illegal gun trader dealing with Indians. Cheyenne's boss, Ian Stewart, puts a down payment on a tract of land that the gun trader uses. Trouble ensues.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Booger goes back to school! On this episode of The Cowboy Way, the cowboys visit the Montgomery Stockyard to research cattle prices and Booger gets bitten by the auctioneering bug. Will his auctioneering classes pay off? Back at the ranch, the guys catch heat from a neighbor when their herd escapes into his field, and a rebellious heifer takes them on one heck of a ride. Misty's brother-in-law, Chip, stops by and gives Cody an earful that his feeding pasture has turned to dirt.  And when the cattle stock market takes a nosedive, the cowboys' million-dollar business partner calls the gang into his office for a tough talk.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The cowboys head west to Louisiana in this episode of The Cowboy Way! The boys hit the road to find the perfect bull for their herd, if Booger's backseat antics don't drive them all crazy first. They discover a cowboy candy store where a famous saddle maker fits Bubba's horse for a custom saddle. Cody gets challenged to a roping contest by some teenagers. And when they accidentally find themselves in the fanciest restaurant in town, the guys test their cowboy palate with fine French cuisine. Escargot anyone? Back home Jaclyn and Kaley try hot yoga for their first and maybe last time, and Misty takes a shine to modeling.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723063115 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogerty lives in a rundown house with his grandson, Woody. Lucas tries to get the old man to send the boy to school. The ladies of North Fork want Woody removed from the home and ask Lucas to help them.</desc>
    <date>19611127</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72473.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723063115 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Famous writer Mark Twain visits North Fork and Mark, who idolizes him, is hurt by his rudeness. Lucas intervenes and discovers the source of  Twain's bitterness comes from personal tragedy. Later, both Marks become friends.</desc>
    <date>19611204</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72474.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723073015 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>They Killed Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frontiersman Jim Bridger spins an incredible tale to a group of settlers, claiming he was once killed by Blackfeet warriors yet somehow lived to tell the tale. They think he's joking, but Bridger soon proves that he really did rise from the dead.</desc>
    <date>20240118</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/49053fbc9fd4e71e781cd495c1e326f2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723073015 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>Brothers in Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When they are ambushed by a Blackfeet war party, Jim Bridger and a lone Shoshone brave must work together to find a way to defeat their common enemy. If they can't overcome their suspicions and learn to trust each other, they may not survive the day.</desc>
    <date>20240208</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/026519c3c1e72d4423485f5f99e1d5d4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723083015 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Real Lone Star Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When young Texas Ranger Ira Aten is having trouble hunting down a ruthless outlaw, he enlists the help of John Hughes, an aloof rancher with an uncanny talent for tracking bad guys. The two men form an unlikely and unexpected bond while traversing the dusty path toward justice. With Hughes' guidance, Aten finally catches up to the outlaw and ends his reign of terror. Along the way, Hughes decides to become a Ranger himself and transforms from loner to lawman. Hughes' adventure with Aten is just the first chapter of a storied career that inspires the popular novel, The Lone Star Ranger. Some years later, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews Aten years later to uncover the real story of the Lone Star Ranger and separate the truth from the fiction.</desc>
    <date>20210418</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/wild_west_chronicles_-_s01.backgroundtitle_14.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723083015 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Bass Reeves: Trailblazing Lawman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping the bonds of slavery, Bass Reeves takes refuge among the indigenous people of The Indian Territory, where he is welcomed into their culture. When the Civil War ends, his new-found tracking skills and fluency in native languages lead to his appointment as the first Black Deputy U.S. Marshal west of the Mississippi River. Though he faces discrimination from his peers, Reeves earns their respect when he accepts Judge Isaac Parker's daunting order to hunt down one of the most ruthless killers in The Indian Territory and bring him back dead or alive. Some years later, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews Judge Parker to learn more about the amazing career of Bass Reeves, who goes on to arrest 3,000 felons, kill 14 men in self-defense, and complete 32 years of service without being wounded.</desc>
    <date>20210425</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c3da2fc3fadb4a20893/12205e3c-98c6-4f6d-ae9e-3adf05f21805thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>John Coffee Hays: A Texas Legend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A Tennessee native, John Coffee Hays heads to the frontier of Texas in the 1830s and signs on as an early member of the Texas Rangers. In 1844, Hays becomes a legend when he leads a small band of rangers in a desperate fight with the Comanche.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ea75d1d7e1e3b687a3332869615bb8a6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown at the Arena</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Only seven cowboys remain, eager for the chance to prove they can win it all. The immunity challenge examines each cowboy's patience and control in a point system challenge. The contestant with the highest score won't have to sweat the next elimination round. When it looks like it might come down to a tie, the last cowboy to ride prevails. In the two-part elimination challenge, the contestants must gather and load a herd into a trailer before racing off to a neighboring field where they must doctor a few yearlings in open pasture. The green team starts strong, but a few wrong moves have major repercussions. On the blue team, a cowboy takes the lead, curious to see if his teammate will sink or swim under pressure. The elimination comes down to two rivals who don't hold back when it comes to letting Trace know why the other should go home. In the end, Trace sends the cowboy whose heart doesn't seem to be in it to win it, but they don't go quietly.</desc>
    <date>20210331</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ee24e0a0312cab5e2e1ea8779fe9e570.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Pride and Prejudice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Buck guides the cavalry to a Sioux camp to release hostages. They find the Sweetwater store owner's wife, Sally, and daughter, Jennifer, who the Sioux kidnapped years earlier. However, their reunion is not a happy one as complications arise.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723123046 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded Army deserter shows up at the McCain Ranch desperate for a horse. Lucas takes him in just as the Army Cavalry unit appears to take the deserter into custody. In town, the harsh commanding officer demands he be executed for desertion.</desc>
    <date>19600315</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72419.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723123046 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark drinks some tainted water from a barrel and contracts typhoid fever. Lucas is forced to use an eccentric old doctor. During bouts of a continuous intense fever, Mark becomes delirious and has a vision of his deceased mother, who he never knew.</desc>
    <date>19600322</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723133032 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lariat Jones, an old friend of Lucas', comes to North Fork to open up a new gambling casino. Jones has an excellent reputation as an honest gambler. But when two strangers become his partners, accusations of cheating become deadly for Jones.</desc>
    <date>19600329</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72421.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723133032 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful headstrong young woman named Marge Crandell doesn't like to be told what to do by anyone. Several men vie for her attention and when Lucas finds her dead, one of the men becomes a prime suspect due to a simple clue, a half-smoked cigar.</desc>
    <date>19600405</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72422.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Incident at Dawson Flats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne comes to town to be in Johnny McIntyre's wedding. Johnny and Lafe, his bride's brother, are celebrating. As Cheyenne arrives, Lafe shoots at him, thinking he's wanted. Tragedy occurs when Johnny accidentally shoots and kills Lafe.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Duel at Judas Basin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne, Bronco Layne, and Tom Sugarfoot Brewster battle an illegal gun trader dealing with Indians. Cheyenne's boss, Ian Stewart, puts a down payment on a tract of land that the gun trader uses. Trouble ensues.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>On this episode of The Cowboy Way, the road trip concludes as the cowboys learn how to round up cattle Louisiana-style. The guys jump into airboats and dodge gators to move a herd out of a marsh.   Back home, Cody brings the boys to the Montgomery History Museum to do some family research, and discovers Bubba shares the same last name as Booger's mother!  Are Booger and Bubba...related? When Jaclyn signs Matthew up for tee-ball, Booger jumps in to coach - and discovers it's probably easier herding cattle than 4-year olds. Kaley and Bubba get the whole gang together for a much-needed day of family fun at the lake.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's a high-flying episode of The Cowboy Way. Misty surprises Cody with the gift of a thrilling ride on an aerobatic glider - only problem is, Cody is terrified of heights! Back on solid ground, some of the herd escapes into a neighboring trailer park. Can the guys wrangle them in before they do any real damage? Jaclyn starts the search for a new family home, but a rough dirt-road stands between them and their dream house. And it's down to the wire for the cowboys' cattle deal as the guys try to find a buyer before their million-dollar herd runs out of grass.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723183015 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun from Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A killer, John Holliver, and his followers come to North Fork looking for revenge. All of the residents are terrified since they ran him out of town five years earlier. Lucas, now acting marshal, realizes that he must face Holliver and his men alone.</desc>
    <date>19611211</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72475.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723183015 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The High Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Two mountain men, Ambrose and Gorwin, come to the McCain Ranch. Ambrose is captivated by Lucas' rifle but Lucas won't trade it. After Gorwin is killed trying to steal it, the family holds Lucas accountable.</desc>
    <date>19611218</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72476.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723192945 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>The Spirit of Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After his fur trapping expedition is surprised by a Crow war party, legendary mountain man Jim Bridger suddenly finds himself in a desperate struggle to rescue his fellow trappers when one of them goes missing, and another is on the brink of madness.</desc>
    <date>20240215</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/dd94ae4b1a978566a19e44664b618bde.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723192945 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>The Fossil Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When bloodthirsty Canadian trappers try to kill him, mountain man Jim Bridger takes cover in an unexplored valley. There, he runs headlong into a family of escaped slaves who show him the huge footprints and fossilized bones of long-dead monsters.</desc>
    <date>20240307</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b53cf81178284d0ba6fcfff0c3a55f5f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723202945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Bill Hickok &amp; the First Quick-Draw Duel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Wild Bill Hickok and his buddy, Davis Tutt, see their friendship fall apart over gambling debts and the affections of a beautiful woman. After Tutt swipes Wild Bill's prized timepiece as payback for a disputed debt, things begin to heat up. Then, when Tutt parades through town with the watch in one hand and Hickok's former girlfriend in the other, Wild Bill's blood begins to boil. Tutt refuses to return the watch, and he continues to flaunt the beautiful woman on his arm. The two men meet in the middle of town to settle their differences once and for all in what will become the very first quick-draw duel of the Old West. Both men reach for their pistols at the same time and fire! In an attempt to separate the truth from the fiction, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews George Ward Nichols, the journalist who immortalized the duel and created the legend of Wild Bill Hickok.</desc>
    <date>20210411</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/v4/episode/8320789/screencap/6085e52eebc37.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723202945 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Susan Anderson: Frontier Medicine Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Freshly-graduated from medical school, Dr. Susan Anderson sets up a practice in Cripple Creek, Colorado, a rough-and-tumble mining town. At a time when only ten percent of physicians are female, Dr. Anderson faces her share of doubters and has a difficult time attracting patients in the frontier town. When miners suddenly rush into her office with an injured boy, she defies prevailing wisdom and decides to save his mangled arm instead of amputating the limb. The risks are enormous. If the boy's arm becomes infected, and he dies, she will lose everything. Years later, Dr. Anderson relives the story while treating Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, who comes down with fever while passing through Cripple Creek.</desc>
    <date>20210502</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c0da2fc3fadb4999833/f1b313ea-4ed8-4367-885e-13101a5fc4fcthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>John Mullan: Roadbuilder of the West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Army officer John Mullan heads west to help establish an important wagon route through the Northern Rockies. But, before he can build his road, Mullan must survive the hardships of the frontier and a dangerous encounter with Yakima warriors.</desc>
    <date>20240505</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/66e868c60340f39f5e729e83/cfe684c1-952f-4f9b-bbbb-7f9fdd64f4c6/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Steered Off Course</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The remaining six contestants battle it out for the immunity belt buckle with an oldfashioned horse race. Two-by-two, they race over rough terrain, ravines, and a pond until the three winners go up against each other to win safety from elimination. Two cowboys bond over their rodeo experience and confide in each other about their past. The elimination challenge tests the cowboys' ability to drive cattle out of hazardous and rugged terrain. Using only the map provided, each team has to locate three stray steers and drive them back to a trailer. The blue team comes up with a smart strategy, but one member grabs the wrong steer, sending the rest of the team searching for a steer they'll never find. The green team works together and creates a streamlined plan that they execute with ease. During elimination, one cowboy doesn't fret throwing their teammate under the bus if the result means staying in the game. Trace sends the cowboy, who acts too much on impulse, packing.</desc>
    <date>20210407</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/951462a43cb02a1797e2e8f1b6e6973e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250723235629 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>The Littlest Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ike struggles with his handicap and is bitter after being beaten by men who take advantage of him. But, when he meets Arthur, a terminally ill boy, his outlook begins to change. Despite his circumstances, Arthur has an undeniable lust for life.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723235629 +0000" stop="20250724002918 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas receives several mysterious threatening notes. He discovers they are being sent from ex-convict, John Beaumont, who is bent on revenge. Beaumont wants Lucas dead since he is the one responsible for his imprisonment.</desc>
    <date>19600412</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72423.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
