<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717231011 +0000" stop="20250718004440 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718004440 +0000" stop="20250718022722 +0000">
    <title>Secure the Bag 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Greed is Lit's first love. Lit lost his uncle, who practically raised him, over money he stole from bank robbers. Lit decides to go back to the house where he lost his uncle, but Lit is hiding a secret. It wasn't just money he found.</desc>
    <date>20230321</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6a3e884449fa2c385f2d2eff37bdb5ed.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718022722 +0000" stop="20250718040340 +0000">
    <title>To Live and Die in DC</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Lance Hill sticks to the street code of DC and is admired by those who crave fast money, who put risk over reward. It's his turn to tell his story... If he lives.</desc>
    <date>20231030</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718040340 +0000" stop="20250718062752 +0000">
    <title>The Green Grass</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When money, success, and power becomes your platform it undoubtedly attracts an audience of onlookers; some of who will stop at nothing to get a taste of the good life. But as the plot thickens and the heat intensifies, Shawn's credibility will most certainly be challenged. He'll need to dig deep within himself to stop his life from spinning wildly out of control. This thrilling drama will test his limits as he struggles to find the balance between who he is and who he imagines himself to be. And in the aftermath he'll count up the cost of The Green Grass.</desc>
    <date>20190504</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0a0f35a895107a571b8a7bc56f8f4a0c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718062752 +0000" stop="20250718081700 +0000">
    <title>The Exit Row</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sasha Dade is dedicated to her demanding, yet comfortable life as a wife, mother and advertising executive near the nation's capital. Clint Meyers is a top selling real estate agent and investor who projects sensitivity and charisma but harbors a methodical dark side. Their worlds collide when a chance encounter on a traumatic flight leads to a deadly obsession.</desc>
    <date>20230328</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6da0c19cf7fd037e049c4c118f51f952.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718081700 +0000" stop="20250718101515 +0000">
    <title>The Break of Dawn</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After leaving an abusive relationship, college student Dawn Monae discovers that her ex has committed suicide. After some time, she meets a man named Keith online, but her roommates suspect that he isn’t who he says he is. Little do they know, he has an agenda that no one saw coming.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e6d579fd1c855263ea471d901bf7011b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718101515 +0000" stop="20250718120137 +0000">
    <title>The 4th Quarter: Legacy</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Aging quarterback, Dallas Hughes, returns to the game in a make or break season, after failing to lead his team to the playoffs and the team has drafted his replacement. Set against the backdrop of Atlanta sports, Dallas must come to grips with his future, while putting the pieces back together of his broken family.</desc>
    <date>20230912</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/61313b9937b8257cd834e59a5bb3b7d6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718120137 +0000" stop="20250718133749 +0000">
    <title>Missing You This Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Carmen’s family has an annual Christmas tradition that supports her neighborhood. When her mother dies suddenly, she looses the holiday spirit, and no longer wants to continue, until she’s visited by her late father’s spirit who encourages her to keep hope alive.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/missing_you_this_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718133749 +0000" stop="20250718151309 +0000">
    <title>A Holiday for Harmony</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jaxon Moore is a struggling arcade bar owner with debt and facing a possible shutdown before the holiday season. When his sister dies unexpectedly in a car crash, he becomes the guardian of his young niece Harmony, who inherited a trust fund from her late mother. Jaxon hopes he can use the trust to save his struggling business, but faces obstacles when Harmony‚Äôs father decides to come back into her life.</desc>
    <date>20240822</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/a_holiday_for_harmony.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718151309 +0000" stop="20250718170203 +0000">
    <title>Rain for Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malik decides to bring his girlfriend home to Houston for Christmas. When she meets his family, they think he is all wrong for her. He meets his grandpa‚Äôs nurse, Rain, and soon realizes the true meaning of love and what he really wants for Christmas.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/rain_for_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718170203 +0000" stop="20250718185419 +0000">
    <title>Naughty or Nice</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Melody, an exotic dancer, and her doctor boyfriend, Patrick, prepare to spend the holidays with Patrick’s family. When they arrive, they are met by Patrick’s overprotective judgmental mother, and she unleashes her wrath on Melody, as she’s not good enough for her son. Will Melody become part of the family? Or succumb to Patrick’s mother’s insecurities.</desc>
    <date>20241101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/1151185c7d0ec1c457cb2415be74c0e2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718185419 +0000" stop="20250718204102 +0000">
    <title>Christmas with da Fam</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malcom proposes to Serenity, she takes him home to meet her family for the holidays. The spirit is alive, until they discover that Serenity’s ex Denzel is living with her family after a house fire. A rivalry develops between Malcolm and Denzel that ends up in a hilarious battle of wits over the holiday weekend.</desc>
    <date>20241105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/Christmas_with_da_fam.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718204102 +0000" stop="20250718225254 +0000">
    <title>Mixed Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aurora wants to enjoy the holidays this year in some warmth and sunshine, and invites her three best friends to Miami for a Christmas trip to remember. When they arrive at their AirBnb, they discover it’s been double booked…by Aurora’s ex-girlfriend and her new partner Axel. They have no choice but to combine their plans, and celebrate the holiday together.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/mixed_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250718225254 +0000" stop="20250719001654 +0000">
    <title>What A Day Before Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nathan and Naomi are at odds about the direction of their marriage, and Nathan‚Äôs reluctance to get in the Christmas Spirit. As an ultimatum, Naomi insists Nathan spend the holidays with her and her family, but it‚Äôs Christmas Eve. Nathan enlists the help of his cousin Keith, and the two embark on a road trip and race against time to get home for the holidays and save his marriage.</desc>
    <date>20240823</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/what_a_day_before_Christmas.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250719001654 +0000" stop="20250719030325 +0000">
    <title>More Than Friends</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Angela, a heterosexual, learns her friend, Tennille, loves her, she is surprised to find that she may feel the same.</desc>
    <date>20220725</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
