<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713223735 +0000" stop="20250714003543 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lC6QNvelSJtOzkzzEC6D6jn1Hh3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714003543 +0000" stop="20250714023053 +0000">
    <title>Boss Moves</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Lena coerces her husband, Crutch, to betray, Kane, best friends become sworn enemies. Locked in a deadly battle of mind games, nothing is as it seems, so make your next move your best move, because it could be your last.</desc>
    <date>20210601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8adc50214856e003d130b8e4d907fa07.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714023053 +0000" stop="20250714035341 +0000">
    <title>Black Girl Magic</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Fall under the spell of these five hilariously talented black women from all walks of life, and all parts of the U.S., in this side splitting stand-up special. Starring NY's Brooklyn Jones, LA's Alycia Cooper, Chicago's Just Nesh, Milwaukee's Kelly Kellz and hosted by Atlanta's Ashima Franklin. Filmed on location live from Punta Cana, Dominican Republic.</desc>
    <date>20220307</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ptY2GqKlFZ9L0XbKEkNr5KlOT6F.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714035341 +0000" stop="20250714054021 +0000">
    <title>Behind Closed Doors</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Stacy is a freshman at a Historic Black College &amp; University. She Meets and falls in love with a Grad Student named Benjamin. He's nice and charming at first. Until he starts to control her and physically, psychologically, and verbally abuse her. Can Stacy get out of this domestic violence relationship before it's too late?</desc>
    <date>20200506</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jrQ1UYaWMhioqvJCcIQYGInxvnK.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714054021 +0000" stop="20250714072103 +0000">
    <title>Behind Closed Doors 2: Toxic Workplace</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Newly hired employee, Joy, has high hopes for success at her new marketing job. Her boss' intentions are anything but professional.</desc>
    <date>20220423</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e62179841baa3cbc4ddd34137ce1263c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714072103 +0000" stop="20250714085109 +0000">
    <title>A Masquerade Trapp</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This pastor is a pimp; hustling through Christian dating apps. His pimp game is strong, and he's loved by all the ladies of the night. Until another pimp's woman leaves him, to be with the pastor. From the pulpit to the strip, pimpin' ain't easy.</desc>
    <date>20230418</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/776100c45056ead1fb5cec81345f299f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714085109 +0000" stop="20250714102631 +0000">
    <title>1-800 Missing</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Driven by the disappearance of his daughter, Kevin, an undercover cop, vows to bring her home. Chicago's missing become his personal mission. He joins forces with his partners, determined to take down the toughest kidnappers and reunite all the missing children with their families.</desc>
    <date>20240702</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714102631 +0000" stop="20250714115651 +0000">
    <title>10 Kilos in the Trunk</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tonya needs to make some quick cash for the holidays, and takes a job transporting cocaine. On the way to the drop-off, her car breaks down in the middle of nowhere. While walking to a gas station for help, she is stopped by a police officer, and arrested for several warrants. Now in jail, Tonya, gets her friend Monica to make the delivery. Monica must get the car fixed, avoid a thief looking to steal the product, and make the delivery by the deadline or both will face deadly consequences.</desc>
    <date>20231101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b4ebaef5665411f71b47d802b0fcadfb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714115651 +0000" stop="20250714132024 +0000">
    <title>Kinfolk</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Eboni, is a hair stylist dreaming of owning a successful salon in her hometown. Her feuding family complicates her plans, but her dedication and drive, along with the support of her half-siblings Beau and Hillary. Meanwhile, their estranged father's attempts to reconcile with his past create further challenges.</desc>
    <date>20241226</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/28234f7f264f2aeaba60eb48e2c9253b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714132024 +0000" stop="20250714144828 +0000">
    <title>Sugar Daddy Killer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sasha has just ended a relationship with her boyfriend and is looking for a fresh start. Her friend Tonya tells her she needs to get a Sugar Daddy to forget about her boyfriend, and get her bills paid. Sasha starts dating a Sugar Daddy and decides she is going to scam him. When Sasha’s Sugar Daddy wants more than conversation, she is forced to kill him. Now Sasha decides to start killing one Sugar Daddy after the next to get all the money she can.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/afd67bc17632c12e978e583cdc35fb55.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714144828 +0000" stop="20250714161614 +0000">
    <title>Judge Knott</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A father’s horrible mistake causes a lifetime of pain for his children. His son tries his best to live a normal life, but his childhood trauma follows him into his marriage. He must face his trauma head on to break this generational curse.</desc>
    <date>20241107</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f52ec225ad03a9ecdec1c7a62095c974.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714161614 +0000" stop="20250714181837 +0000">
    <title>American Girl</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After an argument with her emotionally abusive step-father, a smart 19-year-old woman from rural Georgia hastily moves to Atlanta with hopes of staying with a friend. Motivated by the social justice movement of 2020, she wants to work for Stacy Abrams and register people to vote. After an argument with her friend, she finds herself suddenly homeless and must survive on the mean streets of Atlanta by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>20230420</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/98b1aecd0dce96fc998b36c99db6edbf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714181837 +0000" stop="20250714200426 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Score</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After starting their new record label, Donica Blair and Shequell Harris have entered a dangerous arena full of guns, lies, and deceit. Now they are racing against time to right their wrongs and save their own lives before they are next in a string of murders. Meanwhile their partner Seven, has fallen victim to the deadliest of them all; the Black widow.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714200426 +0000" stop="20250714214917 +0000">
    <title>Runway of Shadows</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters Ivy and Zara are separated at a very young age due to their father’s deceit. When Ivy and Zara unexpectedly cross paths at a prestigious runway show, the stage it set for a series of mysterious and unsettling events.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714214917 +0000" stop="20250714232346 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714232346 +0000" stop="20250715010007 +0000">
    <title>Troubled Mystic</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tracie is a single mother who meets Corey Daniels, the calculated and “perfect guy” looking for his next perfect family to manipulate by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>20241030</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f7df975ec413ad1c5cde5d61b67b1ef1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
