<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716234531 +0000" stop="20250717003310 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma v. Mom: Custody Battle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E46</episode-num>
    <desc>How do you determine whether someone is fit to be a parent? Should a parent previously ruled unfit by the court system ever be allowed to regain custody? What should you do if your parenting skills are called into question by a family member? Dr. Phil's guests are feuding mother and daughter, Barbara and Nicole, who have been battling for two years over the custody of Nicole's son, Ethan.</desc>
    <date>20081104</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717003310 +0000" stop="20250717012044 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Save My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents, listen up! Your A-student or football champion could be abusing ADD/ADHD medication right under your nose. Dr. Phil alerts you to the latest risky teen trends and gives you advice for knowing what your kids are doing before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>20091103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8023.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717012044 +0000" stop="20250717020718 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Family Secret &amp; Struggle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Eighteen-year-old Atira is being accused of tearing her family apart. Her mother, Yolanda, sister, Alexa, and brother, Stuart, say the young mom is a "lazy slob," who yells, shoves and cusses, and they’re tired of the chaos she creates. Atira admits she’s full of anger but says her family makes no effort to understand her. Is Atira just an out-of-control, bratty teen, or is a dark secret from her past causing her to lash out? When Dr. Phil digs into this family’s history, will Yolanda, Alexa and Stuart begin to better understand Atira? Then, Atira confronts Yolanda for ignoring her cries for help as a child. Where was her mom when she says she needed her most? Will mother and daughter find a common ground on which to rebuild their relationship? Then, former prosecutor Loni Coombs, author of the new book, “You’re Perfect” ... and Other Lies Parents Tell, joins Dr. Phil. Learn about her six parenting tips for effective listening. Plus, find out how a marshmallow can help you learn critical information about your child’s future, and the most important thing Dr. Phil says you must do with your child every day.</desc>
    <date>20130304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717020718 +0000" stop="20250717025306 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Disasters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E54</episode-num>
    <desc>Darcy says that her sister, Jennifer’s, home is in a state of complete chaos. She says Jennifer and her husband, Ralph, have no rules, their kitchen is bare, the electricity is often shut off, and they put their needs ahead of those of their four children -- who are acting out as a result. Darcy says her nephews, 8 and 10, smoke marijuana, play with weapons and recently started a local forest fire -- and that the 10-year-old once wrote a note asking for someone to kill him in his sleep. She says her 12-year-old niece was recently called to truancy court, and her 16-year-old niece is having unprotected sex in the home with her older, live-in boyfriend. Ralph concedes that he’s struggling to provide for his family financially and has made mistakes as a parent, but says Jennifer is to blame, claiming she’s checked out as a mother. Jennifer admits she’s detached from her family, struggles with depression and has trouble maintaining the household. With this family in dire need of a resolution, Dr. Phil stages a no-nonsense intervention. Are Jennifer and Ralph willing to take the necessary steps to save their family?</desc>
    <date>20130524</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11054.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717025306 +0000" stop="20250717034318 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Family Trauma and Challenges</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Shannon, 24, says two years ago, her ex-boyfriend stabbed her multiple times, and she feels betrayed by her mother, Dian, because she didn’t visit her in the hospital. Can they make peace with the past and fix their relationship? Plus, Kasey says she wants her 24-year-old son to stop living at home and playing video games all the time -- but is she part of the problem?</desc>
    <date>20140116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717034318 +0000" stop="20250717043044 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cindy and George Anthony:The Interview</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E402</episode-num>
    <desc>George and Cindy Anthony speak out for the first time about their daughter, Casey's trial.</desc>
    <date>20110913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10402.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717043044 +0000" stop="20250717051553 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Anthonys:The Revelations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E403</episode-num>
    <desc>George and Cindy Anthony discuss differing views on their daughter's trial.</desc>
    <date>20110914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10403.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717051553 +0000" stop="20250717060354 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Anthonys:The Trial,The Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E404</episode-num>
    <desc>The courtroom dynamics of the Casey Anthony trial are examined.</desc>
    <date>20110919</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10404.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717060354 +0000" stop="20250717064913 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Online Girlfriend Faked Her Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E44</episode-num>
    <desc>A married, stay-at-home mom catfishes an unsuspecting man, posing as several different women. Now she faces her victim.</desc>
    <date>20131031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12044.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717064913 +0000" stop="20250717073712 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets, Lies &amp; Regrets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E58</episode-num>
    <desc>What would you do if you found out your spouse was hiding a major secret? Dr. Phil sits down with couples struggling to figure out their next step after learning a deep, dark secret. Joseph and Natalie have been married less than six months and both say they’re very much in love, but a playful game of dress up awakened repressed feelings from Joseph’s childhood, and now he questions his sexual identity. Are his cross-dressing desires just a phase or indicative of lifelong transgender identity? Is Natalie prepared to hear the truth, and can their marriage survive? And, Carrie caught her husband, Ed, in not just one huge lie, but many! Ed has so many secret ex-wives, children and grandchildren that Dr. Phil has to use a dry erase board to sketch out the new family tree! Are his lies marriage deal- breakers, or can this couple start over from scratch? And, does Ed have more to confess? Don’t miss this compelling show!</desc>
    <date>20110309</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717073712 +0000" stop="20250717082511 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Fighting Over the Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E66</episode-num>
    <desc>When you imagine getting an inheritance, will your financial problems be solved or can the money be more trouble than it’s worth?</desc>
    <date>20051129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717082511 +0000" stop="20250717091059 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Pablo’s Other Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E143</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman attempts to confront her cheating husband with his alleged mistresses.</desc>
    <date>20140429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12143.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717091059 +0000" stop="20250717095824 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Discipline Video: Judge Accused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E62</episode-num>
    <desc>A viral video depicting a judge whipping his daughter sparks outrage.</desc>
    <date>20111109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717095824 +0000" stop="20250717104438 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl in the Closet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E79</episode-num>
    <desc>The exclusive interview with a woman who was held captive in a closet.</desc>
    <date>20120206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717104438 +0000" stop="20250717113036 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E132</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil is launching his parenting boot camp and teaching parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7132.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717113036 +0000" stop="20250717121730 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E217</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7217.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717121730 +0000" stop="20250717130434 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E218</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7218.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717130434 +0000" stop="20250717135312 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E219</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7219.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717135312 +0000" stop="20250717143912 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Chelsea Refuses to Grow Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it asking too much for your 20-something child to make his or her own money and live independently? Barbara says her daughter, Chelsea, needs to grow up! She says she’s given her daughter nothing but the best, and all she has to show for it is a lying child who won’t speak to her. Chelsea says she can’t live up to her mom’s “rich bitch” expectations and just wants to be left alone. Mother and daughter see each other on the Dr. Phil stage for the first time in seven months, and sparks fly! Is Barbara surprised to learn the secret Chelsea reveals? Then, Chelsea’s grandmother isn’t immune to her granddaughter’s conniving ways. Learn why she feels used. And, Barbara says Chelsea has spent thousands of dollars of her family’s money, and anytime she earns her own, she spends it and doesn’t pay her family back. Dr. Phil conducts an experiment to see what the young woman will do with $500. You may be surprised by the results!</desc>
    <date>20101105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717143912 +0000" stop="20250717152510 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce That Daughter-in-Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E108</episode-num>
    <desc>When Pierre, his wife, Amanda, and his mother, Yolande, came to see Dr. Phil, the couple complained his mom was a meddling-mother-in-law. Amanda said Yolande never approved of her, and Yolande admitted she wanted her son to be with a more educated woman. Is this family still at odds?</desc>
    <date>20080505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6108.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717152510 +0000" stop="20250717161148 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Isn’t Enough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E42</episode-num>
    <desc>If you think pretty people are immune to heartache, think again. The headlines are filled with stories of striking women who were devastated by infidelity, despite their outward beauty. Dr. Phil sits down with Joey, a husband and father, who says he can’t pass up a pretty face. His wife, Shannon, says he’s slept with close to 100 women since their wedding day. The personal trainer justifies his actions by saying Shannon is overweight and not hot enough for him. Will he get a wake-up call about his cheating ways? Or will his wife take him back yet again? See the shocking text messages to Joey’s mistress, and hear Dr. Phil’s strong message for the hapless husband when a disturbing secret is revealed. Can Dr. Phil encourage Joey to choose another path and look beyond the physical?</desc>
    <date>20101112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717161148 +0000" stop="20250717165800 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate My Daughter In Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Family conflict between a woman and her daghter-in-law.</desc>
    <date>20130207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717165800 +0000" stop="20250717174325 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>16 and on the Path of Destruction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E314</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother describes her daughter's self-destructive behaviors.</desc>
    <date>20131211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12314.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717174325 +0000" stop="20250717183111 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Faking It!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Secrets, aliases, disguises. These are some of the tactics Dr. Phil's guests have used to manipulate people and get what they want. See what happens when these liars and cons are confronted.</desc>
    <date>20070917</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717183111 +0000" stop="20250717191853 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marriage Crisis: Drowning in Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E67</episode-num>
    <desc>Couples who say their marriage is on the rocks due to debt.</desc>
    <date>20081208</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7067.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717191853 +0000" stop="20250717200614 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Lazy Husbands and Cling On Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When you think of negotiations, you may think of corporate boardrooms, but negotiating happens every day " even in your own house. Learn the principles of making a deal, how to compromise to get what you want and the biggest mistakes you can make when buying a new car. Plus, learn the five things you might not realize you can bargain for!</desc>
    <date>20091110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8032.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717200614 +0000" stop="20250717205651 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Child Discipline Done Right</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil blows the whistle on what many parents are doing wrong. Find out if you're guilty of making the same mistakes.</desc>
    <date>20031015</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L2027.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717205651 +0000" stop="20250717214239 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Drunk in Her Classroom?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E422</episode-num>
    <desc>Police say a substitute teacher's blood-alcohol level was three times the legal limit, and video of their encounter in the school parking lot looks like a lesson in bad behavior.</desc>
    <date>20151123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13422.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717214239 +0000" stop="20250717222843 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Spanked My Wife with a Wooden Spoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man makes headlines for spanking his wife with a wooden spoon.</desc>
    <date>20140922</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717222843 +0000" stop="20250717231454 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Husband Spanks Me &amp; I Apologize??</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E301</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with a man who spanked his wife with a wooden spoon.</desc>
    <date>20140923</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13301.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717231454 +0000" stop="20250718000147 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Family On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Suzanne says her sister, Jennifer, is a neglectful parent, and she's considering taking action to gain custody of Jennifer’s three children. Suzanne says when the family's home caught fire, Jennifer saved her daughter's friend's baby and left her own children to fend for themselves. Jennifer's 16-year-old daughter, Alyssa, suffered a broken ankle after jumping from the second story, and her 12-year-old son ran back into the burning house to save his 9-year-old sister. Jennifer maintains she is a good mom, and says there was too much smoke and fire to go back for her kids. Was there more she could have done? Is there truth behind Suzanne's accusations? Then, hear Alyssa's emotional plea to Jennifer. Will it make an impact? Don't miss this compelling, all-new Dr. Phil.</desc>
    <date>20121101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718000147 +0000" stop="20250718004654 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat Ban</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Children kicked off flights, prohibited from eating in restaurants and banned from vacation hot spots -- from parents to patrons, today’s guests all have an opinion about what’s being called the “brat ban” policies that many places are adopting that enforce kid-free zones. Dr. Phil's first guest, Serita, took her 14-month-old son to her local public library, but when the boy became too noisy, Serita was not only told to leave -- she was arrested! Learn how the incident escalated and got both mother and son banned. Then, it made front page headlines when a shopper slapped a stranger’s toddler at Walmart. The man at the center of the controversy speaks publicly for the first time about the incident that landed him in jail. And, Pittsburgh restaurant owner Mike Vuick caused an uproar from angry parents when he banned children under 6 from his dining room. What caused Mike to impose the ban, and has business suffered or thrived as a result? Plus, is banning kids more about banning bad parenting? It's a polarizing question that has audience members at odds. And, find out how to keep your kid from becoming a brat!</desc>
    <date>20110912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
