<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6">
    <display-name>Dark Matter TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/42d62b39-7f22-4113-a8c5-7445f69ca756/dark_matter_tv_logo_dark.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250723234653 +0000" stop="20250724012718 +0000">
    <title>Honeymoon</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A newlywed couple's idyllic country-lake honeymoon descends into chaos.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/143236326-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724012718 +0000" stop="20250724034054 +0000">
    <title>Marrowbone</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A ghostly presence and a lawyer come between four young siblings. They must stand together or be torn apart.</desc>
    <date>20240227</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/139097171-0.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724034054 +0000" stop="20250724053521 +0000">
    <title>We Have Always Lived in the Castle</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Two sisters live in isolation with their deranged uncle following the deaths of the rest of their family. When a cousin comes to visit, family secrets and scandals unravel. Based on the beloved Shirley Jackson novel.</desc>
    <date>20240424</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/143313500-0.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724053521 +0000" stop="20250724071022 +0000">
    <title>SPLINTER</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapped in a gas station by a parasite, a couple and an escaped convict must find a way to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/143236322-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724071022 +0000" stop="20250724090107 +0000">
    <title>V/H/S 2</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mysterious VHS tapes with horrific contents are found in a missing student's abandoned house.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/143236316-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724090107 +0000" stop="20250724105505 +0000">
    <title>The Golem</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A mystical woman must save her village from invaders, but the entity she conjures to protect them is a far greater evil.</desc>
    <date>20230918</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/127017486-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724105505 +0000" stop="20250724115101 +0000">
    <title>Jo AKA Cop Crime Scene Paris</title>
    <sub-title>The Catacombes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jo' takes the audience behind the scenes of Paris’ most iconic locations, as we follow St-Clair in his relentless pursuit of justice. Brilliant and brutal, St-Clair must outwit pathological killers to solve the most shocking murders: a supermodel is thrown off the Eiffel Tower; a child-killer is found tortured to death in the doorway of Notre Dame; an heiress is brutalized during a sex romp at The Hôtel de Crillon; a jeweler is burned to death on Place Vendôme; a Sorbonne professor is poisoned in front of Opéra; a woman hunting Nazi war loot is bludgeoned to death in the Place Des Vosges. St-Clair is partnered with rookie detective Bayard, a good-looking college-educated cop whose by-the-book approach stands in marked contrast to St-Clair’s lone-wolf methods. Supervising them is Commissaire Dormont, a tough-minded boss with a long tumultuous history with St-Clair. Rounding up St-Clair’s team are sharp-tongued coroner Angelique Alassane and the eccentric but gifted forensic expert Nicolas Normand. St-Clair’s personal life is as challenging and dangerous as the cases he solves. American TV star Jill Hennessy (“Law &amp; Order”, “Crossing Jordan”, “Luck”) plays St-Clair’s adviser and friend Karyn, an unorthodox nun who works in the city’s underbelly. St-Clair’s most formidable challenge is his own daughter Adele, a young Emergency Room nurse as implacable as her father."</desc>
    <date>20231109</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/426006/131917104-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724115101 +0000" stop="20250724132403 +0000">
    <title>Aura</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple discover Kirlian Photography apparatus in their new house. Intrigued by the concept of photographing peoples' Auras they unwittingly release an ancient evil. Only the local psychic can help and she knows far more than she reveals.</desc>
    <date>20230829</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/127017599-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724132403 +0000" stop="20250724153627 +0000">
    <title>Arthur And Merlin</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A young Celtic warrior and a hermit wizard must unite to defeat an evil druid.</desc>
    <date>20230922</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/128668286-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724153627 +0000" stop="20250724172604 +0000">
    <title>2036 Origin Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a deadly crash, mission controller Mackenzie Wilson assists an artificial intelligence system, A.R.T.I., to uncover a mysterious object under the surface of Mars that could change the future of Earth.</desc>
    <date>20230830</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/127032294-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724172604 +0000" stop="20250724191522 +0000">
    <title>Encounter</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of friends uncover an otherworldly object in a rural field, which they soon discover holds greater secrets than they could imagine.</desc>
    <date>20230829</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/127017431-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724191522 +0000" stop="20250724200918 +0000">
    <title>Interview With A Murderer</title>
    <sub-title>Part 3: Broken Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Criminologist Prof David Wilson conducts a series of interviews with convicted murderer Bert Spencer, the man suspected of - yet never charged with - killing paperboy Carl Bridgewater in 1978.</desc>
    <date>20200305</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/426006/131917156-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724200918 +0000" stop="20250724215551 +0000">
    <title>Shark Week</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of complete strangers find themselves isolated by a wealthy madman on his island compound. They are forced into a horrifying gauntlet where they must survive a barrage of ever deadlier species of shark.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/184956187-0.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724215551 +0000" stop="20250724234435 +0000">
    <title>3-Headed Shark Attack</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The world's greatest killing machine is three times as deadly when a mutated shark threatens a cruise ship. As the shark eats its way from one end of the ship to the next, the passengers fight the deadly predator using anything they can find.</desc>
    <date>20150104</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/184956189-0.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5eea605674085f0040ddc7a6" start="20250724234435 +0000" stop="20250725013024 +0000">
    <title>Mega Shark vs Giant Octopus</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Strange things are afoot in the depths of the sea. First a passenger plane vanishes over the Pacific Ocean. Then an oil platform is obliterated. Marine biologist Emma MacNeil is dispatched to investigate the phenomena, and, with the help of Japanese scientist Seiji Shimada, she makes a discovery that will rock the world: An enormous prehistoric shark and a giant octopus have been awakened from their icy slumbers -- and they're hungry.</desc>
    <date>20250626</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/425433/185145323-0.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
