<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724235828 +0000" stop="20250725002834 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725002834 +0000" stop="20250725005839 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725005839 +0000" stop="20250725013033 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725013033 +0000" stop="20250725020029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big as Barney - No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029620_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725020029 +0000" stop="20250725023025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Emperor's Contest - Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029621_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725023025 +0000" stop="20250725030027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who - Sweet Treats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for Halloween tonight! Everyone knows what they're going to be for Halloween. BJ is going to be a pirate, Melanie is going to be a cat, David will be a superhero, and Baby Bop is going to be a ballerina princess. Everyone has decided on a costume all except for Riff. Barney tries to give Riff ideas on a costume like a sailor, a firefighter, or a dancer. Riff surprises everyone in the end by wearing a one-man band costume. Then, it's time for the Halloween party to begin! Barney and his friends have fun Trick-or-Treating in the park at night. But when Ramon loses all his Halloween candies, BJ shares his Halloween candies with him.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029622_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725030027 +0000" stop="20250725033026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show - The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029623_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725033026 +0000" stop="20250725040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dream Big - Thats What A Mommy Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching birds fly overhead, Riff begins to daydream of flying. He decides to build his very own rocket ship and fly to Mars. The flight is not exactly a success, but Barney encourages Riff to never give up on his dream. After seeing many moms playing with their kids in the park, Baby Bop is curious as to what makes somebody a mommy. With Barney's help, Baby Bop learns all about what makes mommies so special.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029624_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725040000 +0000" stop="20250725043010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Egg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the kids find a mysterious, colorful egg in the park, Barney takes them on a trip to Kenya to try to find out what kind of animal could have laid the egg. While in Kenya, Barney and the kids meet Ayira who introduces them to many people, cultures, and animals of the country!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029646_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725043010 +0000" stop="20250725050004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Bird of a Different Feather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Rusty are looking for items for superhero costumes, when Barney comes to life, wearing a tutu. Tracy comes in and explains that she needs to find a bird of paradise for a school project. Ben, unsure, tells her they're only found in Hawaii and what they look like. Barney then takes the kids to Hawaii, using his Travel Book. In Hawaii, they learn different words, how to make leis and even a hula dance. Meanwhile, Ben and Rusty search for the bird, with a few close calls (a feather and what ended up being a coconut). During the Luau, it's revealed that the Bird of Paradise is actually a flower, not a bird. Ben, believing that it was a bird earlier, is shocked to hear that and apologizes to Rusty for getting him caught up in things. In the end, it all ends up just fine.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029647_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725050004 +0000" stop="20250725053007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bonjour Barney!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Emma wants to paint an award-winning painting for the Art In The Park Show, but she isn't satisfied with her artwork. Barney takes her to France to learn how to paint from his friend Pierre. While there, they learn about France. And Emma learns how to paint by following her heart!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029648_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725053007 +0000" stop="20250725055826 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Home Sweet Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Earth Day, a great time for everyone to learn how to help take care of our world, but Ben is wasting paper while BJ isn't too concerned about cutting down a tree to make room for a new playground. After a trip to the rainforest and a meeting with Mother Nature, everyone learns the importance of taking care of our world. As Earth Day comes to an end, Barney reminds us all that taking good care of our Earth is the natural thing to dofor the people we love.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029649_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725055826 +0000" stop="20250725063011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos | Winter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps Baby Bop see that winter can be a wonderful time for fun. Then, when she least expects itthe snow begins to fall! Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029650_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725063011 +0000" stop="20250725070010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo |Boats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. Baby Bop enjoys her homemade boat but wants to ride in a big one. Barney shows her boats on the computer, while BJ and Riff prepare a surprise. When they return, a sailing ship awaits Baby Bop on the playset!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029651_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725070010 +0000" stop="20250725073010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose | Arts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. Barney and the little dinosaurs enjoy an Art Festival. BJ and Riff share some musical art and Baby Bop shares a painting of a very special friendBarney!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029652_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725073010 +0000" stop="20250725080007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movement | Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When some of the children invite Barney to join them for a race, BJ and Baby Bop decide hell need their help. By the end of the day, everyone finds out that there are many fun ways to exercise. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers that as more time that goes by, the more she misses them!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029653_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725080007 +0000" stop="20250725082827 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio | BJ's Snack Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ has a dream after eating too many sweets, where he eats as many sweets as he wants and ends up with a big stomachache. When he wakes up, hes happy to find out it was only a dream. When he asks for a healthy snack, his friends are happy to oblige.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029654_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725082827 +0000" stop="20250725090006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop Til You Drop | Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029655_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725090006 +0000" stop="20250725093006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin' Hood | Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029656_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725093006 +0000" stop="20250725100016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Butterflies | The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is sad because she lost her pet caterpillar, Monty. Barney and the others try to help her find it. Baby Bop is surprised to discover Monty inside a chrysalis. Everyone is excited to find Monty now a beautiful butterfly! Rachel carelessly litters in the park then later has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029657_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725100016 +0000" stop="20250725103015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China | Welcome, Cousin Riff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ receives a letter from his pen pal in China revealing that his pen pal will be coming to visit. With the help of friends, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives. Barney has a tee-rific surprise for BJ and Baby Bop. Cousin Riff is moving to town!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029658_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725103015 +0000" stop="20250725110015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits | Listen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective and a case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is a pet rabbit. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029659_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725110015 +0000" stop="20250725112830 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725112830 +0000" stop="20250725120013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725120013 +0000" stop="20250725123015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big as Barney - No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029620_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725123015 +0000" stop="20250725130010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Emperor's Contest - Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029621_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725130010 +0000" stop="20250725133012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who - Sweet Treats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for Halloween tonight! Everyone knows what they're going to be for Halloween. BJ is going to be a pirate, Melanie is going to be a cat, David will be a superhero, and Baby Bop is going to be a ballerina princess. Everyone has decided on a costume all except for Riff. Barney tries to give Riff ideas on a costume like a sailor, a firefighter, or a dancer. Riff surprises everyone in the end by wearing a one-man band costume. Then, it's time for the Halloween party to begin! Barney and his friends have fun Trick-or-Treating in the park at night. But when Ramon loses all his Halloween candies, BJ shares his Halloween candies with him.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029622_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725133012 +0000" stop="20250725140017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show - The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029623_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725140017 +0000" stop="20250725142823 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dream Big - Thats What A Mommy Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching birds fly overhead, Riff begins to daydream of flying. He decides to build his very own rocket ship and fly to Mars. The flight is not exactly a success, but Barney encourages Riff to never give up on his dream. After seeing many moms playing with their kids in the park, Baby Bop is curious as to what makes somebody a mommy. With Barney's help, Baby Bop learns all about what makes mommies so special.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029624_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725142823 +0000" stop="20250725150015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shrinking Blankey - The Awful Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's blankey seems to be getting smaller; she's convinced it's shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, Baby Bop is growing. When Riff takes a bite of ice cream, he realizes has a very sore tooth. Afraid of going to the dentist, Barney and his friends put on a show to help Riff see there is nothing to be afraid of - the dentist is his friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029625_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725150015 +0000" stop="20250725153016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Blame Game - What's Your Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. Meanwhile, Myra, has decided she doesn't like her name. After learning about many names and what they mean, Barney helps Myra see how special her name truly is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029626_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725153016 +0000" stop="20250725160019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose - BJ the Great</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. When they were in a pretend country of India, they saw a real elephant and in the end, Melanie gets a email from her friend in India (who has also seen a real elephant in India!). BJ wants to be a great magician, but he doesn't want to spend any time practicing. He convinces Baby Bop to help him do a trick, and makes her disappear. When BJ thought she is gone forever, he realizes the importance of practice. Luckily, Baby Bop hasn't disappeared after all!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029627_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725160019 +0000" stop="20250725163018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos - A Visit to Santa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn. Melanie misses the mailman, so Barney takes her to Santa's workshop at the North Pole to deliver her wish list in person.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029628_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725163018 +0000" stop="20250725170020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725170020 +0000" stop="20250725173024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725173024 +0000" stop="20250725180017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725180017 +0000" stop="20250725183016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword in the Sandbox - A Storybook Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel fails miserably when he tries to join the others in jump rope. Convinced that he's too little to do anything right, Barney tells him the story of The Sword in the Sandbox. Through the legend of King Arthur, Daniel learns there are many things he can do... if he tries hard enough.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029632_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725183016 +0000" stop="20250725190021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff to the Rescue! - A Wild West Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Riff is asked to be captain of a baseball team, he doesnt think he can do it. But Barney gives him the courage to try, by recounting the tale of his great-great-grandfather Riffle the Wild West hero!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029633_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725190021 +0000" stop="20250725193022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shrinking Blankey - The Awful Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's blankey seems to be getting smaller; she's convinced it's shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, Baby Bop is growing. When Riff takes a bite of ice cream, he realizes has a very sore tooth. Afraid of going to the dentist, Barney and his friends put on a show to help Riff see there is nothing to be afraid of - the dentist is his friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029625_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725193022 +0000" stop="20250725200019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Blame Game - What's Your Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. Meanwhile, Myra, has decided she doesn't like her name. After learning about many names and what they mean, Barney helps Myra see how special her name truly is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029626_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725200019 +0000" stop="20250725203021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose - BJ the Great</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. When they were in a pretend country of India, they saw a real elephant and in the end, Melanie gets a email from her friend in India (who has also seen a real elephant in India!). BJ wants to be a great magician, but he doesn't want to spend any time practicing. He convinces Baby Bop to help him do a trick, and makes her disappear. When BJ thought she is gone forever, he realizes the importance of practice. Luckily, Baby Bop hasn't disappeared after all!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029627_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725203021 +0000" stop="20250725210025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos - A Visit to Santa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn. Melanie misses the mailman, so Barney takes her to Santa's workshop at the North Pole to deliver her wish list in person.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029628_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725210025 +0000" stop="20250725213028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725213028 +0000" stop="20250725220022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725220022 +0000" stop="20250725223025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725223025 +0000" stop="20250725230029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword in the Sandbox - A Storybook Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel fails miserably when he tries to join the others in jump rope. Convinced that he's too little to do anything right, Barney tells him the story of The Sword in the Sandbox. Through the legend of King Arthur, Daniel learns there are many things he can do... if he tries hard enough.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029632_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725230029 +0000" stop="20250725233023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff to the Rescue! - A Wild West Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Riff is asked to be captain of a baseball team, he doesnt think he can do it. But Barney gives him the courage to try, by recounting the tale of his great-great-grandfather Riffle the Wild West hero!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029633_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725233023 +0000" stop="20250726000026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lights! Camera! Action! - A Movie Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie comes up with the perfect idea to get people to donate to Grace's food drive - put on a movie premiere in the caboose! Barney and friends pitch in to help, but they all have different ideas about what kind of movie to make. Everything they try falls apart. It's curtains for Melanie's movie until she comes up with a blockbuster idea of her own.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029634_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250726000026 +0000" stop="20250726003029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch a Thief - A Mystery Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Detective BJ is on the case when several sports balls suddenly disappear. Determined to find the mysterious ball thief, BJ falsely accuses Riff of being the thief. BJ learns he cannot jump to conclusions and must find the whole story to see who the thief really is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029635_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
