<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250718235710 +0000" stop="20250719014521 +0000">
    <title>Abilene Town</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's the late 1800s and a marshal must stop a volatile and growing conflict between homesteaders and cattle drivers in his small town on the Kansas frontier.</desc>
    <date>19460111</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/68453bdd0e3ae292ef4755d223037323.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719014521 +0000" stop="20250719031805 +0000">
    <title>Gunslinger</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a town marshal is gunned down, his wife bravely returns fire at the gunmen and kills one. The widow is named the town's temporary marshal. At her husband's funeral, she spies the second killer and plans to finish avenging her husband.</desc>
    <date>19560601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/38cd94511c248bd4b7c473763db5c36c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719031805 +0000" stop="20250719040000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Frenchman Cesar Tiffauges, who is used to getting whatever he desires, wants to buy the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges, a sadistic man, abuses his followers regularly with beatings. When Lucas refuses, his son Mark becomes the object of cruelty.</desc>
    <date>19581226</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/onyXhYGUvzOtBMArVgOQviGwdIF.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719040000 +0000" stop="20250719052920 +0000">
    <title>Kansas Pacific</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>With talks of a Civil War brewing, Southern saboteurs know they must keep Northern forces from using the U.S. train system. They devise a daring and dangerous plan to stop and capture a railroad engine, preventing the completion of a railroad line.</desc>
    <date>19530222</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4aa34ddf0ec665128b159785f87dfde4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719052920 +0000" stop="20250719060000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Texas Fence-Cutting War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When homesteaders keep cutting down her fences to access grazing land and water, a widowed landowner teams up with famed Texas Ranger Ira Aten to protect her property. Aten hopes his explosive plan of action will force the cutters to compromise.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6477c2e4a2fc3fadb4cf837f/634d99a9-4a29-4011-81ef-aebbc029d874thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719060000 +0000" stop="20250719062910 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark takes a job on new neighbor Will Temple's ranch but is taken back by Temple's badly scarred face. When a cavalry officer stops by the McCain Ranch looking for a deserter who committed murder, both Mark and Lucas question who Temple really is.</desc>
    <date>19611030</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719062910 +0000" stop="20250719070000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>While repairing a fence on his property, Lucas witnesses a murder. The killer, Corey Hazlett, is the son of a wealthy rancher named Frank Hazlett. When Lucas agrees to testify at Corey's trial, there are threats to harm Mark.</desc>
    <date>19611106</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72470.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719070000 +0000" stop="20250719080000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Annie MacGregor Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While on the trail, Annie MacGregor and her Scottish family's wagon wheel breaks. The family patriarch doesn't want any help until Major Adams' wagon train stops. Conflict arises when they practice their traditions, including playing bagpipes.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-wgn_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719080000 +0000" stop="20250719082945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Train Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Bat Masterson, former gunfighter and sheriff, is now working as a newspaperman. He heads west again to uncover the story behind one of the country's greatest train robberies. Although Butch and Sundance are long gone, Masterson tracks down Sundance's former girlfriend, Etta Place, to draw out more details. To pull off the audacious robbery, they used official Union Pacific lanterns to signal the train and fool the engineer into believing a bridge was out. As Etta reluctantly relives the events of the robbery and its aftermath, it's obvious that she is still smitten by Sundance after all of these years.</desc>
    <date>20210627</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769b32a2fc3fadb4716fff/a906ae0d-cfea-4a80-a544-08b52303e9e9thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719082945 +0000" stop="20250719090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Legend of the Blue-Eyed Apache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When eleven-year-old Herman Lehmann is torn away from his frontier home by an Apache raiding party, he must adapt in order to survive. He soon forgets the life he unwillingly left behind and is adopted by an Apache family. For close to a decade, he lives as a Native American, learning their language and customs. Eventually, he even joins the same type of raiding party that separated him from his family. Though the years pass by, Herman's mother never gives up hope that she will be reunited with her son. One day, she hears a rumor of a blue-eyed Apache now living on a reservation. Could this be her long-lost son? Some years later, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews Herman's mother to uncover the real story of the blue-eyed Apache.</desc>
    <date>20210530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTQxMTU1Y2ItOGQ4NC00OWNjLThmODctYmRlOTE2OGUyOWM3XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719090000 +0000" stop="20250719100000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Hamilton: The Last Mountain Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Coming of age on the frontier, young Bill Hamilton joins Old Bill Williams on an epic adventure during the final days of the fur trade. The last true mountain man, Hamilton's courage is tested when he faces an epic showdown with Bannock warriors.</desc>
    <date>20240407</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a4d2d95a31645642ff8fb6514b9508ae.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719100000 +0000" stop="20250719110000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Snakes in the Grass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>With only eight cowboys left, the competition is neck-and-neck, and everyone has their eyes set on the immunity buckle. The immunity challenge tests their speed and control on horseback in a tournament-style battle, and they go head-to-head until only one remains. Two teammates, who have had it out for each other from the start, decide to set their differences aside for the team's greater good, and to their surprise, they work well together. In the elimination challenge, each team has to sort a herd of cattle by their ear tag colors and drive them into three separate corrals. The blue team comes together to implement a strategy that proves to be effective. The green team makes a risky decision that could cost them the challenge. During elimination, a contestant throws their biggest rival under the bus yet again. Trace sends another cowboy packing.</desc>
    <date>20210324</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e36ccd0acf83e352c138d7d0e4661b58.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719110000 +0000" stop="20250719120000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Moon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A cholera outbreak spreads fear among the townspeople of Sweetwater. They blame a defenseless, mentally disabled boy named Danny, who traveled to town with a medicine show. Now, the riders must protect him from an angry mob of citizens.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719120000 +0000" stop="20250719140000 +0000">
    <title>Abilene Town</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's the late 1800s and a marshal must stop a volatile and growing conflict between homesteaders and cattle drivers in his small town on the Kansas frontier.</desc>
    <date>19460111</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/68453bdd0e3ae292ef4755d223037323.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719140000 +0000" stop="20250719153144 +0000">
    <title>Gunslinger</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a town marshal is gunned down, his wife bravely returns fire at the gunmen and kills one. The widow is named the town's temporary marshal. At her husband's funeral, she spies the second killer and plans to finish avenging her husband.</desc>
    <date>19560601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/38cd94511c248bd4b7c473763db5c36c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719153144 +0000" stop="20250719160000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Frenchman Cesar Tiffauges, who is used to getting whatever he desires, wants to buy the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges, a sadistic man, abuses his followers regularly with beatings. When Lucas refuses, his son Mark becomes the object of cruelty.</desc>
    <date>19581226</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/onyXhYGUvzOtBMArVgOQviGwdIF.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719160000 +0000" stop="20250719180000 +0000">
    <title>The Warrant: Breaker's Law</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal John Breaker and his deputy ride to a town held hostage by a ruthless gang as they transport a prisoner through the West. With the fate of a community at stake, they must decide if they will abandon the town or make a stand for justice.</desc>
    <date>20230508</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/31f4a4ad64a390f247b75fe74659466f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719180000 +0000" stop="20250719182926 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Amazing Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wade Randall comes to North Fork and mesmerizes children with big stories of his past gun battles with outlaws. Lucas suspects he is all talk and exposes the truth after Randall refuses to accept a shootout challenge.</desc>
    <date>19621126</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72505.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719182926 +0000" stop="20250719190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Squeeze Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A land speculator named Willard Prescott contacts Lucas about buying his land as the railroad is fast approaching the area. He bribes Lucas and when he refuses, Prescott makes it clear he will stop at nothing to get his land, one way or the other.</desc>
    <date>19621203</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72506.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719190000 +0000" stop="20250719192926 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of Mark's friends dies due to a shooting accident, he is totally against his father having a rifle. Lucas explains in vain the need for a rifle on the frontier, leading to Mark running away. Meanwhile, Lou has problems with a wanted outlaw.</desc>
    <date>19621210</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72507.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719192926 +0000" stop="20250719200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Anvil Chorus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>North Fork's blacksmith, Nils Swenson, volunteers to fill in for Marshal Micah Torrance while he is out of town. To keep the peace, Nils starts a policy that everyone turns in their gun upon entry to the town. His plan backfires when outlaws arrive.</desc>
    <date>19621217</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72508.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719200000 +0000" stop="20250719210000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>Lucien Maxwell: Legend of New Mexico</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Having explored the frontier with his good friend Kit Carson, Lucien Maxwell is eager to settle down with his family. But before he can establish a ranching empire in New Mexico, Maxwell must first survive a deadly clash with the Jicarilla Apache.</desc>
    <date>20240414</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/accd1e80f00f30e3cbf549ba6a5c17de.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719210000 +0000" stop="20250719212946 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Susan Anderson: Frontier Medicine Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Freshly-graduated from medical school, Dr. Susan Anderson sets up a practice in Cripple Creek, Colorado, a rough-and-tumble mining town. At a time when only ten percent of physicians are female, Dr. Anderson faces her share of doubters and has a difficult time attracting patients in the frontier town. When miners suddenly rush into her office with an injured boy, she defies prevailing wisdom and decides to save his mangled arm instead of amputating the limb. The risks are enormous. If the boy's arm becomes infected, and he dies, she will lose everything. Years later, Dr. Anderson relives the story while treating Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, who comes down with fever while passing through Cripple Creek.</desc>
    <date>20210502</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c0da2fc3fadb4999833/f1b313ea-4ed8-4367-885e-13101a5fc4fcthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719212946 +0000" stop="20250719220000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Billy the Kid: Birth of an Outlaw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Teenaged fugitive William Bonney is given a second chance when a kindhearted ranch owner offers him a job. But when his new employer is killed in cold blood, Bonney reverts to his criminal ways, seeking vengeance and transforming into Billy the Kid.</desc>
    <date>20230413</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6612d5fbf03cec06115541f5/ee6c238f-7845-4c29-8770-de87f6532b4b/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719220000 +0000" stop="20250719230000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Massacre at Gunsight Pass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne travels on a stagecoach to deliver prisoner Johnny Eldorado to Fort Bridger. When an arrogant Russian passenger shoots and kills a Shoshone brave on the way, they must hurry to a relay station to find safety.</desc>
    <date>20241220</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719230000 +0000" stop="20250719233046 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded Army deserter shows up at the McCain Ranch desperate for a horse. Lucas takes him in just as the Army Cavalry unit appears to take the deserter into custody. In town, the harsh commanding officer demands he be executed for desertion.</desc>
    <date>19600315</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72419.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250719233046 +0000" stop="20250720000036 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark drinks some tainted water from a barrel and contracts typhoid fever. Lucas is forced to use an eccentric old doctor. During bouts of a continuous intense fever, Mark becomes delirious and has a vision of his deceased mother, who he never knew.</desc>
    <date>19600322</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250720000036 +0000" stop="20250720014604 +0000">
    <title>The Gambler</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a card shark receives a letter from a distant and troubled son, he travels to rescue the boy and his mother. During a train ride, the gambler meets a friendly, prideful young card player and shares his wisdom.</desc>
    <date>19800408</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/def93a4fafd6565f611db6712634c492.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
