<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250725235724 +0000" stop="20250726014350 +0000">
    <title>Concrete Cowboys</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When two lively cowboys from Montana are set up by a crooked sheriff, they wind up on the run. After arriving in Nashville, the two open a detective agency together and are soon hired to prevent the kidnapping of a country singer.</desc>
    <date>19791017</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8baee413f74e4230f598bbad52b933d1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726014350 +0000" stop="20250726033016 +0000">
    <title>Once Upon a Texas Train</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An outlaw and a Texas Ranger have a life-long personal feud, but now, as grumpy older men, they must put their differences aside and face a common problem - a young gang of outlaws ravaging Texas.</desc>
    <date>19880103</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b151ca7f9af3d348c32dd88121fee7ff.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726033016 +0000" stop="20250726040000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Three-Legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A troubled 18-year-old named Johnny Clover ransacks the North Fork Schoolhouse, stealing art supplies. Lucas later tries to help Johnny, but he lives with a controlling uncle who proves to be difficult to deal with.</desc>
    <date>19590421</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72384.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726040000 +0000" stop="20250726060000 +0000">
    <title>The Last Days of Frank and Jesse James</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When the famous James brothers give up robbing banks and attempt to live as reputable gentleman farmers, they are soon forced to seek revenge on the men who bomb their mother's house, crippling her, and killing their stepbrother.</desc>
    <date>19860216</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7wZ0RsR966ddGx7BWeiZqO2Q727.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726060000 +0000" stop="20250726063006 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark find a young woman named Jennifer and her ill brother, Charles, hiding in their barn. Doc Burrage treats the boy for measles and they take refuge at the McCain Ranch, but soon Lucas learns that she may be a runaway princess from Europe</desc>
    <date>19620108</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72479.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726063006 +0000" stop="20250726070000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gunfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Infamous outlaw Charlie Gordo is in the North Fork Jail waiting for the U.S. Marshal to take him to Yuma for hanging. Micah learns that the lawman is dead, and Gordo's gang is arriving soon. Micah, Lucas, and others defend the jail from the gang.</desc>
    <date>19620115</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72480.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726070000 +0000" stop="20250726080000 +0000">
    <title>Freedom on the Range</title>
    <sub-title>Freedom on the Range</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>From brave lawmen to rugged cowboys, discover the untold stories of African Americans' cultural significance in the Old West.</desc>
    <date>20240711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/23-fast-0046_ottera_deliverables_fotr_1920x1080-tt.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726080000 +0000" stop="20250726082945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Bat Masterson &amp; the Dodge City Dead Line: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman Bat Masterson looks back on his time as sheriff of Dodge City when he and Wyatt Earp worked together to bring law and order to the notorious frontier town. As they struggle to pacify the rowdy cowhands passing through town, the two men draw their own proverbial line in the sand. South of the railroad track that splits the town, they let the cowboys run wild. But on the north side, they outlaw all guns in an effort to create a zone of civility. When a troublemaker crosses this dead line with his gun, it sets off a chain reaction of violence that endangers the town's beloved entertainer, the celebrated singer Dora Hand.</desc>
    <date>20210509</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c95a2fc3fadb4b1514c/0c8513b0-5fe2-48b6-9e66-346e4d9990dbthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726082945 +0000" stop="20250726090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Bat Masterson &amp; the Dodge City Dead Line: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman Bat Masterson looks back on his time as sheriff of Dodge City when he and Wyatt Earp worked together to bring law and order to the notorious frontier town. As they struggle to pacify the rowdy cowhands passing through town, the two men draw their own proverbial line in the sand. South of the railroad track that splits the town, they let the cowboys run wild. But on the north side, they outlaw all guns in an effort to create a zone of civility. When a troublemaker crosses this dead line with his gun, it sets off a chain reaction of violence that ends the life of the town's beloved entertainer, the celebrated singer Dora Hand. After tracking down her killer, Masterson shoots him in the arm as he tries to escape. When the judge learns there are no witnesses, however, he sets the killer free due to lack of evidence, leaving Masterson with a moral dilemma. Does he seek revenge or await the slow wheel of justice?</desc>
    <date>20210516</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769d4fa2fc3fadb4d24a0a/4ebf40f0-fb2a-44c5-ad1b-28c8355bc655thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726090000 +0000" stop="20250726100000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>Lewis &amp; Clark: Captains of Discovery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Under orders from President Jefferson to explore America's vast unknown frontier, Meriwether Lewis and William Clark lead an expedition up the Missouri River in an attempt to reach the Pacific Ocean...a journey no American has made before, and one that may not even be possible. Leaving Fort Mandan after their first winter on the frontier, the Corps of Discovery enters completely uncharted territory. But as the waterways they travel become too shallow for boats, Lewis and Clark desperately seek the Shoshone tribe and their horses. To communicate with the elusive tribe, they rely on Sacagawea, a 16-year-old Shoshone woman, who accompanies the expedition with her newborn son. Lewis and Clark hope Sacagawea will help them trade for the Shoshone's horses, which will provide the only means of crossing the forbidding Rocky Mountains before winter returns.</desc>
    <date>20220310</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d0c4e8348278fcaf46867508ef74373b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726100000 +0000" stop="20250726110000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Every Cowboy for Themselves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The competition takes a new turn now that it's down to the top four cowboys. This time around, there's no immunity challenge, and teams are a thing of the past. Every cowboy stands on their own, and one wrong move could cost them the competition. The cowboys have two shots at making it to the final three with a two-part elimination challenge. In Part One, the first cowboy to rope, drive and load two steers and their horse in a trailer wins. Two cowboys are neck and neck the entire round, but only one comes up on top. Part two's obstacle course tests the contestants' control and handling of the unruly colts they've been training since early on in the competition. But just when the finish line is in view, Trace throws a curveball into the competition that catches the cowboys off guard. While some thrive under the pressure, ultimately, the cowboy that can't adapt in the moment goes home.</desc>
    <date>20210421</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/693acdfe75844db7a99fce79322a5389.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726110000 +0000" stop="20250726120000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem for a Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Cody meets his Western idol, Hezekiah Horn, a writer who is disgusted with the violence of the Indian police and the development of the West. Meanwhile, an unfortunate chain of events creates tragedy for Horn and his son.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726120000 +0000" stop="20250726140000 +0000">
    <title>Concrete Cowboys</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When two lively cowboys from Montana are set up by a crooked sheriff, they wind up on the run. After arriving in Nashville, the two open a detective agency together and are soon hired to prevent the kidnapping of a country singer.</desc>
    <date>19791017</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8baee413f74e4230f598bbad52b933d1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726140000 +0000" stop="20250726160000 +0000">
    <title>Once Upon a Texas Train</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An outlaw and a Texas Ranger have a life-long personal feud, but now, as grumpy older men, they must put their differences aside and face a common problem - a young gang of outlaws ravaging Texas.</desc>
    <date>19880103</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b151ca7f9af3d348c32dd88121fee7ff.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726160000 +0000" stop="20250726180000 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of 5 Mile Cave</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A boy enchanted with tales from the Old West unlocks a mystery that could save their family farm. While his widowed mother struggles to avoid foreclosure, a mysterious stranger arrives looking for a room to rent. A bond with the boy grows as the drifter recounts breathtaking stories of Shooter Green, a legendary gunslinger accused of Arizona's biggest gold robbery. The truth is revealed, along with the secret of the drifter's past when a crooked lawman appears, hot on the trail of the stolen gold.  Past and present collide in this tale of action, adventure and drama. Stars Adam Baldwin (The Last Ship, Full Metal Jacket, The Patriot), Jeremy Sumpter (Peter Pan, Soul Surfer), Jill Wagner (Braven, Christmas Cookies), and Jet Jurgensmeyer (Last Man Standing, American Sniper).</desc>
    <date>20190402</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/58d7ba7730b6084a2f024983b14815ed.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726180000 +0000" stop="20250726182931 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While hunting, Lucas misses an easy shot at a cougar just a few feet away, and seconds from attacking Mark. After discovering that his gun is not the problem, Lucas begins to doubt his abilities with a rifle, leading him to do some soul-searching.</desc>
    <date>19621224</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmQ5ZDJhM2QtNThhMS00NGY3LWE2MjAtOTgxOWU5ZGU3NTU0XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726182931 +0000" stop="20250726190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Incident at Line Shack Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad boss John Gangling runs an operation at Line Shack Six. Gangling pays his men in gold and when he finds that Charlie Been saves his wages in a money belt, he kills him for it. An innocent Indian who happens to stop by is accused of murder.</desc>
    <date>19630107</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72510.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726190000 +0000" stop="20250726192931 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark find Winslow Quince stranded in the desert with a broken wagon wheel. They stop to help, and when they get to North Fork with Quince, many note his gold coin purchases and lavish gifts. Lucas is suspicious, and townsfolk want answers.</desc>
    <date>19630114</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72511.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726192931 +0000" stop="20250726200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sidewinder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gridley Maule comes to North Fork with revenge on his mind and confronts Lucas, who shot and killed his father years ago during a bank robbery. When Gridley tries to get Mark to fight, Micah puts him in jail, and Lou steps in to reform the young boy.</desc>
    <date>19630121</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72512.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726200000 +0000" stop="20250726210000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Hamilton: The Last Mountain Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Coming of age on the frontier, young Bill Hamilton joins Old Bill Williams on an epic adventure during the final days of the fur trade. The last true mountain man, Hamilton's courage is tested when he faces an epic showdown with Bannock warriors.</desc>
    <date>20240407</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a4d2d95a31645642ff8fb6514b9508ae.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726210000 +0000" stop="20250726212945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>John Wesley Hardin: Killer on the Texas Frontier</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When outlaw John Wesley Hardin murders a sheriff, a hard-charging Texas Ranger joins forces with a cool-headed police detective to hunt the killer. The unlikely duo must learn how to work together to end Hardin's reign of terror once and for all.</desc>
    <date>20241113</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/670a3c41fe6af2e62a277013/7197a98b-c172-4453-91ac-a95f7939db9c/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726212945 +0000" stop="20250726220000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Wong Fee Lee Stakes His Claim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Chinese immigrant Wong Fee Lee joins a convoy of miners headed to Deadwood, where he hopes to strike gold and start a business. But when the Black Hills Bandits stand in their way, Wong must find the strength to lead his fellow prospectors in battle.</desc>
    <date>20241002</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/670a3c41fe6af2e62a2771ad/817ef984-b880-4f55-a7a1-479c379f1319/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726220000 +0000" stop="20250726230000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Greater Glory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who endures many hardships but maintains her strong faith in God impresses Cheyenne. With her husband wounded and unable to work, Cheyenne, and Billy the Kid, join forces to help her drive her herd of cattle 50 miles.</desc>
    <date>20241220</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726230000 +0000" stop="20250726233102 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lariat Jones, an old friend of Lucas', comes to North Fork to open up a new gambling casino. Jones has an excellent reputation as an honest gambler. But when two strangers become his partners, accusations of cheating become deadly for Jones.</desc>
    <date>19600329</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72421.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250726233102 +0000" stop="20250727000021 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful headstrong young woman named Marge Crandell doesn't like to be told what to do by anyone. Several men vie for her attention and when Lucas finds her dead, one of the men becomes a prime suspect due to a simple clue, a half-smoked cigar.</desc>
    <date>19600405</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72422.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250727000021 +0000" stop="20250727014430 +0000">
    <title>The Quick and the Dead</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A mysterious stranger crosses paths with a frontier family traveling to the Wyoming Territory. He becomes the family's defender against a ruthless gang bent on taking all they have and robbing them of their dreams, lives, and futures.</desc>
    <date>19870228</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hYxCza930TAoLS04xCtITnDOfZP.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
