<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712000029 +0000" stop="20250712003027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Glad to Be Me - Arts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff has many special qualities, but sometimes, his shyness makes it hard for him to meet new friends. When Barney introduces Riff to some of his friends in the park, its Baby Bop that ends up feeling less-than-special as the kids seem more impressed with Riff and his special talents. Barney helps Baby Bop realize that theres more to being special than the things you can do. The way you feel and the way you make others feel makes you special, too. Its a special day in the park as Barney and the little dinosaurs enjoy an Art Festival. BJ and Riff share some musical art and Baby Bop shares a painting of a very special friendBarney! As the festival comes to an end, Barney reminds his friends everywhere that no matter what kind of art they make, its always special when it comes from their hearts!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029595_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712003027 +0000" stop="20250712010029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movement - BJ’s Snack Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When some of the children in the park invite Barney to join them for a race, BJ and Baby Bop decide hell need their help. They show him several ways to get ready for the big race by warming up and stretching. By the end of the day, everyone finds out that there are many fun ways to exercise. When BJ starts to feel sick after eating too many sweets, he lies down in hopes of feeling better. He has a dream about a snack fantasyland where he eats as many sweets as he wants and ends up with a big stomachache. When he wakes up, hes happy to find out it was only a dream. When he asks for a healthy snack, his friends are happy to oblige.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029596_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712010029 +0000" stop="20250712013026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Counting - Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ and Riff find a pirate map, but in order to find the treasure, they have to be able to count. Since Baby Bop has not learned to count yet, Barney offers to help teach her so she can participate. In the end, Baby Bop learns to count and realizes that feeling good about herself is the greatest treasure in the world! Its time for a music concert in the park. As Riff works on his one-man band, the others make posters for the show. Everyone enjoys Riffs calypso rendition of a favorite song, and they all enjoy helping each other.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029597_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712013026 +0000" stop="20250712020025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pets - Vets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ learns that having a pet is a much bigger responsibility than he ever expected when he offers to take care of a friends dog. When he accidentally loses the dog, everyone has to work together to find it. When Baby Bops favorite teddy bear is torn, she wants to take him to the veterinarian for help. Barney and Riff pretend to be veterinarians. They show Baby Bop that theres nothing to be afraid of, because doctors and veterinarians are our friends too.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029598_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712020025 +0000" stop="20250712023025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Winter - Summer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop is surprised by the first day of cold weather, its Barney that helps her see that winter can be a wonderful time for fun. Baby Bop is getting discouraged, wondering if it will ever snow. Then, when she least expects itthe snow begins to fall! On a hot summer day, Barney teaches BJ about all the fun activities you can do during the summer. BJ gets so excited that he corrals Riff into joining him to do a whole summers worth of activities, all in one day! With some help from Baby Bop and the children, Barney teaches BJ that summer means relaxation, too!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029599_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712023025 +0000" stop="20250712030025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Caring - Rhythm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a very special day at the Parkits Barneys birthday, and there are surprises around every corner. When Barney begins to open his presents, Riff worries that his hand-made gift wont be good enough. In the end, Barney loves Riffs gift and reminds everyone that the best gift of all is one that comes from the heart. Baby Bop is practicing her marching because she will be joining a real marching rhythm band and is having trouble keeping a beat. Barney, BJ and Riff help Baby Bop learn about rhythm just in time for her to join the band.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029600_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712030025 +0000" stop="20250712033024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Games - Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop has trouble following the rules and taking turns while playing games. Barney and Riff help her learn how to follow the rules and Baby Bop learns that rules make games fun for everyone! BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles. When Barney suggests he rest in the caboose, BJ becomes frustrated, as hed rather be outside playing. Barney reminds him of the wonderful world of books, and the little dinos decide to write a book of their ownbased on the exciting true-life adventures of Captain Pickles!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029601_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712033024 +0000" stop="20250712040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making Mistakes - Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>BJs enthusiastic efforts to decorate the park go awry when he accidentally paints the caboose several different colors. Barney helps BJ learn that everyone makes mistakes. Together with his friends, BJ cleans up the mess he made on the caboose. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers she misses them more than she expected and the more time that goes by, the more she misses them! Barney shows Baby Bop ways to keep friends close in our hearts while theyre away.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029602_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712040000 +0000" stop="20250712043002 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All Aboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends transform the task of collecting litter pieces scattered across the park into an engaging game. Among them is Kami, the youngest of Barney's companions, who finds it challenging to keep pace with the other kids, leaving her feeling disheartened. Barney steps in and proves to each friend that their uniqueness makes them extraordinary.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029530_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712043002 +0000" stop="20250712050004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Up, Down, and Around!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Tony excitedly takes his kite to the park to share with his friends, an unexpected gust of wind sends it soaring into the branches of a tree! Barney and the kids revel in the beauty of nature's gifts and sing heartwarming tunes that celebrate all that trees provide. Together, they work to determine how they will rescue Tony's kite from its leafy perch.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029531_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712050004 +0000" stop="20250712053006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Tea-riffic Manners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather in the park for an exciting tea party they had planned, which begins with each of them showing each other the various ways they've contributed, from cookies to decorations. As the day progresses, the tea party proves to be a fun opportunity to reinforce lessons about good manners!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029532_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712053006 +0000" stop="20250712060007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Puppy Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd wanders around the park searching for his dog Bingo, who playfully hides in different areas of the park. Barney and the kids help find Bingo, and subsequently help Mr. Boyd prepare Bingo for a trip to the veterinarian for a checkup. This eventful day gives the kids an opportunity to learn lessons about how to care for a dog.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029533_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712060007 +0000" stop="20250712063012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bunches of Boxes!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are so excited for a day of play and fun! When a bunch of empty boxes arrived from the Enjoy-Your-Toys Company, their adventure begins. They use their imagination to have the best time ever by transforming the boxes into special toys.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029534_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712063012 +0000" stop="20250712070010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Stop! Go!”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After playing with Stop and Go signs with Angela, Baby Bop leaves to direct some traffic of her own. Barney and his friends think of other ways to stop and go and discuss reading, especially traffic signs!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029535_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712070010 +0000" stop="20250712073010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Red, Yellow and Blue!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps his friends put together a Caboose Color Collection which showcases the primary colorsred, yellow and blue. This activity sparks Barney and the kids' imagination, and along with Baby Bop, they realize just how colorful the world can be!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029536_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712073010 +0000" stop="20250712080006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play for Exercise!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are amazed to find out that playing games and having fun in the park is a great way to exercise. When the rain starts to fall, they use their imagination to come up with clever ways to stay active and have fun indoors.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029537_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712080006 +0000" stop="20250712083011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Come Blow Your Horn!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids are full of excitement as five of Mr. Boyd's brass-playing friends are planning a special show in the park tonight! Angela is determined to learn the trumpet, but she finds it challenging. To help them get ready for the band's practice, Mr. Boyd introduces the children to various types of horns, making it a fun learning experience!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029538_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712083011 +0000" stop="20250712090007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A New Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Meet Colleen, Mr. Boyd's niece! Barney and the kids love having fun together every day but making a brand NEW friend is something extra special! With Barney's help, they all learn how to get to know new friends.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029539_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712090007 +0000" stop="20250712093011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Numbers! Numbers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony has a box filled with numbers that he made with his dad and is proudly showing them to everyone. Suddenly, a strong gust of wind scatters the numbers all around! Barney and his friends team up to go on an exciting number hunt, helping Tony find and collect his homemade numbers again.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029540_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712093011 +0000" stop="20250712100018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>This Way In! This Way Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Angela is in the park to release her turtle, Terry, after observing him with her classmates in school. Barney, Nick, and Sarah are delighted to see Terry come out of his shell, which leads to a discussion about the meanings of in and out. Baby Bop arrives with her chrysalis, and together with Angela's turtle, Barney and his friends are inspired to do In and Out activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029541_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712100018 +0000" stop="20250712103015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Into Fun!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a rainy spring day, and the children can be found inside painting and creating. The weather becomes an exciting opportunity for the kids to learn all about the season of Spring and discuss all the fun activities they can partake in this season. This includes flying a kite, riding a bike, and enjoying the rainbows in the sky.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029542_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712103015 +0000" stop="20250712110008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play It Safe!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After feeling tired of being told to be careful, BJ learns that saying be careful is a way of showing love and concern. This important lesson prompts Barney to teach his friends essential safety rules. Spending time with Barney is always enjoyable, but it's also crucial to learn how to play it safe to stay protected and happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029543_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712110008 +0000" stop="20250712113011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Three Lines, Three Corners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends begin the day by playing hopscotchwith a twist. They discover that making a triangle requires 3 lines and 3 corners, which sparks their excitement to explore more shapes. To have even more triangle fun, Barney takes them on a camping trip where they get to explore and learn about different shapes in the world around them.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029544_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712113011 +0000" stop="20250712120010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Parade of Bikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Its the day of the bike parade, but Nick has had a bike accident that leaves his bike in need of repair by Mr. Boyd. Mr. Boyd works quickly to help fix Nick's bike in time for the parade. While waiting, Barney takes the opportunity to teach his friends all about bike safety, making sure they're ready to ride safely and have a great time in the parade!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029545_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712120010 +0000" stop="20250712123013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Happy Day!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids discuss their desire for a special day, Beth creates Happy Day, a special holiday in which each friend makes a wish and the others try to make it come true. When Beth hurts herself, BJ learns the importance of doing good deeds for others.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029546_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712123013 +0000" stop="20250712130016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Family and Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney plans a magical picnic for his friends and their families to spend quality time together and create lasting memories. Each kid has brought a family treasure to show Barney, which they all excitedly spend time sharing with one another.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029547_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712130016 +0000" stop="20250712133013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Splish! Splash!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather at the park, talking about how hot it is and wondering what to do on such a day. Thanks to Barney's brilliant idea, what starts as a too hot afternoon turns into a totally cool day as he introduces them to the wonders of water. Excitedly, they all team up to find creative ways to stay cool and have a splashing good time together!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029548_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712133013 +0000" stop="20250712140014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>BJ's Really Cool House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Even though the park feels like a second home for Barney and his friends, BJ dreams of building his very own totally awesome, completely cool house. While they eagerly wait to see it, they start talking about the different rooms a house can have. However, when BJ forgets to include a space for Baby Bop in his plans, Barney reminds him that family is what truly makes a house feel like a home.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029549_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712140014 +0000" stop="20250712143018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Fountain of Fun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd excitedly tells Barney and the kids about the upcoming arrival of a brand-new fountain for the park! While they eagerly await the special delivery, Barney and the children make the most of their time by enjoying the park's delights. They swing on the swings, admire the beautiful flowers, and create wonderful memories together, all while looking forward to the fountain's grand entrance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029550_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712143018 +0000" stop="20250712150022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>On Again, Off Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The children gather for an exciting game of on and off, which turns into a learning adventure for Barney, Baby Bop, and their friends. They explore all the different ways things can be turned on and off, discovering new ideas along the way. Later, Barney and his friends join forces to help Baby Bop find adorable costumes for her beloved teddy bear, making it a delightful day full of play and discovery!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029551_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712150022 +0000" stop="20250712153022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sharing Is Caring!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the park, Mr. Boyd is organizing a special toy drive to help children in need. When Baby Bop feels unsure about donating her toys, Barney and his friends come together to show her the joy of sharing and how it can make a difference, particularly in someone else's life.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029552_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712153022 +0000" stop="20250712160000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Here Kitty, Kitty!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Whitney introduces Angela to the concept of an animal shelter as she shares an adorable picture of kittens. When Miss Jo misplaces her beloved cat, Cody, she decides to place a lost cat sign in the park to notify anyone who passes by. Barney and the children eagerly join the search. Throughout the search, the kids learn all about cats and the responsibilities of pet care.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029553_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712160000 +0000" stop="20250712163017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon a Fairy Tale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gianna and Kami have a delightful dress-up session, followed by a charming tea party with Barney as their special guest. Meanwhile, Mario announces hed like to write his own fairy tale. In their eagerness to help Mario, the children enthusiastically act out some of their most cherished fairy tales, offering him ideas and inspiration.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029554_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712163017 +0000" stop="20250712170022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Hot! It's Cold!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The children discuss the various ways to cool off on a hot day, especially with a nice cold drink of water or some ice cream. Throughout the day, Barney and the children learn about hot and cold, but the fun really begins when Barney turns the playground into a winter/summer wonderland!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029555_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712170022 +0000" stop="20250712173021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Perfectly Purple Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sarah accidentally spills red paint into the blue paint, a mess turns into a perfectly purple day. The kids use this opportunity to explore the creation of different colors by mixing them together. Inspired by this delightful turn of events, Barney and the kids organize a surprise party for Colleen, entirely centered around her most beloved color: purple.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029556_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712173021 +0000" stop="20250712180024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Day and Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Excitedly recounting her recent sleepover, Beth shares the fun moments she had with her friends at night. After the kids wish to see nighttime, so Barney uses this opportunity to transform the park, and explain the differences between day and night!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029557_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712180024 +0000" stop="20250712183024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play Piano With Me!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stumbling upon Mr. Boyd and Bingo repairing a player piano, Barney recognizes a wonderful chance for learning and exploration with the kids. Excitedly, the children engage in playful games, immersing themselves in the delightful sounds of real pianos and even play a few notes themselves. Through this experience, they gain great knowledge about the piano, all with the guidance and encouragement of Barney and their newfound curiosity.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029558_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712183024 +0000" stop="20250712190024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Picture of Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Together, the kids use their creativity to create a drawing depicting Barney and themselves having a blast playing baseball. After playing a game of imaginary baseball, they bring Barney into the fun. After accidentally hurting BJ's feelings by forgetting to add him to the drawing, Barney and the children learn what it takes to be a good friend. BJ realizes he has many friends and enjoys a day playing with Barney and the children.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029559_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712190024 +0000" stop="20250712193024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A-Counting We Will Go!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids explore the wonderful world of counting by playing a variety of fun games, like Barney may I? Barney and the kids help Baby Bop learn how to count to 10 by including her in games, and by taking her on a make-believe shopping trip in the caboose.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029560_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712193024 +0000" stop="20250712200017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Big Little Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps Baby Bop and the children discover big and little things in the world around them. When Nick expresses his concern about being the smallest among the kids, Barney steps in to demonstrate how each person's unique size holds its own usefulness. When the group heads out to the park, they begin a creative retelling of Jack and the Beanstalk. Barney and his friends discover everyone is special, regardless of size.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029561_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712200017 +0000" stop="20250712203016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A World of Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are excited to show Barney all the international flags they are hanging throughout the Caboose, in preparation for the International Fair in the playground later that day. The children learn all about many different countries, including Brazil and Kenya. They learn about the clothing worn by local people, the fascinating animals that live in each land and they also partake in various activities they might join in other countries around the world.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029562_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712203016 +0000" stop="20250712210018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Your Neighbor?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A make-believe neighborhood in the caboose prompts Barney to teach the kids all about different community helpers. The kids explore all the different roles people have in the community that help them live safely and happily, including doctors, police officers, and teachers. The kids realize its great to celebrate the different ways people help others!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029563_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712210018 +0000" stop="20250712213019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Squares, Squares Everywhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick announces to the group that he has a workbook assignment for school to fill out, which involves finding as many squares as he can around the park. Barney decided this is a great opportunity for him and the other kids to join in, and its great fun when Barney and the kids can help a friend!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029564_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712213019 +0000" stop="20250712220019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Go For A Ride!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the children have fun playing with toy cars. They take this opportunity to learn about buses and cars, including all the mechanics inside that make them similar. After learning about different kinds of vehicles they may see on the roads, the kids build a bus to take them to their favorite neighborhood spots.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029565_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712220019 +0000" stop="20250712223017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>That Makes Me Mad!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Nick accidentally gets white paint on Sarahs picture, the children must find a way to deal with their emotions. Barney helps his young friends find good ways to express and deal with angry and negative emotions.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029566_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712223017 +0000" stop="20250712230017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Your Birthday, Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After an abundance of mail arrives at the Caboose for Barney, the kids realize it must be a very special day. Its Barneys birthday! Barneys friends along with Baby Bop and BJ, put together a stupendous party celebration for him in the park, including decorations and cake galore!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029567_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712230017 +0000" stop="20250712233018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Showtime!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, BJ and the kids spend the day preparing for a very special performance for their friends in the park. They all gather in the caboose to prepare for a stupendous night of singing, dancing, and magical fun.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029568_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712233018 +0000" stop="20250713000017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>At Home in the Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah and Tony create a beautiful birdhouse to place out in the park. They are happy to learn that the birds will have lots of company; many other animals make their homes in the park too! Barney and the kids travel around the park, noticing and discussing all the various animals that call the park home.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029569_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250713000017 +0000" stop="20250713003018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody's Got Feelings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The children realize its normal to experience all different types of emotions. With Barneys help, the children learn all about how to handle how they are feeling, especially feeling happy, sad, and angry.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029570_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
