<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718235624 +0000" stop="20250719004626 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Munchausen Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil takes goes inside the unthinkable: making your own child sick to fulfill a disturbing need for attention. The idea might sound unimaginable, but for people with a psychological disorder called Munchausen by Proxy, it's irresistible. Note: Viewer discretion is advised.</desc>
    <date>20071011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719004626 +0000" stop="20250719013432 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Old Flames</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E70</episode-num>
    <desc>What happens when you can't let go of a meaningful relationship from the past? What are the boundaries when getting in touch with an old flame while you're married? Although toying with old flames can get you burned, it can also be the spark that rekindles lost love.</desc>
    <date>20060113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4070.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719013432 +0000" stop="20250719021932 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Alcoholics, But Great Parents!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Renee and Lee insist their 6-year-old granddaughter is not safe in the care of her parents, Chris and Jessica, because they are severe alcoholics. Despite admitting their alcoholism, Chris and Jessica insist they are great parents, and claim Chris’ parents stole their daughter from them when they demanded Chris and Jessica sign over temporary guardianship of their little girl. Dr. Phil shows Renee and Lee shocking footage of what his cameras captured during Chris and Jessica’s home interviews. After seeing the footage, will Chris and Jessica still stand by their position that their drinking does not place their daughter in danger?</desc>
    <date>20180912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719021932 +0000" stop="20250719030731 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Fighting Over the Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E66</episode-num>
    <desc>When you imagine getting an inheritance, will your financial problems be solved or can the money be more trouble than it’s worth?</desc>
    <date>20051129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719030731 +0000" stop="20250719035523 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lover, My Abuser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah is a pretty, intelligent, successful woman with everything going for her — so why won't she leave her abusive boyfriend, Robert? She says he punches her, chokes her, spits in her face, and has even threatened to kill her, but she believes he can be rehabilitated. Is she in over her head? If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic violence, don’t miss Dr. Phil's exit action plan for safely leaving an abusive partner</desc>
    <date>20120221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719035523 +0000" stop="20250719044116 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Complicated Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E96</episode-num>
    <desc>Craig and Cherie say the last half of their 16-year marriage has been anything but happily-ever-after. Cherie says Craig is chauvinistic, verbally abusive and demands sex, which she admits she only gives him about three to four times a year. Craig says Cherie withholds sex to control him, and as a result, he has become a slave to his anger. Cherie fears the tension in their household is taking a toll on their 11-year-old daughter, who is often caught in the crossfire of their fighting. Dr. Phil challenges the couple to a communication test. Can they heal their wounds and rekindle their romance? Then, meet the couple who inspired the movie, The Vow. Shortly after Kim and Krickitt Carpenter were married, a terrible car crash changed everything. Krickitt lay in a coma for weeks, and awoke with no recognition of her husband. The couple shares their inspiring, though oftentimes heartbreaking, journey of falling in love all over again. How did they find their way back to each other? And what is it like seeing their lives played out on the big screen? If you’ve ever wondered whether love can survive the toughest of challenges, you won’t want to miss this show! This show contains strong sexual content. Viewer discretion advised.</desc>
    <date>20120306</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10096.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719044116 +0000" stop="20250719052806 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Lying Husband (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E45</episode-num>
    <desc>In a three-part series, a man makes a shocking confession to his wife, only after he failed a polygraph test.</desc>
    <date>20071119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719052806 +0000" stop="20250719061354 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s Shocking Confession (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E315</episode-num>
    <desc>In part two, Dr. Phil continues working with a couple who are struggling to stay together after the husband’s shocking confession.</desc>
    <date>20071120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6315.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719061354 +0000" stop="20250719065937 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s Shocking Confession (Pt 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E316</episode-num>
    <desc>In part 3, what started out as a husband’s admitting to a sex addiction turned into a shocking story of murder.</desc>
    <date>20071121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6316.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719065937 +0000" stop="20250719074823 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Gender Confused Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil tackles the sensitive topic of children who identify more with the opposite sex. What do you do if your son wants to wear dresses and play with dolls? Or if your daughter tells you she wants to be a boy?</desc>
    <date>20081029</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719074823 +0000" stop="20250719083748 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Hands Off My Teen Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E47</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie says her 19-year-old daughter's boyfriend, Michael, is a gay, drug abusing gangbanger. What would cause her to have such a negative opinion of him? And is there any truth to her allegations? Learn why Michael initially agrees to a drug test, and then refuses. Will he finally break down and take it? And why does Melanie’s daughter, Caylin, support him anyway, regardless of the outcome? Then, Lori says her 17-year-old daughter, Mackenzie, is obsessed with a boy who's already broken up with her four times. Find out why Dr. Phil has a stern message for this mom.</desc>
    <date>20110221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9047.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719083748 +0000" stop="20250719092406 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Big Time Moochers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E125</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents express frustration with their twin sons' disrespectful behavior.</desc>
    <date>20110519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9125.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719092406 +0000" stop="20250719101112 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Starving For Perfection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Have you ever looked in the mirror and thought, "If I could lose five more pounds, I'd be perfect"? Darlene and Jennifer have been starving themselves in the name of perfection, but are they also killing themselves on their quest?</desc>
    <date>20061116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719101112 +0000" stop="20250719105915 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brandon Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E71</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most asked-about guests, Brandon, returns with an update.</desc>
    <date>20100209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719105915 +0000" stop="20250719114503 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Disasters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E54</episode-num>
    <desc>Darcy says that her sister, Jennifer’s, home is in a state of complete chaos. She says Jennifer and her husband, Ralph, have no rules, their kitchen is bare, the electricity is often shut off, and they put their needs ahead of those of their four children -- who are acting out as a result. Darcy says her nephews, 8 and 10, smoke marijuana, play with weapons and recently started a local forest fire -- and that the 10-year-old once wrote a note asking for someone to kill him in his sleep. She says her 12-year-old niece was recently called to truancy court, and her 16-year-old niece is having unprotected sex in the home with her older, live-in boyfriend. Ralph concedes that he’s struggling to provide for his family financially and has made mistakes as a parent, but says Jennifer is to blame, claiming she’s checked out as a mother. Jennifer admits she’s detached from her family, struggles with depression and has trouble maintaining the household. With this family in dire need of a resolution, Dr. Phil stages a no-nonsense intervention. Are Jennifer and Ralph willing to take the necessary steps to save their family?</desc>
    <date>20130524</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11054.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719114503 +0000" stop="20250719123219 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Paralyzed by Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>No matter how hard we try to protect ourselves, all of us will experience an unexpected trauma in our lives. Whether it's divorce, an illness or a violent attack, each one of us is a potential victim. When misfortune befalls you, how should you react? Will this be something that poisons you for the rest of your life, or will it be something that you adapt to in a way that you can move on? If you're struggling to overcome a trauma, learn to take back control, stop fueling irrational fears and move forward with your life.</desc>
    <date>20090217</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719123219 +0000" stop="20250719132024 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>When In-Laws Cross The Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bloody attacks, arrests, mug shots and undercover stings - Dr. Phil explores these extreme outcomes of in-law conflicts. Meet two wives whose rocky relationships with their in-laws led to criminal consequences.</desc>
    <date>20060919</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5005.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719132024 +0000" stop="20250719140946 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>First Year Marriage Survival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The honeymoon is over! Dr. Phil talks with newlyweds about their troubles, and he and Robin share some stories of how they make their marriage work.</desc>
    <date>20031014</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L2022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719140946 +0000" stop="20250719145709 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Brides</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E76</episode-num>
    <desc>A newlywed wife does not trust her husband. Plus- a follow-up with popular past Shamika and Marlon.</desc>
    <date>20060116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719145709 +0000" stop="20250719154500 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Deadbeat Dads</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Children accuse their dad of neglect.</desc>
    <date>20120220</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719154500 +0000" stop="20250719163140 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Queen Hits Rock Bottom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it possible for a former beauty queen to find sobriety?</desc>
    <date>20120209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719163140 +0000" stop="20250719171929 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>More In-Laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E129</episode-num>
    <desc>It's the invasion of the in-laws! Despite an intervention by Dr. Phil, a couple and their respective mothers still struggle to get along. See how Ernie and Kerry are doing, and what happens when their moms agree to set their differences aside and meet for coffee. Since the last show, Kerry says her relationship with her mother-in-law has never been better! Unfortunately, her relationship with her mother has never been worse. Then, Alaina and Ray are married with two children, and they all live with Ray’s mother, Eda. The two women are constantly at each other’s throats and it's threatening the entire family. Is this household too close for comfort, and will they be able to find a solution?</desc>
    <date>20050908</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3129.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719171929 +0000" stop="20250719180319 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Our Son is a 40YO Homeless Camper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E64</episode-num>
    <desc>41 year old man lives in his car but claims he isn't homeless.</desc>
    <date>20190130</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17064.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719180319 +0000" stop="20250719184921 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Rude Teens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents: If your teen talks back, acts out or is just plain rude, you better tune in!</desc>
    <date>20100909</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719184921 +0000" stop="20250719193638 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Son Picked the Wrong Fiance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E79</episode-num>
    <desc>For the first time, a woman meets her soon-to-be daughter-in-law, whom she has called manipulative, immoral and disrespectful.</desc>
    <date>20130214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719193638 +0000" stop="20250719202053 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Spoiled Rotten Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E126</episode-num>
    <desc>Two moms ask Dr. Phil to give their sons a reality check. Rita says her son, Eric, changed his name to “King Keith” and is forgoing a college education to pursue a singing career. Has he lost touch with reality? And, Cheryl says her college-educated son, Patrick, is lazy and lacks ambition.</desc>
    <date>20120502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10126.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719202053 +0000" stop="20250719210759 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Get Your Act Together</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E52</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil gives family freeloaders a wake-up call.</desc>
    <date>20080117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6052.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719210759 +0000" stop="20250719215615 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Overprotective Moms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The intense behavior of mothers who constantly monitor their children is examined and put to the test.</desc>
    <date>20051012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719215615 +0000" stop="20250719224231 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Broken Family Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sara says her ex-husband, Mark, has brainwashed their three grown children against her, and she just wants to reclaim a place in their lives. Mark and his new wife, Mikel, say they’re afraid of Sara but are willing to face her onstage with Dr. Phil. Can these exes put the past behind them and make peace? And, is Sara’s 22-year-old daughter willing to fix their broken relationship?</desc>
    <date>20131101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719224231 +0000" stop="20250719232925 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Husband Thinks I'm Hacking Our House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Husband accuses his wife of hacking the family.</desc>
    <date>20181001</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17014.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250719232925 +0000" stop="20250720001600 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Russian Hackers or Lying Wife?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E302</episode-num>
    <desc>Is a wife really secretly hacking her own family?</desc>
    <date>20181002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17302.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250720001600 +0000" stop="20250720010338 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mega Moochers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E44</episode-num>
    <desc>Today's guests are sick and tired of a relative's never-ending mooching ways! Will these extreme freeloaders learn to stand on their own two feet?</desc>
    <date>20070110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5044.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
