<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724011104 +0000" stop="20250724015750 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top Health Fixes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E69</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors reveal the best way to get rid of your child's excess mucus. Plus, at-home cures for canker sores, warts and stomachaches. And why surgery might be the answer for droopy eyelids and chubby cheeks.</desc>
    <date>20130111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05069.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724015750 +0000" stop="20250724024447 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Teen Pregnancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The number of teen pregnancies in the United States is skyrocketing at an alarming rate. Learn about the many options for girls who are pregnant, scared and alone. And, see an eyebrow transplant performed live!</desc>
    <date>20081212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724024447 +0000" stop="20250724033135 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Embarrassing Body Questions Answered</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Nothing is off limits as The Doctors address your most embarrassing body problems. Learn why you get tongue-tied at the most inconvenient of times, and how to get rid of back hair. And, what your bowel movements tell you about your health.</desc>
    <date>20091119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724033135 +0000" stop="20250724041742 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Saved My Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman suspects she has thyroid cancer after an episode of The Doctors. Did she catch it in time? Haylie Duff dishes up family-friendly recipes that are good for you! A woman accuses a sex toy company of spying on her! The latest drug danger facing your teen could be found in the gardening store? Plus, could a vodka protect your liver?</desc>
    <date>20161011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724041742 +0000" stop="20250724050414 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fattest Woman In The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E130</episode-num>
    <desc>She was the heaviest woman in the world, tipping the scales at over 1100 pounds … can a new bariatric surgery save her life? Then, the inspiring story of a Saved by The Bell star who started going blind at age 13 and now thinks it’s the best thing to ever happen to him! A breast cancer survivor turns to The Doctors after her reconstruction goes wrong! Can she be healed? And, one of our most infamous guests - “The Sperminator” – is back with baby news!</desc>
    <date>20170329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724050414 +0000" stop="20250724055144 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Grossest Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when you think you've seen it all, The Doctors make your skin crawl in an all new episode. Meet a woman who survived a 51-pound tumor in her abdomen! And, spiders in your ears, parasites in your eyes, fungus on your face - could it happen to you?</desc>
    <date>20121017</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d0338cd40fb07a72f0bf2ea25f784298.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724055144 +0000" stop="20250724063805 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hoarder Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoarder update from social media star Glozell. Skin removal surgery shocker! Eyelid popping! Can fish oil improve your sperm count?</desc>
    <date>20200430</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724063805 +0000" stop="20250724072335 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Cheating Death...With Sanjay Gupta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E40</episode-num>
    <desc>In an emergency, the split-second decisions we make can mean the difference between life and death. CNN’s chief medical correspondent, Dr. Sanjay Gupta, joins The Doctors to reveal what you need to know about life-saving medicine.</desc>
    <date>20091028</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02040.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724072335 +0000" stop="20250724081004 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Unhealthy Lady-Like Habits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E85</episode-num>
    <desc>Women are taught to always cross their legs, never pass gas in front of anyone, and many never leave the house without makeup. The Doctors reveal why these old-fashioned expectations and other lady-like habits can harm your health!</desc>
    <date>20110121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03085.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724081004 +0000" stop="20250724085537 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Health Traps</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E145</episode-num>
    <desc>From hotels to nail salons, The Doctors shine a light on health dangers that lurk in the places you visit most. And, learn which room in your house is a potential fire trap. Plus, Nancy Davis and the fight against MS.</desc>
    <date>20100505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02145.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724085537 +0000" stop="20250724094036 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask The Doctors: Nonstop Urination</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E109</episode-num>
    <desc>“Ask The Doctors” episode. Woman who can’t stop urinating herself! Could you enhance your “manhood” with stem cells? Sleep doctor helps woman who shouts in her sleep! Why do you wake up every night … at the same time? We know why! Hollywood’s hottest plastic surgeons discuss the latest cosmetic trends! Dr. Nita Landry answers all your gyno questions!</desc>
    <date>20180319</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724094036 +0000" stop="20250724102133 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Excess Skin Removal!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A 300-pound weight loss leaves a man with pounds of sagging skin…but you won’t believe what he looks like now! It’s a transformation that will leave you speechless! Plus, a massager to treat C-section pain delivers an unexpected side effect…orgasms? And, speaking of sex, what does your nose know? The surprising link between a chronic runny nose and erectile dysfunction! Then, can the secret to slimming down be found in a sandbox? Dr. Berman puts this new workout to the test! And, find out the one thing killing your diet that’s not diet or exercise!</desc>
    <date>20161003</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724102133 +0000" stop="20250724110715 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Teen Sex Sting!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E90</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman takes justice into her own hands and busts son-in-law who wanted to meet up with her for sex! Dad uses daughter as bait to catch a predator? The Doctors investigates vigilante justice! The Doctors Exclusive: Comedian Kym Whitley in the operating room for her double chin surgery! Decluttering tips from top home organizer. The practical takeaway to get your house back in order! Three great mayo swaps for a healthier lunch!</desc>
    <date>20200129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12090.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724110715 +0000" stop="20250724115353 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Naked Truth About Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors take it all off to reveal the benefits of being in the buff! How well do you know your partner’s body? Learn how to check for lumps, bumps and growths with a life-saving couples’ co-exam. Plus, how to tell if your spouse is faking the big O and more!</desc>
    <date>20120920</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/883bb1fffb033327e3a865b0ac025e21.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724115353 +0000" stop="20250724124028 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Best Treatments From Head To Toe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E135</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share treatments from head to toe. Brooke Burke reveals how to regain your pre-pregnancy figure. And, Olympic champion Steve Holcomb shares how eye surgery helped him win gold.</desc>
    <date>20100426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724124028 +0000" stop="20250724132718 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>LIVE Procedure of "Natural" Filler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E108</episode-num>
    <desc>A new “natural” filler is revealed LIVE on the show! A woman discovers her home has become a beehive and turns to THE DOCTORS for help! Would you choose to stay pregnant for 5 years to avoid maternity leave? THE DOCTORS tackles paid maternity leave. In a THE DOCTORS exclusive, a mom raises awareness about the rare disease turning her daughter into a “hulk baby” … and THE DOCTORS surprises her in ways she never saw coming! Climate control bedding is put to the test! And, are your kids at risk for kitchen burns? Are you making cleaning mistakes that could make you sick? Get the facts!</desc>
    <date>20241017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09108.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724132718 +0000" stop="20250724141229 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Doctors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors teach you how to improve your health sunup to sundown! Find out how to eliminate not-so-fresh morning breath, avoid frustrating razor bumps and make sleepless nights a thing of the past.</desc>
    <date>20090908</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724141229 +0000" stop="20250724145915 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Smile Shame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E124</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman overcomes bulimia, but sees the toll on her teeth. Now she’s so ashamed of her smile, she rarely leaves her home. Can THE DOCTORS help? A domestic violence survivor gets a life-changing surgery! A first date fail leads to a bill? A couple faces charges after using a drone to spy into their neighbors’ homes? The Krazy Coupon Lady reveals money-saving secrets to outsmart retailers! Could yoga be the therapy you need? Find out! Plus, a new app designed to catch distracted drivers in the act!</desc>
    <date>20170320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09124.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724145915 +0000" stop="20250724154546 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Tired? Here's Why</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E42</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling tired and worn down? The Doctors reveal the top four reasons you may feel fatigued -- and none are lack of sleep! Plus, take 10 years off your face without a scalpel or filler! Could it work for you?</desc>
    <date>20121107</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/547fc29b8780c7eddaeed643f4e3991d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724154546 +0000" stop="20250724163252 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Stop Sabotaging Your Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E133</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you sabotaging your body without even knowing it? Learn the hidden dangers in the foods you eat and lotions you use. And, shop smarter with The Hungry Girl, Lisa Lillien.</desc>
    <date>20100402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724163252 +0000" stop="20250724172113 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>No Surgery Nose Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Precocious puberty affects girls as young as 5 years of age. Find out what changes to watch for in your daughters. And, always wanted to have a nose job, but afraid to go under the knife? See Dr. Ordon's no-surgery nose job!</desc>
    <date>20080923</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724172113 +0000" stop="20250724180801 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Easing Your Body Aches</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E72</episode-num>
    <desc>From backaches, to headaches to earaches, learn simple solutions to relieve nagging aches and pains. And, learn a unique and effective way to treat colicky babies.</desc>
    <date>20091210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02072.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724180801 +0000" stop="20250724185416 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Life's Biggest Milestones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E89</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether it’s puberty, menopause or old age, learn how to stay healthy at every age. Plus, get the ultimate guide to treating adolescent acne, and learn how to help your baby take his or first steps!</desc>
    <date>20100122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02089.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724185416 +0000" stop="20250724193953 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health of Guinness Record Holders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a dramatic, jaw-dropping, not-to-be-missed episode of The Doctors! Meet amazing people with record-breaking talents and learn their mind-boggling health secrets. Plus, want to have more orgasms? Find out how from a woman who’s had more than 80 thousand!</desc>
    <date>20120921</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5d00a598dfd7a0d523628b63da8a6e60.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724193953 +0000" stop="20250724202634 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bridal Detox Disaster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Is professional honey trapping a good idea? The bride who had a detox drink disaster! Can kimchi be a cure for baldness? Mystery behind exploding nail polish remover! Visit to nail salon sends woman to E.R.! Can expired sunscreen cause burns? Shocking pictures: man with a golf ball sized growth on his head! Can you get sepsis from blisters? Meet the company founders who embrace integrative work lives! Should you go furniture-free for your health? Find out which apples to eat for a longer life!</desc>
    <date>20191018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12016.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724202634 +0000" stop="20250724211324 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What’s Really in Your Food?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E107</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a shocking investigation that will change your eating habits forever: The Doctors and celebrity chef Rocco DiSpirito reveal what’s really in your food. Plus, the top seven foods that fight fat and make your stomach flat!</desc>
    <date>20120227</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04107.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724211324 +0000" stop="20250724220116 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Valerie Harper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E611</episode-num>
    <desc>In a daytime exclusive, Hollywood legend Valerie Harper, perhaps best known for her iconic role as Rhoda on The Mary Tyler Moore Show, sits down with The Doctors in her first television interview since announcing she's been diagnosed with terminal brain cancer.</desc>
    <date>20130311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05611.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724220116 +0000" stop="20250724224754 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Build Your Best Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E133</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you suffer from migraine headaches? Learn about one surprising cure for your throbbing head! And, getting cavities filled used to be a painful process. Learn about a new, painless procedure that fixes your cavities.</desc>
    <date>20090325</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724224754 +0000" stop="20250724233408 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Waiting Room Confessions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>At the doctor’s office, sometimes the waiting is the hardest part. Get the information you need to know to relieve the anxiety before your next appointment.</desc>
    <date>20101006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250724233408 +0000" stop="20250725002000 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>When Food Becomes Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E44</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors explores a community project aimed at healing the sick – with food! A new discovery could mean a cure for alcoholism? A young mom begins losing her vision after pregnancy? Beauty blogger recommends DIY lightening down there? A dad forced to change his daughter’s diaper on a dirty restaurant bathroom floor – and you won’t believe the photo!</desc>
    <date>20180914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11044.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250725002000 +0000" stop="20250725010642 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Crisis Survival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E109</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you prepared for life’s imminent health obstacles? Learn to manage infertility, how to respond when someone faints and discover the silent killer that takes more lives than breast cancer and AIDS combined.</desc>
    <date>20110302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250725010642 +0000" stop="20250725015340 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Q&amp;A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E48</episode-num>
    <desc>Think a sore throat just means a cold or flu? It could be something much worse — find out! And what you SHOULD and SHOULDN’T’ be taking your pills with. Are you choosing correctly? Plus, banish back fat with an instant fix that’s sure to surprise you!</desc>
    <date>20121115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05048.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
