<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706000525 +0000" stop="20250706004517 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After her emotional testimony and revelation, Sonya is left with no choice but to await the judge's verdict. On the day of Sonya's sentencing, Judge Tortuga gives both sides a chance to present a final argument. Atty. Vega and Atty. Balmaceda close their respective cases by appealing to the sympathies of the court. Meanwhile, Anna uncovers a vital piece of evidence against Jacob. After sharing her discovery with Paco, Anna immediately takes action against her treacherous stepfather.</desc>
    <date>20180222</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s3_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706004517 +0000" stop="20250706012458 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Sonya does not show signs of worry despite being found guilty of homicide. In contrast, a clueless Domeng fears for his mother as she remains imprisoned. Thankfully, Paco's legal expertise proved to be substantial as they are able to file petition for bail. Jacob resorts to dirty tactics to counter Paco. Judge Tortuga's righteousness prevails. Now that Sonya's chances of freedom are stronger, her family and friends pull out all the stops to fulfill her much-deserved liberty.</desc>
    <date>20180223</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s3_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706012458 +0000" stop="20250706020040 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As Sonya finally returns home, her family and friends throw a simple celebration for her temporary release from prison. During the party, Paco receives a surprise anonymous phone call. Taking matters into his own hands, Paco decides to meet up with the mysterious informant in private. Unknown to him, Domeng has been watching his every move. Soon, a series of gruesome events befall on the Alipios.</desc>
    <date>20180226</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706020040 +0000" stop="20250706023722 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Domeng gets shot as he tries to save his brother from Roman's killer. Panicked, Paco's heart condition flares up and he collapses. With both her sons at death's door, Sonya breaks down. The Alipios' loved ones rush to the hospital to offer their support. Anna, caught between her lingering feelings for Paco and current relationship with Archie, is forced to make a choice. Meanwhile, Jacob sets his eyes on his next target.</desc>
    <date>20180227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706023722 +0000" stop="20250706031443 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sonya panics when Domeng suddenly flatlines. The doctors manage to save his life, but Sonya soon learns that Domeng needs to undergo an expensive surgery and Sonya vows to do whatever it takes to save her son. Upon regaining consciousness, Paco immediately informs his mother of what transpired the night before. Seething with anger, Sonya confronts the man responsible for her family's sufferings.</desc>
    <date>20180228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706031443 +0000" stop="20250706035343 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after his confrontation with Sonya, Jacob finds himself on the receiving end of another assault as Anna condemns him as Edward's real killer. Forced to pick a side, Jean chooses the man who has supported her through thick and thin. However, Jean soon remembers the many suspicious happenings surrounding Jacob. Hopeful that Jacob is the good man she believes him to be, Jean tries to uncover his secrets. What she finds, however, shocks her to the core.</desc>
    <date>20180301</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706035343 +0000" stop="20250706042725 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean meets up with Sonya after arriving at a haunting discovery here she reveals everything she found out about her wicked husband, including his plan to run away from his crimes. Having condemned Sonya for allegedly killing Edward, Jean unexpectedly asks her a huge favor. News of Jacob's scheduled departure soon reaches Atty. Vega, who, along with her team, is working doubly-hard to get him convicted.</desc>
    <date>20180302</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706042725 +0000" stop="20250706050355 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean pulls out all the stops to prevent Jacob from leaving the country. Her efforts pay off as her wicked husband goes behind bars. Amid her husband's plight, Jean continues to put on a false front.  Meanwhile, Paco obtains crucial information from a credible witness that could lead to Jacob's lifetime imprisonment. Later, Paco and Sonya learn about Anna's noble act.</desc>
    <date>20180305</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706050355 +0000" stop="20250706070000 +0000">
    <title>Sa Haba ng Gabi</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a zombie outbreak happens, two housemaids and a driver will need to survive their longest night ever as they get trapped inside the mansion.</desc>
    <date>20211029</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/sahabanggabi2x3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706070000 +0000" stop="20250706073550 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Carlos is injured while training Bianca in Batangas. Meanwhile, Gabriel feels torn between joining the triathlon and focusing on his day job. He turns to Lydia for advice. When Carlos learns that Gabriel will be competing, he decides to join the race as well. Later, Gabriel and Carlos get into a heated exchange.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706073550 +0000" stop="20250706080514 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria convinces Roman to attend Carlos' triathlon. However, a sudden discovery prevents her from watching her son's competition. Meanwhile, an unexpected person joins the Villorias to support Gabriel. On the day of the event, Gabriel and Carlos have another heated confrontation. Bianca tries to intervene, but is ultimately disappointed.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706080514 +0000" stop="20250706083330 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Determined to win, Carlos plays dirty during the competition. Gabriel, on the other hand, prioritizes the well-being of his fellow contenders. Carlos wins the race, but Gabriel receives a more meaningful reward at the finish line. Carlos then reminds Bianca of their deal about relationships. Meanwhile, Rigor reveals himself to Carlos.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706083330 +0000" stop="20250706090128 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Roman orders Carlos to fire Bianca as Tiger Shark's endorser. Instead of following his father's command, Carlos hides the truth from Bianca. Gabriel, on the other hand, finally makes his intentions clear to Bianca. Meanwhile, Rigor convinces Victoria to meet with him and threatens to reveal their shocking secret to Roman.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706090128 +0000" stop="20250706093048 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a video of Gabriel and Bianca goes viral, Isabel immediately seizes the opportunity and presents it to Roman. Roman then orders Isabel to bring Gabriel to him. Meanwhile, Bianca learns she is no longer Tiger Shark's endorser. Angry, she confronts Carlos for hiding the truth. Gabriel, on the other hand, meets with Roman and receives a business proposal.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706093048 +0000" stop="20250706095925 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bianca is devastated after being terminated from Tiger Shark, made worse by Jay-Jay’s failing grades. Gabriel and Rigor argue over Gabriel’s rejection of Tiger Shark’s offer. Meanwhile, Carlos finds missing data from Isabel’s report and pitches an idea to Roman, who seems intrigued.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706095925 +0000" stop="20250706102754 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Carlos protests Roman’s decision to hire Gabriel as Tiger Shark’s new endorser. Despite family opposition, Roman has the final say and calls Bianca and Gabriel to his office. Just when Bianca is losing hope, Ambet delivers good news. The next day, during a meeting, an unexpected visitor shocks everyone.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706102754 +0000" stop="20250706105605 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Rigor reveals Ambet's hidden past to Gabriel, sparking another heated argument between them that puts Lydia's life in danger. Gabriel later confronts his coach about the revelation. Meanwhile, Carlos mourns Roman's full takeover of Tiger Shark. Seeing her son's misery, Victoria calls Rigor with an ultimatum.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706105605 +0000" stop="20250706112434 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Determined to win Victoria back, Rigor uncovers traces of Ambet’s dark past, sparking a dispute over Ambet’s credibility as Gabriel’s coach. Meanwhile, Gabriel and Bianca endure intense training. They later meet Roman, who reveals his decision to replace Gabriel’s coach. Gabriel, however, stands firm.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706112434 +0000" stop="20250706120014 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After discovering Cassie’s true identity, Marga becomes determined to fight for her place in the Mondragon household. She wastes no time in imposing her will on the hapless house helpers. However, this does not sit well with Cassie, who remains perplexed by her parents’ sudden strictness. Robert, on the other hand, issues a stern warning to Daniela. Meanwhile, Gino and Jude are growing suspicious of Kulas and Jessa’s closeness.</desc>
    <date>20190102</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706120014 +0000" stop="20250706123626 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Eager to know the truth behind Kulas’ claims, Cassie takes matters into her own hands. Later, Marga tricks Cassie into going to Camila's thanksgiving party after discovering what she did. There, Cassie crosses paths with a ghost of his mother’s past. Soon after, Daniela becomes restless upon bumping into an unwelcome guest at the event. Tensions arise when Cassie attempts to squeeze the truth out of her half-sister regarding Robert and Romina's secret.</desc>
    <date>20190103</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706123626 +0000" stop="20250706131308 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Romina notice that Cassie will stop at nothing to find out what they are hiding from her. Realizing that she and Cassie are growing apart, Romina feels the need to reveal her daughter's true identity. However, Robert insists on taking a long family vacation before dropping the bombshell. Meanwhile, Alvin comes up with a plan to use Cassie to his advantage. After securing a new identity, Alvin applies for a job at Cassie's school.</desc>
    <date>20190104</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706131308 +0000" stop="20250706135011 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert remains determined to take Cassie and Romina to Australia. However, his stubbornness to consider Cassie's feelings only causes more friction between them. Fed up with the worsening tension in their household, Romina decides it is time to talk it out. Marga thinks this is the perfect opportunity for her to win against Cassie. While they are all preoccupied with the Mondragons’ possible migration, Alvin attempts to get closer to his biological daughter.</desc>
    <date>20190107</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706135011 +0000" stop="20250706142618 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Believing that Carlos knows all about her past, Cassie goes out of her way to meet Marga's father. To her dismay, Carlos refuses to give her the answers she wants. Upon learning about Cassie's action, Robert fumes and grows even more adamant to take his family to Australia. This does not deter Cassie from searching for the person who left her the mysterious note. Meanwhile, Savannah catches Daniela meeting with another man and begins to question her dear friend's faithfulness.</desc>
    <date>20190108</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706142618 +0000" stop="20250706150049 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Without evidence to support Cassie's allegations about the cryptic letter, Marga is confident that she will be proven innocent. To her horror, a witness comes in to verify the claims, making her look guilty and no matter how much she tries to explain, no one believes her. Feeling like no one is on her side, Marga grows even more furious at Cassie and vows to make her pay. However, their altercation goes a little too far and results in an accident.</desc>
    <date>20190109</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706150049 +0000" stop="20250706153436 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Encouraged by her mother's words, Marga takes advantage of her influence to ultimately ruin Cassie's reputation. However, the other Mondragon refuses to back down and uses her wits to defend herself from Marga's lies. Robert decides to hire a private investigator to confirm his suspicions. Daniela, meanwhile, is shaken to the core upon finding out that her worst nightmare has been lurking around her family all along.</desc>
    <date>20190110</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706153436 +0000" stop="20250706160824 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After crossing paths with Alvin, Romina deems it necessary to ask him an important favor. This reaches Daniela, who later resolves to get rid of her former ally. Meanwhile, Cassie becomes even more confused about her identity after getting into another altercation with Marga. Failing to contain her curiosity, the young Mondragon confronts Robert. Elsewhere, the Bartolomes discover that the Mondragon patriarch hired someone to investigate Kulas.</desc>
    <date>20190111</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706160824 +0000" stop="20250706164226 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Fed up by her father's excuses, Cassie grows more determined to uncover her parents' secrets. With a little push from Alvin, she decides to search for the root of her dilemma. Daniela, on the other hand, chooses to change gears to keep the skeletons in her closet safely hidden. However, Romina begins to suspect her sudden change in attitude. Meanwhile, Robert gets rattled upon receiving another mysterious note.</desc>
    <date>20190114</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706164226 +0000" stop="20250706183358 +0000">
    <title>All Souls Night</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Shirley is a caregiver and finds herself working for a strange family living in fear of her father.</desc>
    <date>20181031</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/allsoulsnight2x3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706183358 +0000" stop="20250706190000 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sonya and Domeng attend to Asyong and Unyo as the two move into their home. Meanwhile, thinking that the Lamostes have plotted against Gabriel's life, Carolina confronts and assaults Jean. Enraged for meddling with his plans, Jacob then beats Roman.</desc>
    <date>20180104</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s2_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706190000 +0000" stop="20250706193542 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As Sonya finally returns home, her family and friends throw a simple celebration for her temporary release from prison. During the party, Paco receives a surprise anonymous phone call. Taking matters into his own hands, Paco decides to meet up with the mysterious informant in private. Unknown to him, Domeng has been watching his every move. Soon, a series of gruesome events befall on the Alipios.</desc>
    <date>20180226</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706193542 +0000" stop="20250706201224 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Domeng gets shot as he tries to save his brother from Roman's killer. Panicked, Paco's heart condition flares up and he collapses. With both her sons at death's door, Sonya breaks down. The Alipios' loved ones rush to the hospital to offer their support. Anna, caught between her lingering feelings for Paco and current relationship with Archie, is forced to make a choice. Meanwhile, Jacob sets his eyes on his next target.</desc>
    <date>20180227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706201224 +0000" stop="20250706204945 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sonya panics when Domeng suddenly flatlines. The doctors manage to save his life, but Sonya soon learns that Domeng needs to undergo an expensive surgery and Sonya vows to do whatever it takes to save her son. Upon regaining consciousness, Paco immediately informs his mother of what transpired the night before. Seething with anger, Sonya confronts the man responsible for her family's sufferings.</desc>
    <date>20180228</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706204945 +0000" stop="20250706212845 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after his confrontation with Sonya, Jacob finds himself on the receiving end of another assault as Anna condemns him as Edward's real killer. Forced to pick a side, Jean chooses the man who has supported her through thick and thin. However, Jean soon remembers the many suspicious happenings surrounding Jacob. Hopeful that Jacob is the good man she believes him to be, Jean tries to uncover his secrets. What she finds, however, shocks her to the core.</desc>
    <date>20180301</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706212845 +0000" stop="20250706220227 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean meets up with Sonya after arriving at a haunting discovery here she reveals everything she found out about her wicked husband, including his plan to run away from his crimes. Having condemned Sonya for allegedly killing Edward, Jean unexpectedly asks her a huge favor. News of Jacob's scheduled departure soon reaches Atty. Vega, who, along with her team, is working doubly-hard to get him convicted.</desc>
    <date>20180302</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706220227 +0000" stop="20250706223857 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean pulls out all the stops to prevent Jacob from leaving the country. Her efforts pay off as her wicked husband goes behind bars. Amid her husband's plight, Jean continues to put on a false front.  Meanwhile, Paco obtains crucial information from a credible witness that could lead to Jacob's lifetime imprisonment. Later, Paco and Sonya learn about Anna's noble act.</desc>
    <date>20180305</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706223857 +0000" stop="20250706231626 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>As the Alipios rejoice over Jacob's imprisonment, the latter laments on Atty. Balmaceda's incapacity to keep him out of jail. The lawyer proves otherwise by resorting to dirty means to fulfill his client's demand. The move apparently sends Sonya and Jean in utmost disbelief, who are well aware that Jacob has no power to file petition for bail. Meanwhile, Nessa's suspicions pave the way to save Domeng from danger. Elsewhere, Jean gets the chance to finally reunite with her dear Anna.</desc>
    <date>20180306</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706231626 +0000" stop="20250706234928 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob and Insp. Asuncion plot another scheme to kill Domeng. As Domeng is about to be transferred to another hospital, Dindo shockingly takes over the ambulance without anyone's knowledge. Unfortunately for the gunman, Rizalina stays alert and halts his assassination attempt. Sonya grows fearful after failing to get updates regarding her son's transport. Atty. Vega's camp finally discovers the identity of the fake nurse who tried to kill Domeng.</desc>
    <date>20180307</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250706234928 +0000" stop="20250707002518 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Aryann and Tristan help to clear Waldo's name after Gomez drags his name into a scandal. Jenna forms another devious plot as she digs deeper into Waldo and Aryann's past.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
