<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707000000 +0000" stop="20250707003000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Put A Heart In The Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Moving deeper into the build of the Cheetah Evolution, Stacey and the crew pull the skin off this cat and start putting in the guts. Overviews of suspension, steering, and brakes get this project up and running. Moving into the heart of this beast, Stacey shows us that good things do come in small packages—the LSX 454 small block is sure to get your pulse rate up. And once the transmission is mounted, look out! Headers follow, and this cat is almost ready to run. Stacey’s tool tech will give you a lift… all this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150410</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0108.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707003000 +0000" stop="20250707010001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Paws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A road trip, an overview of the Cheetah interior including seat and dash installation, rear lights and a tool tech. The GearZ crew heads out on the prowl to visit a budding young mechanic with a passion for 4X4’s. Back in the garage, Stacey gets in tight with the Cheetah, installing seats and the dash. Selecting gauges and placement are discussed, an AC unit will help keep this cat cool, taillights are fitted, and the side pipes will give this Cheetah some growl! Stacey’s tool tech will keep your project on time and on budget. And Fast Orange cleans more than your hands. All this on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150417</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0109.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707010001 +0000" stop="20250707012959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Beaten &amp; Downtrodden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Auction cars and what you might really find out once the car is in your garage: suspension, brakes and electrical concerns. In the current fad of “flipping” cars for cash, Stacey takes on the good, bad, and ugly of a ’66 Biscayne that was bought at auction. Nice looking paint can’t hide the safety issues that are found once this car is put on the lift. From suspension, to brakes, to battery cables… and even down to the lug nuts, this auction beauty turns out to be more of a beast. Safety and sport-style handling are only a few repairs away this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0110.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707012959 +0000" stop="20250707020001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Automotive Icon Turns 40</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the crew head north to celebrate 40 years of Heartthrob Exhaust and see just how far this company has come since its modest beginnings in a garage. After that we dig into a cracked dash and show how easy it is to replace one yourself with some aftermarket parts from LMC Truck, and then we look at a painless solution will help clean up years of spliced wires and old electrical tape that might be lurking under your hood. It’s simple gearhead stuff that everybody needs to know and it’s only on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150501</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0111.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707020001 +0000" stop="20250707022959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Gets Her Growl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey digs back into the Cheetah project by finishing up the stance with custom wheels and tires, and then goes through the ins and outs of putting a classic Hilborn fuel injection on a modern LS engine… and the dyno numbers show that the engine likes it as much as you will! After that Stacey sits down with a budding car designer that is making a big impact everywhere he goes and there’s also a tip on the importance of seals and gaskets. It’s all about getting out and turning wrenches, and you’re only gonna find it on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20150508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0112.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707022959 +0000" stop="20250707030000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Curves On Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey explores the history of the legendary Jaguar D-type racecar and introduces a D-type Jag from Race Car Replicas that is sure to become a legend of its own. From race wheels to classic spoke wheels with true knock-offs, Stacey looks at options for getting the best look and most rubber on the road with this Jag. A tip might keep you from losing your mind when dealing with lug nuts that don’t want to budge and we talk shop about performance parts for your own cars. So, come hang out while we take on a legendary cat of a different color this week on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20150515</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0113.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707030000 +0000" stop="20250707033001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>New Bed Old Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the crew hit the ground running with a late model replacement bed from LMC that’s sure to revive and old Ford farm truck and get it out of the pastures and back on the highway. Then it’s off to show budding Jeep enthusiasts a couple of entry level options they can use when it comes to modifying their vehicle. We get a visit from a couple who learn how to install new seat upholstery. Stacey’s found something cool for all you second generation Camaro owners. And we’re just getting started! So get ready to turn some wrenches on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20150522</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0114.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707033001 +0000" stop="20250707040002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gearz On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew and Cornwell Tools team up to help a new shop in Arkansas get some much-needed tools to help them take they’re shop the next level. Then Stacey puts together the final pieces of the Sgt. Rock project by making a trip to France and the beaches of Normandy. Then it’s back to the shop to show you how easy it is to put fuel injection on your muscle car. It’s all here… and only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20150529</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0115.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707040002 +0000" stop="20250707043001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Nuts Bolts Building Sgt Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 10 Starts off with America’s favorite military tribute truck! Sgt. Rock is back and ready for final assembly! Garage Guru, Stacey David, takes us on a tour de force of custom fabrication as he covers all the nuts and bolts of what it’s taken to get Sgt. Rock ready to rumble. Builders of all levels are in for a great show as Stacey tackles one of a kind steering columns, gas pedals and designing a console that not only fits form, but also function. Gauge techs will keep your instrument panels in line. And a quick tip will keep your wires from fraying and your hoses from splitting. All this and more as Sgt. Rock and Season 10 hit the road full throttle.</desc>
    <date>20160304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0116.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707043001 +0000" stop="20250707050001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt Rock Interior Other Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A custom build can lose some power if the theme doesn’t stay consistent. Stacey shows how to do that by taking you through the process of how to make door and kick panels that keep the rugged military WWII bomber vibe flowing throughout the interior of Sgt. Rock. After that, its some tips on how to fit a radiator and that all-important cooling fan in a place where space is limited. Finally, the gas tank and battery placement are critical on a custom vehicle and Stacey goes through the steps in doing that as well. If you’ve always wanted to build a custom vehicle, this episode is sure to get your fabrication gearZ turning.</desc>
    <date>20160311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0117.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707050001 +0000" stop="20250707060003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Fish n' Chips</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark takes some time for himself and leaves Daren in charge of the shop. The crew gets the newly painted panels installed on the '70 Cuda 383 Automatic FE5 Rallye Red Car. And Mark discovers a chip on the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car and no one will own up to it.</desc>
    <date>20130319</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E11_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707060003 +0000" stop="20250707070005 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Game Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The fuel and brake lines are installed in the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car. Daren quits and won't return until Mark begins the restoration of his '70 Plum Crazy Challenger. A phone-call from the Phantasm car owner forces Mark to make a promise he might not be able to keep.</desc>
    <date>20130326</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E12_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707070005 +0000" stop="20250707080006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Phantasm ‘Cuda</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The GYC crew is under the gun to get the '71 Cuda 340 Triple Black 'Phantasm' Tribute car finished by the end of the week. With the exhaust, ornamation, and the engine start still ahead of them, will they be able to finish the car before the director of the 'Phantasm' movie franchise arrives?</desc>
    <date>20130402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E13_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707080006 +0000" stop="20250707090006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Back in Triple Black</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the team rush to complete the triple-black, '71 Cuda, Phantasm homage car. The director and star of Phantasm, Don Coscarelli and A. Michael Baldwin, visit Graveyard Carz to check out the homage car and hopefully, drive it around town.</desc>
    <date>20140107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707090006 +0000" stop="20250707100007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>AAR You Ready for This?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The team tears down Mike Hill's '70 Superbird and finishes up final touches on Chris Driscoll's '70 AAR Cuda. Daren confronts Mark about stealing parts from his car and Mark gets a rematch on Chris Driscoll's race track.</desc>
    <date>20140114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707100007 +0000" stop="20250707110006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Go for It!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Holly asks Mark if she can work on cars. Mark Cain from Bad Boy Blasters brings the crew a huge gift. The '70 Barracuda Convertible is torn down and sent to the dipper, progress is made on the '70 Sunroof Challenger and Mark gets a surprise from one of his favorite actors.</desc>
    <date>20140121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707110006 +0000" stop="20250707120007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Get Your Hands Dirty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark installs the hood decal on the '70 Sunroof Challenger, Holly helps Josh disassemble the Barracuda suspension, Mark and Daren work on the 440 engine for the Challenger, and the team assembles one of the rarest Mopar options, the sunroof for the '70 Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20140128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707120007 +0000" stop="20250707130007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>W-O-M-A-N, Mark Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The team rushes to ready the '69 Dodge Daytona for Tom Partridge and his family's visit. The guys settle a leadership dispute the old fashioned way, the Graveyard Carz van gets a face lift, and Daren retaliates when Mark won't let him sign for deliveries.</desc>
    <date>20140204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707130007 +0000" stop="20250707140010 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Pop Secrets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Holly helps Mark on the '70 Challenger, Daren annoys everyone with his popcorn and causes Mark to damage a very rare car. Tony D'Agostino, from Tony's Mopar Parts, visits and lends a hand on the '70 sunroof Challenger. Mark lets Holly in on the big secret and Daren reveals a secret of his own.</desc>
    <date>20140211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707140010 +0000" stop="20250707150009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Let the Sunshine In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark gets a portable showroom, the '70 Hemi Charger is dissembled and the team finishes the 1970 Sunroof Challenger. Mark finally reveals his big secret project to the Graveyard Carz team and Royal makes a video tribute to the Sunroof Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20140218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707150009 +0000" stop="20250707160009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Royal Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the ghouls build out the 440 Super Commando engine for their '70 Plymouth Superbird and install the suspension for the '69 Daytona Charger. Daren finally has enough of Mark's foolishness.</desc>
    <date>20140225</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707160009 +0000" stop="20250707170010 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Grand Torino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Body man Derrick becomes an official Graveyard Carz crew member and assists in the disassembly of the rare '67 Plymouth Hemi GTX Convertible. Josh and Daren play "the game" with Mark.</desc>
    <date>20140304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707170010 +0000" stop="20250707180011 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Waltons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the Ghoulz get a massive sheet-metal order from AMD for their '70 Plymouth Superbird. Meanwhile, the owners of the '72 Charger visit and talk about what made their car so special. Daren gets the offer of a lifetime on his '70 Challenger R/T.</desc>
    <date>20140311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707180011 +0000" stop="20250707190013 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>It's the Great Pumpkin, Goldberg!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a Moparween at Graveyard Carz! Just when things couldn't get crazier, Bill Goldberg shows up to go over his '68 GTX Convertible and knock some sense into the guys. He can handle the NFL and the WCW, but can he hold his own at GYC?</desc>
    <date>20140318</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E11_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707190013 +0000" stop="20250707200014 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Daytona Reborn Pt. 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is behind on his promise to get Tom Partidge's '69 Daytona Charger finished by the end of the month. The crew kicks into high gear to get Tom's Daytona looking great and out the door.</desc>
    <date>20140325</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E12_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707200014 +0000" stop="20250707210015 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Daytona Reborn Pt. 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is behind on his promise to get Tom Partridge's '69 Daytona Charger finished by the end of the month. The crew bands together to do whatever is necessary to fulfill Mark's promise to the owner and bring it back to life.</desc>
    <date>20140401</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E13_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707210015 +0000" stop="20250707220016 +0000">
    <title>Top 10 Mopar Muscle Moments</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ghoulz pay tribute to their favorite moments over the previous seasons. This special episode looks back over seasons 1-3 of Graveyard Carz, but includes all new interviews to highlight some previously unrevealed details.</desc>
    <date>20140731</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S04_E00_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707220016 +0000" stop="20250707230015 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Elephant in the Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A 1970 Dodge Charger engine is restored in this Special episode.</desc>
    <date>20140731</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S04_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250707230015 +0000" stop="20250708000000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Daren and Royal Go Topless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A rare 1970 Charger and a 1970 Barracuda 383 are featured.</desc>
    <date>20141118</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S04_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>General Disassemble Lee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A 1968 Charger, a 1970 Challenger R/T, and a 1969 Charger are featured.</desc>
    <date>20141125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S04_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
