<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817">
    <display-name>Waypoint TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/waypointtv_logo_dark.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709005959 +0000" stop="20250709013001 +0000">
    <title>The Green Way Outdoors</title>
    <sub-title>"Alaska Sockeye Salmon"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Green Way Outdoors team heads to Alaska to target sockeye salmon. The beautiful color of these harvested fillets will blow your mind.</desc>
    <date>20250401</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709013001 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title>The Reel American Road Trip</title>
    <sub-title>"The Manistee River with Koz and Crystal River"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Danny tries his hand at being a guide on the Manistee River with Koz. Then later Danny tries his fly fishing skills on the Crystal River to see if he can land a monster salmon on the fly.</desc>
    <date>20250106</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709023001 +0000">
    <title>Stomping Grounds</title>
    <sub-title>"Florida' Highway on the Water"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>From country music star Brian Kelley’s big 56’ Sunny Briggs Sportfishing Yacht, to getting caught in a storm aboard a small Hurricane deck boat in the Gulf of Mexico, this episode of Stomping Grounds has host Ryan McVinney exploring boat culture in Florida’s Panhandle region, from the Emerald Coast to The Big Bend and the Forgotten Coast. Brian Kelley, aka “Beach Cowboy”, or BK for short, makes up one half of the country music group Florida Georgia Line (FGL) and has just released his own solo album Sunshine State of Mind. Kelley invites viewers aboard his vessel the “Brittney Marie” which was named after his wife, for a look at the couple’s Stomping Grounds. Songs from his album play on the boat’s sound system - including a tune about shopping for a boat on Boat Trader</desc>
    <date>20220407</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709023001 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Exploring New York City's Hidden Culinary Gems: Cooking Goat Brains, Lobster &amp; MORE"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>New. York. City. That’s where our host Josh Rosen kicks off his journey in Episode 4—and where he lived for 16 years and started up the surf-centric apparel brand, Saturdays NYC. Back in his old stomping grounds, Josh first meets up with the award-winning chef and Mumbai native, Chintan Pandya, currently blowing up the New York food scene with his unapologetic and authentic Indian cuisine (pro tip: try the goat brains). Next, Josh travels through the boroughs, heads upstate, and along the coast to source local ingredients—from sake brewers and pig farmers to catching fresh lobster just 100 miles from Wall Street. As always the adventure will end with a feast, right back in Chintan’s kitchen.</desc>
    <date>20240604</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709033001 +0000">
    <title>Duck Camp Dinners</title>
    <sub-title>"In a Camp Down by the River"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Duck Camp Dinners crew leaves the bayous and heads down river to Venice, Louisiana where they prepare for their first duck hunt in the delta.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709033001 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title>Goin' Coastal</title>
    <sub-title>"Two Georges Marina"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and George from Two Georges Marina battle the wind and tide on a tough day of fishing which leads Josh to fish another day, solely for revenge on the Sheepshead!</desc>
    <date>20240507</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709041601 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Lonestar Redfish"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>We find ourselves fishing with Troy from Lonestar Beer.  Not only is Troy a great friend he is also a big supporter of Hunters Extravaganza.  We get to catch up in the offseason and spend a day on the water discussing future events and reflect on what all Texas has to offer.</desc>
    <date>20231220</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709041601 +0000" stop="20250709043002 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Deer Day"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Follow TTHA President/CEO Christina Pittman and her husband Matt this week as they tag along side Dr. James Kroll for his annual deer day! This is a great opportunity to learn from one of the best. We are blessed to be able to share his knowledge with other like minded outdoor enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>20241010</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709043002 +0000" stop="20250709044602 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Trinity Oaks - Bucks for the Brave"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>We are blessed for the opportunity to follow along the guys from Trinity Oaks for Bucks for the Brave. The men and women that served in  our armed services and as first responders, had jobs that required the, to be willing to sacrifice their own lives every day, in order to protect or save someone else's. Not many of us can say that, nor understand what that truly means. The things they've had to see, and the sacrifices they've made in their daily lives, can have a profound impact on them. Trinity Oaks' Bucks for the Brave platform allows the loved ones and communities that support these heroes to share their stories and unite us all in honoring and recognizing their service to our great nation. We are proud to continue to be a part of this incredible program, getting these heroes in the outdoors for the hunt of a lifetime.</desc>
    <date>20250121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709044602 +0000" stop="20250709050002 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Morrow Ranch"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Follow TTHA President/CEO Christina Pittman and her husband Matt this week as they chase Whitetails at Morrow Ranch.  This is a hunt that they had purchased earlier at the Disabled Outdoorsman in the year to be able to spend some time in the woods.  A few days away to relax and spend quality time with loved ones should always be a priority.  Morrow Ranch is definitely a go to place for low fence Texas hunting.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709050002 +0000" stop="20250709054939 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Getting a Crash Course in Bull Riding, Tex-Mex Cuisine &amp; the Spirit of Texas | DIRT Texas"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Anyone can be a cowboy—that’s the biggest thing the DIRT crew learned in Texas. From riding bulls in Fort Worth to off-roading in the Chihuahuan desert to forging their own path across this vast state with the help of local trailblazers Liz and Lou Lambert. Lucky for us, they even stopped by Huckberry’s own backyard in Austin for a quick ruck and a couple games of chicken sh*t bingo. When the dust finally settled, we fired up the barbecue for our beefiest feast yet and raised our ranch waters high to 10 DIRT episodes in the can.</desc>
    <date>20240723</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709054939 +0000" stop="20250709060008 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand TIps and Gear</title>
    <sub-title>HuntStand Tips &amp; Gear - "How to Attract Trophy Bucks with Cereal Grains"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>HuntStand Pro Contributor Cody Butler runs us through how he plants cereal grain food plots to attract giants for the fall.</desc>
    <date>20241121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709060008 +0000" stop="20250709062959 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest Outdoors</title>
    <sub-title>FinQuest - "Pelagic Playground"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the premiere of FinQuest, freshwater pro Ryan Miller dives into the world of saltwater fishing in Florida. Guided by Alex Burgess, Ryan tackles sailfish and tuna while mastering kite fishing. The adventure continues with his family as they enjoy a thrilling hydrofoil ride in Jupiter, Florida, blending fishing excitement with family fun on the water.</desc>
    <date>20241015</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709062959 +0000" stop="20250709065959 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Clowning with Peacocks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ryan Miller targets exotic fish in Lake Ida with local guide Kevin Cannon in Episode 2 of FinQuest. Catching peacock bass and clown knife fish, Ryan also enjoys family fun with a skimboarding session in Jupiter, Florida.</desc>
    <date>20241015</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709065959 +0000" stop="20250709073000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Ambers &amp; Kings"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 3 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller joins Captain Alex from Supremacy Fishing Charters for an offshore adventure targeting big fish off shore. Starting at the Palm Beach Inlet, the team uses planar fishing techniques to hook wahoo and other catches like kingfish and amberjack. Along the way, firefighter Johnny Bennett shares his journey from fishing to starting a popular fish dip business. The day wraps up with thrilling doubleheader catches and a conservation message, showcasing the importance of sustainable fishing practices.</desc>
    <date>20241125</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709073000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Snook On Board"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 4 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller explores Jupiter’s Inner Coastal Waterway, blending fishing, paddleboarding, and community engagement. With the help of Matthew from Jupiter Live Bait, Ryan showcases bait preparation techniques before catching snook in the vibrant ICW. He highlights Jupiter's community spirit by joining a local clean-up initiative with Jeremy from Blue Line Paddleboards. The episode features paddleboarding adventures with Ryan’s family, connecting with nature and marine life, and ends with a conservation message about preserving Jupiter’s pristine environment.</desc>
    <date>20241202</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709083000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Longbeard Mitten Mayhem"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Over a decade after the game changing Longbeard XR was introduced by Winchester, the wait is finally over for their next ground breaking turkey load. After years of perfecting the recipe behind the scenes, Winchester finally unveiled the new Longbeard TSS at a turkey camp in northern Michigan. First watch the jaw dropping Longbeard TSS pattern board testing, then see it go to work on some spring gobblers.</desc>
    <date>20250317</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709083000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Remembering A Legend"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Nestled in the hills of Ohio just west of the Appalachians is a very special deer camp ripe with memories from deer season’s past. With the development of the 350 Legend straight-walled cartridge by Winchester in 2019, a world of opportunities now existed in states like Ohio and Michigan. In this episode, with the 350 Legend in hand, three mature whitetails meet their maker, from the same blind, over the course of three seasons.</desc>
    <date>20250317</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709093000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Six Decades Of Dominance"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s been 60 years since AA was introduced to the shooting sports world. Since that day, an immeasurable number of AA hulls have hit the ground and countless shooters have stood center stage raising a trophy where millions of dollars have been won. Professional and recreational shooters alike have trusted AA for six decades. In this episode, load up for stories of high school, collegiate competitors and the world’s best as they bust clays with the legendary shot shell. - GUESTS: Zach Keenbaum (Team Winchester) Desi Edmunds (Team Winchester) Kayla Wilgus (Team Winchester) Amy Cawley (Team Winchester) Anthony Matarese (Team Winchester)</desc>
    <date>20250417</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709093000 +0000" stop="20250709095959 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Clays With Purpose"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>For the first time in history, the World English Sporting Clays Championship was held in the United States at the incredible M&amp;M Hunting Preserve owned by the Matarese family in New Jersey. Watch as Winchester’s best shooters vie for Gold as they compete against over 2,500 shooters and 17 countries. We’ll also join the Kids and Clays foundation in Florida as they host an event that will most certainly touch your soul.</desc>
    <date>20250502</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709095959 +0000" stop="20250709103000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Painting Aluminum Hulls"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team is at  - John’s lake house on Tupper Lake, NY, where they are tackling a new paint Job using Interlux’s paint specifically designed for aluminum hulls. John and the crew take us step by step on what takes to paint on aluminum hulls as well as some other tips from guest hosts.</desc>
    <date>20250414</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709103000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Refit on a Surplus Console"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team is taking  - the Marine Surplus Console for the Aqua sport project and giving it a much needed face lift. They meet the team at Boat Outfitters to find an acrylic covering board to fit the console and cover the pre existing holes. They then head over to meet with crew at AwlGrip to get some ideas on color matching the console with the Aqua sport.</desc>
    <date>20250414</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709111757 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Opening Day In Mississippi"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode we turkey hunt here in southwest Mississippi with Cragg Fitz from Trained Assassins TV. It's the opening week of turkey season in Mississippi and the birds are gobbling and looking for love. They whip us on opening morning but we stumble upon one that afternoon and make our move and he makes his! You won't want to miss this episode!</desc>
    <date>20220628</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709111757 +0000" stop="20250709113028 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Midwest Turkey Tour 2024"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The "Trained Assassins" are back and it’s turkey season in the Midwest. In this first episode, Slade, Blake, and Ryan start in Missouri, run into some trouble, but end up getting it done on the first leg of the 2024 turkey tour.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709113028 +0000" stop="20250709114629 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"The Grind"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode we show you how we handle selling real estate in the midst of turkey season. When it is time to chase turkeys, our productivity as agents definitely slows a little bit, so that means we have to spend more hours ensuring our clients get what they deserve from us. We bounce around in this one going from taking the kids to school, handling business at the office, showing an amazing property, and finally getting some time to hunt. We hope this episode gives you a bit more insight on just how hectic and fast paced our Springs are at Hunting Land Man in Southwest Mississippi.</desc>
    <date>20220628</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709114629 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Flips And Flops"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, Slade takes us through his new investment property, and breaks down - what’s involved in taking a raw land tract and creating extremely desirable turn-key - hunting properties. - Caleb and Slade double up on some Wilkinson County gobblers for Calebs first turkey - kill ever.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709123000 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"First Things First"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Meredith McCord arrives in late spring and joins Capt. Justin Leake on the hunt for a fish she’s never caught before. Lo and behold, it’s a day fit for a king.</desc>
    <date>20250131</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709123000 +0000" stop="20250709130001 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Tarpon Producer"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>With Meredith McCord halfway around the world, Capt. Justin Leake gives show producer Chris Hermans his first shot at landing a tarpon after filming them for 9 seasons. Does art imitate life?</desc>
    <date>20250131</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709130001 +0000" stop="20250709133001 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Billfish Tourney"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Justin Leake joins some old friends on board the Fall Line in hopes of scoring big in the Bay Point Billfish Open. This trip will test the limits of all the anglers as the skilled captain and crew do the impossible in hopes of bringing home the prize.</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709133001 +0000" stop="20250709140018 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Electric Deep Drop"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Justin and Florida WaterSports pro Jeff Lange go deep off Panama City Beach to test the limits of a new battery powered reel. The results are surprising.</desc>
    <date>20250616</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709140018 +0000" stop="20250709143021 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Camp Cutters"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Three friends finally pack their bags and head west for the annual HuntStand pronghorn hunting camp—each with a unique goal in mind.</desc>
    <date>20221205</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709143021 +0000" stop="20250709150011 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"The Muley Freak"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After several years of shifting focus back to his native whitetails, Dahlke returns to mule deer country with the Muley Freak, Erik Van Woerkom. Follow along on this Utah mule deer hunt.</desc>
    <date>20241121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709150011 +0000" stop="20250709153004 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Second Chance | Hunting the November Rut in Ohio"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hunting has a way of grounding us, reminding us of what truly matters: shared moments and unforgettable memories. Chance and Ashleigh Eckert are on their first out-of-state hunt in the rolling hills of Ohio. After overcoming a life-changing kidney transplant, their story is one of faith, love, and resilience. While the goal was a big buck, the true reward was the time spent together and the lessons learned along the way. Because hunting is about so much more than the harvest — it’s about the journey.</desc>
    <date>20250113</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709153004 +0000" stop="20250709160012 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"The Maestro"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>For decades, Paul Butski has set the standard in turkey calling. His name is etched into the NWTF Grand National Calling Championships Hall of Fame, and his influence stretches far beyond the stage. He didn’t just win competitions, he shaped the way we talk to turkeys – and more importantly, the way we hunt them.</desc>
    <date>20250508</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709160012 +0000" stop="20250709162959 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Iowa Madness"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A Southwest Mississippi GIANT “Barry” has Slade’s brain in scrambles as he is preparing to head to Iowa after waiting 5 years to finally draw his tag. The chase is on let’s see if  the Hunting Land Man can seal a deal!</desc>
    <date>20240103</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709162959 +0000" stop="20250709170009 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Barry"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Southwest Mississippi GIANT “Barry” has made more daylight appearances than possibly any mature bucks in existence. Now that Slade is back from the midwest The chase is on.</desc>
    <date>20240112</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709170009 +0000" stop="20250709173005 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Doe Patrol"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, hunting season swiftly coming to an end. With - the real estate world getting busier, Slade and his family set out - to fill some tags, and fill up the freezer. It’s time to go on a Doe - Patrol!</desc>
    <date>20240301</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709173005 +0000" stop="20250709180011 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Mule Deer Dilemma"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting are taking turns filming and hunting Mule Deer in Colorado where they both harvest big mature Colorado bucks with Browning 6.8 Westerns at long range. They leave Colorado and go to Nebraska to hunt with Heritage Outfitters and double up on two great spots and stalk bucks.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709180011 +0000" stop="20250709182959 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Western Turkey Tracks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting team up with a crew from Simmons Sporting Goods and head west to chase the Wild Turkey! Good times, Good Friends and Great Hunting make for an awesome Spring hunting trip.</desc>
    <date>20250319</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709182959 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"2 Limits Of Ducks And 2 Swamp Bucks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting work on moving a duck blind in September before duck season then hunt it later that season for a two man limit in a flooded rice field. After that hunt Kyle heads to the deer stand where he is able to catch up with a big buck a friend had missed a couple days earlier. On the way to look for the buck he shot he comes across some buzzards that lead him to a different dead buck equal in size. Two Limits of ducks and two Swamp bucks is a hard couple of hunts to top.</desc>
    <date>20250619</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709193000 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Diving the Artificial Reefs of Pensacola"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon explores the sunken vessels and beautiful waters of the Florida Panhandle with local guide, Brady Hale.</desc>
    <date>20250505</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709193000 +0000" stop="20250709200003 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Offshore in Florida's Panhandle"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon learns how to return fish caught out of deep water using a descending device, a tool that is helping conserve the fish population everywhere that it is being used.</desc>
    <date>20250509</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709200003 +0000" stop="20250709202959 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Protecting The Keys"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon Simmons goes on a Lionfish Hunt that takes him to some of the most beautiful reefs in the Florida Keys.</desc>
    <date>20240205</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709202959 +0000" stop="20250709210001 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Cobia And Tuna"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a family filled episode as Brandon Simmons goes offshore with his Cousin to find Cobia and Tuna while also bringing his family to his childhood home</desc>
    <date>20240213</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709210001 +0000" stop="20250709213003 +0000">
    <title>Captain's Log</title>
    <sub-title>"May I have this dance?"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Jonathan Moss is ready to tango with the Sailfish of Stuart, Florida.</desc>
    <date>20221011</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709213003 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title>Operation Healing Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>"Steve Hopper"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the boys of '67, Steve Hopper details his experiences as part of Charlie Company's war in Vietnam.</desc>
    <date>20221118</date>
    <icon src="https://d97g6zbo9kng8.cloudfront.net/1920x1080_16x9_WaypointTV_11.22.2021.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709223001 +0000">
    <title>The Raven Project</title>
    <sub-title>"Prep Time"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While Randy and Dustin are trying to get the farm ready for Fall plots and create new access trails, Cody is at the river living life to the fullest. Randy finally has had enough and is doing something about Cody’s lack of effort on the farm.</desc>
    <date>20220725</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709223001 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"The Maestro"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>For decades, Paul Butski has set the standard in turkey calling. His name is etched into the NWTF Grand National Calling Championships Hall of Fame, and his influence stretches far beyond the stage. He didn’t just win competitions, he shaped the way we talk to turkeys – and more importantly, the way we hunt them.</desc>
    <date>20250508</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"Stack the Racks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Can the everyday landowner really manage their property well enough to hold and retain mature bucks year after year? From habitat improvements and food plots to pressure control and property layout, discover what truly influences a buck’s decision to stay—or stray.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250709235959 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"We the Hunters Part 2"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Part II of our exclusive profile of the current state of hunting in America and whether or not we believe there is light at the end of the tunnel.</desc>
    <date>20220907</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250709235959 +0000" stop="20250710003001 +0000">
    <title>Spring Thunder</title>
    <sub-title>"An Opening-Day Osceola | Southern Turkey Hunting At Its Finest | "</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Finally, the 2021 turkey season is here. The earliest turkey that is legal to hunt is in South Florida, and that's where Phillip Culpepper and the guys are headed. Things get up close and personal on the first morning of the season.</desc>
    <date>20210719</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250710003001 +0000" stop="20250710010000 +0000">
    <title>Spring Thunder</title>
    <sub-title>"3 MOUNTAIN GOBBLERS DOWN!! | Best Merriam's footage ever??? | "</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hunting with longtime friends Jeff and Deb Smith at 7J Outfitters in Sundance Wyoming. The Spring Thunder Crew split-up and take down 3 fired-up longbeards!!</desc>
    <date>20240208</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250710010000 +0000" stop="20250710013000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>“The Veteran”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Every spring brings a new opportunity to take a step forward &amp; recall the memories of seasons past. World War II Veteran and retired Judge Arden Hill has spent most of his life chasing turkeys in the hills of Tennessee. Now in his 90’s, Arden doesn’t let age stand in the way of his love for spring turkey hunting. Also: patterning turkey shotguns and hunting spring gobblers.</desc>
    <date>20240410</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
