<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704010027 +0000" stop="20250704013030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704013030 +0000" stop="20250704020023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704020023 +0000" stop="20250704023026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704023026 +0000" stop="20250704030031 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword in the Sandbox - A Storybook Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel fails miserably when he tries to join the others in jump rope. Convinced that he's too little to do anything right, Barney tells him the story of The Sword in the Sandbox. Through the legend of King Arthur, Daniel learns there are many things he can do... if he tries hard enough.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029632_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704030031 +0000" stop="20250704033025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff to the Rescue! - A Wild West Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Riff is asked to be captain of a baseball team, he doesnt think he can do it. But Barney gives him the courage to try, by recounting the tale of his great-great-grandfather Riffle the Wild West hero!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029633_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704033025 +0000" stop="20250704040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lights! Camera! Action! - A Movie Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie comes up with the perfect idea to get people to donate to Grace's food drive - put on a movie premiere in the caboose! Barney and friends pitch in to help, but they all have different ideas about what kind of movie to make. Everything they try falls apart. It's curtains for Melanie's movie until she comes up with a blockbuster idea of her own.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029634_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704040000 +0000" stop="20250704043001 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All About Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrate the things that make us special! Barney and his friends discover that trying something new can be fun. Jackson treats everyone to his healthy but unusual snack, while Baby Bop has a special picnic for BJ consisting mostly of her favorite foods.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029576_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704043001 +0000" stop="20250704050002 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Baby Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Oh baby! Oh baby! David has a new baby brother and is now a big brother. But David doesnt know what a big brother is supposed to do and isnt sure hes ready. Barney and his friends help David learn about new babies and how to be a big brother.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029577_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704050002 +0000" stop="20250704053004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Keep On Truckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends keep on truckin'! BJ enjoys helping with his tow truck, while Barney shows everyone what it's like to be behind the wheel of a real truck. When Jackson's special truck loses a tire, Barney wheels in to the rescue!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029578_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704053004 +0000" stop="20250704060005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>I'm A Builder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing some big construction machines roll by, Barney and his friends are inspired! With a little imagination, they build a castle made out of boxes. By exploring the ways things are built, and the big machines and tools used to build them, Barney builds in the fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029579_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704060005 +0000" stop="20250704062827 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Coming On Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Exercise is good for everybody and every body! From running to touching toes to jumping jacks to some favorite songs and games, Barney and his friends grow strong through various activities and having fun with exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029580_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704062827 +0000" stop="20250704065828 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Play Games!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>It's fun and games with Barney and his friends! BJ's favorite way of getting exercise is by playing sports and games. When Baby Bop is shy about trying new games, Barney and his friends show her how tee-rific trying something new can be.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029581_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704065828 +0000" stop="20250704073010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>You Can Count On Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick shows Barney and the rest of the kids his number cards that he and his mom had put together. He doesn't really think they're fun at first. But Barney helps his friends discover just how fun numbers can be by taking them on a number hunt in the park. With Barney and his friends, you can always count on a fun day!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029582_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704073010 +0000" stop="20250704080012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Wonderful World of Colors and Shapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Picture this! When Barney shows off his new painting, his friends are inspired to create their own art show. Discovering how to create new colors and draw shapes, Barney and his friends put on a super-dee-duper art show</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029583_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704080012 +0000" stop="20250704082833 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Easy as ABC</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop uses the caboose mailbox to deliver a special invitation to her tea party, she discovers that no one can read her handwriting. Barney and his friends find creative ways to help her learn her ABCs so she can spell her name!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029584_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704082833 +0000" stop="20250704085845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Look What I Can Do!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends are playing a fun game of I Can Do where they each share something they can do. When BJ suggests having an I Can Do show, Baby Bop becomes worried. Barney shows Baby Bop that while trying something new can sometimes be scary, with help from family and friends, it can also be fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029585_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704085845 +0000" stop="20250704093007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making A Move!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Welcome to the neighborhood! Anna has just moved to the neighborhood and is missing her old friends. Barney and his friends help her discover that moving is an adventure with new places to explore and new friends to meet.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029586_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704093007 +0000" stop="20250704100008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Home, Safe Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Safety first! After learning about fire safety when firefighter Bill visits the caboose, Barney and his friends are inspired to do a little safety inspection of their own. BJ's accident shows why you should only skate outside, and saying be careful is a good way to tell someone how much you love them!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029587_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704100008 +0000" stop="20250704103010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road Again!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends have a wheel good fun day learning about cars. Barney creates a colorful, kid-size car, the dinos learn about seatbelt safety, and everyone discovers there are many different styles of cars.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029588_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704103010 +0000" stop="20250704110011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Friends, The Doctor and Dentist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Time for a check-up! Barney helps his friends discover the world of doctors and dentists as they learn about healthy habits like brushing teeth, getting checkups, eating healthy foods and getting exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029589_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704110011 +0000" stop="20250704113011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China | Welcome, Cousin Riff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ receives a letter from his pen pal in China revealing that his pen pal will be coming to visit. With the help of friends, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives. Barney has a tee-rific surprise for BJ and Baby Bop. Cousin Riff is moving to town!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029658_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704113011 +0000" stop="20250704120010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits | Listen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective and a case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is a pet rabbit. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029659_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704120010 +0000" stop="20250704123010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden | Get Happy!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants everyone to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029660_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704123010 +0000" stop="20250704130009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big As Barney | The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029661_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704130009 +0000" stop="20250704133018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Games | No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Riff help Baby Bop learn how to follow the rules and learn that rules make games fun for everyone! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029662_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704133018 +0000" stop="20250704140017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Emperor's Contest | The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E14</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029663_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704140017 +0000" stop="20250704143015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Seeing | Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An ordinary game of hide and seek takes a not-so-ordinary turn when Baby Bop claims that an elephant is hiding in the park! BJ thinks that his sister may be seeing things but Barney takes this opportunity to help the young dinos learn about their sense of sight. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029664_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704143015 +0000" stop="20250704150014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show | Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E16</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029665_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704150014 +0000" stop="20250704153013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Shrinking Blankey | Things I Can Do</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bops blankey seems to be getting smaller; shes convinced its shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, she is growing. | Baby Bop isnt satisfied with her skills. She wants to play keyboard like Riff and wants to skate like Barney.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029666_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704153013 +0000" stop="20250704160022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose | Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help! | BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029667_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704160022 +0000" stop="20250704163021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Blame Game | Airplanes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. BJ brings his new toy plane to the park. Riff borrows it and takes it apart out of curiosity. When BJ finds out, he isn't mad and shows Riff how to put it back together.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029668_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704163021 +0000" stop="20250704170020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid | The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029669_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704170020 +0000" stop="20250704173017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All Aboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends transform the task of collecting litter pieces scattered across the park into an engaging game. Among them is Kami, the youngest of Barney's companions, who finds it challenging to keep pace with the other kids, leaving her feeling disheartened. Barney steps in and proves to each friend that their uniqueness makes them extraordinary.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029530_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704173017 +0000" stop="20250704180019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Up, Down, and Around!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Tony excitedly takes his kite to the park to share with his friends, an unexpected gust of wind sends it soaring into the branches of a tree! Barney and the kids revel in the beauty of nature's gifts and sing heartwarming tunes that celebrate all that trees provide. Together, they work to determine how they will rescue Tony's kite from its leafy perch.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029531_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704180019 +0000" stop="20250704183026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Tea-riffic Manners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather in the park for an exciting tea party they had planned, which begins with each of them showing each other the various ways they've contributed, from cookies to decorations. As the day progresses, the tea party proves to be a fun opportunity to reinforce lessons about good manners!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029532_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704183026 +0000" stop="20250704190012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Puppy Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd wanders around the park searching for his dog Bingo, who playfully hides in different areas of the park. Barney and the kids help find Bingo, and subsequently help Mr. Boyd prepare Bingo for a trip to the veterinarian for a checkup. This eventful day gives the kids an opportunity to learn lessons about how to care for a dog.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029533_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704190012 +0000" stop="20250704193026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch a Thief - A Mystery Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Detective BJ is on the case when several sports balls suddenly disappear. Determined to find the mysterious ball thief, BJ falsely accuses Riff of being the thief. BJ learns he cannot jump to conclusions and must find the whole story to see who the thief really is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029635_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704193026 +0000" stop="20250704200025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Lamp - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrating her birthday in the park with friends, Layla is more interested in hot dogs than her mother's Middle Eastern food. When Barney reads the story of Aladdin and the Magic Lamp, Layla is transported to a Middle Eastern marketplace where she learns different cultures have many exciting foods and customs to offer.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029636_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704200025 +0000" stop="20250704203028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Amazing Captain Pickles - A Hero Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Pickles and Wonder Princess both wanted to be the super-est superheroes. When Captain Pickles said he could jump over the moon, everyone wanted to see. BJ knew he couldn't really jump that high, but he could jump high enough to save Emma's balloon. Everyone was proud of him, even if he couldn't jump over the moon. BJ was a hero.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029637_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704203028 +0000" stop="20250704210029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Game for Everyone - A Sports Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes up with the idea to have a sports day in the park. All day, they play games like soccer and hopscotch among others, all for fun. Meanwhile, Baby Bop meets a girl with special needs named Jill, as well as her mom. As Baby Bop gets to know Jill more, she encourages her to play hopscotch with the others. In the end, Baby Bop and Jill win the trophy for hopscotch and she and her mother leave.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029638_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704210029 +0000" stop="20250704213021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Dragon - A Fairy Tale Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids judge a spider by its creepy looks, Barney tells them the story of The Reluctant Dragon where a shepherd became friends with a dragon, who was judged by her appearance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029639_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704213021 +0000" stop="20250704215845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bienvenido, Barney!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's friend Monty the butterfly passes through the park with a flock of friends on their way to Mexico. When Monty gets left behind, Barney takes everyone on a visit to Mexico to return Monty to his insect friends and family and give Baby Bop the chance to say goodbye to her butterfly friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029640_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704215845 +0000" stop="20250704222836 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big Brother Rusty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's excited to find out that Rusty's family is adopting a new baby sister from China; however, Rusty's not sure if he's going to be a good brother, and he doesn't know much about China. Barney shows Rusty and the others some info China on the computer and BJ and Baby Bop talk about siblings. Through Barney's Travel Book, Barney takes Rusty, BJ and Baby Bop on an adventure to China where he can learn more about his new sister's heritage. When they get there, the people are celebrating Chinese New Year. From lion dances and talented performers to tasty treats, making lanterns and puppet shows, the celebration never runs out of fun. By the time he returns to the park, Rusty excitedly meets his new baby sister, named Mei Ling, and realizes he will be the best big brother ever.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029641_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704222836 +0000" stop="20250704230030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Ahora Mismo!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is late to the park and is disappointed to realize he missed his chance at riding a real pony. He has waited his whole life for this, and now it looks as if hes missed his opportunity. Luckily, Barney takes Ben to Spain where they meet Regalo, a dancing horse with Riff and Baby Bop. Ben and Barney return to the park just in time for him to ride the pony after all! Ben is thrilled to ride a horse and learned an important lesson about patience and waiting.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029642_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704230030 +0000" stop="20250704232845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Venice, Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Emma is stuck with a school project and can't play soccer with Joshua. Having to interview her parents and get info about an interesting ancestor, she is frustrated with the assignment. Barney helps her discover that her ancestors were from Venice, Italy. Using his Travel Book, Barney takes Joshua, Emma, and Riff to Venice, Italy. He gives his friends a gondola ride as well as telling them about famous explorer Marco Polo. Barney's friend, Anna Maria tells Emma that she knew her great grandfather and takes her to his shop, where they try on masks and make some of their own. Emma learns that if she makes the mask in parts, she'll get it done. Barney reminds her of this lesson, so she will do the same for her school project.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029643_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704232845 +0000" stop="20250704235849 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sweeter Than Candy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, Baby Bop, and BJ are helping the kids get ready for a school play. Barney tells everyone that putting on shows began in Greece. Of course, the little dinos and kids want to visit the country, so off they go! While there, they meet some friends and decide to put on a play in an amphitheatre. Barney knows a great story that originated in Greece called King Midas. By the end of the day, everyone has learned that wanting too much is not a good thing, especially BJ!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029644_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250704235849 +0000" stop="20250705003029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Music Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ben accidentally includes Kioko's prized music box from Switzerland in a cardboard box of yard sale items-the music box is sold! Kioko is sad and Ben wants to make things right, so he and Barney travel to Switzerland in search of a replacement gift. While there, they sample Swiss food, customs and games-but no music box! Luckily when Ben returns the music box is returned!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029645_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250705003029 +0000" stop="20250705010034 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Egg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the kids find a mysterious, colorful egg in the park, Barney takes them on a trip to Kenya to try to find out what kind of animal could have laid the egg. While in Kenya, Barney and the kids meet Ayira who introduces them to many people, cultures, and animals of the country!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029646_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250705010034 +0000" stop="20250705012848 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Bird of a Different Feather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Rusty are looking for items for superhero costumes, when Barney comes to life, wearing a tutu. Tracy comes in and explains that she needs to find a bird of paradise for a school project. Ben, unsure, tells her they're only found in Hawaii and what they look like. Barney then takes the kids to Hawaii, using his Travel Book. In Hawaii, they learn different words, how to make leis and even a hula dance. Meanwhile, Ben and Rusty search for the bird, with a few close calls (a feather and what ended up being a coconut). During the Luau, it's revealed that the Bird of Paradise is actually a flower, not a bird. Ben, believing that it was a bird earlier, is shocked to hear that and apologizes to Rusty for getting him caught up in things. In the end, it all ends up just fine.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029647_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
