<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711010021 +0000" stop="20250711013022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>I'm A Builder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing some big construction machines roll by, Barney and his friends are inspired! With a little imagination, they build a castle made out of boxes. By exploring the ways things are built, and the big machines and tools used to build them, Barney builds in the fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029579_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711013022 +0000" stop="20250711015843 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Coming On Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Exercise is good for everybody and every body! From running to touching toes to jumping jacks to some favorite songs and games, Barney and his friends grow strong through various activities and having fun with exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029580_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711015843 +0000" stop="20250711022845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Play Games!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>It's fun and games with Barney and his friends! BJ's favorite way of getting exercise is by playing sports and games. When Baby Bop is shy about trying new games, Barney and his friends show her how tee-rific trying something new can be.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029581_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711022845 +0000" stop="20250711030027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>You Can Count On Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick shows Barney and the rest of the kids his number cards that he and his mom had put together. He doesn't really think they're fun at first. But Barney helps his friends discover just how fun numbers can be by taking them on a number hunt in the park. With Barney and his friends, you can always count on a fun day!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029582_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711030027 +0000" stop="20250711033029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Wonderful World of Colors and Shapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Picture this! When Barney shows off his new painting, his friends are inspired to create their own art show. Discovering how to create new colors and draw shapes, Barney and his friends put on a super-dee-duper art show</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029583_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711033029 +0000" stop="20250711040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Easy as ABC</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop uses the caboose mailbox to deliver a special invitation to her tea party, she discovers that no one can read her handwriting. Barney and his friends find creative ways to help her learn her ABCs so she can spell her name!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029584_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711040000 +0000" stop="20250711043005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Egg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the kids find a mysterious, colorful egg in the park, Barney takes them on a trip to Kenya to try to find out what kind of animal could have laid the egg. While in Kenya, Barney and the kids meet Ayira who introduces them to many people, cultures, and animals of the country!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029646_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711043005 +0000" stop="20250711050008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Bird of a Different Feather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Rusty are looking for items for superhero costumes, when Barney comes to life, wearing a tutu. Tracy comes in and explains that she needs to find a bird of paradise for a school project. Ben, unsure, tells her they're only found in Hawaii and what they look like. Barney then takes the kids to Hawaii, using his Travel Book. In Hawaii, they learn different words, how to make leis and even a hula dance. Meanwhile, Ben and Rusty search for the bird, with a few close calls (a feather and what ended up being a coconut). During the Luau, it's revealed that the Bird of Paradise is actually a flower, not a bird. Ben, believing that it was a bird earlier, is shocked to hear that and apologizes to Rusty for getting him caught up in things. In the end, it all ends up just fine.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029647_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711050008 +0000" stop="20250711053002 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bonjour Barney!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Emma wants to paint an award-winning painting for the Art In The Park Show, but she isn't satisfied with her artwork. Barney takes her to France to learn how to paint from his friend Pierre. While there, they learn about France. And Emma learns how to paint by following her heart!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029648_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711053002 +0000" stop="20250711060006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Home Sweet Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Earth Day, a great time for everyone to learn how to help take care of our world, but Ben is wasting paper while BJ isn't too concerned about cutting down a tree to make room for a new playground. After a trip to the rainforest and a meeting with Mother Nature, everyone learns the importance of taking care of our world. As Earth Day comes to an end, Barney reminds us all that taking good care of our Earth is the natural thing to dofor the people we love.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029649_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711060006 +0000" stop="20250711063006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos | Winter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps Baby Bop see that winter can be a wonderful time for fun. Then, when she least expects itthe snow begins to fall! Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029650_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711063006 +0000" stop="20250711070005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo |Boats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. Baby Bop enjoys her homemade boat but wants to ride in a big one. Barney shows her boats on the computer, while BJ and Riff prepare a surprise. When they return, a sailing ship awaits Baby Bop on the playset!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029651_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711070005 +0000" stop="20250711073005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose | Arts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. Barney and the little dinosaurs enjoy an Art Festival. BJ and Riff share some musical art and Baby Bop shares a painting of a very special friendBarney!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029652_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711073005 +0000" stop="20250711080012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movement | Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When some of the children invite Barney to join them for a race, BJ and Baby Bop decide hell need their help. By the end of the day, everyone finds out that there are many fun ways to exercise. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers that as more time that goes by, the more she misses them!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029653_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711080012 +0000" stop="20250711082832 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio | BJ's Snack Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ has a dream after eating too many sweets, where he eats as many sweets as he wants and ends up with a big stomachache. When he wakes up, hes happy to find out it was only a dream. When he asks for a healthy snack, his friends are happy to oblige.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029654_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711082832 +0000" stop="20250711090011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop Til You Drop | Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029655_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711090011 +0000" stop="20250711093011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin' Hood | Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029656_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711093011 +0000" stop="20250711100011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Butterflies | The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is sad because she lost her pet caterpillar, Monty. Barney and the others try to help her find it. Baby Bop is surprised to discover Monty inside a chrysalis. Everyone is excited to find Monty now a beautiful butterfly! Rachel carelessly litters in the park then later has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029657_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711100011 +0000" stop="20250711103010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China | Welcome, Cousin Riff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ receives a letter from his pen pal in China revealing that his pen pal will be coming to visit. With the help of friends, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives. Barney has a tee-rific surprise for BJ and Baby Bop. Cousin Riff is moving to town!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029658_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711103010 +0000" stop="20250711110010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits | Listen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective and a case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is a pet rabbit. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029659_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711110010 +0000" stop="20250711113009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pets - Vets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ learns that having a pet is a much bigger responsibility than he ever expected when he offers to take care of a friends dog. When he accidentally loses the dog, everyone has to work together to find it. When Baby Bops favorite teddy bear is torn, she wants to take him to the veterinarian for help. Barney and Riff pretend to be veterinarians. They show Baby Bop that theres nothing to be afraid of, because doctors and veterinarians are our friends too.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029598_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711113009 +0000" stop="20250711120008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Winter - Summer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop is surprised by the first day of cold weather, its Barney that helps her see that winter can be a wonderful time for fun. Baby Bop is getting discouraged, wondering if it will ever snow. Then, when she least expects itthe snow begins to fall! On a hot summer day, Barney teaches BJ about all the fun activities you can do during the summer. BJ gets so excited that he corrals Riff into joining him to do a whole summers worth of activities, all in one day! With some help from Baby Bop and the children, Barney teaches BJ that summer means relaxation, too!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029599_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711120008 +0000" stop="20250711123009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Caring - Rhythm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a very special day at the Parkits Barneys birthday, and there are surprises around every corner. When Barney begins to open his presents, Riff worries that his hand-made gift wont be good enough. In the end, Barney loves Riffs gift and reminds everyone that the best gift of all is one that comes from the heart. Baby Bop is practicing her marching because she will be joining a real marching rhythm band and is having trouble keeping a beat. Barney, BJ and Riff help Baby Bop learn about rhythm just in time for her to join the band.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029600_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711123009 +0000" stop="20250711130012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Games - Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop has trouble following the rules and taking turns while playing games. Barney and Riff help her learn how to follow the rules and Baby Bop learns that rules make games fun for everyone! BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles. When Barney suggests he rest in the caboose, BJ becomes frustrated, as hed rather be outside playing. Barney reminds him of the wonderful world of books, and the little dinos decide to write a book of their ownbased on the exciting true-life adventures of Captain Pickles!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029601_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711130012 +0000" stop="20250711133014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making Mistakes - Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>BJs enthusiastic efforts to decorate the park go awry when he accidentally paints the caboose several different colors. Barney helps BJ learn that everyone makes mistakes. Together with his friends, BJ cleans up the mess he made on the caboose. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers she misses them more than she expected and the more time that goes by, the more she misses them! Barney shows Baby Bop ways to keep friends close in our hearts while theyre away.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029602_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711133014 +0000" stop="20250711140019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Days of the Week - Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ, Baby Bop and Riff can hardly wait for the petting zoo that is coming to the park. Barney helps them pass the time while teaching them about the days of the week. When the animals finally do arrive, everyone realizes that it was all worth the wait! Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029603_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711140019 +0000" stop="20250711143016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711143016 +0000" stop="20250711150017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711150017 +0000" stop="20250711153012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711153012 +0000" stop="20250711160014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711160014 +0000" stop="20250711163016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711163016 +0000" stop="20250711170015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711170015 +0000" stop="20250711173017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711173017 +0000" stop="20250711180020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711180020 +0000" stop="20250711183022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711183022 +0000" stop="20250711190016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711190016 +0000" stop="20250711192837 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Look What I Can Do!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends are playing a fun game of I Can Do where they each share something they can do. When BJ suggests having an I Can Do show, Baby Bop becomes worried. Barney shows Baby Bop that while trying something new can sometimes be scary, with help from family and friends, it can also be fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029585_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711192837 +0000" stop="20250711200019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making A Move!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Welcome to the neighborhood! Anna has just moved to the neighborhood and is missing her old friends. Barney and his friends help her discover that moving is an adventure with new places to explore and new friends to meet.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029586_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711200019 +0000" stop="20250711203020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Home, Safe Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Safety first! After learning about fire safety when firefighter Bill visits the caboose, Barney and his friends are inspired to do a little safety inspection of their own. BJ's accident shows why you should only skate outside, and saying be careful is a good way to tell someone how much you love them!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029587_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711203020 +0000" stop="20250711210022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road Again!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends have a wheel good fun day learning about cars. Barney creates a colorful, kid-size car, the dinos learn about seatbelt safety, and everyone discovers there are many different styles of cars.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029588_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711210022 +0000" stop="20250711213023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Friends, The Doctor and Dentist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Time for a check-up! Barney helps his friends discover the world of doctors and dentists as they learn about healthy habits like brushing teeth, getting checkups, eating healthy foods and getting exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029589_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711213023 +0000" stop="20250711220026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome, Cousin Riff™ - Special Skills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney has a tee-rific surprise for BJ and Baby Bop. Cousin Riff is moving to town! Riff amazes everyone with his awesome musical abilities. When Barney suggests that they put on a show, Riff becomes shy - he's never performed in a show before. With encouragement from Barney, Riff joins in and does what he knows best - making music!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029590_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711220026 +0000" stop="20250711223027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Airplanes - Boats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ brings his brand-new toy plane to the park. Riff borrows the plane while BJ is off playing. Unfortunately, curiosity gets the best of Riff and he ends up taking the plane apart to see how it works. Luckily, BJ isnt mad when he finds out. Instead, he shows Riff how to put the plane back together again. Baby Bop is having a great time playing with her homemade boat. However, what she really wants is to ride in a big boat. Barney takes her to look at boats on the computer while BJ and Riff work on a big surprise for her. When Barney and Baby Bop return to the playground, they discover that BJ and Riff have built a sailing ship on the playset for Baby Bop!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029591_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711223027 +0000" stop="20250711230028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Butterflies - Bugs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is sad because she lost her pet caterpillar, Monty. Barney and the others try to help her find it. Baby Bop is surprised to discover Monty inside a chrysalis. Everyone is excited to find Monty now a beautiful butterfly! Barney and Baby Bop are thrilled when BJ sets up a bug zoo in the caboose, but Riff isnt so sure he wants to be around bugs. When the park is magically transformed into a amphitheatre with performing insects, Riff discovers that bugs dont bug him after all.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029592_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711230028 +0000" stop="20250711233028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shapes - Colors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop, BJ and the children prepare for the Shapes Carnival in the park. Riff knows he will do well at the carnival because he is wearing his lucky medal. When he loses the medal, Riff is afraid he wont be able to play the games. With Barneys guidance, Riff has fun playing the games and he realizes he didnt need his lucky medal play and have fun. When it starts to rain at the park, Baby Bop joins Barney and BJ inside the caboose. Baby Bop pokes her head out to see if the rain has stopped and spies a beautiful rainbow in the sky! When the others come to see itits gone. Baby Bop is very disappointed because she liked all the pretty colors, so Barney and the others paint their own life-sized rainbow. When it starts to rain again, the homemade rainbow falls down and gets all wet. Luckily, a real rainbow takes its place!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029593_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250711233028 +0000" stop="20250712000029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Seeing - Hearing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An ordinary game of hide and seek takes a not-so-ordinary turn when Baby Bop claims that an elephant is hiding in the park! Barney and Riff are happy to play along, but BJ thinks that his sister may be seeing things. Fortunately, Barney takes this opportunity to help the young dinos learn about their sense of sight while having tons of fun! BJ and Riff engage in a friendly contest to see which of them can find (or make) the loudest sound in the park. The playful competition continues to escalateand along the way, the sounds of animals, musical instruments, and even fire engines are introduced.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029594_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712000029 +0000" stop="20250712003027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Glad to Be Me - Arts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff has many special qualities, but sometimes, his shyness makes it hard for him to meet new friends. When Barney introduces Riff to some of his friends in the park, its Baby Bop that ends up feeling less-than-special as the kids seem more impressed with Riff and his special talents. Barney helps Baby Bop realize that theres more to being special than the things you can do. The way you feel and the way you make others feel makes you special, too. Its a special day in the park as Barney and the little dinosaurs enjoy an Art Festival. BJ and Riff share some musical art and Baby Bop shares a painting of a very special friendBarney! As the festival comes to an end, Barney reminds his friends everywhere that no matter what kind of art they make, its always special when it comes from their hearts!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029595_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712003027 +0000" stop="20250712010029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movement - BJ’s Snack Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When some of the children in the park invite Barney to join them for a race, BJ and Baby Bop decide hell need their help. They show him several ways to get ready for the big race by warming up and stretching. By the end of the day, everyone finds out that there are many fun ways to exercise. When BJ starts to feel sick after eating too many sweets, he lies down in hopes of feeling better. He has a dream about a snack fantasyland where he eats as many sweets as he wants and ends up with a big stomachache. When he wakes up, hes happy to find out it was only a dream. When he asks for a healthy snack, his friends are happy to oblige.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029596_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250712010029 +0000" stop="20250712013026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Counting - Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ and Riff find a pirate map, but in order to find the treasure, they have to be able to count. Since Baby Bop has not learned to count yet, Barney offers to help teach her so she can participate. In the end, Baby Bop learns to count and realizes that feeling good about herself is the greatest treasure in the world! Its time for a music concert in the park. As Riff works on his one-man band, the others make posters for the show. Everyone enjoys Riffs calypso rendition of a favorite song, and they all enjoy helping each other.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029597_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
