<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712230051 +0000" stop="20250713002237 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713002237 +0000" stop="20250713014524 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Housewife</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Florence is a housewife who yearns for something new and exciting in her love life. Things turn deadly real quick when she doesn’t get what she wants.</desc>
    <date>20240820</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ghbD9Xw6cbibMczyWNiCsOVU482.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713014524 +0000" stop="20250713031637 +0000">
    <title>Death by Envy</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An entire neighborhood is rattled when a man with a promising future is murdered in front of his wife.</desc>
    <date>20220614</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e6e8497968b8587a968661fb89742c21.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713031637 +0000" stop="20250713051322 +0000">
    <title>Dangerous Men</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Emmanuel, is an assassin who goes against the order of his contractor X and refuses to carry out a hit placed on Senator Kingston. Emmanuel is forced to take turn a homeless man into the perfect killer. The deadly duo forms an alliance with Kingston and go after X. This leads to the ultimate showdown between the assassin and the head of the organization. Get ready for non-stop action, masterful fight sequences.</desc>
    <date>20230120</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mGwiiiUj3RavBzSs6DpkenfKbfS.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713051322 +0000" stop="20250713074037 +0000">
    <title>Cuzzo</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jealousy and betrayal ensue, when Will enlists the help of his cousin, in helping to get his wife pregnant.</desc>
    <date>20220125</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4cc4a878477031b09b8b9501950d4abd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713074037 +0000" stop="20250713094307 +0000">
    <title>Cuffin Season</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Nate is a part-time Uber drive and a music video director, and is becoming a rising star in the music and video world. Everything is going great, except for the fact that he doesn’t have citizenship. He knows the easiest way for him to get citizenship is to get married, but he won’t settle for just any woman. Will he run out of time before immigration is onto him?</desc>
    <date>20220730</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5f5726e7d2a2fbf465f7031453e40ed9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713094307 +0000" stop="20250713111409 +0000">
    <title>Dank</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Herc is trying to make it in the NBA but his finances are making the journey difficult. So he decides to purchase and sell “REEFER” an alternate CBD strand that is being pushed in the streets by a crooked mayor.</desc>
    <date>20240104</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713111409 +0000" stop="20250713130532 +0000">
    <title>Counterplay</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Antwan Walker and his beautiful wife Nia have the perfect marriage. When Antwan’s wandering eye leads him to flirt with his co-worker Monica, what follows is a psychological thriller as Antwan slowly realizes that Monica has a hidden agenda.</desc>
    <date>20240326</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bLETMcahs7dDiWwU6qtfIqNIHlz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713130532 +0000" stop="20250713145149 +0000">
    <title>Dangerous Thirst</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Royelle's husband, Trevion, proposes delving into the swinging lifestyle, she reluctantly agrees, igniting a tumultuous sexual journey. What starts as a tantalizing exploration of their desires soon transforms into a journey fraught with jealousy, distrust, and emotional turmoil, threatening to unravel the very fabric of their marriage as she begins to find herself in a sex scandal, engulfed by lies, betrayal, and murder.</desc>
    <date>20240406</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWE0MDBkNjctOTE5Yy00YTUyLWEzODItYzc0ZmVmYmZlYjc1XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713145149 +0000" stop="20250713162955 +0000">
    <title>Clutch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Detectives Clutch and Angel navigate a criminal underworld with the help of three women, whom Clutch is familiar with, to solve the disappearance of a group of women. Their investigations take them deeper into unknown and even more corrupt places in the underworld, that are worse than they thought.</desc>
    <date>20241029</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a01a16449594be179bbe3f698aceaf9c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713162955 +0000" stop="20250713175846 +0000">
    <title>Bunny and Clive</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Down and out alcoholic reporter Dougie Pierce has been faced with losing his job for not bringing in a reputable report of anything that is worth reading. That is until one day he runs into the city’s most notorious duo in crime Lola and Clive aka “Bunny &amp; Clive”. When he becomes their hostage, he gets a full on one-on-one interview with this criminal power couple and why they do what they do. He has the most important story of this generation, that is if he makes it out alive to tell it.</desc>
    <date>20240601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f56644b9380aeb1d224700bbef125996.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713175846 +0000" stop="20250713193833 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713193833 +0000" stop="20250713210217 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWVkNzQ1MjAtYmNjZS00NDc0LTg0YzktNzVlNGViODYyMmUxXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713210217 +0000" stop="20250713223735 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250713223735 +0000" stop="20250714003543 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lC6QNvelSJtOzkzzEC6D6jn1Hh3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
