<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1">
    <display-name>Combat War Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b376f55c-aa7f-43c5-9c26-c20509874201/combat_war72b13823df22f4e6ea012a4b54cc6b02RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704002635 +0000" stop="20250704022615 +0000">
    <title>Battlefields</title>
    <sub-title>A Century of Tanks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>April 16, 1917, for the first time in history, French tanks fight their way through the black sludge of Chemin des Dames. One year before, in October, British tanks tried their luck in Somme. In both cases, the long-awaited miracle did not take place. Yet, a century later, the tanks are still here, monsters of technology that are becoming increasingly efficient.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0GAGB9GGDROZ/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704022615 +0000" stop="20250704032923 +0000">
    <title>Battlezone: The Gulf War</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The ultimate test of tank technology is the battlefield. American tanks form the sharp end of the sword in Desert Storm. The U.S. marine corp was still using the older M-60 tank, although with some modifications.</desc>
    <date>20151213</date>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0AUKSMZ35G7Q/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704032923 +0000" stop="20250704040408 +0000">
    <title>Battlezone: The Korean War</title>
    <sub-title>Big Picture: United Nations Forces Counterattack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Our allied units throw a powerful counterattack against the Reds, Infantry tanks, artillery, and air all combine to throw the Reds back to the North, The Navy blasts the enemy with rockets. Captain Zimmerman interviews Chaplain Joseph Murphy of Boston, Massachusetts, and Captain John Rock, former company commander with the 1st Cavalry Division in Korea.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0MZVKBAG9IZA/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704040408 +0000" stop="20250704050256 +0000">
    <title>3 Days in the Life of Lt. Kravtsov</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lt. Kravtsov's mission demands him to quickly assume command and guide his troops through treacherous circumstances. With limited time, he faces the immense challenge of maintaining morale, making tough decisions, and protecting his men in the face of overwhelming odds.</desc>
    <date>20120509</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/46BVUpXAw5IVhZYtXS3C1WOXnMO.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704050256 +0000" stop="20250704055808 +0000">
    <title>3 Days in the Life of Lt. Kravtsov</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>This story underscores the harsh realities of war and the profound impact it has on young soldiers like Lt. Kravtsov. It raises questions about sacrifice, the fragility of life, and the emotional toll of warfare. Will Lt. Kravtsov defy the odds and survive his assigned three days? The answer remains uncertain in this poignant narrative of youth and the cost of war.</desc>
    <date>20120509</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ggaEamxpmWuCKLjTnE9O6rrJJef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704055808 +0000" stop="20250704070048 +0000">
    <title>Napoleonic Wars in Russia</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In June 1812, Napoleon's 'Grand Army' invaded Russia with over 800,000 soldiers. Despite initial optimism, they faced hardships like hunger and desertion. Alexander I, the Russian Emperor, withdrew from Vilna to engage the enemy. Napoleon hoped for a quick victory, but the Russian strategy was to retreat and draw the invaders deeper into their territory. The French army's discipline waned.</desc>
    <date>20120601</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ptpYLEyiwbnU7a5MoyFDTwTj16Z.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704070048 +0000" stop="20250704080446 +0000">
    <title>Napoleonic Wars in Russia</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Napoleon's army advanced toward Moscow in June 1812, eager to defeat Russia's forces and impose peace on their terms. However, the Russians resisted fiercely. The Cossack corps and the Russian vanguard, led by Neverovsky, fought bravely against superior French cavalry. Despite facing overwhelming odds, Neverovsky's men formed a square, defending fiercely, before retreating.</desc>
    <date>20120602</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x9yMCTQbezDLQwsGKmmyEMH2EdR.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704080446 +0000" stop="20250704090826 +0000">
    <title>Napoleonic Wars in Russia</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>August 26, 1812. The eve of the bloodiest battle of the Napoleonic Wars in Russia. Two huge armies, quarter million people, clashed near Borodino village, 124 km west of Moscow. Napoleon aimed to seize the village and break through Russian defenses. Bagration's troops bravely fought, but the price was high. Bagration got mortally wounded, but the Russians managed to repel the French attacks.</desc>
    <date>20120603</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x0YqngQ3DIdTU9jKGCmBgFkhRtc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704090826 +0000" stop="20250704100321 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Barbarossa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Battle of Britain is over. The Luftwaffe has been driven to exhaustion, and Germany suffers its first major defeat. Even though Britain remains undefeated, it is so isolated that Hitler has no concerns about turning his attention East. Operation Barbarossa, the German invasion of the USSR, takes the Soviets completely by surprise and the Red Army suffers terrible casualties.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0N60XS675MXI/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704100321 +0000" stop="20250704105828 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle of Kiev</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After the swift success at Smolensk, Hitler has diverted the bulk of Heinz Guderian's panzers down to the South, so as to capture the Ukrainian capital Kiev, considered more important than Moscow in Hitler's mind. It begins a gigantic clash and turns out to be the biggest military encirclement in history.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0WC5726V93TB/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704105828 +0000" stop="20250704115301 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Defence of Sevstopol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Erich von Manstein's soldiers have trapped a massive Soviet force in Crimea, but the doomed troops have no intentions of surrendering, strongly motivated by patriotism. Manstein assembles the greatest concentration of artillery in history, which includes the world's biggest railway-gun nicknamed 'Dora,' and for eight months Soviets troops are savagely bombarded; destroying Sevastopol's only harbor.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0YK7KLETKP1K/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704115301 +0000" stop="20250704125002 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>Battle of Moscow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>October 1941, Germany's Army Group Center is only some 25 km west of Moscow. The Russian winter, however, is only a few weeks away. With not enough soldiers or military equipment, the Soviet high command's only hope left is that the weather will save the capital. The battle ends in a bloody failure for the German Army, and it is forced to retreat.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0A5Y4I9JQHUT/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704125002 +0000" stop="20250704134635 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Rzhev Meat Grinder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The capture of Rzhev, the city that connects all railroads in Western Russia, is imperative. It will cost the lives of some 3 million Soviet soldiers and 500 000 German soldiers. It will take the Soviets a total of 3 years to throw the Germans firmly out of the city. These bloodbaths will become known by the veterans and historians as 'The Rzhev Meat-Grinder'.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0WOGMZLXRKKL/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704134635 +0000" stop="20250704144244 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>Stalingrad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After the failure to take both Moscow and Leningrad, Hitler sets his sights on the oil fields in the Caucasus. If captured, the Red Army will lose 70-90% of all its oil resources. Therefore, the famous city on the Volga, Stalingrad, must be 'held at all costs.' The German General Staff thinks taking the city will be a matter of a few weeks, but events steadily turn against the Germans.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0VB6V9XNQ3I2/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704144244 +0000" stop="20250704153802 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>Battle of The Caucasus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ewald von Kleist has broken through to the Terek river, slap in front of the vital oil fields of Grozny and Baku. Only freezing temperatures in the Caucasus prevent von Kleist's 1st Panzer Army from breaking through to Ozoni Kizi and Tbilisi. The Soviets launch a desperate counter-attack that holds the Germans back.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0WVUPCGKVEZW/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704153802 +0000" stop="20250704163331 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle of Kursk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After two years of war, Hitler was no closer to victory in the East, and his forces had suffered a devastating defeat at Stalingrad. Now the Germans gathered their strength for one last massive offensive to decide the outcome of the war.</desc>
    <date>20100426</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rImj3JdeAs7ktLSdbF6iNEdGqrC.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704163331 +0000" stop="20250704172932 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Bagration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>By summer 1944, Germany has undeniably lost the battle of the USSR. After the Soviet victories at Moscow, Stalingrad, Kursk, and Leningrad, the Soviet Union, with its practically unlimited resources of manpower and matériel, begins to rapidly push the Germans back toward the German border. On 22 June 1944, Stalin launches Operation Bagration, named after a Russian hero of the Napoleonic Wars.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0M52LZWZMIG5/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704172932 +0000" stop="20250704182412 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The War in the Air</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>On 22 June 1941, German pilots were the first to see the sun rise. Before the day was over, the Soviet Air Forces had lost almost 2 000 aircraft. The early German air superiority gave a significant boost to German confidence, and severely damaged Soviet military capability and morale.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0OKJ1VZL1XFZ/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704182412 +0000" stop="20250704191751 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The War at Sea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hours before the start of Operation Barbarossa, the Germans, along with their Finnish allies, begin mining the Gulf of Finland to prevent any naval evacuation of Soviet troops and ships. When Operation Barbarossa begins, Axis U-boats begin pounding the grand Soviet Navy, primarily based at Leningrad.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0QV247HR2Z3U/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704191751 +0000" stop="20250704201252 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Partisan War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>By 1943-1944, as the Germans are desperately struggling to hold their ground, they are increasingly hindered by the Soviet partisans, which contain many former Red Army soldiers that had been cut off behind enemy lines. The Germans responded with intensive counter-insurgency campaigns and brutal reprisals against the civilian population.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM04DRY4AGWH3J/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704201252 +0000" stop="20250704210806 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Shortly before the outbreak of the Second World War, the Polish and British have succeeded in de-coding the top secret German military codes known as 'Enigma.' This information, referred to as 'Ultra' by the Allies, becomes vital for the Allies' military situation in North Africa, the Soviet Union, and Northern France.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0S4MUQQPKW5K/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704210806 +0000" stop="20250704220415 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle of Berlin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Germany has without question lost World War II in Europe, but Hitler, by now a heavily medicated and deluded character, refuses to give up hope; he orders the roughly one million German soldiers left in the ruined city to defend Berlin, now a strange mix of combat veterans, teenage boys from the Hitler Youth, and old men from the People's Army.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0LIWEXD2BLC8/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704220415 +0000" stop="20250704225835 +0000">
    <title>Soviet Storm</title>
    <sub-title>The War Against Japan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The war in Europe is over. However, in the Pacific East, the United States is still fighting the Japanese, who consider surrender the greatest humiliation for a soldier. Stalin promises to help Roosevelt, but the dropping of the Atomic bomb on Japan suddenly alters the calculus for the Allies. Despite the devastation, the Japanese military vows to fight on.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0ML333RDOTW6/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704225835 +0000" stop="20250704235340 +0000">
    <title>The Dawns Here Are Quiet</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It is late spring of 1942, and World War 2 is in full swing. A long way off from the front-line the Germans make an air landing operation in an attempt to get through to the Kirov railway and the White Sea - Baltic Sea Canal. The only obstacle in their way is an anti-aircraft artillery unit of corporal Vaskov and five young women in training.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM01ZJUMCZ7008/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250704235340 +0000" stop="20250705004856 +0000">
    <title>The Dawns Here Are Quiet</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It is late spring of 1942, and World War 2 is in full swing. A long way off from the front-line the Germans make an air landing operation in an attempt to get through to the Kirov railway and the White Sea - Baltic Sea Canal. The only obstacle in their way is an anti-aircraft artillery unit of corporal Vaskov and five young women in training.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0JY8KUU50X6P/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65e87f35335524a69e8e0ce1" start="20250705004856 +0000" stop="20250705014204 +0000">
    <title>The Dawns Here Are Quiet</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It is late spring of 1942, and World War 2 is in full swing. A long way off from the front-line the Germans make an air landing operation in an attempt to get through to the Kirov railway and the White Sea - Baltic Sea Canal. The only obstacle in their way is an anti-aircraft artillery unit of corporal Vaskov and five young women in training.</desc>
    <icon src="https://image.xumo.com/v1/assets/asset/XM0EH5I050UUA0/1280x720.jpg?fb=https%253A%252F%252Fimage.xumo.com%252Fv1%252Fchannels%252Fchannel%252F88889356%252F1280x720.jpg%253Ftype%253DtrcChannelTile" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
