<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709003503 +0000" stop="20250709023351 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Green Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>During a canal restoration project near Midsomer Worthy, on which Joyce is working as a volunteer, several skeletons are discovered shortly after a tunnel collapse. DCI Barnaby begins his investigations when it is found that one skeleton had modern dental work. Meanwhile, DS Troy, having been promoted to Inspector has his last case in Midsomer, to look into the murder of a youth, Simon Mayfield (Henry Cavill), who had caused problems for many in the village.</desc>
    <date>20031102</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nhfabQSsoGFCTT09gx1rzwm8Vq7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709023351 +0000" stop="20250709043228 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Tidings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>DS Dan Scott, a charming young man but with a bit of an urban chip on his shoulder, arrives in Midsomer as DS Troy's replacement. He is instantly involved in his first case, a woman stabbed after attending a Spanish-themed evening in Midsomer Mallow. Not long after, a retired doctor for whom she had worked is murdered during the village's annual garden open day. It quickly becomes clear that the two victims knew a secret about one of the villagers. Are both crimes connected?</desc>
    <date>20040104</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aIU38yMvh21kAjGhHwtnmp7bYCs.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709043228 +0000" stop="20250709062742 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Fisher King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Back in 1970, Roger Heldman died in what appeared to be an accident, during a dig at Midsomer Barrow. It unearthed two important Celtic pieces, a spear and chalice. In present day, Roger's son Gareth is killed with the spear, after having altercations with several villagers. At the climax of the summer solstice celebration Gareth's half brother David Heartley-Reade is killed while performing a ceremony to save his failing marriage.</desc>
    <date>20040111</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3ot5o0bSjljuuT9nDRAi8QmjoHT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709062742 +0000" stop="20250709081958 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of Commission</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>DCI Barnaby and DS Scott arrive in Midsomer St. Michael to investigate the apparently accidental death of former prize-winning author Richard Rackham. But it is discovered that he had had his neck expertly broken before his tumble down the stairs. The village's 12th annual Literary festival brings feuding writers, publishers, and editors to town. When Mr Rackham's editor is then found dead during the festival's opening ceremony, it leads police on a trail of deception, fraud, and hidden truths.</desc>
    <date>20040118</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wrBYTFkpZpSjJODMntSQqV3XVr7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709081958 +0000" stop="20250709101214 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Maid In Splendour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The village pub of Midsomer Worthy, The Maid in Splendour, is the workplace of many locals. One night, popular barman Jamie Cruickshank is found dead near an abandoned cottage in the woods. The new manager Stephen Bannerman, who is thoroughly disliked by many, wants to sell the Maid to property developers in secret. When Stephen is murdered, Barnaby and Scott have to find out whether Jamie or Stephen was the intended target of the first murder.</desc>
    <date>20040125</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y1VAyLGu8s6CG5UdQvvRAY7hE6r.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709101214 +0000" stop="20250709120439 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Straw Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Midsomer Parva have all come out one evening to see the revival of an old Pagan festival. The centrepiece is a straw effigy of a woman. When it is set alight and people look on in wonder, it soon turns to horror when the local curate screams out in pain from within the effigy. The villagers quickly turn against Liz Francis, a local teacher who had organised the event.</desc>
    <date>20040229</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nrOBSdUgTLPdvICauwBZ9dy7A9K.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709120439 +0000" stop="20250709135711 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Ghosts Of Christmas Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Nine years after Ferdy Villiers committed suicide at the family home of Draycott Hall, the extended Villiers family gather together to celebrate Christmas. When a riddle in a Christmas cracker proclaims that two members of the family will be dead by midnight on Boxing Day, everyone takes no notice, until elderly Aunt Lydia nearly dies after getting locked in the garage, after her car has restarted itself and then later in the night, falls down the stairs.</desc>
    <date>20041225</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ZtPtLMhYmIDZEDoDc5Js6z9IIl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709135711 +0000" stop="20250709155708 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Garden Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Midsomer Deverell are angered over plans by the Inkpen family to convert the public memorial garden into a tea shop. When Elspeth Inkpen's daughter 'Fliss' is found murdered in the garden, shortly after a village meeting, Barnaby and Troy suspect that someone may be determined to stop the destruction. As their investigations continue, they discover a web of snobbery, greed, illegitimacy and mourning.</desc>
    <date>20000910</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wJ5m7R7576zeEsXefNCnjI5Yt0j.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709155708 +0000" stop="20250709175601 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Destroying Angel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gregory Chambers, manager of the Easterly Grange Hotel, goes missing just before the funeral of Karl Wainwright, his employer, after venturing into the woods to collect wild mushrooms. His wife tells everyone, including the police, that nothing is untoward. During a search of the woods, a severed hand is found. The case becomes more complex when the beneficiaries of Wainwright's will start receiving death threats.</desc>
    <date>20010826</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gnSefZ3VHWU2eAXp6qOQT0f72iT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709175601 +0000" stop="20250709195428 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Electric Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Not only do Midsomer Parva's wheat fields include crop circles, they also contain an added mystery element, when the naked body of a dead man is found. It is later discovered that he was first electrocuted, has puncture marks on his back, and a chunk of his hair missing. Barnaby and Troy have their work cut out with rivalries, secret affairs and loves, jealousies and hatred.</desc>
    <date>20010902</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/otd1IjvygEXA3skbVhZNPVCUhhA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709195428 +0000" stop="20250709215315 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Who Killed Cock Robin?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The village doctor of Newton Magna involves the police after he accidentally hits a man in the road following a party; however, the injured man is nowhere to be found. Then the body of Robin Wooliscroft, who disappeared over a year before, is pulled up from a well. The detectives come up against suspicions, lies, disapproving families, resentments and hidden secrets before another victim is found and they get to the truth.</desc>
    <date>20010909</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eJYOgPrqzQiuvr63lelb4c4d3aw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709215315 +0000" stop="20250709235208 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Autumn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the remote hamlet of Goodman's Land, local postman and casanova Dave Cutler gets murdered whilst doing his early postal delivery. Barnaby and Troy, with WPC Jay Nash, start investigating. They discover Dave had slept with many women in the village. A witness later recalls having heard strange 1950s dance music before the murder. When others become victims to the killer, the detectives need to find a possible link to connect the murders before Jay gets into a perilous situation herself.</desc>
    <date>20010916</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vIBCvCqI7Iz9pgStgDfD9M5XNgj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709235208 +0000" stop="20250710013731 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Rider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The appearance of a headless horseman at Quitewell Hall foreshadows a number of deaths amongst an aristocratic family.</desc>
    <date>20120201</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b467aebVPvYT8pRWgoFy1RgbfCW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
