<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39">
    <display-name>Get.Factual</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d8ac3d3f-88be-4d2a-89f3-608f02e15728/GetFactual_Dark_Mode_Logordx.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708005755 +0000" stop="20250708014939 +0000">
    <title>Crime Scene Eulau - The Mystery of the 13 Skeletons</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This documentary focuses on a spectacular discovery made in a quarry near the village of Eulau, not far from the central German town of Naumburg. Neolithic graves contained the skeletons of three women, two men and eight children, buried tenderly 4500 years ago, some affectionately entwined. In 2008, for the first time anywhere in the world, it was possible to perform a DNA analysis on the earliest evidence of the existence of a nuclear family. This was a sensation - but why did these people all die at the same time? Were they the victims of a violent crime? Who were they, and how did this terrible drama unfold? Archaeologists insist that these victims will not be forgotten, since these days it is possible to do far more than simply date and record such finds. Modern scientific methods have revolutionised archaeology, enabling us to discover how and why the family from Eulau in the German state of Sachsen-Anhalt died 4500 years ago. By enlisting the help of a CID profiler, archaeologists and anthropologists employ state-of-the-art analytical methods to investigate this Stone Age crime. In the process we discover key information about an era before recorded history which has previously been shrouded in mystery - and astonishing information about the composition of the population here also comes to light. It seems that the third millennium before Christ saw two major waves of migration, from Eastern and Western Europe, which determine the composition of the population here. In the middle of what is now Germany these two migratory movements met. Could this be the background to the mysterious murders of Eulau?</desc>
    <date>20230529</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708014939 +0000" stop="20250708015601 +0000">
    <title>FALLBACK - ZDF - 1031100029_en</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <date>20231213</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708015601 +0000" stop="20250708025421 +0000">
    <title>Scotland - Highlands and Islands</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mysterious castles overlooking lonely lakes, and men in kilts playing the bagpipes; whiskey, and the Loch Ness monster: everybody is familiar with the clichés about Scotland. What few people realise, however, is that Great Britain‘s northernmost region also contains fascinating countryside and wildlife.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/scotlandhighlandsandislands_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708025421 +0000" stop="20250708030029 +0000">
    <title>FALLBACK - ZDF - 1031100030_en</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <date>20231213</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708030029 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title>Eagle Lakes</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Lauenburg Lake District is located between Lübeck and Lauenburg on the River Elbe. With more than 470 square kilometres, it is the third largest natural reserve in Schleswig-Holstein. Due to its extensive forest areas, 40 lakes and its proximity to Mecklenburg’s biosphere reserve Lake Schalsee, it forms the largest protectoral area alongside the former inner-German border.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/eaglelakes_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050102 +0000">
    <title>World War A - When Aliens Attack</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Scientists are already looking feverishly for evidence of extraterrestrial life. With the ExoMars mission, ESA will soon find life on Mars. If there are only tiny microbes, there could also be life in other places in the universe. But can life in space exist at all? The exobiologist Jean-Pierre de Vera collects microorganisms around the world and tests them in his Mars simulation laboratory. Can they survive under the deadly conditions of Mars? Researchers believe there are planets on which alien life can exist. In 1991 the Swiss astrophysicist Michel Mayor discovered the world's first exoplanet. Since then, about 3,000 planets have been detected outside our solar system. Heike Rauer from the German Aerospace Center is looking for habitable planets. Will she find a second earth? The European Southern Observatory is also searching for life in space, building the largest telescope in the world. In the next 20 years the E-ELT should be able to prove the existence of life on distant planets. How would extraterrestrials look? Some scientists suspect that they may well resemble us humans. Under other environmental conditions, alien life could also arise completely differently. It could be formed from methane and silicon. Different gravity would form alien bodies completely differently. Could extraterrestrials send us messages? At the SETI Institute in California, alien hunters like Seth Shostak are listening to signals from alien civilizations. But mere listening is no longer enough. Some SETI researchers now want to send messages to the aliens themselves. They hope to finally get an answer. But would that be a bad idea? Many scientists warn of the dangers of establishing contact. The former SETI researcher and science fiction author David Brin also fears that it could be a devastating mistake. With well-meant news we could end up attracting attention from hostile civilizations. Should we really tell them that we exist and where they can find us?</desc>
    <date>20230317</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/worldwarawhenaliensattack_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708050102 +0000" stop="20250708060051 +0000">
    <title>Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland" is a wildlife documentary about a white-tailed eagle family, a young otter and a giant catfish that share the wetlands of this country in Central Europe. Hungary lies in the bottom of the huge Pannonian Basin encircled by the peaks of the Alps and the Carpathians.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/wildhungaryawaterwonderland_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708060051 +0000" stop="20250708065735 +0000">
    <title>Wild Serbia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Serbia is in the heart of the Balkans, a “little Europe“ within Europe; with its rich variety of landscapes and natural beauties, it certainly does this name justice. This nature documentary presents Serbia's breath-taking, picturesque regions and unique wildlife on a journey to the most beautiful and wildest areas of the Balkan peninsula, from high mountains across gentle hills to the vast plains of the Puszta.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/wildserbia_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708065735 +0000" stop="20250708075749 +0000">
    <title>Big is beautiful</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The world is full of giants, huge creatures that fill us with awe and wonder. Some are gentle giants. Others are deadly hunters. There are different ways of defining ‘big’ - biggest in volume, or the biggest of their kind. But one thing is for sure, the huge animals of this world are fascinating, diverse and beautiful.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bigisbeautiful_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708075749 +0000" stop="20250708090051 +0000">
    <title>World War A - When Aliens Attack</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Scientists are already looking feverishly for evidence of extraterrestrial life. With the ExoMars mission, ESA will soon find life on Mars. If there are only tiny microbes, there could also be life in other places in the universe. But can life in space exist at all? The exobiologist Jean-Pierre de Vera collects microorganisms around the world and tests them in his Mars simulation laboratory. Can they survive under the deadly conditions of Mars? Researchers believe there are planets on which alien life can exist. In 1991 the Swiss astrophysicist Michel Mayor discovered the world's first exoplanet. Since then, about 3,000 planets have been detected outside our solar system. Heike Rauer from the German Aerospace Center is looking for habitable planets. Will she find a second earth? The European Southern Observatory is also searching for life in space, building the largest telescope in the world. In the next 20 years the E-ELT should be able to prove the existence of life on distant planets. How would extraterrestrials look? Some scientists suspect that they may well resemble us humans. Under other environmental conditions, alien life could also arise completely differently. It could be formed from methane and silicon. Different gravity would form alien bodies completely differently. Could extraterrestrials send us messages? At the SETI Institute in California, alien hunters like Seth Shostak are listening to signals from alien civilizations. But mere listening is no longer enough. Some SETI researchers now want to send messages to the aliens themselves. They hope to finally get an answer. But would that be a bad idea? Many scientists warn of the dangers of establishing contact. The former SETI researcher and science fiction author David Brin also fears that it could be a devastating mistake. With well-meant news we could end up attracting attention from hostile civilizations. Should we really tell them that we exist and where they can find us?</desc>
    <date>20230317</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/worldwarawhenaliensattack_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708090051 +0000" stop="20250708100240 +0000">
    <title>Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland" is a wildlife documentary about a white-tailed eagle family, a young otter and a giant catfish that share the wetlands of this country in Central Europe. Hungary lies in the bottom of the huge Pannonian Basin encircled by the peaks of the Alps and the Carpathians.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/wildhungaryawaterwonderland_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708100240 +0000" stop="20250708110124 +0000">
    <title>Wild Serbia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Serbia is in the heart of the Balkans, a “little Europe“ within Europe; with its rich variety of landscapes and natural beauties, it certainly does this name justice. This nature documentary presents Serbia's breath-taking, picturesque regions and unique wildlife on a journey to the most beautiful and wildest areas of the Balkan peninsula, from high mountains across gentle hills to the vast plains of the Puszta.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/wildserbia_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708110124 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title>Big is beautiful</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The world is full of giants, huge creatures that fill us with awe and wonder. Some are gentle giants. Others are deadly hunters. There are different ways of defining ‘big’ - biggest in volume, or the biggest of their kind. But one thing is for sure, the huge animals of this world are fascinating, diverse and beautiful.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bigisbeautiful_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708125702 +0000">
    <title>Cleopatra</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>She commanded armies and built warships. She was ruthless with rivals and quick to eliminate traitors. She spoke at least nine languages, received diplomats and negotiated with kings. But the last woman to rule Egypt is a legend today because of her powers of seduction.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708125702 +0000" stop="20250708135736 +0000">
    <title>Elizabeth I</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In an era dominated by men, Queen Elizabeth I was the only woman. She ruled England for 45 years, laying the foundation for the British Empire, and when she died in 1603 she gave her name to an entire epoch: the Elizabethan Age. Nobody would have thought this possible when she was younger – least of all herself.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708135736 +0000" stop="20250708145634 +0000">
    <title>Queen Louise of Prussia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Some countries attain crucial characteristics under female rule, such as the England of Queen Elizabeth I and the Russia of Catherine the Great. And then there are women who do not rule and yet manage to leave their mark on their land, their era. One of these, known as the Queen of Hearts during her lifetime, was Louise of Prussia. Though she had no official political or military power, she wielded influence over the men who did - predominantly her husband King Frederick Wilhelm III - and she had the stature and style to become a symbolic figure.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708145634 +0000" stop="20250708155813 +0000">
    <title>The Leaden Age</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the mid-fifties Franco's foreign policy successes opened up new perspectives for Spain. After years of stagnation the country was now moving forwards. Thus, Franco's rule was legitimized. Resistance fell silent. The dictator sat firmly in the saddle. But along with the new friends, new influences also entered the country.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/thetruthaboutfrancospainsforgottendictatorship_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708155813 +0000" stop="20250708165644 +0000">
    <title>Lost Treasures of the Silk Road</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>China - the “Middle Empire” has long been thought to have developed completely independently of the West. Historic writings from as far back as the fourth pre-Christian millennium document the image of an isolated China, which has apparently evolved without any noteworthy boundary points to the West.</desc>
    <date>20230525</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708165644 +0000" stop="20250708175436 +0000">
    <title>Secret Societies</title>
    <sub-title>The Masks of the Conspirators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Did the Americans really manage to land on the Moon in the 1960s? Or was this ground-breaking event staged in the desert of Nevada? Were the people behind the 9/11 attacks really fanatical Muslims or did the American government play a part? Could Jesus have had descendants, as some authors speculate? The history of humankind is full of conspiracy theories.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/secretsocieties_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708175436 +0000" stop="20250708185450 +0000">
    <title>Animals That Changed History - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>Plagues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>For most of our history, people have fallen victim to crippling disease, and not had a clue where it came from. Despite our best efforts, we are vulnerable - not, perhaps, to lions, tigers, and bears - but more to the killers we can’t even see. In America during the early 1980s, a mysterious new disease claims the lives of 159 people, most of them gay men.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/animalsthatchangedhistory_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708185450 +0000" stop="20250708195504 +0000">
    <title>Animals That Changed History - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>Inspiration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As a species, we believe we are more than just animals. We are inspired to express ourselves through words, art, music, and scientific endeavours. Our ancestors painted animals on cave walls - usually large mammals, like bison and deer. Animals were out first artistic subject, our first inspiration.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/animalsthatchangedhistory_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708195504 +0000" stop="20250708205406 +0000">
    <title>Cleopatra</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>She commanded armies and built warships. She was ruthless with rivals and quick to eliminate traitors. She spoke at least nine languages, received diplomats and negotiated with kings. But the last woman to rule Egypt is a legend today because of her powers of seduction.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708205406 +0000" stop="20250708215640 +0000">
    <title>Elizabeth I</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In an era dominated by men, Queen Elizabeth I was the only woman. She ruled England for 45 years, laying the foundation for the British Empire, and when she died in 1603 she gave her name to an entire epoch: the Elizabethan Age. Nobody would have thought this possible when she was younger – least of all herself.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10_0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708215640 +0000" stop="20250708225738 +0000">
    <title>Queen Louise of Prussia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Some countries attain crucial characteristics under female rule, such as the England of Queen Elizabeth I and the Russia of Catherine the Great. And then there are women who do not rule and yet manage to leave their mark on their land, their era. One of these, known as the Queen of Hearts during her lifetime, was Louise of Prussia. Though she had no official political or military power, she wielded influence over the men who did - predominantly her husband King Frederick Wilhelm III - and she had the stature and style to become a symbolic figure.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/womenwhomadehistory_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250708225738 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title>The Leaden Age</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the mid-fifties Franco's foreign policy successes opened up new perspectives for Spain. After years of stagnation the country was now moving forwards. Thus, Franco's rule was legitimized. Resistance fell silent. The dictator sat firmly in the saddle. But along with the new friends, new influences also entered the country.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/thetruthaboutfrancospainsforgottendictatorship_s01_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709010302 +0000">
    <title>World War A - When Aliens Attack</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Scientists are already looking feverishly for evidence of extraterrestrial life. With the ExoMars mission, ESA will soon find life on Mars. If there are only tiny microbes, there could also be life in other places in the universe. But can life in space exist at all? The exobiologist Jean-Pierre de Vera collects microorganisms around the world and tests them in his Mars simulation laboratory. Can they survive under the deadly conditions of Mars? Researchers believe there are planets on which alien life can exist. In 1991 the Swiss astrophysicist Michel Mayor discovered the world's first exoplanet. Since then, about 3,000 planets have been detected outside our solar system. Heike Rauer from the German Aerospace Center is looking for habitable planets. Will she find a second earth? The European Southern Observatory is also searching for life in space, building the largest telescope in the world. In the next 20 years the E-ELT should be able to prove the existence of life on distant planets. How would extraterrestrials look? Some scientists suspect that they may well resemble us humans. Under other environmental conditions, alien life could also arise completely differently. It could be formed from methane and silicon. Different gravity would form alien bodies completely differently. Could extraterrestrials send us messages? At the SETI Institute in California, alien hunters like Seth Shostak are listening to signals from alien civilizations. But mere listening is no longer enough. Some SETI researchers now want to send messages to the aliens themselves. They hope to finally get an answer. But would that be a bad idea? Many scientists warn of the dangers of establishing contact. The former SETI researcher and science fiction author David Brin also fears that it could be a devastating mistake. With well-meant news we could end up attracting attention from hostile civilizations. Should we really tell them that we exist and where they can find us?</desc>
    <date>20230317</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/worldwarawhenaliensattack_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250709010302 +0000" stop="20250709020451 +0000">
    <title>Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Wild Hungary - A Water Wonderland" is a wildlife documentary about a white-tailed eagle family, a young otter and a giant catfish that share the wetlands of this country in Central Europe. Hungary lies in the bottom of the huge Pannonian Basin encircled by the peaks of the Alps and the Carpathians.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/wildhungaryawaterwonderland_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
