<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708004335 +0000" stop="20250708020643 +0000">
    <title>The Right Ingredients</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Follows the story of four different couples with mismatched personalities, goals, and scenarios, and shows how a good relationship can take multiple ingredients, but it only takes the right one to make it last a lifetime.</desc>
    <date>20250318</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708020643 +0000" stop="20250708043120 +0000">
    <title>The Walk of Rufus</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Eldest son, Rufus, takes over the family empire of running the streets of Chicago, but change comes at a cost.</desc>
    <date>20210721</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/eec18682d8bc49f80ee218022483e0ff.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708043120 +0000" stop="20250708060015 +0000">
    <title>The Walk of Rufus 2: Theodis</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Theodis and Rufus are brothers who grow up to become powerful Chicago Kingpins. When rufus is murdered, Theodis sets out on a path of revenge making those responsible for his brother's death pay a high price.</desc>
    <date>20240409</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gAx7pfo6QopxXpcsDr84iWDzerh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708060015 +0000" stop="20250708080632 +0000">
    <title>The Frozen Hearts: A Love Story</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A couple attempt to find their way back to each other after a traumatic loss. Bombarded with advice and opinions from their friends and family about their relationship, will they work it out? Or fall out of love?</desc>
    <date>20240123</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d05b90e83facecb48eb09023b3d623c4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708080632 +0000" stop="20250708095017 +0000">
    <title>Street Crimes Unit</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Detective Mills and Detective Smith are assigned to the Street Crimes Unit of the Police Department. While on a stakeout one day, Mills and Smith see a local politician, Alex Johnstone, arguing with his mistress. Days later the mistress goes missing. Mills decides to investigate Alex Johnstone, even after being told by his supervisor not to do so. Mills convinces Smith that they must find the evidence that connects Alex Johnstone to the missing woman before he tracks them down.</desc>
    <date>20240521</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/aecb7b97a90a4a649c9c281eacf27a91.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708095017 +0000" stop="20250708111532 +0000">
    <title>Say Less</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Kimbra is struggling in her current relationship with her boyfriend Donta, who is mentally abusive and and sleeps around with other women. When she finds the courage to leave and stand up for herself, she is killed by an unknown assailant. As the police try to find evidence to convict Donta, her friends must find the strength to find out the truth, and seek justice for Kimbra’s death.</desc>
    <date>20240820</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708111532 +0000" stop="20250708123917 +0000">
    <title>Kingsmen</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Follows the story of the King family, a known crime syndicate in Dallas. When the beloved patriarch is killed, they fall under the wrath of a rival crime family, as well as local law enforcement. The four eldest brothers will do everything they can to protect their family.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lDYnFSW8VVdEtItGcsNBxurldWg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708123917 +0000" stop="20250708141358 +0000">
    <title>Induced 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After a harrowing event that nearly kills Claudia, she and her husband try their best to move on. Claudia and Marcus then hire a new mid-wife to assist as they prepare for their new child. But they don’t know that Erica is lurking in the shadows, and she wants that baby.</desc>
    <date>20240903</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/1828f35a0c38d6fe8f7f412f49df7756.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708141358 +0000" stop="20250708154236 +0000">
    <title>Hidden Secrets</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In this captivating drama anthology, secrets unravel within eight unique stories. In a diverse world, characters from various walks of life confront hidden truths, connections, and sparking unexpected consequences. With each tale offering a glimpse into private lives, viewers are left questioning motives, trust, and morality.</desc>
    <date>20240611</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708154236 +0000" stop="20250708174613 +0000">
    <title>Plain Sight</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Raven Harris is a woman with a plan. She's determined to create the life that she and her brother Rashon have been dreaming of, but someone is determined to not only turn her life into a nightmare but to end it.</desc>
    <date>20240312</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4f7776b27bc3d8a06a7c20c11232e4de.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708174613 +0000" stop="20250708191428 +0000">
    <title>Back Home</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Drug kingpin Jay looks to expand his drug empire with the help of his business partners, and his girlfriend Passion. However, Polo and Marco have their own agenda’s, which could lead to chaos, as a potential drug war descends upon Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/609aa989726588d38d523bfe3705d83f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708191428 +0000" stop="20250708205207 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708205207 +0000" stop="20250708230740 +0000">
    <title>Troublesome</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Veteran homicide detective Michael reluctantly partners with rookie Derrick. Witnessing a double homicide, they survive a deadly chase, but Derrick is wounded. The suspects are linked to the kingpin, who retaliates by ordering murders across the city. As chaos erupts, the FBI joins the case, revealing the kingpin's identity. Michael finds a weak link, offering a chance to finally catch him.</desc>
    <date>20250609</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bba572182a25acd3645156c83fc0e787.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250708230740 +0000" stop="20250709010003 +0000">
    <title>The Kitty Hallow Killer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A serial killer is on the loose in Houston killing pedophiles and rapists. When Mason and Jessica get into a horrible car accident on their wedding day, Jessica wakes up with no memory of her life or even her husband. As her memories start to come back in pieces, she is afraid that her husband, Mason, could be The Kitty Hallow Killer.</desc>
    <date>20250527</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGZhYTlhMWYtOTMwNC00OWVkLWEzYWUtNmExNzllYmY1MDJjXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250709010003 +0000" stop="20250709023301 +0000">
    <title>Pinch</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A talented MC uses larceny to fund his dreams of becoming a rap star, but his life changes when he meets Allie, now the once self-centered thief is transformed into the Robin Hood for the hood.</desc>
    <date>20201221</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c0529ac93daca7b4601ad78f657f4503.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
