<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250714232346 +0000" stop="20250715010007 +0000">
    <title>Troubled Mystic</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tracie is a single mother who meets Corey Daniels, the calculated and “perfect guy” looking for his next perfect family to manipulate by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>20241030</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f7df975ec413ad1c5cde5d61b67b1ef1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715010007 +0000" stop="20250715023724 +0000">
    <title>Vegas Vixens</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In Las Vegas, an escort’s murder ignites a fierce pursuit of justice. Her sister, undercover agent Sophia, teams up with disillusioned Detective Reddick to bring her killer to justice. As they delve deeper, a web of sex trafficking and drugs emerges, revealing hidden secrets and betrayals. Facing danger and corruption within the system, the women fight to dismantle a criminal empire and find closure in a city where justice seems elusive.</desc>
    <date>20241009</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f5862403f55484283608f6daedbc850f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715023724 +0000" stop="20250715043327 +0000">
    <title>My Husband's Mistress</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Behind the glamorous facade of the aviation industry, a dirty betrayal unfolds. A devoted wife's world is shattered when she discovers her husband's affair with her best friend. As the truth unravels, a battle for love, revenge, and survival ensues.</desc>
    <date>20250314</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/eeaf019f31b415c24f4fd70b41e4dfa3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715043327 +0000" stop="20250715060745 +0000">
    <title>Single Saved and Searching</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Leah puts all of her trust in God when it came to her relationships. For some reason her relationships still weren’t working out. After a big breakup with a long time boyfriend Leah sends out a prayer that would turn into an unexpected journey. God gives Leah a gift that makes men appear at her will, but Leah still questions why God gave her this gift.</desc>
    <date>20240402</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/dc13bb86851cbaba2d5bf368c8e5eb2f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715060745 +0000" stop="20250715073217 +0000">
    <title>Bottle Girl</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Diamond's dream of going to college is threatened by financial hardship. A desperate job at a glamorous Atlanta lounge exposes her to a world of temptation and danger. Can she navigate the high-stakes world of money, drugs, and sex, or will it consume her?</desc>
    <date>20241125</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/08803fb158a5a3b39e0351d5f604fc16.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715073217 +0000" stop="20250715104221 +0000">
    <title>Redemption</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Lost and grieving, Chris seeks solace in the wrong crowd. A chance encounter with the enigmatic Patrick leads him down a dangerous path, forcing him to confront his own morality and the consequences of his choices.</desc>
    <date>20250311</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715104221 +0000" stop="20250715121815 +0000">
    <title>My Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Trina, a young model, becomes entangled with the charming Max. As their relationship deepens, she uncovers his dark secrets: a double life, a psychotic ex-girlfriend, and a dangerous obsession. When Trina crosses a line, she becomes the target of a deadly game of cat and mouse. Betrayal, madness, and murder ensue as the lines between love, obsession, and survival blur.</desc>
    <date>20250304</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kzAArDmLvZRykW8Y3iFtGXvKP8s.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715121815 +0000" stop="20250715135505 +0000">
    <title>Quiet as Kept</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jay is unlawfully detained. His ex-girlfriend returns, and his business partners work to clear his name. Meanwhile, a crooked cop is under suspicion for murder, and connections are made between him and Jay. Torn between duty and loyalty, Detective Johnson is caught in the middle. As the prosecution struggles, Jay and his business partners work to exist the dangerous world cleanly.</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5fa2e5e76cbd14dc53effefd218e9aa9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715135505 +0000" stop="20250715154355 +0000">
    <title>Father Knows Best</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Zoe Miles, raised by a controlling father who introduces her to a life of crime, grapples with the lingering trauma of her mother's death. Yearning to embrace the spiritual life she shared with her grandmother, Zoe finds herself trapped in a cycle of violence, forced to rob drug dealers after witnessing a terrifying crime. Desperate to escape this destructive path, she struggles against her father's suffocating control, fearing the loss of his approval and the validation she desperately seeks.</desc>
    <date>20250601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/18d26cbc267a4ee268c4ea4278f205de.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715154355 +0000" stop="20250715171956 +0000">
    <title>Curfew: Sins of the Father</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Former police captain Thomas Cooper, once a respected figure, finds himself entangled in a dangerous deal with a notorious crime boss. His involvement leads to a love triangle and ultimately a betrayal. Now, haunted by his past, Thomas must confront the consequences when his son, Christian, becomes a target of the crime boss's revenge.</desc>
    <date>20250218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/smDUGZZxv6gAaZxk4yjv9SuJ70K.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715171956 +0000" stop="20250715184812 +0000">
    <title>Back Home</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Drug kingpin Jay looks to expand his drug empire with the help of his business partners, and his girlfriend Passion. However, Polo and Marco have their own agenda’s, which could lead to chaos, as a potential drug war descends upon Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/609aa989726588d38d523bfe3705d83f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715184812 +0000" stop="20250715202551 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715202551 +0000" stop="20250715224123 +0000">
    <title>Troublesome</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Veteran homicide detective Michael reluctantly partners with rookie Derrick. Witnessing a double homicide, they survive a deadly chase, but Derrick is wounded. The suspects are linked to the kingpin, who retaliates by ordering murders across the city. As chaos erupts, the FBI joins the case, revealing the kingpin's identity. Michael finds a weak link, offering a chance to finally catch him.</desc>
    <date>20250609</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bba572182a25acd3645156c83fc0e787.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250715224123 +0000" stop="20250716001641 +0000">
    <title>All the Love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman begins her journey to adulthood, navigating love and self-discovery, while being haunted by a mysterious past that she can’t fully remember. As murders and violence swirl around her, she wonders who she can trust. Will she find love or suffer the same mysterious fate as her birth parents?</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6589e799a5ad0a6e19fa52d1d64f0025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
