<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d">
    <display-name>CNN Originals</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/00f41feb-c13e-4a3d-b7ca-c9bb253d19be/CNN_Originals_RDX_color_logo.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250717235258 +0000" stop="20250718004238 +0000">
    <title>American Style</title>
    <sub-title>1990s/2000s: 21st Century Vogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 01/20/2019. As the millennium came to an end, women made strides in the workplace and in media. In the 2000s, the internet brought drastic changes to American life.</desc>
    <date>20190120</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oNWMME87apSWNV4kYI7w24mvM05.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718004238 +0000" stop="20250718013240 +0000">
    <title>United Shades of America</title>
    <sub-title>The Time for Reparations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/16/2020. Kamau heads to New Orleans to explore the topic of reparations. He learns that while there is a popular assumption that reparations means doling out a check, many scholars and activists believe the first step is an unflinching acknowledgement of the scale and scope of slavery and the systemic oppression that followed with Jim Crow laws, redlining and Black Codes.</desc>
    <date>20200816</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/series/310297/episodes/5f3a9932d8a30.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718013240 +0000" stop="20250718022244 +0000">
    <title>United Shades of America</title>
    <sub-title>Venezuelans in Florida</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/23/2020. Kamau heads to South Florida, home of the largest number of Venezuelans in the United States. He meets with newly arrived Venezuelans, as well as established Venezuelan-Americans in the community, to better understand the complicated crisis that displaced millions from their homes. It’s a story of loss, hope, and how the U.S. system’s actions regarding Venezuelans here and abroad, has political implications for us all.</desc>
    <date>20200823</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/series/310297/episodes/5f44891651071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718022244 +0000" stop="20250718031249 +0000">
    <title>United Shades of America</title>
    <sub-title>Iranian-Americans in NY</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/30/2020. Within the conventional American imagination, Iran is too often associated with little that is good: the 1979 Islamic Revolution, the Iran hostage crisis, and its nuclear program. But the United States and Iran are as connected as they are oppositional––deeply intertwined through culture and politics. Kamau visits New York City to talk to recent Iranian immigrants and those who came here decades ago, to learn about their American experience.</desc>
    <date>20210613</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/v4/episode/8408258/screencap/60c8c04421781.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718031249 +0000" stop="20250718040319 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Hawaii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/14/15. There’s another side to Hawaii that many tourists don’t know about. Go with Anthony Bourdain as he explores the unknown area.</desc>
    <date>20150614</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fRqe6sBYlQn3zD0m1K9vMFUe6Cv.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718040319 +0000" stop="20250718045349 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Beirut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/21/15. Anthony Bourdain travels to Beirut, where he discovers a beautiful country known for its vibrant nightlife and legendary cuisine.</desc>
    <date>20150621</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vTtbylD5Ul8jEvMNNELGt9IQGWz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718045349 +0000" stop="20250718054420 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>New Jersey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/31/15. Anthony Bourdain travels to his childhood home state with his brother Chris, where they rekindle memories at the classic roadside joint, Hiram’s.</desc>
    <date>20150531</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f9HZRKSdby10MtqTAeGfSsZuVXy.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718054420 +0000" stop="20250718063425 +0000">
    <title>United Shades of America</title>
    <sub-title>The Homeless Crisis in LA</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/30/2020. Kamau spends time on LA’s notorious Skid Row. This large area of downtown LA is the epicenter of the nation’s devastating housing crisis and home to a community of thousands of houseless individuals whose tents have become the marker of failed policy and economic inclusion in our country. Here, Kamau explores the racial, socio-economic and statistical dynamics that drive this national crisis. He meets with those who call “The Row” home and those compelled to help.</desc>
    <date>20200830</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/v4/episode/7882698/screencap/60acf44e25851.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718063425 +0000" stop="20250718072425 +0000">
    <title>American Style</title>
    <sub-title>1940s/50s: War Boots to Work Suits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 01/13/2019. During a time of unprecedented expansion in prosperity and consumerism, America felt pressure for conformity as paranoia set in over a growing cold war.</desc>
    <date>20190113</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LW6GfgfiptjLNS3dEZ8iOhbvxv.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718072425 +0000" stop="20250718081426 +0000">
    <title>American Style</title>
    <sub-title>1960s/70s: Born to be Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 01/13/2019. With a new president and a sense of confidence, the youth culture evolves into its own and demands equal rights and recognition of their unique identities.</desc>
    <date>20190113</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fjJXVDzTBN4ef8liQ05M0Wjl86q.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718081426 +0000" stop="20250718090426 +0000">
    <title>American Style</title>
    <sub-title>1980s: Material World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 01/20/2019. The Reagan era brought in optimism, which led to extravagance and greed, as brands capitalize on spending and Wall Street capitalizes on the public.</desc>
    <date>20190120</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nBxrwTzwLdc6jml2N1fQjWhhxdk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718090426 +0000" stop="20250718095407 +0000">
    <title>American Style</title>
    <sub-title>1990s/2000s: 21st Century Vogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 01/20/2019. As the millennium came to an end, women made strides in the workplace and in media. In the 2000s, the internet brought drastic changes to American life.</desc>
    <date>20190120</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oNWMME87apSWNV4kYI7w24mvM05.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718095407 +0000" stop="20250718095959 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Calabria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/9/2022. Calabria is a region of rugged landscapes, dramatic mountain ranges, and some 500 miles of incredible coastline. Connected to Basilicata in the north and separated from Sicily in the south by the narrow Strait of Messina, Calabria is also the homeland of the Tucci family’s ancestors. In this episode, Stanley Tucci travels through the region, discovering the history of this beautiful and troubled place, as well as the history of his own family. Joined by his parents and reunited with Italian relatives, he reflects on the inspiration people draw from Calabria, and why those who leave this region feel compelled to return.</desc>
    <date>20221009</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fG8fsFsm9kMUsTkC7HCifVmagBj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718095959 +0000" stop="20250718104410 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Calabria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/9/2022. Calabria is a region of rugged landscapes, dramatic mountain ranges, and some 500 miles of incredible coastline. Connected to Basilicata in the north and separated from Sicily in the south by the narrow Strait of Messina, Calabria is also the homeland of the Tucci family’s ancestors. In this episode, Stanley Tucci travels through the region, discovering the history of this beautiful and troubled place, as well as the history of his own family. Joined by his parents and reunited with Italian relatives, he reflects on the inspiration people draw from Calabria, and why those who leave this region feel compelled to return.</desc>
    <date>20221009</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fG8fsFsm9kMUsTkC7HCifVmagBj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718104410 +0000" stop="20250718113413 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Sardinia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/16/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits the Italian island of Sardinia. Famous for its harsh, rugged landscape, crystal blue ocean, and passionately preserved traditions, Tucci will learn how Sardinian food culture varies wildly throughout the island. He experiences the culinary delights of its coastal cities influenced by previous civilizations, and ventures inland to discover the rural heart of Sardinia, which remains untouched from outsider influence. This mysterious and mystical island is full of treasures and Sardinians are proud of their heritage and culinary diversity. One thing is certain: whoever steps foot on this island, will never want to leave.</desc>
    <date>20221016</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6NEc6YIycrsCbP94bWzAGC8ViJd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718113413 +0000" stop="20250718122416 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Puglia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/23/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits Puglia, a region famous for its fragrant olive oil, beautiful vegetables, cheeses, and durum wheat. Despite being such a fertile region, Puglia is also one of Italy's poorest and Tucci discovers how today’s spirit of innovation was forged out of hard times. From Bari’s raw seafood to Cisternino’s Fornelli and Foggia’s burnt grain to cheesemaker Vito’s Apulian blue cheeses, it is clear that by reclaiming their past, the Pugliese are taking ownership of their past and embracing the future on their own terms.</desc>
    <date>20220515</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xuXw7L80avbHcUjtc9beOG2PL1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718122416 +0000" stop="20250718131416 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>A Family Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/11/2021. Every sitcom is, at its heart, a reflection of America’s core social “situation” - the family. This episode explores how sitcoms evolve to reflect the changing face of this most fundamental social unit. From I Love Lucy to the blended Brady Bunch, from working class families in All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time and Roseanne to the aspirational The Cosby Show, from the groundbreaking Black-ish to Fresh off the Boat, sitcom humor has helped broaden our horizons and open our minds to what a Modern Family can be. Featuring sitcoms such as Brady Bunch, I Love Lucy, All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time, Roseanne, The Cosby Show, Black-ish, Fresh off the Boat, and Modern Family.</desc>
    <date>20210711</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rjRmsubnWj2RCQj8nY3tCy8qymS.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718131416 +0000" stop="20250718140421 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Sex &amp; the Sitcom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/11/2021. Lucy and Desi couldn’t sleep in the same bed but Fleabag sleeps with her priest. American’s changing attitudes towards sex, women’s rights, and gender identity – and the winding path from sex as taboo to sex as punchline – have been mapped out with remarkable clarity on the sitcom screen. From “closeted” gay characters like Uncle Arthur on Bewitched to Ellen’s coming out to Mitch and Cam’s marriage on Modern Family; from Edie, the first Black trans woman on The Jeffersons to Joey Soloway's groundbreaking Transparent; sitcom laughs have helped audiences understand that the world can be so much funnier when not seen solely through a white, cis-gendered, straight point of view. Featuring sitcoms such as Fleabag, Sex and the City, Bewitched, Modern Family, The Jefferson’s, and Transparent.</desc>
    <date>20210711</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b0xLKtmiRzHNBsYWbV1FfhYHvdv.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718140421 +0000" stop="20250718145422 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Just Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/18/2021. Friends, Seinfeld, Living Single – so many of us know the characters in these shows better than most of our real friends. By the 90s, these “hanging out with friends” sitcoms become the vital force driving the genre – and in many ways, pop culture. But it’s earlier shows like The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Laverne and Shirley, What’s Happening!!, The Facts of Life and Golden Girls that set the stage for peak friends sitcom, and it’s iconic follow-ups like Curb Your Enthusiasm, Community, How I Met Your Mother and New Girl that bring that form into the new millennium. Featuring sitcoms such as Friends, Seinfeld, Living Simple, The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Laverne and Shirley, What’s Happening!!, The Facts of Life, Golden Girls, Curb Your Enthusiasm, Community, How I Met Your Mother, and New Girl.</desc>
    <date>20210718</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3SRQMgGOwItxOQDtvLSSCHekBfZ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718145422 +0000" stop="20250718154422 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Working for Laughs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/25/2021. The workplace is a rich source of comedy as it binds vastly different people together with laughter. From The Mary Tyler Moore Show to Murphy Brown, from WKRP to 30 Rock, from Barney Miller to Brooklyn 99, from Designing Women to Veep, as America’s relationship with their jobs changes - and especially as women break through countless workplace barriers - sitcoms evolve in endlessly humorous ways. Featuring sitcoms such as The Marry Tyler Moore Show, Murphy Brown, WKRP, 30 Rock, Barney Miller, Brooklyn 99, Designing Women, and Veep.</desc>
    <date>20210725</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4bUX7PxQ2oEcQBshbxQRbHBch4C.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718154422 +0000" stop="20250718163427 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Facing Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/1/2021. With cutting-edge humor, pioneering creators and sitcom stars have helped open generations of American minds to the intractable problems of racial injustice and representation. Icons like Norman Lear, Diahann Carroll, Red Foxx and Freddie Prinze smash open doors with All in the Family, Julia, Sanford and Son and Chico and the Man. But with racist roots running as deep as Amos ‘n’ Andy, the sitcom has had a long, hard road to authentic, inclusive 21st century comedies like Black-ish and Fresh off the Boat. Featuring sitcoms such as All in the Family, Julia, Sanford and Son, Chico and the Man, Amon ‘n’ Andy, Black-ish, and Fresh off the Boat.</desc>
    <date>20210801</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zXNH2uTRXO3EUFkNo3nAdIDLgvP.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718163427 +0000" stop="20250718172430 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Liguria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/30/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits one of the most famous and frequented regions of Italy – the Italian Riviera – which is famous for the glitz and glamour of Portofino and stunning picture-perfect fishing villages of the Cinque Terre. Liguria is a thin strip of mountainous land, sandwiched between the Alps and Apennines, and lined with rugged scenery and stunning coastal views. The capital of Genoa, once a wealthy merchant empire, offers a richness of cuisine fit for a prince from personalized stamped pasta to its most internationally acclaimed export, Genoese pesto. Tucci will discover how Ligurians have learned to adapt to life in this difficult landscape and how they have found ingenious solutions to survive frugally yet thrive.</desc>
    <date>20221030</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/89MgM8OHBURBIhGSzkQC7j2AuML.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718172430 +0000" stop="20250718181433 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Calabria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/9/2022. Calabria is a region of rugged landscapes, dramatic mountain ranges, and some 500 miles of incredible coastline. Connected to Basilicata in the north and separated from Sicily in the south by the narrow Strait of Messina, Calabria is also the homeland of the Tucci family’s ancestors. In this episode, Stanley Tucci travels through the region, discovering the history of this beautiful and troubled place, as well as the history of his own family. Joined by his parents and reunited with Italian relatives, he reflects on the inspiration people draw from Calabria, and why those who leave this region feel compelled to return.</desc>
    <date>20221009</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fG8fsFsm9kMUsTkC7HCifVmagBj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718181433 +0000" stop="20250718190436 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Sardinia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/16/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits the Italian island of Sardinia. Famous for its harsh, rugged landscape, crystal blue ocean, and passionately preserved traditions, Tucci will learn how Sardinian food culture varies wildly throughout the island. He experiences the culinary delights of its coastal cities influenced by previous civilizations, and ventures inland to discover the rural heart of Sardinia, which remains untouched from outsider influence. This mysterious and mystical island is full of treasures and Sardinians are proud of their heritage and culinary diversity. One thing is certain: whoever steps foot on this island, will never want to leave.</desc>
    <date>20221016</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6NEc6YIycrsCbP94bWzAGC8ViJd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718190436 +0000" stop="20250718195437 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Movin’ on Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/8/2021. No sitcom finds more endlessly inventive humor in implicit class tensions than Frasier, as a working-class father tries to get along with his sublimely high-brow sons. But though the American Dream of social mobility underpins America’s social contract, that dream is so often beyond reach that it takes sitcom humor to help laugh at the struggles of getting ahead. The Honeymooners, The Beverly Hillbillies, The Andy Griffith Show, Good Times, Alice and Roseanne all offer funny snapshots at class divisions in America, divisions that are even starker in Arrested Development and Schitt’s Creek. But It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia that asks the hardest, perhaps funniest question of all – is this aspirational game we’re all playing really rigged against us? Featuring sitcoms such as The Honeymooners, The Beverly Hillbillies, The Andy Griffith Show, Good Time, Alice, Roseanne, Arrested Development, Schitt’s Creek, and It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>20210808</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8gcFmMG0Ys3t0aapIGw9niZAoGC.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718195437 +0000" stop="20250718204437 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Freaks, Geeks &amp; Outsiders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/15/2021. Though the nerds in Big Bang Theory owned the airwaves in the new millennium, sitcoms have always found humor in fish-out-of-water stories, whether about immigrants, aliens, witches, monsters, nerds, or teens. Bewitched and Sabrina long cast a spell on audiences, while Mork and Mindy and 3rd Rock from the Sun give us fresh, funny alien insights into ourselves. Who can’t help snapping their fingers with The Addams Family theme, or not laugh at Urkel’s “Did I do that?” In one way or another, audiences relate to outsiders, and these iconic characters give license to laugh at our own foibles in ways few other forms of entertainment do. Featuring sitcoms such as Mark and Mindy, Bewitched, 3rd Rock from the Sun, The Addams Family, and Big Bang Theory.</desc>
    <date>20210815</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ph8rgxDSvCmUgaAAkXipXtjb6sW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718204437 +0000" stop="20250718213438 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Escaping Reality</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/22/2021. In ever-changing America, sitcoms have offered an escape from the pressures of a turbulent social and media landscape, often through nostalgia and sheer absurdity. From Gilligan’s Island to Get Smart, from The Love Boat to Full House, they are a funny comfort food – an antidote to fear of a fast-changing world. But what sitcoms offer escape from, and what visions they escape to, reveal deep insights into the state of the American psyche and the sitcom form itself. The Simpsons blows up a live-action sitcom mold grown stale to usher in a new era of adult animation, while BoJack Horseman and The Good Place offer deep soul-searching dives to help audiences cope with the 21st century. Featuring sitcoms such as Gilligan’s Island, Get Smart, The Love Boat, Full House, The Simpsons, BoJack Horseman, and The Good Place.</desc>
    <date>20210822</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l1MA7lSMOHtX2EXRLP3nwTL7Enz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718213438 +0000" stop="20250718222438 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>A Family Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/11/2021. Every sitcom is, at its heart, a reflection of America’s core social “situation” - the family. This episode explores how sitcoms evolve to reflect the changing face of this most fundamental social unit. From I Love Lucy to the blended Brady Bunch, from working class families in All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time and Roseanne to the aspirational The Cosby Show, from the groundbreaking Black-ish to Fresh off the Boat, sitcom humor has helped broaden our horizons and open our minds to what a Modern Family can be. Featuring sitcoms such as Brady Bunch, I Love Lucy, All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time, Roseanne, The Cosby Show, Black-ish, Fresh off the Boat, and Modern Family.</desc>
    <date>20210711</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rjRmsubnWj2RCQj8nY3tCy8qymS.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718222438 +0000" stop="20250718231443 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Sex &amp; the Sitcom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/11/2021. Lucy and Desi couldn’t sleep in the same bed but Fleabag sleeps with her priest. American’s changing attitudes towards sex, women’s rights, and gender identity – and the winding path from sex as taboo to sex as punchline – have been mapped out with remarkable clarity on the sitcom screen. From “closeted” gay characters like Uncle Arthur on Bewitched to Ellen’s coming out to Mitch and Cam’s marriage on Modern Family; from Edie, the first Black trans woman on The Jeffersons to Joey Soloway's groundbreaking Transparent; sitcom laughs have helped audiences understand that the world can be so much funnier when not seen solely through a white, cis-gendered, straight point of view. Featuring sitcoms such as Fleabag, Sex and the City, Bewitched, Modern Family, The Jefferson’s, and Transparent.</desc>
    <date>20210711</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b0xLKtmiRzHNBsYWbV1FfhYHvdv.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250718231443 +0000" stop="20250719000446 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Puglia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/23/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits Puglia, a region famous for its fragrant olive oil, beautiful vegetables, cheeses, and durum wheat. Despite being such a fertile region, Puglia is also one of Italy's poorest and Tucci discovers how today’s spirit of innovation was forged out of hard times. From Bari’s raw seafood to Cisternino’s Fornelli and Foggia’s burnt grain to cheesemaker Vito’s Apulian blue cheeses, it is clear that by reclaiming their past, the Pugliese are taking ownership of their past and embracing the future on their own terms.</desc>
    <date>20220515</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xuXw7L80avbHcUjtc9beOG2PL1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719000446 +0000" stop="20250719005449 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Liguria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/30/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits one of the most famous and frequented regions of Italy – the Italian Riviera – which is famous for the glitz and glamour of Portofino and stunning picture-perfect fishing villages of the Cinque Terre. Liguria is a thin strip of mountainous land, sandwiched between the Alps and Apennines, and lined with rugged scenery and stunning coastal views. The capital of Genoa, once a wealthy merchant empire, offers a richness of cuisine fit for a prince from personalized stamped pasta to its most internationally acclaimed export, Genoese pesto. Tucci will discover how Ligurians have learned to adapt to life in this difficult landscape and how they have found ingenious solutions to survive frugally yet thrive.</desc>
    <date>20221030</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/89MgM8OHBURBIhGSzkQC7j2AuML.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
