<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723">
    <display-name>Documentary+</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3bb2a1fe-7a16-4fa1-9db7-63b7fef3a376/documentaryplus_logo_dark_1_WHT.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703094214 +0000" stop="20250703103556 +0000">
    <title>Forensics: Operation Edgewater</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>At 1.20am on a dark rainy Sunday morning the residents of a suburban street are woken by the sounds of a taxi crashing into a brick fence. There was no squealing of brakes. A witness rushes to help and finds the driver slumped over the steering wheel. He is bleeding profusely from wounds in his neck and chest, his foot is still pressing the accelerator, the engine still running.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7acygaeu6sth1q22tjs1emk4q/original/7acygaeu6sth1q22tjs1emk4q.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703103556 +0000" stop="20250703112928 +0000">
    <title>Forensics: Operation Nadia</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>At 7.30am on a mild, summer morning, a middle-aged woman goes into her backyard to unlock the self-contained unit where her 23-year-old daughter lives alone. She lets her daughter’s dog out and notices a pair of overalls lying on the floor, half-in, half-out of the bedroom. The overalls should be with her daughter who, by now, would normally be on her way to work at a recycling facility. The woman takes a closer look and finds her daughter’s body lying face-down on the bedroom floor, cold. She calls out to her husband, they phone emergency services and the operator tells them to roll over their daughter - her throat has - been cut.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1cbgb51p5mtwa1mfq30erkyjg/original/1cbgb51p5mtwa1mfq30erkyjg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703112928 +0000" stop="20250703122643 +0000">
    <title>Forensics: Operation Keppel</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An abandoned car is discovered in a quiet Hamilton street. Police are called and they find an envelope with money in it, an IOU note and a suitcase with women’s clothing in it. They trace the car’s owner as a young mother, Carmen Thomas, who lives in Auckland and hasn’t been seen for several days. Her ex-partner, Brad Callaghan, says that she missed a scheduled pick up of their young son and that he is concerned for her well-being.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/bn5cbjew4jfe13l14dz5bqyf8/original/bn5cbjew4jfe13l14dz5bqyf8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703122643 +0000" stop="20250703132137 +0000">
    <title>Forensics: Operation Drake</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Two males visit a New Plymouth house in the middle of the night, staying only a few hours before they leave. The following day the occupants discover what they think is a body left in the garage. Police are called.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1acti4ftf2h701bv5bu4yetq4/original/1acti4ftf2h701bv5bu4yetq4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703132137 +0000" stop="20250703141605 +0000">
    <title>The Hunt For Gaddafi's Billions: Episode 1</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Inside the relentless hunt for the late Libyan leader Colonel Muammar Gaddafi's money. On the trail of bounty hunters, corrupt politicians and spies. A story of greed, corruption and deceit, up to the highest circles.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/x30d1yjrw06h1eotisc8pnn0l/original/x30d1yjrw06h1eotisc8pnn0l.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703141605 +0000" stop="20250703151350 +0000">
    <title>The Hunt For Gaddafi's Billions: Episode 2</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Inside the relentless hunt for the late Libyan leader Colonel Muammar Gaddafi's money. On the trail of bounty hunters, corrupt politicians and spies. A story of greed, corruption and deceit, up to the highest circles.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/13de4q7rx2evx17f7hpv48sof/original/13de4q7rx2evx17f7hpv48sof.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703151350 +0000" stop="20250703160922 +0000">
    <title>Murderers and Their Mothers: Hamilton</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Thomas Hamilton committed Britain’s deadliest mass shooting when he entered Dunblane Primary School in March 1996 and took the lives of 16 children and their teacher, before turning the gun on himself. Growing up with a hidden family secret and an unhealthy relationship - with his mother, his resentment against the world culminated in an unimaginable, heinous act of evil.</desc>
    <date>20241127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/14sq2z7egn73c1l71566zsu8y/original/14sq2z7egn73c1l71566zsu8y.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703160922 +0000" stop="20250703170615 +0000">
    <title>Murderers and Their Mothers: Peter Sutcliffe: The Yorkshire Ripper</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, serial killer Peter Sutcliffe terrorized the North of England for six years in the 1970s. Nicknamed ‘The Yorkshire Ripper’, he brutally murdered at least 15 women and left many more - seriously injured. Growing up a mummy’s boy, Sutcliffe would later develop a warped view of women and a morbid fascination with the macabre, and would go on to become one of most notorious murderers in British history.</desc>
    <date>20241127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/fj732620pgbz1s25549cpjhka/original/fj732620pgbz1s25549cpjhka.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703170615 +0000" stop="20250703180241 +0000">
    <title>Murderers and Their Mothers: Moore</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter Moore terrorized a community in North Wales for decades, brutally assaulting men in the dead of night under the cover of darkness, all the while living with his doting mother. She - was the centre of his Universe as he was hers, and when she died he embarked on a four-month killing spree, murdering four men in 1995 purely for his own sexual gratification. Moore had been - known as a local hero who, the saviour of the local cinema, nobody suspected Moore, and it was only until his arrest that the truly evil acts of this serial killer were exposed.</desc>
    <date>20241127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/htu9du4t6r5i1bmejjr538kgy/original/htu9du4t6r5i1bmejjr538kgy.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703180241 +0000" stop="20250703185844 +0000">
    <title>Murderers and Their Mothers: Howe</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, 21-year-old Mark Howe developed a deadly obsession with knives, serial killers and violence, and retreated into a virtual world where he shared his unexplainable hatred for his mother with online friends. Once the apple of his mother’s eye, she tried in vain to intervene as her son transformed into a hateful monster. One who would ultimately take her life in a frenzied, violent stabbing, leaving her to bleed to death on her bedroom floor.</desc>
    <date>20241127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/2hcnse9opc619zb4inatwjg3/original/2hcnse9opc619zb4inatwjg3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703185844 +0000" stop="20250703195418 +0000">
    <title>Murderers and Their Mothers: Michael Ryan: The Hungerford Massacre</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, in 1987, Michael Ryan committed Britain’s deadliest massacre of its time, shooting 16 people and injuring 16 more. Doted on by his mother, Ryan grew up to be a spoilt loner who was - obsessed with weapons and the military, creating his own fantasy world in which he modeled himself as a courageous and dangerous action hero. Ryan would go on to carry out a deadly mission of his own making, when he murdered 16 people, including his mother, in cold blood, before finally turning the gun on himself.</desc>
    <date>20241127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/51aotfi731h9154qj53lm92hf/original/51aotfi731h9154qj53lm92hf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703195418 +0000" stop="20250703205016 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Juggling Chainsaws</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It's the Easter Bank holiday in Devon and Cornwall, when the force’s Control Rooms must deal with over a thousand incidents a day with a overstretched crew of frontline officers.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/otz0pzh1iox21o1cn5k8comiq/original/otz0pzh1iox21o1cn5k8comiq.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703205016 +0000" stop="20250703214617 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Breaking Point</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>"This is the worst time I have ever known…if we had more police, they wouldn’t be able to get away with it so easily,” says convenience store owner Colleen, after being robbed for the fifth time in a - little over a year.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/s5vza8ggi8b410jocsexi29hu/original/s5vza8ggi8b410jocsexi29hu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703214617 +0000" stop="20250703224217 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Dark Times</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we see the effects of a changing Britain three years after Brexit, a political event that divided the nation.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1qc5cx2k5gsf71tuviwd6ti2e/original/1qc5cx2k5gsf71tuviwd6ti2e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703224217 +0000" stop="20250703233816 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Random Acts</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode, Random Acts, filmed over just one weekend with Devon &amp; Cornwall police, highlights the extraordinary pressure they’re under.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1fkokr2v2ovij1nkjyixskaqm/original/1fkokr2v2ovij1nkjyixskaqm.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250703233816 +0000" stop="20250704003431 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: No Going Back</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Since 2017 Devon and Cornwall Police are dealing with over 18,000 extra 999 calls, with mental health related incidents now accounting for 40% of their workload.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1lvob47c9utf418hokntpdm54/original/1lvob47c9utf418hokntpdm54.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704003431 +0000" stop="20250704013107 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 1- New York</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Though often overlooked, Latinos have been making contributions to the culture of NYC all along. Whether through food, dance, music or fashion, Latinos have helped make this city what it is: A cultural hub that the world looks to for inspiration. John begins his journey in Jackson Heights, Queens, the borough that shaped him as a man and as an artist, where he highlights the Latino spot that helps make every borough feel like home…the Bodega. He then meets up with DJ Tony Touch to discuss the many ways in which Latinos helped build Hip-Hop culture. Later, he visits the Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre to discuss the lack of access Latinos have to Broadway stages. He then shines a light on Luar, a fashion brand created, owned and operated by Raul Lopez, a true kid from the barrio, who unlike so many Latino designers before him is getting the recognition he deserves. John also pays tribute to salsa music and the people who keep it alive throughout the city. Lastly, John hosts one of his “Legends Dinners” with the help of Colombian chef, Stephanie Del Carmen who focuses on cooking and honoring indigenous food. Food that John, comedian Aida Rodriguez, DJ Tony Touch, Fat Joe and Broadway star Sergio Trujillo enjoy while discussing all things Latin.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/965c76c0p6z11ashduwti9kmu/original/965c76c0p6z11ashduwti9kmu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704013107 +0000" stop="20250704022711 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Episode 2.2</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s Friday morning, just after dawn in a secluded Cornish harbour and a member of public has reported seeing a tiny boat unload an unusual cargo into an awaiting Luton van.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/jr6vnlvzhylh16v6149d9al35/original/jr6vnlvzhylh16v6149d9al35.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704022711 +0000" stop="20250704032149 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 2- Miami</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John tours Miami’s historic sector, Little Havana, with community leader Marvin Tapia, and discusses the influence of the Cuban community in Miami. He then meets with the Borges family who through hard work and sacrifice have turned their dreams of owning a Cuban Coffee shop into a reality. John later meets with actor, playwright and activist Carmen Pelaez to discuss the stronghold the right wing has had on the Latino community and the future of Miami politics. John then visits the arts district of Miami which has earned that title largely due to the Latinx artists who have painted its impressive walls. He speaks with Evoca1, a muralist whose ideology has influenced him to tell complex Latinx stories through his art. Later, John meets up with singer/songwriter Elena Rose to discuss the current state of Latin music, Miami as its hub, and the future for her and other women in the industry. John also visits Peruvian chef Juan Chipoco at his flagship restaurant, Ceviche 105 to learn about his journey to becoming a mogul in the industry, by honoring the food of his homeland. Lastly, John meets up with comedian George Harris, who has built community and gives immigrants a safe place to laugh and rejoice in stories that reflect their personal experiences.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/570lljxleruu19fjda59a1yhd/original/570lljxleruu19fjda59a1yhd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704032149 +0000" stop="20250704041757 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Episode 2.3</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>This is the story of two very different manhunts. One case involves a car, traveling at over 100mph which has flipped off the road and hit a tree.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/16lyp94q84ywc1q6lfz184ow4/original/16lyp94q84ywc1q6lfz184ow4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704041757 +0000" stop="20250704051232 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 3- Washington D.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John first meets up with actor Diane Guerrero to chat about her experiences as an immigrant, author and activist over some of the best Latin food in town. He then meets up with Congressman Ritchie Torres from the Bronx to discuss the lack of Latinx representation in government and what can be done about it. John also speaks with Maria Teresa Kumar of Voto Latino to discuss the importance of voter registration within the Latinx community and how that will increase representation. And he goes canvassing to register potential voters with the help of activist and Vice President of Unidos US, Clarissa Martinez De Castro. John then takes a tour of the Smithsonian’s Latin American History exhibition with Founding Director of The National Museum of the American Latino, Jorge Zamanillo to discuss the need for a proper museum that more accurately tells the Latinx story in this country. Later, John meets up with poet/activist Quique Aviles, who has lived in D.C. since he was a child and fights against gentrification through the spoken word. Lastly, John visits the Gala Theater and the immigrant kids who find their voices and their strength through performance art.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1qyriafa984xw1s6mq7l9dlmk/original/1qyriafa984xw1s6mq7l9dlmk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704051232 +0000" stop="20250704060708 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 4- Chicago</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John meets up with renowned actor Michael Peña to learn about what it was like to grow up in the Midwest, while still attempting to retain his Mexican culture. By participating in a Peña family barbeque, John sees first-hand just how much family and friends who become family, help keep traditions alive and create safe spaces for those making a new home in a strange land. John also meets up with Congressman Chuy Garcia, who works tirelessly to bring about equity in government on behalf of the Latinx community. John then connects with Mario Hernández Jr. who shows him around the borough of Pilson, where political murals (a tradition started in Mexico) line the streets. He then talks with local artists who are passing on the tradition of political art to the community through printmaking. John has a chat with some of Chicago's queer youth activists who are actively working to provide education and a safe environment for their peers. Lastly, John gets the lowdown on Humboldt Park from community leader, Mike Oquendo. He introduces John to the Humboldt Park firemen who are entirely Latino and break all stereotypes through their community activism.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/cd8mv17tyr5m117s1pay0nwyw/original/cd8mv17tyr5m117s1pay0nwyw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704060708 +0000" stop="20250704070341 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 5- Puerto Rico</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John travels to the island of Puerto Rico to highlight the many ways in which the island and its people have influenced American culture and the ways in which America is influencing theirs. A hot topic: the issue of statehood, which John finds out, not everyone supports. John learns the deep roots of resistance that lives in the hearts and minds of the Puerto Rican people.</desc>
    <date>20250114</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7285030168667895979/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704070341 +0000" stop="20250704075816 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 6- Los Angeles</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John starts his trip by driving to east L.A. with native Angelino, George Lopez. While eating George’s favorite tacos, the two discuss George’s journey to becoming a star and the importance of allyship. He then shares a cup of coffee with legendary director, Robert Rodriguez who shares how he broke all the rules to forge his own path to success. John then meets up with the L.A. Opera’s new Resident Conductor, Lina Gonzalez-Granados who has broken through the fine arts glass ceiling and is making sure to bring her Latin flare to the world of Opera. John then sits down with one of the few Latina Showrunners in the television business, Gloria Calderón Kellett. They share laughs and discuss her professional journey, the lack of representation behind the camera and her continued fight to change the industry from within. John then heads to the Hollywood hills to meet up with Afro Latina, actress/producer, Gina Torres to discuss how colorism has affected her life and career. Finally, John takes some of today’s hottest Latinx powerhouses to a Michelin star Mexican restaurant in Inglewood to discuss all things Hollywouldn’t, and what needs to happen to truly address the industry’s representation problem.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/ecrarfdewyhs1xgifuiauk8kf/original/ecrarfdewyhs1xgifuiauk8kf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704075816 +0000" stop="20250704082300 +0000">
    <title>A Swim Lesson</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A SWIM LESSON is an ode to an everyday hero: Bill Marsh, a swim teacher who helps children manage their fears and discover their own power when submerged in an overwhelming unknown.</desc>
    <date>20241228</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7278592812998081133/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704082300 +0000" stop="20250704100742 +0000">
    <title>The Hobby</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A McDonald’s Happy Meal shortage. A security guard escort. Guns pulled in a Target parking lot. All of these are caused by a common factor: trading cards. In 2020, a new BOOM began. For the first time, large hedge funds, celebrities like Logan Paul and Steve Aoki, nostalgic millennials, entrepreneurs like Josh Luber, and billionaires scrambled to add sports, Pokémon, and other hot item cards to their collections and portfolios. Over the next two years, the hobby exploded — even causing card grading services to shut down due to overwhelming customer service. This documentary is a character-driven feel good deep dive into the high-stakes, eccentric world of card collecting, following buyers, sellers, card shop owners, graders, online streamers, auctioneers, and more, who all participate in the hobby in their own unique ways. Directed by Morgan Jon Fox.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe/original/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704100742 +0000" stop="20250704112211 +0000">
    <title>Lewis Hamilton: The Winning Formula</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As the only black Formula One driver in history, Lewis' journey to becoming the most decorated Formula One driver in history, is one of dreams, courage, and determination. Directed by Piers Garland.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1/original/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
