<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146">
    <display-name>Runtime</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/2bad1dfc-bfda-46ae-bd0d-36b1e07ccb47/runtime-logo_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250712230000 +0000" stop="20250713010557 +0000">
    <title>Game Day</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A tech whiz loses everything when her startup goes bust and personal life is left in ruins. Discovering that success at her new job depends on becoming a team player in the office and on the company's all-male basketball team, she enlists the help of a basketball-savvy teen to coach her as she desperately attempts to save her job and her future.</desc>
    <date>20191101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4992b5d4c66dd98152c211ea568062f7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713010557 +0000" stop="20250713024648 +0000">
    <title>Sex Trip</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After a shallow womanizer refuses a mysterious homeless woman's request for a kiss, he wakes up the next morning to discover he's been changed into a woman.</desc>
    <date>20240529</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_sex_trip_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713024648 +0000" stop="20250713045902 +0000">
    <title>Rottentail</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Geeky fertility researcher, Peter Cotton, is bitten by a mutant rabbit and changes into the half-man/half-bunny Rottentail. What's a boy to do? Why, take a hippity-hoppity trip home of course! Peter begins a bloody killing spree of revenge that culminates in his childhood hometown of Easter Falls.</desc>
    <date>20180301</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/40db202118c0dced236d93d76ea17e8b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713045902 +0000" stop="20250713060000 +0000">
    <title>The Insider: Reggie Yates</title>
    <sub-title>Reggie Yates: US Jail Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Working inside Guilford County Jail in North Carolina, Reggie helps guard nearly a thousand prisoners whose crimes range from minor misdemeanours to murder.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_insider_reggie_yates_s2_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713060000 +0000" stop="20250713065200 +0000">
    <title>The Secret</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Coleraine, Northern Ireland, 1990. Colin Howell is a leading member of the Baptist community, and an apparently loving husband and father. But when he meets fellow Baptist, Hazel Buchanan, he pursues her and they embark on an affair which will have cataclysmic consequences for them and their families.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_secret_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713065200 +0000" stop="20250713074242 +0000">
    <title>The Secret</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Colin persuades Hazel that the only viable way for them to be together is to kill their spouses Lesley and Trevor, telling her that he has come up with a plan, but that for it to work he will need her full cooperation.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_secret_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713074242 +0000" stop="20250713083332 +0000">
    <title>The Secret</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>With whispers in the community and lingering police suspicions Colin and Hazel are prevented from being together, until the Coroner’s “Suicide” verdicts put an official end to the speculation. But Hazel feels so guilty that she cannot be physical with Colin except under the influence of increasingly powerful drugs, and she puts an end to their toxic relationship.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_secret_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713083332 +0000" stop="20250713101848 +0000">
    <title>Truth or Die</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of college friends celebrate the end of term with a party to end all parties. During a drink and drug-fuelled evening an innocent game of ‘Truth or Dare’ has a very sore loser, sparking a terrifying sequence of events and a whole new twist on the game - where the truth can kill you.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/truth_or_die_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713101848 +0000" stop="20250713120000 +0000">
    <title>Clubbed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Set in the violent world of 80’s clubland, when life in Britain was tough, where run-down inner-cities were seething with drugs and crime. Danny, a lonely factory worker, is depressed, his marriage is over and the local dealers are out for blood. After a savage beating Danny decides to fight back. He gets involved with the local doormen, who take him in and teach him how to stand his ground.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/clubbed_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713120000 +0000" stop="20250713123422 +0000">
    <title>Beyond the Tattoo</title>
    <sub-title>Orange tattoo company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The team travels up to Annapolis, MD to meet Frankie Orange and crew from Orange Tattoo Company.</desc>
    <date>20250124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/beyond_the_tattoo_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_en.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713123422 +0000" stop="20250713142531 +0000">
    <title>Our Wild Hearts</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A wealthy teenage girl from Malibu falls in love with a beautiful wild mustang, adventure, and the father she has never known in the wild Sierra Nevada Mountains.</desc>
    <date>20130309</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/08bcf274e9ecbaac6aed4c9953abda4e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713142531 +0000" stop="20250713163239 +0000">
    <title>Like Dandelion Dust</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Based on the best-selling novel by Karen Kingsbury. When biological parents try to get their child back, a man and his wife must fight to retain custody of their adopted son.</desc>
    <date>20240405</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/like_dandelion_dust_thumbnail_7x10_poster_uk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713163239 +0000" stop="20250713181113 +0000">
    <title>The Ox</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In desperation brought on by near-starvation, Helge Roos kills his master's ox and feeds it to his wife and baby daughter. No-one suspects anything until the meat is finished and Helge tries to sell the hide at a local market. He is spotted by the local vicar and, wracked with guilt, confesses. The vicar assures him that if he gives himself up, he'll be treated leniently, but Helge's sentence is far harsher than anyone predicted...</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_ox_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713181113 +0000" stop="20250713195801 +0000">
    <title>A Husband's Lethal Intentions</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A woman and her son fall under the spell of seemingly perfect man with a dark side.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/husbands_lethal_intentions_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713195801 +0000" stop="20250713214525 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Inn</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A single mother restores a Victorian home and opens a bed-and-breakfast, but the arrival of a guest with a hidden agenda shatters the peace.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/deadly_inn_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713214525 +0000" stop="20250713233000 +0000">
    <title>Deadly Best Friend</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Katy, a happily married mom, welcomes her best friend Gina for a visit. However, Gina's sketchy boyfriend, Ray, and his dangerous brother have a sinister agenda. They hold Katy's family hostage, forcing her to cooperate in their criminal scheme. To save her family, Katy must summon the courage to thwart their plans.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/deadly_best_friend_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250713233000 +0000" stop="20250714011057 +0000">
    <title>Bad Twin</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>THE BAD TWIN: Well-knonw radio host Jen Burgess is estranged from her sinister sister Cassie. But when Cassie reappears and attacks Jen in a rage, Cassie is sent to psychiatric treatment leaving her disturbed and dangerous twin daughters (15) to live with Jen. Unbeknownst to Jen, the twins are controlled by Cassie, who directs them in a campaign to hurt Jen or anyone who comes to her rescue. The stakes are raised when Cassie realizes Jen’s true wealth. Cassie directs the twins to manipulate Jen into adopting them, just before killing her, so she can inherit her wealth. But Jen discovers a split between the twins, realizing one of them has been against her mother’s evil plans. But which one? In the end, it’s this good twin that saves Jen from a harrowing death pitting herself against her bad twin sister.</desc>
    <date>20250227</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bad_twin_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
