<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716001641 +0000" stop="20250716014932 +0000">
    <title>The Queens Ball</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Racine Robinson is the queen pin of a criminal empire, alongside her daughters Cand and Kat. Racine is celebrating her 50th birthday and invited all the regional crime families to come and celebrate. Unbeknownst to her, a contract has been taking out to kil Racine on her birthday. With government intervention, and various talking heads, the death of Racine could lead to open warfare in the city.</desc>
    <date>20240507</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/3f333c3f6cc87afb042efaf1af129e8c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716014932 +0000" stop="20250716032224 +0000">
    <title>The Saved and the Salacious</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ashton, Isaac, and Terrell have dreams of making it big in the gospel music industry, and making an impact in the world; however, worlds collide when they meet the nefarious founder and owner of Titan Records, Rodney "Rod" Wallace.</desc>
    <date>20230919</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qSJyQh6zIm47uiKEyGTn30bb6Xr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716032224 +0000" stop="20250716044435 +0000">
    <title>The Killing Secret</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The outside looking in, Daniel and his wife Brenda appeared to have it all together, but smiles can be deceiving, and kisses can be poison. A healthy marriage is difficult to attain and destroy, but not when secrets are intertwined in the vows, especially one that can kill.</desc>
    <date>20181218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zcI60fonQ1eKOH0NWoPwbOGqr8l.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716044435 +0000" stop="20250716065301 +0000">
    <title>The Calling</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tamar has been called to become a minister, and for most, this would be an honorable moment, but for Tamar, it is the worst thing that could happen. Tamar is the daughter of prominent Deacon Jessup, and is a lesbian. Taught that her desires are not that of God, Tamar has suppressed them for the last 16 years and has never dated a woman. When the Future Minister’s Ministry opens for a new class, Tamar finds herself falling for the only other woman in the class.</desc>
    <date>20230601</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/9839bce44aba1d2fb27fe3841b31881f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716065301 +0000" stop="20250716083530 +0000">
    <title>The Betrayal 3: Neva Ending</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Blood is not always thicker than water, and not all friends are as loyal as you think. Four different relationships display love, hurt, and betrayal.</desc>
    <date>20230501</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716083530 +0000" stop="20250716103424 +0000">
    <title>The Betrayal 4: Wicked Nights</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Wicked days, wicked nights, wicked feelings. Tk &amp; Glizzy won’t rest until one of them controls the city. Following their daily struggles on the streets of Atlanta, we will soon see why the streets are divided &amp; why family means nothing! Blood chaos &amp; mayhem, the kind of betrayal that reminds us that no one can be trusted.</desc>
    <date>20240618</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716103424 +0000" stop="20250716120154 +0000">
    <title>Dream on Dreamer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mario's life unravels when he quits med school for acting, angering his wife, Erica, who leaves with their daughter. His friend Derrick faces his own crisis with his side chick. Desperate, they turn to Mario's drug-dealing brother, Paul. This leads them into the dangerous world of Queen Pin Malkia, where their lives are put at risk.</desc>
    <date>20240830</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5df558d0a9031e4a8bc47dd4b0eda0f4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716120154 +0000" stop="20250716134118 +0000">
    <title>The Games We Play</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Married and settled, Beejay and Montez, are so busy that they have not been intimate in months. When Beejay confesses this detail to her girlfriends, they convince her that all men cheat, and that they can prove it.</desc>
    <date>20230726</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tsYeXxGal6N60rD48yjarLy3xJ5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716134118 +0000" stop="20250716151114 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Challenge</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Alfred &amp; Della Hughes, a successful couple, face marital strife. Alfred's neglect and an affair strain their bond. Della, overwhelmed by household duties, feels undervalued. Their children witness their parents' escalating conflicts, leading to a tumultuous breakdown. Though their children plead for unity, divorce looms. A family intervention, sparked by a heartfelt gift, forces them to confront their deep-seated love and the possibility of reconciliation.</desc>
    <date>20250513</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716151114 +0000" stop="20250716163412 +0000">
    <title>Concealment 2: Open Marriage</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Deandre &amp; Nia, betrayed by each other &amp; blackmailed by their college friend Isis, reluctantly open their marriage. Isis steals their money &amp; disappears. Deandre seeks help to recover his losses. Both are involved in secret affairs, concealing crucial information from their partners, leading to tragic consequences.</desc>
    <date>20250422</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ea9e3e469f85ce03779ec2784e2d746e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716163412 +0000" stop="20250716184018 +0000">
    <title>Through Sickness and Hell</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a police officer is trapped in a toxic marriage, he must find the strength to break free from his abusive wife, risking his career, reputation, but also his life as he battles the damaging stigma surrounding domestic violence against men.</desc>
    <date>20250318</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tM9dNTbDD2d4YxcnHL854INubQW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716184018 +0000" stop="20250716200203 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716200203 +0000" stop="20250716214150 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716214150 +0000" stop="20250716230535 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWVkNzQ1MjAtYmNjZS00NDc0LTg0YzktNzVlNGViODYyMmUxXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250716230535 +0000" stop="20250717004053 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250717004053 +0000" stop="20250717020606 +0000">
    <title>Finders Keepers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jaylin is a struggling single father trying to support his children and make ends meet. One day he comes upon a box of pills and tries to sell them for the cash. Until thugs approach him, and now a simple gamble, becomes life threatening.</desc>
    <date>20231129</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/plex/a62bcd6d-f7d3-49f5-8206-4646804e0e67.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
