<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718000147 +0000" stop="20250718004654 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat Ban</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Children kicked off flights, prohibited from eating in restaurants and banned from vacation hot spots -- from parents to patrons, today’s guests all have an opinion about what’s being called the “brat ban” policies that many places are adopting that enforce kid-free zones. Dr. Phil's first guest, Serita, took her 14-month-old son to her local public library, but when the boy became too noisy, Serita was not only told to leave -- she was arrested! Learn how the incident escalated and got both mother and son banned. Then, it made front page headlines when a shopper slapped a stranger’s toddler at Walmart. The man at the center of the controversy speaks publicly for the first time about the incident that landed him in jail. And, Pittsburgh restaurant owner Mike Vuick caused an uproar from angry parents when he banned children under 6 from his dining room. What caused Mike to impose the ban, and has business suffered or thrived as a result? Plus, is banning kids more about banning bad parenting? It's a polarizing question that has audience members at odds. And, find out how to keep your kid from becoming a brat!</desc>
    <date>20110912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718004654 +0000" stop="20250718013344 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet Success</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E102</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca says her sister, Pamela, has repeatedly betrayed her by sleeping with the important men in her life, including her ex-husband, her child's father and even her current boyfriend. Rebecca confides that she feels so scorned that she now has a difficult time trusting anyone. Pamela admits that she made mistakes but says she's tired of feeling guilty, and she feels Rebecca needs to forgive her and move on. But is Rebecca ready to leave the past behind? Can Dr. Phil help repair their relationship? Then, Steve says that over the last five years, his girlfriend, Megan, has stolen nearly a half million dollars from him. He claims she has forged his name on checks, taken out credit cards in his name and has taken more than $167,000 from his elderly mother. Megan admits to taking the money but says she did it for a good reason. Is Megan with Steve for the love or the money? And, if Steve thinks it's for the money, why does he stay? Dr. Phil explains the 16 powerful tools that the world’s most successful people use, as outlined in his book, Life Code: The New Rules for Winning in the Real World. If you’re ready to stop being used and abused and start being a star in your own life, don’t miss this show!</desc>
    <date>20130212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11102.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718013344 +0000" stop="20250718022131 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Butt Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you have someone in your life who's so annoying and frustrating that you just want him or her to go away? What do you do when you're co-parents with someone you can't get along with? And, what if your daughter secretly dated, and then married, a man you despise?</desc>
    <date>20080118</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718022131 +0000" stop="20250718030842 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Affair, Lies, &amp; Audiotape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One man says he caught his wife cheating – on audiotape – but she denies the accusations. Who’s really telling the truth? Dr. Phil gets to the bottom of the alleged affair on tape. Can this relationship survive without trust?</desc>
    <date>20111103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718030842 +0000" stop="20250718035559 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Twisted Family Tragedy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From the outside, Tayler's life seemed picture perfect -- but no one could have imagined the disturbing secrets she was hiding behind her smile. From the ages of 6 to 17, Tayler says her dad, Russell, molested her, gave her drugs, and took her to Mexico on numerous occasions, where she was forced to do unspeakable things. How could these horrific events have occurred without anyone noticing? Tayler's mom, Deanna, says she was unaware of the alleged abuse, and just thought Tayler and her father had a special father-daughter bond. Were there warning signs she missed? Now 19 and addicted to heroin, Tayler says she feels alone, abandoned and confused -- but she also admits that she misses her father. Can Dr. Phil help get her on a path to both emotional and physical recovery? Then, hear from Tayler's two younger sisters. What did they witness? Were they being groomed by their father? And, where is Russell today? If you're a parent, tune in to learn how to protect your child from a predator.</desc>
    <date>20121015</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718035559 +0000" stop="20250718044306 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>How to Fix a Broken Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E118</episode-num>
    <desc>You've heard people complain, "If I only knew then what I know now, I wouldn't be in this mess," but what about those times when you choose not to see the writing on the wall? Dr. Phil meets couples who say their relationships went from bad to worse after they said, "I do," and now their families are broken.</desc>
    <date>20090520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7118.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718044306 +0000" stop="20250718052958 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Football Star Accused: Did He Do It?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In a Dr. Phil exclusive, a 17-year-old football star accused of rape -- and the alleged victim -- speak out about how one alcohol-fueled night changed their lives in an instant. Matt says he and three friends were drinking at a party nearly nine months ago when the four boys had sex with a 16-year-old classmate. He claims she initiated the encounter and that the sex was consensual. Matt and the three boys are charged with second-degree rape, and Matt says his dreams of getting a college scholarship have been put on hold. How does he describe the events of that night? And, what, if anything, does he say he’d do differently? Then, hear from the alleged victim, who is speaking out for the first time. What does she recall happening that night? And, how has the ordeal impacted her life? Plus, Matt’s parents, Dianne and Mark, insist their son is innocent and say they believe the alleged victim is out for attention. Dr. Phil has a powerful message for the couple.</desc>
    <date>20130912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718052958 +0000" stop="20250718061707 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Football Star's Alleged Victim Speaks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E304</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil delves into the dangers of teenage sex and underage drinking -- and how three families have been affected. In Part 2 of his exclusive interview, the 16-year-old girl who claims high school football star Matt and three other classmates raped her at a party opens up about what she says happened that night. Why does she say her peers care more about the accused football players than they do her? Don’t miss Matt and his parents’ reactions to what she has to say. Then, Leah alleges that in 2011, her 15-year-old daughter, Rehtaeh, was raped by four classmates at a party, and that after nearly a year-and-a-half of relentless bullying, the teen took her own life. How could this have been prevented? And what message does Leah have for others in similar situations? Plus, hear from Alexis, who says she too was raped at 15 and “could’ve been Rehtaeh.” What does she say got her through her darkest moments? Don’t miss this powerful cautionary tale for every teen and parent! This program contains strong sexual content.</desc>
    <date>20130913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718061707 +0000" stop="20250718070346 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Fight Over Teen's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Statistics show that 2,000 teens get pregnant every day. Moms and dads: Watch this show with your teenagers, because it can impact their lives and yours! Two families face off over who should raise baby Miley. Paige, 17, and her boyfriend, Jordan, 18, are determined to raise their child on their own, even though they live with Jordan’s dad, Chris. Nikki, Paige’s stepmom, thinks she and her husband should raise the child, because they can better provide for her, and she wants Paige to break up with Jordan. Why does she believe that Jordan is brainwashing Paige? The teen dad says Nikki is the one who’s controlling, and he’s stepped up to the plate. Will the families come to an agreement? See what Dr. Phil tells them they must do to ensure Miley grows up in a healthy environment. Plus, find out the 10 things teens want their parents to know about teen sex.</desc>
    <date>20101108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718070346 +0000" stop="20250718074831 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Dr Phil Catfish Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E92</episode-num>
    <desc>A concerned daughter seeks Dr. Phil’s help to rescue her mother from a deceptive online relationship.</desc>
    <date>20200518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18092.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718074831 +0000" stop="20250718083416 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Catfish Inv. Pt2: Inside Lois’ Safe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E313</episode-num>
    <desc>An investigation uncovers the secrets of a woman’s mysterious safe. What hidden truths and surprises lie inside?</desc>
    <date>20200519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18313.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718083416 +0000" stop="20250718091130 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Catfish Inv Pt3: Where’s Paul Shaw?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E314</episode-num>
    <desc>The final part of a gripping investigation to track down a woman’s elusive fiancé whom she has never met.</desc>
    <date>20200520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18314.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718091130 +0000" stop="20250718095727 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Was Mommy Murdered?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E99</episode-num>
    <desc>The saga of a father's quest for his vanished daughter is discussed.</desc>
    <date>20100303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8099.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718095727 +0000" stop="20250718104543 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Family Drama</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E56</episode-num>
    <desc>A family is on the verge of imploding as their holiday arguments turn violent.</desc>
    <date>20081125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7056.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718104543 +0000" stop="20250718113252 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Oversexed and Unprotected</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Andrew, Mason and Ryan are 21-year-old self-professed ladies’ men who say they have proudly slept with scores of women -- many times without any protection! At the hands of Dr. Phil and a former Navy Seal, these men get a very rude awakening. Hear from their “conquests” and a mother of one of the boys. Will these oversexed men clean up their act? Plus, find out why Dr. Phil says having “the talk” with your teen is simply not enough.</desc>
    <date>20110224</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718113252 +0000" stop="20250718122015 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Why Is My Mom Faking Cancer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jessica says her mother, Patricia, claims she is defying the odds by becoming a record-setting weight lifter while simultaneously battling Stage 3 brain cancer. But Jessica insists her mother isn’t sick at all and that she is lying about her health to gain sympathy and attention. She says Patricia has been spinning stories about various medical ailments for as long as she can remember -- and it’s time to come clean. Patricia strongly denies her daughter’s accusations and insists her diagnosis and incredible survival story are real. Why does she claim Jessica is out to get her? Emotions run high when mother and daughter meet on Dr. Phil’s stage. Do Patricia’s claims hold up? And, can this mother and daughter repair their fractured relationship?</desc>
    <date>20150115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718122015 +0000" stop="20250718130747 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E93</episode-num>
    <desc>From “I do” to “I don’t” want to be in this marriage and feel trapped.</desc>
    <date>20060130</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718130747 +0000" stop="20250718135548 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat-Proof Your Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The challenge of taming tantrums in young children is examined.</desc>
    <date>20101202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718135548 +0000" stop="20250718144109 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Mystery of Melissa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who vanished finally faces her family.</desc>
    <date>20201012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718144109 +0000" stop="20250718152700 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Daughter’s Dark Confession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E304</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who vanished reveals a dark secret.</desc>
    <date>20201013</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718152700 +0000" stop="20250718161433 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Are My Children in a Cult?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E133</episode-num>
    <desc>A father is fighting for custody of his 4 children because his ex-wife is allegedly in a cult.</desc>
    <date>20130521</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718161433 +0000" stop="20250718170207 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Save My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents, listen up! Your A-student or football champion could be abusing ADD/ADHD medication right under your nose. Dr. Phil alerts you to the latest risky teen trends and gives you advice for knowing what your kids are doing before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>20091103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8023.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718170207 +0000" stop="20250718174748 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Toxic and Offensive Inlaws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A Meddling Mother-in-Law or a Lying Cheating Daughter-in-Law? Dr Phil delves into the family drama.</desc>
    <date>20140129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12020.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718174748 +0000" stop="20250718183104 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Teen Can’t Stand Her Stepfather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E104</episode-num>
    <desc>When he last appeared on Dr. Phil, Kip’s brazen and outrageous tirade toward his 17-year-old stepdaughter, Tory, shocked audience members and viewers. But the married father of two refused to back down. When Tory broke down in tears, Kip finally agreed to find a calmer way to express his frustration. Just weeks later, Tory’s mother, Vicky, says the surly relationship has not only gotten worse, the hostility has escalated, and her patience is running thin. She says both Tory and Kip refuse to seek help, and now there is a new bombshell that is making their home life virtually unbearable. What does Kip say is his biggest issue with his stepdaughter? And, will this family finally agree to accept help and repair what’s left of their relationship? Then, Joe, 34, became an instant father to two teenage daughters. One of the girls has run away, and the other feels that he treats her like a slave. Can they resolve their disputes and come together as one? (FOLLOW UP FROM 9093)</desc>
    <date>20110531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9104.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718183104 +0000" stop="20250718191816 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Con Artists and Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E46</episode-num>
    <desc>From petty theft to check fraud, Dr. Phil's guests say they're addicted to stealing, and it's destroying their families.</desc>
    <date>20080123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718191816 +0000" stop="20250718200251 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>“Is My Nigerian Boyfriend Scamming Me?”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Sixty-four-year-old Josie says she met the love of her life, Victor, on Facebook. Even though he’s Nigerian, 30 years younger, and she’s never physically met him, she insists it’s true love. She’s purchased a ticket to Nigeria and hopes to marry Victor, but her older sister, Carmen, her best friend, Angela, and her 19-year-old son, Anthony, say Josie is acting like a teenage fool. They believe Victor is conning Josie into marrying him for a green card. Dr. Phil took cameras to Nigeria to find Victor to see if he’s telling Josie the truth. Josie’s family says they want Dr. Phil to convince Josie that this relationship will never work. Is Victor who he says he is, and will Josie leave for Nigeria after hearing what Dr. Phil has to say?</desc>
    <date>20190208</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17066_V2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718200251 +0000" stop="20250718204850 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>DP Scam - Part One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E55</episode-num>
    <desc>You hear about scams all the time - e-mails and voicemails claiming you have won valuable prizes. Dr. Phil is outraged by what some scammers are doing to him, his family and his viewers. One website offers a Dr. Phil quiz to win $5,000 every hour, another says it has the official Dr. Phil personality test, but even more shocking are 800 numbers that take callers' money for the promise of over the phone therapy with Dr. Phil and Robin. But these 800 numbers connect innocent victims with con artists posing as Dr. Phil staff members. The fake staffers ask anywhere from $375 to $1,000 for consultation time that obviously never takes place.</desc>
    <date>20061109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718204850 +0000" stop="20250718213450 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>DP Scam Part 2 “The Sting”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E304</episode-num>
    <desc>The drama continues as Dr. Phil goes on the hunt for con artists who cheat viewers out of thousands of dollars by posing as him and Robin.</desc>
    <date>20061110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718213450 +0000" stop="20250718222258 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>How To Spot A Scammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E52</episode-num>
    <desc>With the economy in trouble, a lot of people are under pressure and getting desperate. Learn the tools to protect yourself from liars, cheats and scammers who are trying to take advantage.</desc>
    <date>20091125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8052.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718222258 +0000" stop="20250718231044 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Faking It!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Secrets, aliases, disguises. These are some of the tactics Dr. Phil's guests have used to manipulate people and get what they want. See what happens when these liars and cons are confronted.</desc>
    <date>20070917</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718231044 +0000" stop="20250718235624 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Post Malone: Love Story or Scam?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Two women believe their grandmother is being scammed by an unknown online imposter posing as rapper Post Malone.</desc>
    <date>20210927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L20024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250718235624 +0000" stop="20250719004626 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Munchausen Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil takes goes inside the unthinkable: making your own child sick to fulfill a disturbing need for attention. The idea might sound unimaginable, but for people with a psychological disorder called Munchausen by Proxy, it's irresistible. Note: Viewer discretion is advised.</desc>
    <date>20071011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
