<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250724230907 +0000" stop="20250725005521 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Vintage Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The fizz goes out of a sparkling wine launch when the glasses are laced with poison.</desc>
    <date>20150218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lannftGIxJHzMiQSpzcvT4mDQrg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725005521 +0000" stop="20250725024018 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Haunting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Its Christmas and new detective Charlie Nelson moves into Midsomer. Hes thrown straight into an intriguing mystery in the village of Morton Shallows. A man is fatally stabbed with an antique sword.</desc>
    <date>20131224</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8tABWVupBYiM3rn1NRCUEOkkq5S.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725024018 +0000" stop="20250725042517 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Let Us Prey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of murders in Midsomer St Claire seem to be inspired by macabre images on a medieval fresco.</desc>
    <date>20140108</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1kIZ9xpDDe4U5qwgL1F9iNJzqpA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725042517 +0000" stop="20250725061006 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Harvest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When wealthy farmer Martin Strickland is covered in truffle oil and mauled to death by a wild boar, the investigation leads to restaurant Wyvern House and its tyrannical celebrity chef Ruth Cameron.</desc>
    <date>20140129</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zeliFzcL6KDIJeeADWXf5eDjfJ1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725061006 +0000" stop="20250725075544 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Flying Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a body is discovered in a reservoir dropped out of a plane, Barnaby and Nelson find the world of stunt pilots and military heroes hides many dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>20140205</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kB5krKKTBLoDrpEvWt0qC4V8Xvn.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725075544 +0000" stop="20250725094136 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Killings At Copenhagen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When the boss of Calders Biscuit Company is murdered in Copenhagen, Barnaby and Nelson join forces with two female Danish detectives, the abrasive and astute Poulsen and the charming and cool Degn.</desc>
    <date>20140212</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uXCntd4N3rH5m9iiAxS9KpRFD77.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725094136 +0000" stop="20250725112826 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dance With The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A disused airfield at Cooper's Cross is where Simon Bright's vintage car is found by Frances Kirby. Inside she finds Simon dead, as the evening before his death had been on a romantic date with his girlfriend Laura Sharp. Laura is nowhere to be found, both Barnaby and Jones, newly promoted to DS, need to work out if it was a suicide pact gone wrong or whether it was murder and track down Laura.</desc>
    <date>20061111</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qF4KWvjCBaLCP7fnwGNNWCUChlA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725112826 +0000" stop="20250725131531 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Animal Within</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Faith Alexander arrives in Midsomer to meet her long-lost uncle Rex Masters. She receives a real shock, when she discovers that Rex's friends had been told she had died in a plane crash. Things become complicated when Rex's body is found in the nearby river. Barnaby and Jones quickly turn up trying to workout who would wish Rex harm. Several friends of Rex come forward with multiple 'new' wills each being sole beneficiary.</desc>
    <date>20070118</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/djHyhDeVbHaPzznei6mX2Ku9MGx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725131531 +0000" stop="20250725150417 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>King's Crystal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Whilst on a business trip to China, Alan King suddenly dies. The family firm, King's Crystal is in financial uncertainty, including plans to close its factory in Midsomer Magna. Six months later Alan's widow Hilary and his brother Charles are married, much to the chagrin of Alan's son Ian. With family feuds and factory workers angered by the loss of their jobs, there's many motives in the mix. When Peter Baxter, the firm's accountant is found dead, stabbed with a Masonic dagger.</desc>
    <date>20070126</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tvIc7wolHlehggXyS7gQuwzc1HA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725150417 +0000" stop="20250725165123 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Axeman Cometh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Midsomer Rocks festival is due to take place and music fans descend on neighbouring fields to enjoy the fiesta. The recently reformed band Hired Gun, are one of the headline acts and during their opening performance, the bands vocalist Mimi Clifton is electrocuted on stage whilst holding on to her microphone stand, that had an added mystery wire. Barnaby and Jones soon discover other band members could be targets.</desc>
    <date>20070202</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/38G2QX72T4hcsZ3jtGMcEWS0sUh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725165123 +0000" stop="20250725183830 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death And Dust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When popular GP, Doctor Alan Delaney borrows fellow Dr. James Kirkwood's new car to do an evening call-out. He is mysteriously killed in a hit and run during a drive through woods in a thunderstorm. Barnaby and Jones start investigating in Midsomer Market and discover that James may have been the intended victim. The case leads them to North Walesformer home of Delyth Mostyn, James's fiance to delve further.</desc>
    <date>20070508</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d16oDfe5xRkqz6X3wCqLSh63uA0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725183830 +0000" stop="20250725202727 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Picture Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In the pretty village of Luxton Deeping, there's fierce conflict between the traditional film and modern digital photographers. When their societies committee decide not to accept digital images at the annual photographic exhibition, it appears to make things worse. It leads to a confrontation at the private view. The following day Lionel Bell is found murdered in woodland, strangled with the cord of his light meter.</desc>
    <date>20070603</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hYiCsblCms9LmSXTev4jua63cC8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725202727 +0000" stop="20250725221431 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>They Seek Him Here</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The inhabitants of Midsomer Magna are in the spotlight, quite literally when a production crew descend on the village and imposing Manor House. To film a version of The Scarlet Pimpernel. Not only the film crew arrive, but a notorious criminal as well, George Ince, lurking around the Manor. When Nick Cheney, the film's director is found dead, by the use of the prop guillotine. The detectives need to sift through many motives which lead to the complexity.</desc>
    <date>20080427</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ldk4F0pIttkoIkd4X3VwquGWWjJ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250725221431 +0000" stop="20250726000329 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death In A Chocolate Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>In the village of Midsomer Holm, a rehabilitation scheme for reformed criminals continues. When Ronnie Tyler departs, he gets a good send off from everyone, including DCI Barnaby. Another attendee is Jack Colby, a disgraced ex-policeman and former colleague of Barnaby. Jack is decidedly frosty towards his once-former friend and refuses to chat. When Jack is later murdered, Barnaby must search for answers in Jack's past for motives.</desc>
    <date>20080511</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wKxcARB2sRmr927mivbb5CAQ3PI.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726000329 +0000" stop="20250726015025 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dogleg Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Down at the prestigious Whiteoaks Golf Club, there is much rivalry and snobbery amongst its members. When Alistair Kingslake is coerced into the thicket to look for his ball on the notorious 13th hole, known as Crisp's Folly, he soon gets bludgeoned to death. There's many suspects, from fellow members, several villagers who only have limited time on the course and the club's staff. It is not long before another member is found stabbed in woodland close to the course.</desc>
    <date>20090722</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h3gpjWH14hPYVYoMGNyFSwuV5Yk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
