<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726000329 +0000" stop="20250726015025 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dogleg Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Down at the prestigious Whiteoaks Golf Club, there is much rivalry and snobbery amongst its members. When Alistair Kingslake is coerced into the thicket to look for his ball on the notorious 13th hole, known as Crisp's Folly, he soon gets bludgeoned to death. There's many suspects, from fellow members, several villagers who only have limited time on the course and the club's staff. It is not long before another member is found stabbed in woodland close to the course.</desc>
    <date>20090722</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h3gpjWH14hPYVYoMGNyFSwuV5Yk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726015025 +0000" stop="20250726033733 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When a newly discovered treasure by the 19th-century landscape artist Henry Hogson, makes an impression, it is later sold at auction for 400,000. Shortly after the previous owner of the artwork is tortured and killed. The following day another Hogson is stolen in a burglary and Barnaby finds himself having to investigate both. In order to get success, he needs to become an expert on Hogson with the help of art teacher Matilda Simms, they uncover many hidden secrets, deception and more.</desc>
    <date>20090805</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qGjxLzPUrZdk90lhTbXJyGKw0t0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726033733 +0000" stop="20250726052938 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets And Spies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Former secret agent Geoffrey Larkin arrives in the village of Midsomer Parva and heads for a visit to Allenby House, a country manor run by former spies, the Frazer family as a safe house. With an air of hostility towards Geoffrey, it is not long before he is murdered, by some who blame the 'beast of Midsomer', who believe the creature exists. Barnaby, a former spy himself, gets involved in the case.</desc>
    <date>20090729</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vHfe8ppjSF0mRgOp6qjKLy4z3Rp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726052938 +0000" stop="20250726072146 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Glitch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>George Jeffers, a professor of Midsomer University and cycling enthusiast, threatens to go public, he is found with his state-of-the-art invention Kernel Logic. This angers American software boss Clinton Finn and fears he will lose millions if the truth is exposed. When schoolteacher Emily Harte is killed in a hit and run, things become more complicated. With someone known as 'the Bucketman' throwing red paint over cars belonging to employees of a local computer firm, among others.</desc>
    <date>20090923</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/afTP5yk79dy4gbEptEMKaBOHU1n.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726072146 +0000" stop="20250726090852 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Small Mercies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In Little Worthy, model maker Bob Moss was just going to open his beloved model village, when he stumbled across the body of young Richard Tanner. He had been stabbed and his corpse tied down like Gulliver in the stories of Lilliput. Barnaby and Jones start questioning all the villagers and discover many quirky characters in the process. When the girl Richard was secretly meeting in the grounds of the model village, is murdered during the Crazy Craft Race.</desc>
    <date>20091028</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ul1WbnrnL6fq12EhKE7EeN6h4H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726090852 +0000" stop="20250726105804 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Creeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A cat burglar known as 'the Creeper' could be responsible for murder, not just burglaries. When a writer friend David Roper is found smothered in bed on the Chettham family estate, a few days after arriving. The police soon learn that Mr Roper had been planning to write a book that could have exposed many Chettham family secrets of years past. That would make someone quiet uneasy and edgy. The mystery deepens when a second victim who knew the family is shot in woodland.</desc>
    <date>20100127</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/67pfleWseGdwgfoyaz7lkXU9Trl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726105804 +0000" stop="20250726124500 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Great And The Good</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A school teacher Connie Bishop, Nancy Carroll, who is known to sleepwalk, begins to believe that she has slit the throats of her mentor and a local handyman. Her friends are not convinced that she is to blame; neither does Barnaby. A local philanthropist and his social climbing wife are planning the annual Frobisher night -- will it go ahead without a hitch? The detectives begin to piece the puzzle together and catch the killer.</desc>
    <date>20100414</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pokyn3NiCdIF76a3yNBkRNxoWHZ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726124500 +0000" stop="20250726143053 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dagger Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The unveiling of a newly-discovered novel by deceased Midsomer crime-writer George Summersbee is jeopardised.</desc>
    <date>20150128</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tADG1S5tQHtMKGIHrbq2IIzOlqP.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726143053 +0000" stop="20250726161710 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A pub landlady is crushed to death during a magic show in Midsomer Oaks.</desc>
    <date>20150204</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5Y8EArXMFN0yRW3m7oU47HOcW2U.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726161710 +0000" stop="20250726180345 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballad Of Midsomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Could a ballad made famous by late, lamented folk singer Johnny Carver be an inspiration for murder?</desc>
    <date>20150211</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r3bvxqGlEB27MY2ir81upJgG5qj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726180345 +0000" stop="20250726194959 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Vintage Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The fizz goes out of a sparkling wine launch when the glasses are laced with poison.</desc>
    <date>20150218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lannftGIxJHzMiQSpzcvT4mDQrg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726194959 +0000" stop="20250726213459 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death In The Slow Lane</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a local DJ is crushed to death at a traditional girls boarding school, new DCI John Barnaby soon discovers that murder and deception are never far away.</desc>
    <date>20110323</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7b8xKVf0BvbLwpxxutF9d4DyjDY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726213459 +0000" stop="20250726231810 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Secrets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The reclusive life of elderly eccentrics William and Mary Bingham comes under police scrutiny when a social services investigator is killed. Barnaby and Jones must unearth generations of secrets</desc>
    <date>20110330</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wTzVLtiGleRBZIDOa6PxrUGTUoB.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250726231810 +0000" stop="20250727010234 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Echoes Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young woman is dressed like a bride and drowned in a bath, it triggers a spate of ghoulish wedding-themed murders in Great Worthy. The case takes Barnaby and Jones to a donkey sanctuary.</desc>
    <date>20110420</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ohBdMQ0YMKGd7CjU4DkAqC1xbTV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
