<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709010025 +0000" stop="20250709013024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play It Safe!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After feeling tired of being told to be careful, BJ learns that saying be careful is a way of showing love and concern. This important lesson prompts Barney to teach his friends essential safety rules. Spending time with Barney is always enjoyable, but it's also crucial to learn how to play it safe to stay protected and happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029543_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709013024 +0000" stop="20250709020021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Three Lines, Three Corners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends begin the day by playing hopscotchwith a twist. They discover that making a triangle requires 3 lines and 3 corners, which sparks their excitement to explore more shapes. To have even more triangle fun, Barney takes them on a camping trip where they get to explore and learn about different shapes in the world around them.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029544_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709020021 +0000" stop="20250709023021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Parade of Bikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Its the day of the bike parade, but Nick has had a bike accident that leaves his bike in need of repair by Mr. Boyd. Mr. Boyd works quickly to help fix Nick's bike in time for the parade. While waiting, Barney takes the opportunity to teach his friends all about bike safety, making sure they're ready to ride safely and have a great time in the parade!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029545_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709023021 +0000" stop="20250709030024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Happy Day!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids discuss their desire for a special day, Beth creates Happy Day, a special holiday in which each friend makes a wish and the others try to make it come true. When Beth hurts herself, BJ learns the importance of doing good deeds for others.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029546_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709030024 +0000" stop="20250709033022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Family and Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney plans a magical picnic for his friends and their families to spend quality time together and create lasting memories. Each kid has brought a family treasure to show Barney, which they all excitedly spend time sharing with one another.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029547_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709033022 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Splish! Splash!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids gather at the park, talking about how hot it is and wondering what to do on such a day. Thanks to Barney's brilliant idea, what starts as a too hot afternoon turns into a totally cool day as he introduces them to the wonders of water. Excitedly, they all team up to find creative ways to stay cool and have a splashing good time together!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029548_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709042829 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709042829 +0000" stop="20250709050003 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709050003 +0000" stop="20250709053004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big as Barney - No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029620_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709053004 +0000" stop="20250709060005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Emperor's Contest - Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029621_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709060005 +0000" stop="20250709063012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who - Sweet Treats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for Halloween tonight! Everyone knows what they're going to be for Halloween. BJ is going to be a pirate, Melanie is going to be a cat, David will be a superhero, and Baby Bop is going to be a ballerina princess. Everyone has decided on a costume all except for Riff. Barney tries to give Riff ideas on a costume like a sailor, a firefighter, or a dancer. Riff surprises everyone in the end by wearing a one-man band costume. Then, it's time for the Halloween party to begin! Barney and his friends have fun Trick-or-Treating in the park at night. But when Ramon loses all his Halloween candies, BJ shares his Halloween candies with him.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029622_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709063012 +0000" stop="20250709070006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show - The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029623_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709070006 +0000" stop="20250709072813 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dream Big - Thats What A Mommy Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching birds fly overhead, Riff begins to daydream of flying. He decides to build his very own rocket ship and fly to Mars. The flight is not exactly a success, but Barney encourages Riff to never give up on his dream. After seeing many moms playing with their kids in the park, Baby Bop is curious as to what makes somebody a mommy. With Barney's help, Baby Bop learns all about what makes mommies so special.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029624_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709072813 +0000" stop="20250709080009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shrinking Blankey - The Awful Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's blankey seems to be getting smaller; she's convinced it's shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, Baby Bop is growing. When Riff takes a bite of ice cream, he realizes has a very sore tooth. Afraid of going to the dentist, Barney and his friends put on a show to help Riff see there is nothing to be afraid of - the dentist is his friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029625_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709080009 +0000" stop="20250709083006 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Blame Game - What's Your Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. Meanwhile, Myra, has decided she doesn't like her name. After learning about many names and what they mean, Barney helps Myra see how special her name truly is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029626_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709083006 +0000" stop="20250709090009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose - BJ the Great</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. When they were in a pretend country of India, they saw a real elephant and in the end, Melanie gets a email from her friend in India (who has also seen a real elephant in India!). BJ wants to be a great magician, but he doesn't want to spend any time practicing. He convinces Baby Bop to help him do a trick, and makes her disappear. When BJ thought she is gone forever, he realizes the importance of practice. Luckily, Baby Bop hasn't disappeared after all!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029627_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709090009 +0000" stop="20250709093008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos - A Visit to Santa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn. Melanie misses the mailman, so Barney takes her to Santa's workshop at the North Pole to deliver her wish list in person.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029628_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709093008 +0000" stop="20250709100010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709100010 +0000" stop="20250709103014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709103014 +0000" stop="20250709110017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709110017 +0000" stop="20250709113015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>That Makes Me Mad!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Nick accidentally gets white paint on Sarahs picture, the children must find a way to deal with their emotions. Barney helps his young friends find good ways to express and deal with angry and negative emotions.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029566_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709113015 +0000" stop="20250709120015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Your Birthday, Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After an abundance of mail arrives at the Caboose for Barney, the kids realize it must be a very special day. Its Barneys birthday! Barneys friends along with Baby Bop and BJ, put together a stupendous party celebration for him in the park, including decorations and cake galore!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029567_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709120015 +0000" stop="20250709123015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Showtime!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, BJ and the kids spend the day preparing for a very special performance for their friends in the park. They all gather in the caboose to prepare for a stupendous night of singing, dancing, and magical fun.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029568_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709123015 +0000" stop="20250709130015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>At Home in the Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah and Tony create a beautiful birdhouse to place out in the park. They are happy to learn that the birds will have lots of company; many other animals make their homes in the park too! Barney and the kids travel around the park, noticing and discussing all the various animals that call the park home.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029569_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709130015 +0000" stop="20250709133016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody's Got Feelings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The children realize its normal to experience all different types of emotions. With Barneys help, the children learn all about how to handle how they are feeling, especially feeling happy, sad, and angry.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029570_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709133016 +0000" stop="20250709140017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Caring Hearts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After creating a friends and family tree for a school project, the children discuss all the people in their lives they care about. This provides a perfect opportunity for Barney and his friends to learn about love and relationships.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029571_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709140017 +0000" stop="20250709143019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Make Music!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A fun day in the park with friends involves a musical rhythm clapping game. Barney introduces a new game that helps reinforce learning about music, rhythm, and musical instruments. This new found inspiration causes the kids to make their very own marching band.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029572_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709143019 +0000" stop="20250709150020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movin' Along</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a great day to move around in the park! Barney and his friends have fun with creative movement, while learning new dances, having races, and acting out a story. These activities teach the kids how they can move their bodies while doing different activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029573_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709150020 +0000" stop="20250709153017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let Your Creativity Fly!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious paper airplane flies into the park, inspiring the children to talk about all things Airplanes! The children let their creativity fly when they use their imaginations to build their very own airplane.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029574_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709153017 +0000" stop="20250709160018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Imagine That!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The possibilities are endless as Barney and the kids use their imagination to bring their drawings to life. Barney and the children have an island adventure by imagining themselves in Lauras picture, transporting them to a sunny island!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029575_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709160018 +0000" stop="20250709163020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All About Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrate the things that make us special! Barney and his friends discover that trying something new can be fun. Jackson treats everyone to his healthy but unusual snack, while Baby Bop has a special picnic for BJ consisting mostly of her favorite foods.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029576_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709163020 +0000" stop="20250709170021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Baby Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Oh baby! Oh baby! David has a new baby brother and is now a big brother. But David doesnt know what a big brother is supposed to do and isnt sure hes ready. Barney and his friends help David learn about new babies and how to be a big brother.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029577_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709170021 +0000" stop="20250709173018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Keep On Truckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends keep on truckin'! BJ enjoys helping with his tow truck, while Barney shows everyone what it's like to be behind the wheel of a real truck. When Jackson's special truck loses a tire, Barney wheels in to the rescue!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029578_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709173018 +0000" stop="20250709180019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>I'm A Builder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing some big construction machines roll by, Barney and his friends are inspired! With a little imagination, they build a castle made out of boxes. By exploring the ways things are built, and the big machines and tools used to build them, Barney builds in the fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029579_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709180019 +0000" stop="20250709182841 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Coming On Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Exercise is good for everybody and every body! From running to touching toes to jumping jacks to some favorite songs and games, Barney and his friends grow strong through various activities and having fun with exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029580_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709182841 +0000" stop="20250709185842 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Play Games!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>It's fun and games with Barney and his friends! BJ's favorite way of getting exercise is by playing sports and games. When Baby Bop is shy about trying new games, Barney and his friends show her how tee-rific trying something new can be.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029581_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709185842 +0000" stop="20250709193023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>BJ's Really Cool House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Even though the park feels like a second home for Barney and his friends, BJ dreams of building his very own totally awesome, completely cool house. While they eagerly wait to see it, they start talking about the different rooms a house can have. However, when BJ forgets to include a space for Baby Bop in his plans, Barney reminds him that family is what truly makes a house feel like a home.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029549_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709193023 +0000" stop="20250709200012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Fountain of Fun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Boyd excitedly tells Barney and the kids about the upcoming arrival of a brand-new fountain for the park! While they eagerly await the special delivery, Barney and the children make the most of their time by enjoying the park's delights. They swing on the swings, admire the beautiful flowers, and create wonderful memories together, all while looking forward to the fountain's grand entrance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029550_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709200012 +0000" stop="20250709203022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>On Again, Off Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The children gather for an exciting game of on and off, which turns into a learning adventure for Barney, Baby Bop, and their friends. They explore all the different ways things can be turned on and off, discovering new ideas along the way. Later, Barney and his friends join forces to help Baby Bop find adorable costumes for her beloved teddy bear, making it a delightful day full of play and discovery!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029551_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709203022 +0000" stop="20250709210022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sharing Is Caring!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the park, Mr. Boyd is organizing a special toy drive to help children in need. When Baby Bop feels unsure about donating her toys, Barney and his friends come together to show her the joy of sharing and how it can make a difference, particularly in someone else's life.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029552_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709210022 +0000" stop="20250709213010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Here Kitty, Kitty!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Whitney introduces Angela to the concept of an animal shelter as she shares an adorable picture of kittens. When Miss Jo misplaces her beloved cat, Cody, she decides to place a lost cat sign in the park to notify anyone who passes by. Barney and the children eagerly join the search. Throughout the search, the kids learn all about cats and the responsibilities of pet care.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029553_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709213010 +0000" stop="20250709220022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon a Fairy Tale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gianna and Kami have a delightful dress-up session, followed by a charming tea party with Barney as their special guest. Meanwhile, Mario announces hed like to write his own fairy tale. In their eagerness to help Mario, the children enthusiastically act out some of their most cherished fairy tales, offering him ideas and inspiration.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029554_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709220022 +0000" stop="20250709223027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Hot! It's Cold!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The children discuss the various ways to cool off on a hot day, especially with a nice cold drink of water or some ice cream. Throughout the day, Barney and the children learn about hot and cold, but the fun really begins when Barney turns the playground into a winter/summer wonderland!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029555_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709223027 +0000" stop="20250709230026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Perfectly Purple Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sarah accidentally spills red paint into the blue paint, a mess turns into a perfectly purple day. The kids use this opportunity to explore the creation of different colors by mixing them together. Inspired by this delightful turn of events, Barney and the kids organize a surprise party for Colleen, entirely centered around her most beloved color: purple.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029556_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709230026 +0000" stop="20250709233024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Day and Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Excitedly recounting her recent sleepover, Beth shares the fun moments she had with her friends at night. After the kids wish to see nighttime, so Barney uses this opportunity to transform the park, and explain the differences between day and night!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029557_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250709233024 +0000" stop="20250710000024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play Piano With Me!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stumbling upon Mr. Boyd and Bingo repairing a player piano, Barney recognizes a wonderful chance for learning and exploration with the kids. Excitedly, the children engage in playful games, immersing themselves in the delightful sounds of real pianos and even play a few notes themselves. Through this experience, they gain great knowledge about the piano, all with the guidance and encouragement of Barney and their newfound curiosity.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029558_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250710000024 +0000" stop="20250710003024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Picture of Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Together, the kids use their creativity to create a drawing depicting Barney and themselves having a blast playing baseball. After playing a game of imaginary baseball, they bring Barney into the fun. After accidentally hurting BJ's feelings by forgetting to add him to the drawing, Barney and the children learn what it takes to be a good friend. BJ realizes he has many friends and enjoys a day playing with Barney and the children.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029559_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250710003024 +0000" stop="20250710010024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A-Counting We Will Go!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids explore the wonderful world of counting by playing a variety of fun games, like Barney may I? Barney and the kids help Baby Bop learn how to count to 10 by including her in games, and by taking her on a make-believe shopping trip in the caboose.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029560_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250710010024 +0000" stop="20250710013022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Big Little Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps Baby Bop and the children discover big and little things in the world around them. When Nick expresses his concern about being the smallest among the kids, Barney steps in to demonstrate how each person's unique size holds its own usefulness. When the group heads out to the park, they begin a creative retelling of Jack and the Beanstalk. Barney and his friends discover everyone is special, regardless of size.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029561_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
