<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718000000 +0000" stop="20250718005957 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Daren Goes Plum Crazy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daren is given control of the shop for a week. Darenʼs constant pestering and ribbing leads Mark to hand him the reigns of Graveyard Carz for a week. But instead of getting things done, Daren starts inventing new field trips and distractions for the crew, as well as becoming obsessed with getting his personal Dodge Challenger running again.</desc>
    <date>20120628</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S01_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718005957 +0000" stop="20250718015959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Runnin' Down a Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark receives an angry call from the owner of the 1970 Roadrunner, which leads to a mad rush to get the car finished in time. Meanwhile, Josh pushes the crew into committing to some New Years resolutions.</desc>
    <date>20120705</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S01_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718015959 +0000" stop="20250718030000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>More than a Wrench</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Frustrated by the crew's complaints that he spends all day being lazy in the front office. Mark is determined to prove to the guys that there is more to restoring a car than physical labor. Josh and Daren visit the crash site of the mangled orange 1971 'Cuda.</desc>
    <date>20120712</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S01_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718030000 +0000" stop="20250718040001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dipper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the team works to complete a multitude of cars, Mark stresses over the metal dipping of the very rare and valuable ʻ71 Cuda 440-6. Tensions are high and time is limited, is the GYC crew up to the pressure?</desc>
    <date>20120719</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/5108983a-6721-4a83-b296-d7f3655910d9/SV_LOGO_WCARS_FINAL_1920x1080_R2_HERO.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718040001 +0000" stop="20250718045959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>It's Alive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the remains back from the '71 440 Six Barrel, 4 Speed, Shaker Hood Phantom Cuda and determine if the car can be resurrected. A '69 Dodge Daytona Charger arrives ready to be brought back from the dead and Mark gets a 2011 SRT8 Dodge Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20130108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718045959 +0000" stop="20250718060000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Six-Pack to Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the N96 Air Grabber installed on the '71 Charger 440 Six Pack Triple Green car. It's started and is ready for final assembly. The owners of '70 Cuda 383 Automatic FE5 Rallye Red Car visit to check on the restoration progress.</desc>
    <date>20130115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718060000 +0000" stop="20250718070001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Charger!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is hired to restore the body, paint, and suspension of a '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car. The shop gets some needed upgrades and the '71 Charger 440 Six Pack Triple Green car is completed to OEM Specifications.</desc>
    <date>20130122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718070001 +0000" stop="20250718080003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Wet Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The '70 Sunroof Challenger is painted and ready for final assembly. The '69 Daytona Charger is disassembled and readied to be shipped to the media blasters. Mark and the Ghoulz head out to the junkyard to blow off some steam playing paintball.</desc>
    <date>20130129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718080003 +0000" stop="20250718083003 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Coating Your Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter shows you the process of applying a coating from claying, polishing, and maintenance</desc>
    <date>20221102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/RDG-EP-10-Title.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718083003 +0000" stop="20250718090008 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Car Care Accessories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter shows you the most helpful and handy car care accessories</desc>
    <date>20221105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/RDG-EP-11-Title.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718090008 +0000" stop="20250718093006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Back From the Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruno and Matt bring a 1972 Murdered Out Chevy pickup back from the dead by adding a new front clip and upgrading the brakes.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718093006 +0000" stop="20250718100004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Eaton Proving Ground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Today we find the limits to a stock four-wheel drive jeep. As we head out to the Eaton Proving Ground in Marshall, Michigan.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718100004 +0000" stop="20250718103006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Overheating</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>We’ll show what to do when you’re stranded on the side of the road with an overheating problem and teach the right way diagnose and fix the problem.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718103006 +0000" stop="20250718110007 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Truck Add Ons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beginner to Expert, we’ve got it all. We take a 2011 Ford and show how some jobs can be easier than others</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718110007 +0000" stop="20250718113006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Victory Lane Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt takes a trip to Joplin, Missouri to check in with the guys at Chrome Shop Mafia and find out what makes the Freightliner Victory Lane Edition so unique.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718113006 +0000" stop="20250718120004 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Duramax Injector Repair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>LB7 injectors fail on GM engines all the time. Today we’ll show you why you should do the repair yourself and save thousands in the process.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718120004 +0000" stop="20250718123006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Save the Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruno takes a trip to Surf City Garage and learns some techniques from the pros that can help you save money on your next project.</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718123006 +0000" stop="20250718130001 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Paid to Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Bruno work on a truck that belongs to a tournament fisherman who uses his truck for work and play. It racks up a lot of miles. They are going to hook this boat captain up with some new products that will make his life a lot easier on the road!</desc>
    <date>00010111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718130001 +0000" stop="20250718133003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Long Bed Into Short Bed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody wants a classic short bed pickup. Unfortunately, short beds are hard to find for a good price… but long beds are a dime-a-dozen, and cheap! The solution?... chop a long bed down! That is exactly what Stacey does on this episode of GEARZ. He takes a classic 67 Chevy long bed, and walks you through the way to cut the frame properly, so you have a safe and reliable truck when you are done. If you’ve heard about this kind of modification, but always thought it was too difficult or involved for you to do, you need to watch this episode of GEARZ and let the cutting begin!</desc>
    <date>20130315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0079.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718133003 +0000" stop="20250718140001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Monn Buggy Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Who put men on the moon? If you answered “Gearheads” then you are right… of course, we call them engineers and rocket scientists now. But that doesn’t change the fact that a bunch of hot rodders figured out how to get America into Space, and Stacey takes a look at the roots of the Space Program, and the invention of the moon buggy. Then it’s out to the NASA testing grounds to see the annual Moon buggy race. If you think you’ve seen some weird projects, wait until you see what some of these young minds have dreamed up. You may think you’re on another planet, but you’re not… you’re watching GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20130322</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0080.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718140001 +0000" stop="20250718143002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Short Bed Classic Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey picks up right where he left off a few weeks ago and proceeds to install a brand new short bed, on the chassis of a truck that was born a LONG BED. That’s right, with the cutting done, the next step is to assemble a new short bed using all new aftermarket parts. You hear people say, “if it was that easy, everybody would be doing it!” Well, it IS that easy, and a lot of people ARE doing it… and YOU need to be one of them! Now… chop to it!</desc>
    <date>20130329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0081.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718143002 +0000" stop="20250718150003 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>P38 Lightning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It was one of the most lethal airplanes of WWII… the P-38 Lightning. Stacey takes a look at what made it so unique and why the German army nicknamed it the “Forked tailed devil”. But the legend didn’t end in the 1940’s… it continues on as Stacey showcases the new P-38 engine parts from Jon Kaase that you can put on your small block Ford to make it run like greased lightning! After that, Stacey sits down with Rock and Roll legend and certified car nut, James Burton, to dig into the unique connection between cars, guitars, and Rock and roll. Turn it on… crank it up… and hold on!</desc>
    <date>20130405</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0082.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718150003 +0000" stop="20250718153002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Lawn &amp; Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Some of the most neglected tools around the house are lawn and garden tools. Mowers, weed-eaters, chain saws, etc. all usually get thrown in a garage in the fall, never to be touched again until spring. Stacey walks through the simple steps on how to care for those tools, so they give you years of trouble free service. After that, He goes through the many parts you will need to put a manual transmission into a project, with Transmission Tech. Finally, if you’re looking for a simple project to do over the weekend, how about a muffler swap? You say “no”?... Stacey says “yes.”</desc>
    <date>20130412</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0083.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718153002 +0000" stop="20250718160004 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>V8 Interceptor Paint and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The V8 Interceptor is BACK and wearing a striking coat of glossy black paint! How did it happen? Well, Stacey walks you through the process and shows off the incredible paint and body work that was done by the Hot Rod Institute. From the subtle body nips and tucks, to the major fabrication of a new roof, this classic Cougar now has a straighter body than anything that may have rolled off the assembly line in 1967! But the paint is only half the story, as Stacey starts to re-assemble the car with bumpers, lights and engine, you start to get a good look at what is rapidly becoming the ultimate street predator!</desc>
    <date>20130419</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0084.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718160004 +0000" stop="20250718163006 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Winches</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>What is cooler than a vintage tow truck? … Nothing! Stacey proves that point by rolling Heavy Metal back into the GEARZ shop to outfit it with new electric winches, and an amazing custom tool box and light bar. This ’69 International cabover truck may have been rescued from a junkyard, but it won’t be long before this truck starts pulling off rescues of its own! This is recycling at it’s best! Then ride along with Stacey and crew as they travel to Minnesota and get the story on Edwards Manufacturing and how they have managed to stay in business for over a hundred years building simple tools. It’s all good, and it’s all GEARZ!!</desc>
    <date>20130426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0085.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718163006 +0000" stop="20250718170008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ray Barton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When you say “HEMI”, you get people’s attention! But when you say “Ray Barton HEMI” you win races. Stacey and crew take you to Ray Barton Racing Engines to show you the amazing engines and parts they build, and why they go so fast. After that, Stacey digs into the interior of the V8 Interceptor and shows what kind of options you have when you are restoring or customizing the interior of your project. You’ll love the custom PRS guitar and matching wood dash and steering wheel! There is no doubt that this Cougar is the perfect blend of brutal power, and sophisticated elegance.</desc>
    <date>20130503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0086.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718170008 +0000" stop="20250718173007 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt. Rock Exhaust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in SGT. ROCK to take care of steering, brakes, and the exhaust system. With a quick trip to Stainless Works for a custom set of headers and exhaust system, and with the layout of the four-wheel hydraulic steering, it won’t be long before this big military beast is rolling under its own power. After that, he takes on the seat in Heavy Metal tow truck. Just because a project may have come out of a junkyard, doesn’t mean it has to look like junk. Stacey proves that by adding a custom bomber-style seat to this already VERY unique vehicle… this episode of GEARZ is the one to see!</desc>
    <date>20130510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0087.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718173007 +0000" stop="20250718180009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Moby Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey sets out to build a nice hunting rig out of a 2012 GMC 4x4 truck. But this rig belongs to John Godwin of Duck Commander, which means the truck will be spending some serious time on the road… and off… hunting for ducks. On goes a 6” lift, 35” tall tires, and massive bumpers and winch to pull this big white beast out of any mud holes it may end up in. And since it IS such a big white beast, it is only fitting that Stacey name this project “Moby Duck”! If you’ve ever wondered if it’s possible to have a daily driver, that can also be a nice hunting, fishing, or outdoor rig. This episode of GEARZ will show you how to do it.</desc>
    <date>20130517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0088.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718180009 +0000" stop="20250718183009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Super Car, Hot Rods, Go Carts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls the SL-C back into the shop to show off the twin turbo system Schwartz Performance installed. If you thought 1000hp out of an LS-7 was impossible, THINK AGAIN! Even wilder is the fact that this engine is pulling that kind of horsepower on pump gas! If supercars and twin turbos are your thing, you have to see this! After that, Stacey goes through some of the problem areas that you will face when you are building a vehicle and how to pick the right project. Finally He digs into the 1st motorized vehicle that most of us had…the Go-Kart. There's something for everybody in this show. That’s why they call it GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20130524</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0089.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718183009 +0000" stop="20250718190011 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building A Shop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>We dig into the ultimate how-to project… building a shop! It’s an incredible transformation as Stacey and Crew take a huge open warehouse and build it into the new GEARZ shop. Along the way you’ll pick up all kinds of tips and tricks that Stacey uses when he’s setting up a useable work space. With today’s economy, there are more and more people thinking about opening a shop, or converting their existing garage space into a more useable area. This show can help you do that. After that, Stacey shows how to stop rust dead in its tracks by using the simplest tool in the box… a paint brush! It’s all here on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140407</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0090.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718190011 +0000" stop="20250718193010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Gearz Express</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey makes a house call… to Pennsylvania! Why?... to pick up an old fire truck to use as a project truck to make even more house calls with! If this sounds confusing, then you NEED to see this show, because Stacey shows you how to take a vehicle that nobody really has a use for anymore, and convert it into something you can use for your home or business. Sound deadening, tool boxes, and an on-board air system are all things that you’ll see go on as the big green fire truck, begins the conversion into a rolling tool truck</desc>
    <date>20140414</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0091.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718193010 +0000" stop="20250718200012 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>100th Episode Pt. 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s anniversary time…the 100th episode of GEARZ! And we have put together a one-hour special of the history and making of GEARZ, in two episodes! Stacey takes a look back at how the show came about. Then he digs into some of the project vehicles, and looks at the ideas and reasoning that shaped these trend-setting vehicles. If you’re new to GEARZ or wondered how the show was put together, this episode will shed some light on that</desc>
    <date>20140421</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0092.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718200012 +0000" stop="20250718203009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>100th Episode Pt. 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Part two of the 100th Episode special starts with a bang and a lot of tire smoke, as Stacey looks back at some of the wild test drives and feature vehicles that have been on GEARZ over the years. After that, they go behind the scenes and show you some of the funny and potentially dangerous situations that can happen when you work on a show like GEARZ. Finally, we showcase some of the incredible guests that have been on the show, to give you an idea of what to expect in the future. It’s all here and only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140428</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0093.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718203009 +0000" stop="20250718210009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Wrapping The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey rolls in the big green fire truck, with every intention of changing the color and look. But he’s not using paint… he’s using a vinyl wrap! If you’ve ever wondered what the deal is with vinyl wraps and if it is a good thing to do to your project, you need to see this show! But that’s not all, as the wrap is going on, Stacey also takes the time to show how to restore and bring back to life your accessories and trim without spending a lot of money.</desc>
    <date>20140505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0094.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718210009 +0000" stop="20250718213010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Richard Petty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>If you’ve been around cars very much, you’ve heard the term “barn find”. It depicts that “diamond in the rough” vehicle that everybody wants to find. Stacey delves into the barn find phenomenon and unveils what could be the ultimate barn find… the lost Richard Petty Car! Follow the incredible story of the car that Richard and Maurice Petty built in their early days, that was then sold and disappeared for decades... only to be found by Stacey and returned to Richard Petty so it could take its rightful place in the Petty Museum. It’s gearhead archeology at its best, and you’ll only see it on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20140512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0095.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718213010 +0000" stop="20250718220010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey hits the road to visit a GEARZNation member to see if he can lend a hand on his project. The owner is a 16-year-old kid and the subject is his ’96 Dodge pickup that’s looking a little rough from years of use and abuse. That quickly changes as Stacey jumps in to help give the truck a new face, and at the same time offers tips and tricks to breathe a breath of fresh air into the project. See what a difference some time, expertise, and a few parts can make on a beat up old truck! After that, Stacey takes a look at the amazing Moduline Cabinets, and digs into what makes them so great.</desc>
    <date>20140519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0096.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718220010 +0000" stop="20250718223008 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>LMC Casey James Bronco</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey shows you how to tackle the one restoration project that everybody dreams of doing one day... the frame off restoration! You’ll be surprised how simple a job like this can be if you follow his simple tips and tricks and plan the project out properly. In the world of high dollar builds, a simple frame off restoration can get you back on the road enjoying your car or truck and at a fraction of the price. But to get a grasp on how to do it, you have to see this show. After that, Stacey swaps some licks with recording artist Casey James who just happens to be a gearhead at heart… all here… all Gearz!</desc>
    <date>20140526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0097.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718223008 +0000" stop="20250718230009 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Custom Bumper Mounts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>So, you think you want some custom bumpers for your big ol’ truck? Stacey shows you how to find what you’re looking for in the aftermarket, and also how to fabricate and build your own custom mounts to make ‘em sit exactly where you want them. After that he digs into the history of the Sgt. Rock truck and how it is permanently connected to “the greatest generation”. But this truck isn’t just about WWII, as a special tailgate airbrushed by Mickey Harris reveals, It’s about the men and women that have sacrificed for the freedoms we enjoy today. This is one show that will have you waving the flag!</desc>
    <date>20140602</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0098.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718230009 +0000" stop="20250718233010 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey hits the road to help out a Gearz Nation member with his ‘56 Corvette project. Since the guy really wants to drive the car, putting in a modern 5 or 6spd tranny would be really nice. But which one? Well, we not only answer that question, but also give the guy a little helping hand with the transmission too. If you’ve ever wished Stacey made house calls, this is the show to see. After that we take a look at some serious questions that people ask about becoming a tool dealer and if it’s really worth it. You wanted to know… we got the answers for you!</desc>
    <date>20140609</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0099.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250718233010 +0000" stop="20250719000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Street Sweeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey dives into the world of the sleeper, by taking a non-descript ’73 Plymouth Satellite, and begins transforming it into a street pounding monster under the skin. Gone is the lethargic 318 engine and front suspension, and in its place Stacey begins fitting a new state of the art performance suspension. It you are into surprising people at stop lights and run-what-you-brung race nights, then a “Street Sweeper” just might be the sort of approach you want to take on your next project.</desc>
    <date>20140616</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0100.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250719000000 +0000" stop="20250719002959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Street Sweeper E3 Testing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Street Sweeper is back! Stacey delves into just how many parts it takes to completely change the drivetrain and suspension on a classic muscle car. Accessories, transmission, overdrive, headers, the list may seem to go on forever, but it’s all about finding the right parts in the aftermarket, to build the car that YOU want. After that it’s off to the races to see if E3’s new top fuel spark plug can handle the pressure of competition. If you want to see the ins and outs of building a car, GEARZ is the show to see!</desc>
    <date>20140623</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0101.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
