<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708010425 +0000" stop="20250708015039 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl in the Closet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E79</episode-num>
    <desc>The exclusive interview with a woman who was held captive in a closet.</desc>
    <date>20120206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708015039 +0000" stop="20250708023633 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Help My YouTube Addicted Wife!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E47</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband wants his wife to shut down her You Tube channel and focus in their marriage.</desc>
    <date>20171027</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16047.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708023633 +0000" stop="20250708032223 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Trisha's Dramatic Collapse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E309</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his conversation with Trisha, a mother and wife, who is live streaming her entire life. Trisha claims she’s been bullied and harassed by her online “haters.” But Wendy, one of the women Trisha calls a “hater,” says it’s Trisha who has ruined people’s lives by live streaming their personal information, making negative comments about their appearance, and even claiming they are convicts. Find out what caused Trisha to storm off and collapse on stage. And, why did Dr. Phil almost have to call the paramedics?</desc>
    <date>20171030</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16309.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708032223 +0000" stop="20250708040853 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Did She Marry an Imposter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman recounts her marriage to a man, who allegedly concealed his criminal past.</desc>
    <date>20131125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708040853 +0000" stop="20250708045604 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Dads</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E105</episode-num>
    <desc>They threaten, scream, intimidate and even bite. They’re not tantrum-throwing tots, but bullying dads.</desc>
    <date>20070502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708045604 +0000" stop="20250708054316 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Affair, Lies, &amp; Audiotape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One man says he caught his wife cheating – on audiotape – but she denies the accusations. Who’s really telling the truth? Dr. Phil gets to the bottom of the alleged affair on tape. Can this relationship survive without trust?</desc>
    <date>20111103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708054316 +0000" stop="20250708063018 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Lohans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E410</episode-num>
    <desc>In a rare interview, Dina Lohan sets the record straight.</desc>
    <date>20120917</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11410.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708063018 +0000" stop="20250708071523 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>An Unsolved Murder, A Family Divided</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E93</episode-num>
    <desc>In August 2009, Penny’s 40-year-old sister, Shannon, a successful businesswoman, was found dead in her car, at the bottom of a cliff, in what authorities initially believed was a tragic accident but later ruled a homicide -- a case that remains unsolved. Emotions run high when Penny faces her father, Ted, for the first time in two years and drops a bombshell: She believes he hired a hitman to kill Shannon. Ted admits his relationship with Shannon was strained at the time, but he vehemently denies he had anything to do with her death. How will Ted react to Penny’s accusation? Tune in to watch the drama unfold as this father and daughter angrily level charges against each other -- can Penny and Ted find a way to repair their relationship, or have the accusations gone too far?</desc>
    <date>20150202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708071523 +0000" stop="20250708080240 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Twisted Family Tragedy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From the outside, Tayler's life seemed picture perfect -- but no one could have imagined the disturbing secrets she was hiding behind her smile. From the ages of 6 to 17, Tayler says her dad, Russell, molested her, gave her drugs, and took her to Mexico on numerous occasions, where she was forced to do unspeakable things. How could these horrific events have occurred without anyone noticing? Tayler's mom, Deanna, says she was unaware of the alleged abuse, and just thought Tayler and her father had a special father-daughter bond. Were there warning signs she missed? Now 19 and addicted to heroin, Tayler says she feels alone, abandoned and confused -- but she also admits that she misses her father. Can Dr. Phil help get her on a path to both emotional and physical recovery? Then, hear from Tayler's two younger sisters. What did they witness? Were they being groomed by their father? And, where is Russell today? If you're a parent, tune in to learn how to protect your child from a predator.</desc>
    <date>20121015</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708080240 +0000" stop="20250708084911 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Actress Accused: Murder Accomplice?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E84</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman faces accessory charges after her fiancé's arrest for two murders.</desc>
    <date>20130205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11084.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708084911 +0000" stop="20250708093603 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Football Star Accused: Did He Do It?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In a Dr. Phil exclusive, a 17-year-old football star accused of rape -- and the alleged victim -- speak out about how one alcohol-fueled night changed their lives in an instant. Matt says he and three friends were drinking at a party nearly nine months ago when the four boys had sex with a 16-year-old classmate. He claims she initiated the encounter and that the sex was consensual. Matt and the three boys are charged with second-degree rape, and Matt says his dreams of getting a college scholarship have been put on hold. How does he describe the events of that night? And, what, if anything, does he say he’d do differently? Then, hear from the alleged victim, who is speaking out for the first time. What does she recall happening that night? And, how has the ordeal impacted her life? Plus, Matt’s parents, Dianne and Mark, insist their son is innocent and say they believe the alleged victim is out for attention. Dr. Phil has a powerful message for the couple.</desc>
    <date>20130912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708093603 +0000" stop="20250708102312 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Football Star's Alleged Victim Speaks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E304</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil delves into the dangers of teenage sex and underage drinking -- and how three families have been affected. In Part 2 of his exclusive interview, the 16-year-old girl who claims high school football star Matt and three other classmates raped her at a party opens up about what she says happened that night. Why does she say her peers care more about the accused football players than they do her? Don’t miss Matt and his parents’ reactions to what she has to say. Then, Leah alleges that in 2011, her 15-year-old daughter, Rehtaeh, was raped by four classmates at a party, and that after nearly a year-and-a-half of relentless bullying, the teen took her own life. How could this have been prevented? And what message does Leah have for others in similar situations? Plus, hear from Alexis, who says she too was raped at 15 and “could’ve been Rehtaeh.” What does she say got her through her darkest moments? Don’t miss this powerful cautionary tale for every teen and parent! This program contains strong sexual content.</desc>
    <date>20130913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708102312 +0000" stop="20250708111225 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Spouses At War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E62</episode-num>
    <desc>Anger is a toxic emotion in many marriages. It can tear away the very core of what made you fall in love with your spouse. From the outside, Jake and Donna appear to be a perfect couple, but behind closed doors, their knock-down, drag-out fights are driving them to the brink of divorce. Can they end their power struggle in time to save their marriage?</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708111225 +0000" stop="20250708115617 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Monster in the Media?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E93</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother defends her son caught in viral attack video.</desc>
    <date>20200210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708115617 +0000" stop="20250708124007 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Our Son is a 40YO Homeless Camper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E64</episode-num>
    <desc>41 year old man lives in his car but claims he isn't homeless.</desc>
    <date>20190130</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17064.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708124007 +0000" stop="20250708132759 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Angry Women, Scared Husbands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E100</episode-num>
    <desc>You may know that one in four women will become a victim of domestic violence, but did you know that one in nine men will too? Violence against men is rarely talked about and under-reported. Dr. Phil continues his campaign to end the silence on domestic violence with two couples willing to open up about their abusive relationships. Steve says his wife, Monica, punches him and recently pushed him down a flight of stairs. He says he’s not only afraid of her abuse, he’s afraid of how he may retaliate in the heat of anger. The couple has nine children between them – two of whom are severely disabled – and they’re worried about the effect their explosive arguments have on their kids. Then, Charlie worries she’ll get so angry at her new husband, Gary, that she’ll lash out and inadvertently kill him. Gary says that everything he does makes his wife mad, and he just can’t win. Can these women learn to control their tempers and stop the chaos before something tragic happens? Learn more about Dr. Phil’s End the Silence on Domestic Violence campaign and pledge to become a silence breaker!</desc>
    <date>20110527</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708132759 +0000" stop="20250708141511 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Con Artists and Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E46</episode-num>
    <desc>From petty theft to check fraud, Dr. Phil's guests say they're addicted to stealing, and it's destroying their families.</desc>
    <date>20080123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708141511 +0000" stop="20250708145926 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Spoiled Rotten Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E126</episode-num>
    <desc>Two moms ask Dr. Phil to give their sons a reality check. Rita says her son, Eric, changed his name to “King Keith” and is forgoing a college education to pursue a singing career. Has he lost touch with reality? And, Cheryl says her college-educated son, Patrick, is lazy and lacks ambition.</desc>
    <date>20120502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10126.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708145926 +0000" stop="20250708154706 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Mooch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E95</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil talks to women who are the family breadwinners and are sick of living with a mooching mate!</desc>
    <date>20060131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708154706 +0000" stop="20250708163703 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Crazy, Stupid Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E71</episode-num>
    <desc>Amanda says her husband of two years, Jeffrey, was recently caught in an online child sex sting and sentenced to five years in prison, yet she’s not sure if she should leave him. Why does she say she blames herself for what happened? And, hear from Amanda’s parents, Juliet and Timothy, who say they just want their daughter to move on. When Dr. Phil gives Amanda a harsh dose of reality, will she see the situation for what it is? Then, 18-year-old Seri says that two years ago, she fell in love with 26-year-old Hector, who convinced her to quit school and become a prostitute — and give him all the profits. Hector was convicted of sexual assault of a child and is now serving up to 30 years in prison. Seri is raising their daughter and has a new boyfriend, Will, but she admits that she would consider taking Hector back, if given the opportunity. Why does Seri say she still has feelings for her abuser?</desc>
    <date>20130107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708163703 +0000" stop="20250708172235 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Stranger Obsessed with Our Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E138</episode-num>
    <desc>April says another woman is electronically stealing photos of her children and posing as their mother online.</desc>
    <date>20160511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14138.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708172235 +0000" stop="20250708180735 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Ashley Confess? (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E318</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his conversation with husband and wife, Nathan and April, who claim a woman named Ashley is fixated on their beautiful twin daughters.</desc>
    <date>20160512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14318.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708180735 +0000" stop="20250708185337 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Rude Teens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents: If your teen talks back, acts out or is just plain rude, you better tune in!</desc>
    <date>20100909</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708185337 +0000" stop="20250708194009 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Is This Marriage Really Over?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E320</episode-num>
    <desc>From the outside, Jason and Shani had the perfect marriage " a big, beautiful house on the lake and three adorable boys " but recently Jason was crushed to learn that Shani's been having an affair with a mutual friend. Now, Shani is torn between her husband and her lover. What would you do?</desc>
    <date>20080508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6320.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708194009 +0000" stop="20250708202613 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Spanked My Wife with a Wooden Spoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man makes headlines for spanking his wife with a wooden spoon.</desc>
    <date>20140922</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708202613 +0000" stop="20250708211224 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Husband Spanks Me &amp; I Apologize??</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E301</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with a man who spanked his wife with a wooden spoon.</desc>
    <date>20140923</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13301.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708211224 +0000" stop="20250708215759 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Family Court Battles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E100</episode-num>
    <desc>Stalking allegations, surveillance cameras, restraining orders. This is the real-life drama of a mother and daughter who have declared war on each other! Rita claims her daughter, Lisa, is alienating her from her 13-year-old grandson, Koal, and is brainwashing him to hate her. Lisa says Rita is crazy and is using Koal as a weapon to hurt her.</desc>
    <date>20080221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708215759 +0000" stop="20250708224454 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Get Out of My Family Tree!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A Mother-in-Law who spies on her son and 2 sisters fighting over the family will!</desc>
    <date>20101110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708224454 +0000" stop="20250708233013 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Rude Relatives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E51</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you know someone who turns your stomach or makes you cringe the minute he or she walks into the room? Dr. Phil talks to guests who say their relative's rude behavior keeps them on edge.</desc>
    <date>20061122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250708233013 +0000" stop="20250709001427 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Tourette’s Made Me Viral</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E106</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman posts Tik Tok videos of her struggle with Tourette syndrome.</desc>
    <date>20220302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L20106.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709001427 +0000" stop="20250709005808 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Homeless and “Engaged” to Putin?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman believes she's going to be Vladimir Putin's wife.</desc>
    <date>20191111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18035.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250709005808 +0000" stop="20250709014257 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Shot My Millionaire Cheater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E140</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who shot her fiancé in the leg after he cheated wants to marry him.</desc>
    <date>20180426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16140.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
