<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718000356 +0000" stop="20250718020249 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Autumn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the remote hamlet of Goodman's Land, local postman and casanova Dave Cutler gets murdered whilst doing his early postal delivery. Barnaby and Troy, with WPC Jay Nash, start investigating. They discover Dave had slept with many women in the village. A witness later recalls having heard strange 1950s dance music before the murder. When others become victims to the killer, the detectives need to find a possible link to connect the murders before Jay gets into a perilous situation herself.</desc>
    <date>20010916</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vIBCvCqI7Iz9pgStgDfD9M5XNgj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718020249 +0000" stop="20250718034959 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As preparations are underway for Cully Barnaby's wedding, Ned Fitzroy and Beth Porteous are married in Bledlow village. At the gorgeous reception at Bledlow Hall, the maid of honour, Marina Fellowes, is found by a couple of guests murdered in an upstairs room. With the honeymoon postponed, the newlyweds and their guests find themselves being interrogated by the police.</desc>
    <date>20080510</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mhESsfxwBmjh8wSnmRbrLkxaK3U.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718034959 +0000" stop="20250718053712 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Shot At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When the name of Tommy Hicks, who was executed for cowardice and desertion during World War I, is added to the war memorial in Midsomer Parva, the Hicks family are very glad. The son and grandson, Lionel and Mayor Dave Hicks, revel in the occasion. The Hammond family are much more displeased. Henry, the patriarch, is infuriated by the move, having sustained a long-running feud with the Hickses.</desc>
    <date>20080101</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LCIvKnzwkQfnTrGSMResopWTGz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718053712 +0000" stop="20250718072634 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Left For Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The village of Dunstan, leads Barnaby and Jones to investigate the deaths of reclusive couple, Ron and Libby Wilson. Early on in the case, they learn that their son Michael had been killed in a hit and run. Not too far away a fiery dispute is in full swing, between a builder who has a very short fuse and a group of road protesters, protesting about plans for a bypass. With hostilities almost at breaking point, it is not long before another death rocks the village.</desc>
    <date>20080524</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fgnerGKRvOSICEtNfOhENwi8Wo7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718072634 +0000" stop="20250718091550 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Midsomer Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When the body of Charlie Finleyson is found in woodland in Midsomer Sonning. Barnaby and Jones begin to scrutinise the employees at the offices of Midsomer Life magazine. It is discovered that Mr Finleyson was married to the ex-wife of Guy Sandys, the wealthy owner of the magazine. The detectives also become aware of a dispute between Guy and the owner of the Morecroft Hotel. With tensions starting to rise between the locals and visitors from London.</desc>
    <date>20080531</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ew618rTr6XYkfDrhg4R3RFn9UCG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718091550 +0000" stop="20250718110310 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Magician's Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>During a children's magic show, a performer assisting with a trick, is poisoned whilst on stage. It is found that the poison came from a species of Ecuadorean frog. Barnaby and Jones discover that conflict is once again brewing between a village occult guide and enthusiast Ernest Baillol and famous writer Aloysius Wilmington who are both searching for a treasured antique book on the subject.</desc>
    <date>20080614</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mO3WpqHBKIJwgwjjJKzTmVp1PrB.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718110310 +0000" stop="20250718125024 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Days Of Misrule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A team building exercise is imminent planned by a new acting Chief Superintendent John Cotton and Barnaby and Jones are very reluctant to take part. Following an explosion in a truck at a haulage yard, both the detectives see the opportunity as a distraction to investigate. It is not long after that a body is discovered, when a trunk resurfaces from the nearby lake. It is identified as Alec Grainger, a man who had been arguing with James Parkes, the son of Colonel Matt Parkes.</desc>
    <date>20080705</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dAw5JF8lyYPZ5kSBHUJBRXeBBlQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718125024 +0000" stop="20250718143938 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Talking To The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In the village of Monks Barton, two couples seemingly disappear from their cottages. When Barnaby and Jones arrive and learn of the legendary, mysterious haunted woods, they remain sceptical. Shortly after a body is found in a shallow grave, answering to the description of one of the 'missing'. The detectives have to delve much deeper into the woods and beyond to find out if ghosts are really to blame or something else.</desc>
    <date>20080805</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/juPnY9Mf7cU9WIes42qLd92iQY6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718143938 +0000" stop="20250718162414 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Made To Measure Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Milton Cross depend on lord of the manor Edward Milton, for their jobs and income. When Sonia Woodley is found murdered in the churchyard, two years after the death of her abusive husband Gerald, the murder weapon is discovered to be tailor's shears, but which one of villagers is responsible? Barnaby and Jones arrive at Woodley and Woodley, the tailors to find out, to discover that the vicar had received a letter from Sonia a few days before.</desc>
    <date>20100512</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tXZ7Zqn1wMQZbXoJJnnSSB8ZdP5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718162414 +0000" stop="20250718180908 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword Of Guillaume</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>During a council meeting, Mayor Dave Hicks announces plans to awaken an annual trip to Brighton. Barnaby suspects his proposal to buy coastal land there is a fraud. Barnaby reluctantly joins the party, but during their time in Brighton, hated property developer Hugh Dalgleish is beheaded on a ghost train ride. The detectives together with Tom's cousin DCI John Barnaby gather who from the party or someone else could have been responsible before other murders occur and secrets are uncovered.</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3vsfoPqqRENM97cx6wVGBFMLcb7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718180908 +0000" stop="20250718195404 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Saddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ford Florey is anything but quiet, when the Wild West Society bring their show and fair, consisting of many stalls and a shooting re-enactment. The witch on the 'Dunk the Witch' stall, gets truly dunked and goes horribly wrong, when the water starts turning red. Barnaby and Jones have to be alert with a shooter in their midst. With many grudges, jealousies and a dispute over wasteland, known as 'the swamp', as possible motives, it is not long before more people turn up dead.</desc>
    <date>20100908</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8DFMFTMHAc9gjZoFswWVd0jrAaQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718195404 +0000" stop="20250718213832 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On a dark night in the village of March Magna, Joyce Barnaby swerves her car and narrowly misses a shadowy figure in the road. Shortly after a body is found in the local old cemetery. The victim Gerald Ebbs was a member of the council and of the village's library. It is discovered from the villagers that Gerald had had a strange fixation on both the old hospital and cemetery; in particular a grave from within.</desc>
    <date>20100922</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qXbun3EZ9GMJvqNlUAyznQ8VtwY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718213832 +0000" stop="20250718232329 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Master Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Devington Manor Winter School led by internationally renowned musician Sir Michael Fielding, is a magnet for many aspiring piano students. Amongst the latest batch of students is Zoe Stock, a gifted young lady. Whilst in the grounds of the manor and by the riverbank, Zoe sees a woman jump from the bridge and disappear underwater. When Barnaby and Jones start their enquiries into the possible drowning, they discover many shady connections to the past.</desc>
    <date>20101006</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ab8nTnZk7hjjfUoZsaRVyfamFZp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718232329 +0000" stop="20250719010758 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Noble Art</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When boxer John Kinsella wins a world title in New York, the village of Midsomer Morchard are overjoyed at his success. Shortly afterwards a solicitor is found dead by his assistant and Kinsella's manager. Barnaby and Jones start to investigate and come across infidelity, anger, betrayals and blackmail. When a Victorian prize-fight re-enactment turns nasty and Kinsella's manager is found murdered in his home's gym.</desc>
    <date>20101013</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cn661RGTLE6sjtH9yuZcR8glQal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
