<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723000726 +0000" stop="20250723005346 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Does Age Matter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Can May-December romances really last? Christopher Knight, famous for his role as Peter on The Brady Bunch, and Adrianne Curry, winner on America's Next Top Model, began their relationship when they starred together on the reality show The Surreal Life 4, and the public watched as they planned their wedding on their own show, My Fair Brady. Now they both say their 24-year age difference is a huge problem in their chaotic marriage. Adrianne says Christopher treats her like an employee, and Christopher says if she worked for him, she would’ve been fired a long time ago. Can these two work out their generational differences? Then, 38-year-old Shelly wants to know if it’s wrong to be in a relationship with an 18-year-old friend of her son. She says he makes her feel beautiful, but wonders if she’s causing him or her children harm. Dr. Phil doesn’t mince words when he tells her his opinion.</desc>
    <date>20070921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6006.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723005346 +0000" stop="20250723014112 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Controversy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil explores the controversial trend of older women dating much younger men. Is age really just a number? First, Pie, a 58-year-old self-admitted cougar, has been dating 24-year-old Oleg for four months -- and her best friend, Terese, strongly disapproves. Could Pie be headed for heartbreak? Then, 52-year-old divorcée Bella says her relationship with 32-year-old Eddie is the best she has ever had. Eddie says he loves Bella and doesn’t mind that she’s the same age as his mother. Does this couple see a long-term future together? And, 76-year-old Aalsa -- former Miss Cougar America -- says after 40, men go downhill! After dating younger men for four decades, what advice does she have for fellow cougars? Tune in and decide for yourself: Can a relationship really survive a significant age gap?</desc>
    <date>20141210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723014112 +0000" stop="20250723022905 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Sugar Baby Students</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil investigates the latest trend in online dating: sugar babies hooking up with sugar daddies. College girls and recent graduates who are struggling with mounting debt and a weak job market are turning to websites, such as SeekingArrangement.com, that introduce them to wealthy men who, in exchange for companionship - and maybe sex - help them pay their bills. Is this the Internet version of the world's oldest profession, or just a niche dating site? Four self-proclaimed sugar babies: Kristen, 21, Jennifer, 28, Janelle, 30, and Tracy, 31, passionately defend why their relationships differ from prostitution. Are their arranged monthly allowances and extravagant gifts the equivalent of being taken to fancy restaurants by a boyfriend or financially supported by a husband? Meet the creator of the website, Brandon, and hear why he says there's nothing wrong with these "mutually beneficial relationships." Former prosecutor and CNN analyst Sunny Hostin has some legal words of warning for Brandon and the ladies. Plus, an outraged father confronts Brandon in defense of his daughter, who he recently learned is on the site, and see why a self-proclaimed proud sugar daddy makes a hasty exit before meeting Dr. Phil!</desc>
    <date>20110916</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723022905 +0000" stop="20250723031253 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Toxic Marriage Accusations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Nikki says her three-year marriage has turned volatile. She claims her husband, Mark, has punched her in the face, broken her nose and run over her toe with his truck -- among other allegations -- which he denies. Mark claims Nikki instigates most of their fights and has violent outbursts, and he suspects she might be trying to kill him. The couple admits their confrontations happen in front of their two young children, and both say they want to save their marriage. Dr. Phil intervenes for the sake of their kids. Can this toxic relationship be healed?</desc>
    <date>20141107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13020.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723031253 +0000" stop="20250723040037 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parental Abductions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Follow a dad, John Clark's journey as he searches for his missing family.</desc>
    <date>20110104</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723040037 +0000" stop="20250723044727 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Abducted by Their Mother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E404</episode-num>
    <desc>An update with a father whose children were abducted by their mother.</desc>
    <date>20110204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9404.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723044727 +0000" stop="20250723053341 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Engaged to My Teen with Braces</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother is concerned her 17-year-old daughter is dating a 28-year-old divorced father.</desc>
    <date>20140926</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723053341 +0000" stop="20250723061842 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Arrested for Keying Ex-Boyfriends Car (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Autumn claims her ex-boyfriend, D’Andre, abused her, which he denies. Why does she defend him to her parents?</desc>
    <date>20181112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723061842 +0000" stop="20250723070504 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Dad Confronts Daughter’s Abuser (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E306</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with D’Andre, who blames his abusive relationship with his ex-girlfriend, Autumn, on her upbringing.</desc>
    <date>20181113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17306.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723070504 +0000" stop="20250723074959 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Schizophrenia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E51</episode-num>
    <desc>Imagine hearing voices that don't exist, thinking neighbors were controlling your behavior with magnetic waves, or that people on television were sending you secret messages. What if you constantly thought someone was following you, trying to poison you, out to get you? For those who suffer from schizophrenia, delusions and paranoia are part of daily life. Dr. Phil sheds light on a disease that is both complex and frightening.</desc>
    <date>20051123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723074959 +0000" stop="20250723083339 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beaten and Bruised: #WHYISTAY</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil shines the spotlight on domestic violence, speaking with Kaitlyn, who defends her professional fighter husband, Josh, even though he's being held in jail without bail stemming from an August incident. Plus, hear from Trichelle, who faces 20 years in prison after she says she shot and killed her husband in self-defense after years of alleged domestic abuse. Will her words of warning make an impact on Kaitlyn?</desc>
    <date>20140918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723083339 +0000" stop="20250723091800 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cult Leader Mother God</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A family says their relative is a cult leader who calls herself "Mother God."</desc>
    <date>20200914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723091800 +0000" stop="20250723100428 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mother God’s Followers &amp; Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E303</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with a woman who claims she is "Mother God."</desc>
    <date>20200915</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19303.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723100428 +0000" stop="20250723105114 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Wife or My Girlfriend?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man wants Dr. Phil's help in deciding between his wife of 8 years or girlfriend of 2 years.</desc>
    <date>20141126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723105114 +0000" stop="20250723113759 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen writes: Dear Dr. Phil, My husband mentally abuses me. I've never, in my life, had a guy tell me how fat I am, how terrible I look, or criticize how I put my makeup on. He constantly calls me names and makes fat jokes. Sometimes I have to hide in the bathroom when I eat something just so we won't fight about it. Any time I try to get close to him, he literally pushes me away and says, "Don't even touch me until you're under 200 pounds".</desc>
    <date>20250531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723113759 +0000" stop="20250723122611 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lazy &amp; Entitled Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E68</episode-num>
    <desc>Tracy says her daughter, Ashley, 22, and Ashley’s boyfriend, Andrew, 23, are freeloaders who are living rent-free in her home, while she pays all of their expenses. She says they sleep all day and have let her beautiful suburban home turn to filth. Tracy says she accepts blame for allowing the situation to spiral out of control -- learn the one mistake she says she regrets the most. Ashley and Andrew deny the accusations and say they work part-time for Tracy’s business, and they’ve earned everything she's given them. See what happens when Dr. Phil cameras enter the home. Dr. Phil gets real with Ashley and Andrew -- and Tracy. Can he get through to them? Then, Lorrie and Todd say that their 13-year-old-daughter controls their home. The parents admit that they just can't seem to say no to the teen, who they say throws tantrums and manipulates them until she gets her way. Lorrie and Todd say they prepare special meals for her and cut her food -- and it’s putting a strain on their marriage. Dr. Phil shares his insight and devises a plan to get this family back on track. Plus, tune in to find out the three tips you must know to ensure you're not spoiling your child.</desc>
    <date>20130103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11068.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723122611 +0000" stop="20250723131243 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Car Stealing Drug Taking Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents seek Dr. Phil's help for an out-of-control teen.</desc>
    <date>20170227</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L15087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723131243 +0000" stop="20250723140019 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Double Trouble: Sisters Backstage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E319</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents say their out-of-contol teen daughter is corrupting her younger sister.</desc>
    <date>20170228</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L15319.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723140019 +0000" stop="20250723144820 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I'm a Slave to My Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E116</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil talks to controlling guests and the loved ones who feel trapped by them. Jeffrey hates that his wife of seven months, Mindy, goes out clubbing with her younger friends, who he says are a bad influence on her. Mindy leaves the kids with Jeffrey's 16-year-old daughter and parties until 6:00 a.m., while he works the night shift. Mindy calls Jeffrey “a warden,” and says if he had his way, she’d never leave the house. Then, Jason claims his wife, Terrie, is lazy. He says he has to clean the house, do chores, take care of the kids and balance two checkbooks! Terrie says her large chest and arthritis prevent her from doing household tasks. Can Jason get his wife to clean up her act?</desc>
    <date>20060320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723144820 +0000" stop="20250723153515 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Get Out of My Family Tree!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A Mother-in-Law who spies on her son and 2 sisters fighting over the family will!</desc>
    <date>20101110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723153515 +0000" stop="20250723162133 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Explosive Anger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nichole claims her husband gets violent when he drinks which he denies. And, Theresa and Steve say their son Steven’s rage is out of control, and they fear for their lives. Plus, two victims of a road rage incident caught on tape share their story.</desc>
    <date>20130927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723162133 +0000" stop="20250723170931 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Updates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you ever wonder how your favorite Dr. Phil guest is faring since being on the show? Dr. Phil follows up with some of his most talked about guests.</desc>
    <date>20081202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723170931 +0000" stop="20250723175617 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Absentee Mom,Clueless Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E65</episode-num>
    <desc>John says that when his ex-wife, Laurie, moved 1,500 miles away to be with her boyfriend, Joe, she abandoned her children, and he was left to raise the couple’s three boys -- Johnny, 14, and twins Christopher and Alexander, 12 -- on his own. The single dad proudly proclaims that being a committed father makes him “one in a million” -- but is John really in over his head? John admits the boys disrespect his authority and recently, he says Alexander punched him in the face and gave him a black eye. Laurie says her children tell her that they aren’t happy living with their father, and she denies deserting her children -- but is she willing to step up and take Dr. Phil’s advice? Then, hear from the three boys. What do they reveal about their home life? And, is this a case of clueless parenting -- or unruly kids? No parent can afford to miss this all-new Dr. Phil!</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723175617 +0000" stop="20250723184554 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Moms Who Drink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E80</episode-num>
    <desc>There are killers among us, and they're not terrorists ... they're mothers who get drunk and then get behind the wheel, often with their kids in the car. More moms than ever are admitting to sneaking a drink or two while caring for their children. Learn how this epidemic may be affecting moms you know. This show just may be your call to action and help you save a life!</desc>
    <date>20100218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723184554 +0000" stop="20250723193313 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teens Obsessed with Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E88</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents are concerned about the extreme measures their daughters take to get and keep a boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>20100211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723193313 +0000" stop="20250723202139 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Older Teacher &amp; Younger Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E119</episode-num>
    <desc>Does love really conquer all? James, 41, quit his job and left his wife and three children to pursue a relationship with his 18-year-old former student, Jordan. The couple says they're not breaking any laws, want to set the record straight with Dr. Phil, and want Jordan's mother, Tammie, to stop her Facebook "smear campaign" against them. In a national exclusive, Tammie confronts James for the first time on Dr. Phil’s stage. Find out how the attraction began and why Tammie says James is lying. Were there secret meetings before Jordan turned 18? And, what does Jordan stand to lose? Parents, how would you react if your child started a relationship with his or her former teacher?</desc>
    <date>20120303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10119.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723202139 +0000" stop="20250723210937 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Love Stories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E317</episode-num>
    <desc>At 36, Lisa fell in love with her sons’ 14-year-old friend, Adrian. By the time he was 15, they were married and Lisa was pregnant with their first child. Seven years and two kids later, they're still together. Will their love last? And, learn how a former Arizona gubernatorial candidate went looking for international love but wound up homeless on the streets of Ukraine.</desc>
    <date>20120402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10317.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723210937 +0000" stop="20250723215655 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And Illegal?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Thirty-year-old mother of four Melissa Dilan-Hernandez made headlines when she was charged with unlawful sexual activity with certain minors, stemming from her relationship with her fiancé, T.J., who is 17 years old and the father of her 4-month-old child. Melissa is facing up to 15 years in prison and may have to register as a sex offender, yet she says she still doesn’t consider their relationship a crime. How does she justify her love affair with a minor -- and planning a pregnancy with him? T.J. says he wants to spend the rest of his life with Melissa -- but is he willing to wait for her if she goes to jail? And, could their romance stand in the way of his aspirations of becoming a U.S. Marine or police officer? T.J.’s father, Ed, and stepmother, Sea, weigh in with their thoughts on the relationship. Do they approve? Plus, don’t miss Dr. Phil’s stern advice for Melissa and T.J. -- and for any teen who may be blindsided by love.</desc>
    <date>20121120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723215655 +0000" stop="20250723224421 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Controversy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil explores the controversial trend of older women dating much younger men. Is age really just a number? First, Pie, a 58-year-old self-admitted cougar, has been dating 24-year-old Oleg for four months -- and her best friend, Terese, strongly disapproves. Could Pie be headed for heartbreak? Then, 52-year-old divorcée Bella says her relationship with 32-year-old Eddie is the best she has ever had. Eddie says he loves Bella and doesn’t mind that she’s the same age as his mother. Does this couple see a long-term future together? And, 76-year-old Aalsa -- former Miss Cougar America -- says after 40, men go downhill! After dating younger men for four decades, what advice does she have for fellow cougars? Tune in and decide for yourself: Can a relationship really survive a significant age gap?</desc>
    <date>20141210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723224421 +0000" stop="20250723232922 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Regret Marrying Older Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E59</episode-num>
    <desc>Brenda says she fell in love with and married her husband, Don – despite their 26-year age gap. But soon after, she claims her “Prince Charming” turned “crazy” and “temperamental.” Is their age difference at the root of their issues? Then, Bev says she’s concerned for her sister, Melanie, who married her much younger man, Devar, after meeting him on a Jamaican vacation. Is Devar in it for love, or for a green card and money? And, Dr. Phil catches up with best-selling author Mitch Albom.</desc>
    <date>20151210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723232922 +0000" stop="20250724000638 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>49-Year-Old Dad Dating Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Joni claims that Gina used to be one of her besties and that they were inseparable, from spending birthday trips out of town to girls’ nights out, often ending in Gina crashing at Joni’s house. Joni says all that changed when 23- year-old Gina began dating Joni’s 49-year-old father, David, behind her back and giving birth to David’s child. Joni says she feels betrayed by Gina and her father, even going as far as sharing her dislike for her former friend and father’s newfound romance on TikTok. Gina says the picture Joni paints of them being best friends is all a lie, but in any event, Joni needs to accept her relationship with Joni’s father. David says despite his daughter’s disapproval, he is going to continue being in a committed relationship with Gina, but that doesn’t mean he can’t also have a relationship with his daughter.</desc>
    <date>20201019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724000638 +0000" stop="20250724004925 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marrying Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E88</episode-num>
    <desc>Sixty-two-year-old Bill and his 23-year-old girlfriend, Bri, are one of the couples featured on Lifetime’s television series Marrying Millions. Bill and Bri say not only do they come from two different worlds, but they have a 39-year age gap and are at different stages of their lives – Bri wants a family and children, and Bill has been divorced twice. Bill’s first ex- wife claims Bill has a history of cheating, as she says he cheated on her and has warned Bri it could happen to her. While Bill and Bri have been together for four years, they say they are at a crossroads: what happens when he turns 70 and she is only 31? Also, they say their families don’t see eye-to-eye, which impacts their daily lives. How “healthy” is their relationship? The couple takes Dr. Phil’s “Relationship Health Profile Test” and learns the results. Plus, Dr. Phil speaks with superfans from across the U.S. and has a special announcement for them. One superfan even gets his own “Dr. Phil” tattoo ... live! You won’t want to miss this episode!</desc>
    <date>20210126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
