<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704004811 +0000" stop="20250704023259 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of Doc Mays</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Follows the story of Dwayne “Doc” Mays, born in North Carolina and raised in Chicago by his streetwise mother. After the death of his mother when he was 8 years old, he found himself a ward of the foster system, ultimately leading to a life on the streets and of crime. When he meets his future mentor “Street” he would rise to be one of the most notorious gangsters in Chicago’s history of organized crime.</desc>
    <date>20250128</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/96a81eb7c614536319b831c4906c3f9a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704023259 +0000" stop="20250704041446 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Wife</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young freelance photographer in Houston meets a beautiful determined teacher from Atlanta. His best friend tries to warn him about her. There is something a little strange about Claudia. Q loves her dearly but she may not be The Perfect Wife.</desc>
    <date>20221122</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/412ca4e25a6d6d4467092f8d652cbdd6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704041446 +0000" stop="20250704060143 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Wife 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Styles Girls relocate to a new state to start over after the loss of the only place they knew. Unbeknownst to them, the secrets they left behind surface within the walls of their new residence.</desc>
    <date>20221122</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/412ca4e25a6d6d4467092f8d652cbdd6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704060143 +0000" stop="20250704075515 +0000">
    <title>Till Death Do Us</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Marcus falls in love with Jessica, who has her own house and wants to start a family. Shortly after their honeymoon, Jessica's past life comes back in to the present. When Jessica's long lost husband reappears back in her life, and wants his family back. Marcus and Jessica are not willing to give up their new life, but her ex-husband is determined to win her back, even if it means risking his life.</desc>
    <date>20230905</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f78edcf864d6964bea9e9a5166bd8fca.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704075515 +0000" stop="20250704093308 +0000">
    <title>Till Death Do Us 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The fates of Tamara, TJ, and even Marcus himself hang in the balance after the bloody kitchen shooting. Did anyone survive? Will Pastor Marcus's mysterious powers intervene? Meanwhile, Jessica, TJ's ex-wife, faces scrutiny for her past actions and the future of their children. With the threat of child protective services looming, the clock is ticking to find answers and rebuild shattered lives.</desc>
    <date>20240901</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d6856f68934d7b0bf393a451cefbcd1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704093308 +0000" stop="20250704113604 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Traits</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Eric is a prodigal son, who meets Regina on a dating app and they fall in love. The two seem like a match made in heaven, except for Eric’s suspicious mother. Events begin to unfold and Regina’s true nature comes to light.</desc>
    <date>20240102</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/25dfe15257df3155b241cc7e95160b16.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704113604 +0000" stop="20250704131222 +0000">
    <title>To Live and Die in DC</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Lance Hill sticks to the street code of DC and is admired by those who crave fast money, who put risk over reward. It's his turn to tell his story... If he lives.</desc>
    <date>20231030</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704131222 +0000" stop="20250704144953 +0000">
    <title>Unsecured</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Bobby, haunted by the infidelity of his ex-wife, enters a new relationship with Lakeisha while grappling with deep-seated insecurities. Unbeknownst to Lakeisha, his past resurfaces when a witness claims to have seen him involved in a murder.</desc>
    <date>20241004</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/69037664e352dfcace3070128d4b3b2a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704144953 +0000" stop="20250704165748 +0000">
    <title>Women of the Jury</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A man is on trial accused of murder of two young black men, and twelve women are called to serve on the jury. After deliberation, one juror is convinced the man is not guilty, while the majority claims he is guilty. A conversation takes place consisting of arguments, alliances, and near violence. What will the verdict be?</desc>
    <date>20231013</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/17623227fbc8e5175a9e52293bbd2389.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704165748 +0000" stop="20250704184337 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Score</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After starting their new record label, Donica Blair and Shequell Harris have entered a dangerous arena full of guns, lies, and deceit. Now they are racing against time to right their wrongs and save their own lives before they are next in a string of murders. Meanwhile their partner Seven, has fallen victim to the deadliest of them all; the Black widow.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704184337 +0000" stop="20250704202828 +0000">
    <title>Runway of Shadows</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters Ivy and Zara are separated at a very young age due to their father’s deceit. When Ivy and Zara unexpectedly cross paths at a prestigious runway show, the stage it set for a series of mysterious and unsettling events.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704202828 +0000" stop="20250704220258 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704220258 +0000" stop="20250704234037 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704234037 +0000" stop="20250705010342 +0000">
    <title>Cougar</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Donna and her young college son Brandon live in a nice suburban area of Atlanta, until a new and mysterious older woman moves in next door. Donna invites her over to dinner where she and Brandon connect, and build a connection that is deadly and manipulative. A mother must save her son before it’s too late.</desc>
    <date>20250422</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250705010342 +0000" stop="20250705031124 +0000">
    <title>The Foreign Exchange Student</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sinclair John is a beautiful, troubled, young high school senior from Dominica. When her parents suspect she may have had something to do with her boyfriends death, they ship her to America under the Foreign Exchange Student Program. While living with her new family, she wreaks havoc and it's up to Jackie to stop her.</desc>
    <date>20221004</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b1b552b1b91896c34651e30e004caa2a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
