<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715000030 +0000" stop="20250715003030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715003030 +0000" stop="20250715010027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715010027 +0000" stop="20250715012836 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715012836 +0000" stop="20250715015843 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715015843 +0000" stop="20250715022845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715022845 +0000" stop="20250715025849 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715025849 +0000" stop="20250715033033 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715033033 +0000" stop="20250715040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big as Barney - No, No, No!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone loves Barney! When Ryan tries to be just like Barney, he has a hard time filling Barney's shoes. Ryan soon learns that he is special when he's just being himself! Baby Bop is having one of those days! Every time she turns around, someone is telling her no! As her frustration grows, Barney explains that the word no can help you avoid making mistakes or getting hurt.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029620_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715040000 +0000" stop="20250715043005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bunches of Boxes!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are so excited for a day of play and fun! When a bunch of empty boxes arrived from the Enjoy-Your-Toys Company, their adventure begins. They use their imagination to have the best time ever by transforming the boxes into special toys.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029534_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715043005 +0000" stop="20250715050002 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Stop! Go!”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After playing with Stop and Go signs with Angela, Baby Bop leaves to direct some traffic of her own. Barney and his friends think of other ways to stop and go and discuss reading, especially traffic signs!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029535_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715050002 +0000" stop="20250715053003 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Red, Yellow and Blue!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney helps his friends put together a Caboose Color Collection which showcases the primary colorsred, yellow and blue. This activity sparks Barney and the kids' imagination, and along with Baby Bop, they realize just how colorful the world can be!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029536_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715053003 +0000" stop="20250715060009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play for Exercise!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are amazed to find out that playing games and having fun in the park is a great way to exercise. When the rain starts to fall, they use their imagination to come up with clever ways to stay active and have fun indoors.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029537_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715060009 +0000" stop="20250715063008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Come Blow Your Horn!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the kids are full of excitement as five of Mr. Boyd's brass-playing friends are planning a special show in the park tonight! Angela is determined to learn the trumpet, but she finds it challenging. To help them get ready for the band's practice, Mr. Boyd introduces the children to various types of horns, making it a fun learning experience!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029538_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715063008 +0000" stop="20250715070009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A New Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Meet Colleen, Mr. Boyd's niece! Barney and the kids love having fun together every day but making a brand NEW friend is something extra special! With Barney's help, they all learn how to get to know new friends.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029539_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715070009 +0000" stop="20250715073008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Numbers! Numbers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony has a box filled with numbers that he made with his dad and is proudly showing them to everyone. Suddenly, a strong gust of wind scatters the numbers all around! Barney and his friends team up to go on an exciting number hunt, helping Tony find and collect his homemade numbers again.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029540_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715073008 +0000" stop="20250715080005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>This Way In! This Way Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Angela is in the park to release her turtle, Terry, after observing him with her classmates in school. Barney, Nick, and Sarah are delighted to see Terry come out of his shell, which leads to a discussion about the meanings of in and out. Baby Bop arrives with her chrysalis, and together with Angela's turtle, Barney and his friends are inspired to do In and Out activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029541_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715080005 +0000" stop="20250715083007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Into Fun!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a rainy spring day, and the children can be found inside painting and creating. The weather becomes an exciting opportunity for the kids to learn all about the season of Spring and discuss all the fun activities they can partake in this season. This includes flying a kite, riding a bike, and enjoying the rainbows in the sky.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029542_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715083007 +0000" stop="20250715090005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Play It Safe!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After feeling tired of being told to be careful, BJ learns that saying be careful is a way of showing love and concern. This important lesson prompts Barney to teach his friends essential safety rules. Spending time with Barney is always enjoyable, but it's also crucial to learn how to play it safe to stay protected and happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029543_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715090005 +0000" stop="20250715093008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Three Lines, Three Corners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends begin the day by playing hopscotchwith a twist. They discover that making a triangle requires 3 lines and 3 corners, which sparks their excitement to explore more shapes. To have even more triangle fun, Barney takes them on a camping trip where they get to explore and learn about different shapes in the world around them.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029544_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715093008 +0000" stop="20250715100007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Parade of Bikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Its the day of the bike parade, but Nick has had a bike accident that leaves his bike in need of repair by Mr. Boyd. Mr. Boyd works quickly to help fix Nick's bike in time for the parade. While waiting, Barney takes the opportunity to teach his friends all about bike safety, making sure they're ready to ride safely and have a great time in the parade!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029545_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715100007 +0000" stop="20250715103011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Happy Day!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids discuss their desire for a special day, Beth creates Happy Day, a special holiday in which each friend makes a wish and the others try to make it come true. When Beth hurts herself, BJ learns the importance of doing good deeds for others.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029546_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715103011 +0000" stop="20250715110009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Family and Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney plans a magical picnic for his friends and their families to spend quality time together and create lasting memories. Each kid has brought a family treasure to show Barney, which they all excitedly spend time sharing with one another.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029547_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715110009 +0000" stop="20250715113012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715113012 +0000" stop="20250715120016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715120016 +0000" stop="20250715123015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword in the Sandbox - A Storybook Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel fails miserably when he tries to join the others in jump rope. Convinced that he's too little to do anything right, Barney tells him the story of The Sword in the Sandbox. Through the legend of King Arthur, Daniel learns there are many things he can do... if he tries hard enough.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029632_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715123015 +0000" stop="20250715130009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff to the Rescue! - A Wild West Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Riff is asked to be captain of a baseball team, he doesnt think he can do it. But Barney gives him the courage to try, by recounting the tale of his great-great-grandfather Riffle the Wild West hero!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029633_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715130009 +0000" stop="20250715133011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lights! Camera! Action! - A Movie Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie comes up with the perfect idea to get people to donate to Grace's food drive - put on a movie premiere in the caboose! Barney and friends pitch in to help, but they all have different ideas about what kind of movie to make. Everything they try falls apart. It's curtains for Melanie's movie until she comes up with a blockbuster idea of her own.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029634_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715133011 +0000" stop="20250715140015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch a Thief - A Mystery Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Detective BJ is on the case when several sports balls suddenly disappear. Determined to find the mysterious ball thief, BJ falsely accuses Riff of being the thief. BJ learns he cannot jump to conclusions and must find the whole story to see who the thief really is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029635_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715140015 +0000" stop="20250715143014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Lamp - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrating her birthday in the park with friends, Layla is more interested in hot dogs than her mother's Middle Eastern food. When Barney reads the story of Aladdin and the Magic Lamp, Layla is transported to a Middle Eastern marketplace where she learns different cultures have many exciting foods and customs to offer.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029636_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715143014 +0000" stop="20250715150017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Amazing Captain Pickles - A Hero Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Pickles and Wonder Princess both wanted to be the super-est superheroes. When Captain Pickles said he could jump over the moon, everyone wanted to see. BJ knew he couldn't really jump that high, but he could jump high enough to save Emma's balloon. Everyone was proud of him, even if he couldn't jump over the moon. BJ was a hero.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029637_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715150017 +0000" stop="20250715153017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Game for Everyone - A Sports Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes up with the idea to have a sports day in the park. All day, they play games like soccer and hopscotch among others, all for fun. Meanwhile, Baby Bop meets a girl with special needs named Jill, as well as her mom. As Baby Bop gets to know Jill more, she encourages her to play hopscotch with the others. In the end, Baby Bop and Jill win the trophy for hopscotch and she and her mother leave.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029638_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715153017 +0000" stop="20250715160020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Dragon - A Fairy Tale Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids judge a spider by its creepy looks, Barney tells them the story of The Reluctant Dragon where a shepherd became friends with a dragon, who was judged by her appearance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029639_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715160020 +0000" stop="20250715162834 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bienvenido, Barney!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's friend Monty the butterfly passes through the park with a flock of friends on their way to Mexico. When Monty gets left behind, Barney takes everyone on a visit to Mexico to return Monty to his insect friends and family and give Baby Bop the chance to say goodbye to her butterfly friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029640_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715162834 +0000" stop="20250715170015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big Brother Rusty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's excited to find out that Rusty's family is adopting a new baby sister from China; however, Rusty's not sure if he's going to be a good brother, and he doesn't know much about China. Barney shows Rusty and the others some info China on the computer and BJ and Baby Bop talk about siblings. Through Barney's Travel Book, Barney takes Rusty, BJ and Baby Bop on an adventure to China where he can learn more about his new sister's heritage. When they get there, the people are celebrating Chinese New Year. From lion dances and talented performers to tasty treats, making lanterns and puppet shows, the celebration never runs out of fun. By the time he returns to the park, Rusty excitedly meets his new baby sister, named Mei Ling, and realizes he will be the best big brother ever.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029641_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715170015 +0000" stop="20250715173019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Ahora Mismo!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is late to the park and is disappointed to realize he missed his chance at riding a real pony. He has waited his whole life for this, and now it looks as if hes missed his opportunity. Luckily, Barney takes Ben to Spain where they meet Regalo, a dancing horse with Riff and Baby Bop. Ben and Barney return to the park just in time for him to ride the pony after all! Ben is thrilled to ride a horse and learned an important lesson about patience and waiting.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029642_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715173019 +0000" stop="20250715180024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Venice, Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Emma is stuck with a school project and can't play soccer with Joshua. Having to interview her parents and get info about an interesting ancestor, she is frustrated with the assignment. Barney helps her discover that her ancestors were from Venice, Italy. Using his Travel Book, Barney takes Joshua, Emma, and Riff to Venice, Italy. He gives his friends a gondola ride as well as telling them about famous explorer Marco Polo. Barney's friend, Anna Maria tells Emma that she knew her great grandfather and takes her to his shop, where they try on masks and make some of their own. Emma learns that if she makes the mask in parts, she'll get it done. Barney reminds her of this lesson, so she will do the same for her school project.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029643_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715180024 +0000" stop="20250715183023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sweeter Than Candy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, Baby Bop, and BJ are helping the kids get ready for a school play. Barney tells everyone that putting on shows began in Greece. Of course, the little dinos and kids want to visit the country, so off they go! While there, they meet some friends and decide to put on a play in an amphitheatre. Barney knows a great story that originated in Greece called King Midas. By the end of the day, everyone has learned that wanting too much is not a good thing, especially BJ!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029644_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715183023 +0000" stop="20250715190023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Music Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ben accidentally includes Kioko's prized music box from Switzerland in a cardboard box of yard sale items-the music box is sold! Kioko is sad and Ben wants to make things right, so he and Barney travel to Switzerland in search of a replacement gift. While there, they sample Swiss food, customs and games-but no music box! Luckily when Ben returns the music box is returned!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029645_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715190023 +0000" stop="20250715193019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Emperor's Contest - Beethoven's Hear!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a fishing contest in the park! When Ryan is tempted not to follow the rules, Barney tells The Emperor's Contest and Ryan discovers that honesty is the best policy. When Riff meets a friend who can't hear well, Riff wonders if he would still like music. Barney tells everyone about Beethoven, a famous musician who wrote beautiful music even though he couldn't hear it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029621_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715193019 +0000" stop="20250715200020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who - Sweet Treats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for Halloween tonight! Everyone knows what they're going to be for Halloween. BJ is going to be a pirate, Melanie is going to be a cat, David will be a superhero, and Baby Bop is going to be a ballerina princess. Everyone has decided on a costume all except for Riff. Barney tries to give Riff ideas on a costume like a sailor, a firefighter, or a dancer. Riff surprises everyone in the end by wearing a one-man band costume. Then, it's time for the Halloween party to begin! Barney and his friends have fun Trick-or-Treating in the park at night. But when Ramon loses all his Halloween candies, BJ shares his Halloween candies with him.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029622_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715200020 +0000" stop="20250715203025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Best in Show - The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ feels left out when the kids have a Dog Show to show off their pets. BJ doesn't have a dog and wishes he did! A friend shares her dog with BJ so he can join in the fun. Barney's friends are having a hard time deciding what to do because everyone wants to do the same thing! Barney's Native American tale, The Chase, shows them that it's best to think for themselves and not follow the crowd.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029623_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715203025 +0000" stop="20250715205836 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dream Big - Thats What A Mommy Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching birds fly overhead, Riff begins to daydream of flying. He decides to build his very own rocket ship and fly to Mars. The flight is not exactly a success, but Barney encourages Riff to never give up on his dream. After seeing many moms playing with their kids in the park, Baby Bop is curious as to what makes somebody a mommy. With Barney's help, Baby Bop learns all about what makes mommies so special.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029624_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715205836 +0000" stop="20250715213028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Shrinking Blankey - The Awful Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's blankey seems to be getting smaller; she's convinced it's shrinking. But Barney shows her that, actually, Baby Bop is growing. When Riff takes a bite of ice cream, he realizes has a very sore tooth. Afraid of going to the dentist, Barney and his friends put on a show to help Riff see there is nothing to be afraid of - the dentist is his friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029625_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715213028 +0000" stop="20250715220025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Blame Game - What's Your Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcos accidentally breaks an art show project that Melanie has made. Afraid that she will be angry, he doesn't say anything, but then feels guilty. Barney helps him see that honesty is the best policy. Meanwhile, Myra, has decided she doesn't like her name. After learning about many names and what they mean, Barney helps Myra see how special her name truly is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029626_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715220025 +0000" stop="20250715223027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Caboose - BJ the Great</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie is sad because she misses her friend, Marisa who is visiting relatives in India. Barney takes her and the other kids on a trip to the magic caboose to visit pretend countries like Egypt, Tahiti, and India. When they were in a pretend country of India, they saw a real elephant and in the end, Melanie gets a email from her friend in India (who has also seen a real elephant in India!). BJ wants to be a great magician, but he doesn't want to spend any time practicing. He convinces Baby Bop to help him do a trick, and makes her disappear. When BJ thought she is gone forever, he realizes the importance of practice. Luckily, Baby Bop hasn't disappeared after all!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029627_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715223027 +0000" stop="20250715230021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Gift of the Dinos - A Visit to Santa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends are decorating the caboose for Christmas when Barney decides to plan a Secret Santa game. Everyone has to buy or make a gift for the friend whose name they have drawn. Melanie misses the mailman, so Barney takes her to Santa's workshop at the North Pole to deliver her wish list in person.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029628_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715230021 +0000" stop="20250715233023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff's Musical Zoo - The Princess and the Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff decides to create a musical zoo when their zoo trip is postponed. Gathering instruments that sound like real animals, Riff gives Barney and his friends a zoo-mazing experience. When Baby Bop hesitates on keeping her promise to watch Ryan's pet frog, Barney tells her the story of The Frog Prince. And Baby Bop learns about keeping her promises.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029629_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250715233023 +0000" stop="20250716000027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Way to Go! - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop finds out that Daniel is going on a trip the next day, she wants to go on a trip as well. Everyone decides to pretend to travel the same way Daniel will travel. First, they all make cardboard cars out of some scrap boxes. Next, everyone pretends to be an airplane. Then Barney turns the cardboard airplanes into a great big cardboard bus. They go on a camera safari only to discover the last mode of their transportation--a big cardboard cruise ship.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029630_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250716000027 +0000" stop="20250716003025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Misbegotten Moon - A Space Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After noticing parts of the moon are missing in the night sky, Baby Bop is determined to find the rest of it. It's up to Barney and the kids to help Baby Bop take a trip to outer space where they meet Mr. Moon. Baby Bop then learns that the moon is not always full at night.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029631_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
