<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250705231430 +0000" stop="20250706003616 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250617</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706003616 +0000" stop="20250706025307 +0000">
    <title>When Girls Ride</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Samantha leaves the South to have a fresh start with her husband, she ends up meeting two biker girls named Raquel and Tammy. The three women grow close, and decide to start their own women's bike club. Things take a turn for the worse when they lose a girl from their group to violence. The women respond accordingly in order to get justice for their friend.</desc>
    <date>20230801</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c30fc4809bc9548c850bd126aa4a616c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706025307 +0000" stop="20250706043339 +0000">
    <title>The Opps</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ain't no rules to this street game! Realizing the "Opps" are sometimes closer to you than you thought: who do you trust? Your devious wife, or childhood friends?</desc>
    <date>20210210</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a49bb8c5dc5bb04002f1639c28721ecd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706043339 +0000" stop="20250706055433 +0000">
    <title>The Queens Court</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Queens Court is an underground, all female organization that rules on all criminal activity in the city. Nothing is done without the queens courts verdict first, and those who fail to comply will be dealt with, by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>20230206</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f7076773a81beb3bc88f0d0f5527a3e1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706055433 +0000" stop="20250706075600 +0000">
    <title>The Struggle</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A story about Debra and her daughter, Tracey struggling in the heart of Memphis. Debra tries to keep her daughter out of danger and off the streets but it doesn't help with the surrounding of drug dealers, pimps and prostitution. It gets worst when Erin and her gang interfere in situations with Tracey and Kandi. That's when Tracey takes matters in her own hands.</desc>
    <date>20190813</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a7rBgBIMDdDdoxPjLFAPS4sM4Wf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706075600 +0000" stop="20250706094233 +0000">
    <title>The Ring Widow</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crystal and Sean find out that they are renting out one of their airbnb properties to a possible serial killer targeting married men that cheat on their wives.</desc>
    <date>20231017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/maverick/the_ring_widow.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706094233 +0000" stop="20250706113405 +0000">
    <title>Three Secrets</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Struck with the grief after losing her child, Naomi is stuck in a depression while her husband begins to stray from their marriage. Hoping to bring life back into their boring marriage, he invites her to go out with him and they meet a mysterious woman who joins them for the evening. As events unfold She finds herself in an unexpected entanglement built on lies.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x6SBFzYpcg7JTvJoGe11E2TaGjr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706113405 +0000" stop="20250706135051 +0000">
    <title>Tainted Waters</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An unknowingly selfish mechanic, unable to financially save his failing business, agrees to take part in a four man robbery. Now hiding out from the cops, he has to make it through the night in a room of people where he's not the most selfish.</desc>
    <date>20231201</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b8efad14b5c7173e92a6264381596cfe.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706135051 +0000" stop="20250706162247 +0000">
    <title>Droppin Bodies</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Julia, a mother haunted by a violent past, flees her old life to protect her daughter, Kelsey. But when Kelsey is tragically murdered by her boyfriend, Julia is left shattered and betrayed. Abandoned by a justice system that fails to bring her daughter's killer to account, she's forced to confront the darkness she once escaped.</desc>
    <date>20250513</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5c157530e0808ca23be96bc59e365e6d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706162247 +0000" stop="20250706182055 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymoon</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>On her birthday, Summer is publicly humiliated when her fiancé, Chance, and her best friend, Portia, reveal their affair. Seeking revenge, she sabotages their honeymoon with the help of her friend Danisha. A deadly game of cat-and-mouse ensues, with betrayal, violence, and unexpected twists. Ultimately, Summer must confront the consequences of her actions as she fights for her life and seeks justice.</desc>
    <date>20250101</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tH0eIpecCqMHs7YgSzPElEYOZGz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706182055 +0000" stop="20250706200042 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706200042 +0000" stop="20250706212427 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWVkNzQ1MjAtYmNjZS00NDc0LTg0YzktNzVlNGViODYyMmUxXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706212427 +0000" stop="20250706225945 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706225945 +0000" stop="20250707002705 +0000">
    <title>She's Watching</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Richard and Zoey have recently moved into their dream home, only to find themselves being watched by an obsessed neighbor. Watching them every night isn't enough to satisfy her urges, so she makes an offer they can't refuse.</desc>
    <date>20250429</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
