<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250720234204 +0000" stop="20250721012504 +0000">
    <title>The Gatling Gun</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An Apache warrior chief is willing to offer gold, and even sacrifice some of his men, to get his hands on Richard J. Gatling's powerful invention. It's up to a cavalry lieutenant, his scout, and a tough rancher to end the chief's deadly ambition.</desc>
    <date>19710501</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/cbb554397eabe089ee91fe053ef406e1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721012504 +0000" stop="20250721031038 +0000">
    <title>The Deadly Companions</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a former Army officer accidentally kills a woman's young son, he offers to escort the grieving mother through dangerous Indian territory on the way to lay the boy to rest at the family homestead.</desc>
    <date>19610606</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jKViOlqMMdL7H51UgLuNyIMCtKh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721031038 +0000" stop="20250721040000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Rider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Swindled by a charming woman, Cheyenne soon tracks her down as she drives her herd of cattle to Kansas. He joins the drive and finds out that one of the wranglers is a murderer.</desc>
    <date>20250129</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721040000 +0000" stop="20250721060000 +0000">
    <title>Christmas in the Wilds</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When bush pilot Buck Johnson's plane is grounded after an avalanche rescue mission deep in the Rocky Mountains. Jessica and Buck decide they must each make the dangerous trek through the wilderness to be together for their first Christmas.</desc>
    <date>20211102</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5554800e319eae952a1078994e4fdf85.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721060000 +0000" stop="20250721070000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Just Like Old Times</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>On the anniversary of his brother's death, The Kid leaves the station to spend some time alone. Lou tracks him down to check on him. Later, the Kid's childhood girlfriend arrives in town, bringing back even more memories for him to deal with.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721070000 +0000" stop="20250721072940 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A charming man named Mario Rosati arrives at the McCain Ranch and introduces himself as an acquaintance of an old family friend. Lucas and Mark offer him a place to stay for a few days, but they learn that he has an ulterior motive: to kill Lucas.</desc>
    <date>19630311</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72519.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721072940 +0000" stop="20250721080000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Man Running</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man named Sam Gibbs comes to North Fork in need of Marshal Micah Torrance's protection from criminals who are after him. Sam happens to be Mark's grandfather and Lucas' deceased wife's father. Lucas finds peace with his past and helps Sam.</desc>
    <date>19630318</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72520.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721080000 +0000" stop="20250721082945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Bone War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It's not gold that inspires a rush of treasure hunters to flood the windblown bluffs of Wyoming: it's bones. After stumbling upon a strange fossil, a man is caught in the crossfire of rival paleontologists warring over a trove of dinosaur bones.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6477c2cba2fc3fadb4ca7cee/8563d1dc-38d0-446f-a5f7-1b1eb7f3a08fthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721082945 +0000" stop="20250721090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Rush Lawman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When failed prospector John Hicks Adams is elected sheriff of Santa Clara County, he must prove that he won't be a bust as a lawman too. Just weeks into the job, his courage is tested when a band of stagecoach robbers begins terrorizing the area.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6477c387a2fc3fadb4f3f79d/3979085d-584c-4c8a-bc4b-3ec6c0ef48f3thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721090000 +0000" stop="20250721100000 +0000">
    <title>Buffalo Keepers</title>
    <sub-title>Buffalo Keepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Today, the buffalo is the quintessential symbol of strength, freedom, and the unspoiled American West. But in the late 1800s, the nation's buffalo were nearly wiped out by ruthless hide hunters. Those majestic herds, which once numbered in the tens of millions, were down to less than 500 animals. This is the story of the handful of determined men and women who mobilized to save the ones that were left in a last-ditch effort to stave off extinction. Ranchers like Charles and Mary Ann Goodnight rescued orphaned buffalo calves and built small herds. Former buffalo hunters like Buffalo Bill helped build public sympathy. And politicians like Theodore Roosevelt helped pass laws to protect the remaining animals. The effort would be a generational one, with buffalo herds carefully tended, bred, and passed down to new stewards when their old protectors passed away. Thanks to their efforts, there are an estimated 500,000 buffalo thundering across America's grasslands once again.</desc>
    <date>20240711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/22-fast-1838_fcw_ottera_deliverables_june_buf-horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721100000 +0000" stop="20250721120000 +0000">
    <title>Christmas in the Smokies</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Clinging to the only life she's ever known, a headstrong woman (along with her loving parents) finds herself on the verge of losing her family's berry farm in the heart of the Smoky Mountains, to an impending retail expansion.  Over one eventful holiday season, she tries every avenue possible to save the farm. But, when the local town leaders notify her that they will have to seize the property after the holidays, her last hope to unite the town, is to throw a Christmas concert on the farm, headlined by her former love, a ne'er-do-well country music superstar.  As the day of the concert approaches, they all must learn the value of family, faith and community - before time runs out.</desc>
    <date>20151016</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/4c3713a4d1a23aebafdca43edb8de18a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721120000 +0000" stop="20250721140000 +0000">
    <title>The Gatling Gun</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An Apache warrior chief is willing to offer gold, and even sacrifice some of his men, to get his hands on Richard J. Gatling's powerful invention. It's up to a cavalry lieutenant, his scout, and a tough rancher to end the chief's deadly ambition.</desc>
    <date>19710501</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/cbb554397eabe089ee91fe053ef406e1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721140000 +0000" stop="20250721160000 +0000">
    <title>The Deadly Companions</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a former Army officer accidentally kills a woman's young son, he offers to escort the grieving mother through dangerous Indian territory on the way to lay the boy to rest at the family homestead.</desc>
    <date>19610606</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jKViOlqMMdL7H51UgLuNyIMCtKh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721160000 +0000" stop="20250721170000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>These guys can wrangle any bull, but can they tame a wild bulldozer? In this episode of The Cowboy Way, the guys decide to build a new barn for a local rancher but it's man versus machine when Bubba's dozer breaks a pipeline, releasing a torrent of water. Jaclyn admits to her boss she's been looking for a job closer to home, then worries it might get her fired altogether. Will her family have to survive on one income? Cody decides to write a book about the cowboy way of life, but he may have bitten off more than he can chew.   The cowboys struggle to get the barn raised in time to process the first shipment of the herd and might have to call in some favors to do it.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721170000 +0000" stop="20250721180000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <sub-title>Keep on Chuckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It's The Cowboy Way's first road trip ever! Bubba, Cody and Booger cut loose and head north to enter a big chuck wagon race. But they quickly discover this race is not for amateurs.  Loose wagon wheels, knee-deep mud and professional-grade competition raise both the stakes, and their concerns. Will the guys risk life and limb to race and win? And while the cowboys are away, a surprise shipment of cattle comes in days early and their wives must jump into action.  But this drop off is anything but routine when Kaley and Misty discover one heifer has an infection that could threaten the entire herd.</desc>
    <date>20180915</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f3168ccf4b7f860539ca77fa4f9fd0ef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721180000 +0000" stop="20250721183014 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old friends of Lucas', Don Chumera De Lardo and Colonel Black, come to the McCain Ranch. They are there to finish a deed of honor, even insisting on a jousting match. Lucas learns that the feud started over a chess game.</desc>
    <date>19611113</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72471.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721183014 +0000" stop="20250721190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Honest Abe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor of Lucas' believes he is Abe Lincoln after being mentally injured in the Civil War. Townspeople go along with his impersonation since he is a kind man. However, when a saloon patron makes fun of him, trouble ensues.</desc>
    <date>19611120</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72472.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721190000 +0000" stop="20250721210000 +0000">
    <title>County Line: No Fear</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Sheriff Alden Rockwell finally decides to retire, a threat against the father of his friend, Sheriff Jo Porter, may not only ruin his plans for a life of leisure but also bring a dangerous criminal syndicate to both Maksville and York counties.</desc>
    <date>20221206</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/7ef7b2ecfdcc4de025d343cb3bc2c492.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721210000 +0000" stop="20250721233457 +0000">
    <title>McLintock!</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A cattle baron awaits the return of his daughter from school and is surprised that his wife has returned to take their daughter away. He tries to keep the peace and do what is best for everyone.</desc>
    <date>19631113</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rSKUkB28YPbfTh4zt42fdsMbRwR.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250721233457 +0000" stop="20250722000237 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>A Shard of Glass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Haunted by the memory of leaving a man to die, mountain man Jim Bridger is determined not to repeat the mistake. When his trapping party runs out of water while crossing a barren desert, Bridger struggles desperately to keep his companions alive.</desc>
    <date>20240314</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/66e868d10340f39f5e75b08d/08b06d1e-f226-4536-886c-0911f15b73de/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722000237 +0000" stop="20250722003313 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple move to North Fork and settle down under a false name to keep the town from knowing they are parents of a vicious killer on the loose. However, their plan fails when their son shows up and causes chaos.</desc>
    <date>19600216</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72415.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722003313 +0000" stop="20250722010147 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage girl named Heller and her brother are abused by her drunken stepfather. The town becomes aware after Heller is caught stealing from the general store. The children plan the drunk's demise as the cruelty continues. Lucas steps in to help.</desc>
    <date>19600223</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72416.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722010147 +0000" stop="20250722013237 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas and Mark go on a train trip, clouds of swarming grasshoppers force the train to stop. A prisoner takes advantage of the emergency and breaks free, then kills Marshal Dixon. Lucas, with the help of a buffalo hunter, outwits the outlaw.</desc>
    <date>19600301</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72417.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
