<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719000629 +0000" stop="20250719003809 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcial receives an anonymous tip about Pascal's high-profile protectors. This does not stop him from digging deep into the identity of Diana Guerrero, Tiago's mysterious daughter. Hoping to find any lead on her, Marcial gives Jessie a special mission.</desc>
    <date>20190320</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s2_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719003809 +0000" stop="20250719011115 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian makes a baffling discovery upon finding Santi Jr.'s grave. This prompts her to squeeze the truth out of Tiago and Amelia regarding her real identity. Their confrontation leads to a painful revelation. Meanwhile, Marcial learns from Corazon that Tiago threatened to hurt Jessie.</desc>
    <date>20190321</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s2_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719011115 +0000" stop="20250719014555 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>35 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Romina lashes out at Alvin after the authorities arrest him. Cassie soon learns of her true relation to Alvin. Filled with anger and disappointment, Cassie asks to talk to her mother's defiler. Meanwhile, Daniela meets up with Hector in hopes of finding a way out of Alvin's mess. Unknown to her, Kulas is starting to get suspicious.</desc>
    <date>20190215</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_35_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719014555 +0000" stop="20250719022031 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Mondragons decide to push through with their plan to move abroad. Later, Romina and Robert learn that the authorities will soon release the result of Alvin’s DNA test. Little do they know, Daniela and Hector are pulling some strings to shift the odds in their favor. Roxy, on the other hand, tries to convince Cassie to help Alvin regain his freedom.</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719022031 +0000" stop="20250719025422 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jenna pounces on Tristan's misfortunes. Chesca's safety is put in danger after agreeing to meet with Zach.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719025422 +0000" stop="20250719032849 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Chesca's abductors contact Tristan. Waldo is one step closer to achieving his dreams.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719032849 +0000" stop="20250719051637 +0000">
    <title>Mang Jose</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>With the super power of energy absorption and redirection, Mang Jose is a superhero for hire. One day, Tope hires Mang Jose to save his mother who has been abducted by mysterious troopers of King Ina, an enigmatic cunning villain who is out to annihilate all remaining superheroes in hiding.</desc>
    <date>20211117</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/mangjose_1200x1600.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719051637 +0000" stop="20250719054536 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lydia and Gabriel visit the Agbayanis for information about Rigor, but Maila is unable to help. Gabriel and Bianca grow closer, and an incident with Joey prompts the Agbayanis to relocate. Carlos finds his goals but faces discouragement from Roman.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s1_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719054536 +0000" stop="20250719061352 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Bianca and Gabriel promise to stay in touch, but circumstances get in the way. The Agbayanis relocate to Manila, while the Villorias settle into a new home. Soon, Bianca finishes her studies and is accepted into the Philippine National Team.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s1_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719061352 +0000" stop="20250719070000 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Somewhere along the West Philippine Sea, a foreign vessel captures a group of fishermen and accuses them of smuggling drugs. 2nd Lt. Rhian Bonifacio gets shot after sneaking in the vessel to rescue the fishermen.</desc>
    <date>20190121</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719070000 +0000" stop="20250719073530 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiago bends the truth in his confession, betraying his allies in the process. Franco, on the other hand, works nonstop to strengthen their alliance's forces. At the same time, Vera and Bartolome decide that the alliance is in need of a new leader. Meanwhile, Gen. Maximillano orders his subordinates to verify Tiago's testimony. He also makes a surprising offer to Marcial.</desc>
    <date>20190626</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_96qfiibt/version/0/vid_sec/550/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719073530 +0000" stop="20250719080937 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiago's allies are in for a shock when the military raids their hideout. After the smoke cleared, Ethan discovers some vital documents that may have a connection to his late father's last case. Meanwhile, Tiago's hearing begins. Hoping to finally make him pay for his crimes, Rhian takes the witness stand and recounts the full extent of his activities. However, Tiago is unwilling to go down without a fight.</desc>
    <date>20190627</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_92rbhvd8/version/0/vid_sec/522/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719080937 +0000" stop="20250719084428 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After realizing that he was betrayed, Franco decides to take matters into his own hands and seeks revenge against Tiago. Tiago asks for Amelia's help in reaching out to him and Armando. Marcial urges Jessie to find Edgar's files that can prove Tiago's involvement in the training of child soldiers for his terrorist group. Jessie has other plans for the important documents. Rhian advises Ethan and Jessie to acquire Franco's help in fortifying their claim against their enemy.</desc>
    <date>20190628</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_f9zo6bs4/version/0/vid_sec/537/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719084428 +0000" stop="20250719091945 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Armed with anger and a thirst for vengeance, Franco storms to the hospital to finally wipe out Tiago. Ethan protects the erring general as part of his duty and delivers Rhian's message to her former colleague. Amelia, on the other hand, is confident that the incident will help Tiago gain back the public's sympathy. Meanwhile, Jessie tries her best efforts to conceal an important evidence from Corazon. Inside the prison, Rhian gets into a fight with a group of inmates siding with Tiago.</desc>
    <date>20190701</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_mpwwtlhf/version/0/vid_sec/546/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719091945 +0000" stop="20250719095509 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian tries to persuade Franco to testify against Tiago after his failed attempt to assassinate the former general. Tiago, on the other hand, asks his defense lawyer  to keep an eye on his new enemy. Pushed by the recent events that endangered his father's life, Santi expresses his willingness to train and become one of Tiago's army despite Amelia's disapproval. Meanwhile, Jessie and Adalina interview a former child trainee under Tiago's terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>20190702</date>
    <icon src="https://cdnapisec.kaltura.com/p/513551/sp/51355100/thumbnail/entry_id/1_ya9hf58a/version/0/vid_sec/548/width/3840/height/2160/type/3/a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719095509 +0000" stop="20250719103042 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Corazon confronts Jessie about her knowledge on Edgar's) classified files. Bothered by what she discovered about Ivan, Claire asks him about his ties with Franco and his terrorist group. Meanwhile, Rhian begins to worry about Franco after he failed to answer her lawyer's calls. Unfazed by the prosecution's presentation of evidence, Tiago plays his trump card. Elsewhere, Gen. Maximillano takes the witness stand at Marcial's military tribunal.</desc>
    <date>20190703</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719103042 +0000" stop="20250719110607 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhian struggles to provide the court with sufficient evidence to prove her claims against the defendant. Tiago, on the other hand, accuses her and Marcial of smearing his reputation. Soon after, the court hands down its verdict on Tiago's cases. While the former general is triumphant over his victory, Marcial hatches a new plan to continue his fight for justice. Meanwhile, Corazon try to patch things up with Jessie.</desc>
    <date>20190704</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719110607 +0000" stop="20250719114150 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiago and Amelia launch consecutive attacks against their archnemeses. First, they hire a prisoner to eliminate Rhian. Their henchmen then try to stage Franco's resistance to finally get rid of him. Meanwhile, Marcial arrives at an important decision as he struggles to help Rhian while he is inside the military camp. Unknown to Marcial, another danger lies ahead of him.</desc>
    <date>20190705</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719114150 +0000" stop="20250719121631 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping Tiago's henchmen, Marcial and Rhian try to survive in the wilderness. The general finds a way later on to contact his wife while tending to his wounded daughter. Corazon, on the other hand, struggles to cope with her family's disappearance. Meanwhile, Greg delegates some tasks to his subordinates about the ongoing search and rescue operations on the high-ranking general and the wanted spy. Elsewhere, Tiago meets with his new campaign manager to strategize for his senatorial bid.</desc>
    <date>20190711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719121631 +0000" stop="20250719125044 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After helping Rhian and Marcial, Corazon makes it a point not to let Jessie know about what happened. Gen. Maximillano receives an update on the search and rescue operations for the former military members. Rhian and Marcial strategize on how they can take down Tiago. As they carry out their plan, the father and daughter are forced to seek protection against the authorities from a group of civilians. Tiago strives hard to secure a seat in the Senate.</desc>
    <date>20190712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s6_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719125044 +0000" stop="20250719133934 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassandra forms an unlikely friendship with Val and Agnes when they find out they’re being cheated on by the same man. Then, Cassandra is deceived again by a man who leaves her pregnant with Iris. Iris grows up helping her mother until Cassandra meets and marries Oliver, whom she explains to Iris as the man guaranteed by certain signs. Years later, Iris experiences these signs with her best friend, Ali.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719133934 +0000" stop="20250719141236 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ali quits the Philippine Military Academy, disobeying his father's wishes. Cast out from his home, Ali turns to Iris for help. Ali and Iris's friendship develops into something more as Iris helps Ali pursue his dreams.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719141236 +0000" stop="20250719144611 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Coming up with a plan for their future, Ali and Iris head to Greece for their internship. Meanwhile, Cassandra and Agnes are horrified to hear Iris mention a familiar name from their past.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719144611 +0000" stop="20250719151640 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>04 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Iris and Ali receive a warm welcome from Basti in Greece. However, Basti and Ali's close friendship rubs Iris the wrong way. Meanwhile, Val hesitates to tell Cassandra and Agnes that she is marrying the person they have loathed for years.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_04_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719151640 +0000" stop="20250719154620 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>05 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Thinking that Basti is a bad influence on Ali, Iris urges her best friend to stay away from him. Meanwhile, Cassandra and Agnes notice that Valerie is being distant with them.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_05_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719154620 +0000" stop="20250719161953 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>06 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A small misunderstanding with Ali causes Iris to fall into a sulk. Ali then tries to make it up to her by spending time with Iris on a bike tour around the city. Meanwhile, seeing Basti and Ali's unusual closeness, Iris becomes suspicious of Basti's sexual orientation.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_06_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719161953 +0000" stop="20250719164935 +0000">
    <title>Till I Met You</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Iris continues to consider the possibility that Basti is gay. When the rumor spreads and reaches him, a fed-up Ali confronts Iris and breaks up with her. Later, Basti is stunned to hear his own heartbeat while comforting Iris.</desc>
    <date>20160829</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/till_i_met_you_s1_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719164935 +0000" stop="20250719190000 +0000">
    <title>Mia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mia Salazar, a self-destructive, alcoholic doctor who joined the Doctor to the Barrios program to heal from the tragedy of her fiance's death meets the cheerful and nerdy forester Jay Policarpio. Together, the two will embark on a new journey.</desc>
    <date>20200115</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/mia_1200x1600.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719190000 +0000" stop="20250719193328 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving a visit from Neil, Romina gets the shock of her life upon learning what Daniela did to Cassie. Daniela, on the other hand, continues to indulge in the wealth Robert left and endows Carlos with a luxurious gift. Meanwhile, Cassie grows sick of Marga’s provocations and pledges to fight back.</desc>
    <date>20190314</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_19_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719193328 +0000" stop="20250719200729 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Witnessing Romina's violent fit, Cindy decides to take advantage of the situation and makes a proposal to Daniela. In exchange for money, she will make Romina's time in jail a living hell. However, the widow shows no signs of backing down. Meanwhile, guests arrive at the Mondragon mansion for the grand pool party where Marga seizes the opportunity to embarrass Cassie.</desc>
    <date>20190315</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719200729 +0000" stop="20250719204056 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Tension erupts during Marga’s pool party when she accuses Cassie of flirting with Kristoff. Fed up with Marga’s immaturity, Esther inadvertently lays hands on Marga to protect Cassie. After witnessing this, Daniela arrives at a heartbreaking decision. Meanwhile, Cindy punishes Romina for embarrassing her in front of their fellow detainees.</desc>
    <date>20190318</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719204056 +0000" stop="20250719211407 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassie decides to leave the mansion in order to avoid further conflicts. However, she grows suspicious of Daniela after overhearing her conversation with Hector. Cassie then files a protection order against her step-sister, catching the Bartolomes off guard. Meanwhile, Romina enlists Bernard's help to protect Cassie. Atty. Sanchez, on the other hand, succumbs to Hector's threats.</desc>
    <date>20190319</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719211407 +0000" stop="20250719214737 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Unsettled by Atty. Sanchez's sudden change, Romina asks Neil to keep a close watch on the lawyer. Afraid to do the task alone, Neil enlists Gino's help and they discover something suspicious about the attorney. Meanwhile, Cassie tries to fish information from Alvin regarding her mother's case. Marga, on the other hand, comes up with another plan to get back at Cassie.</desc>
    <date>20190320</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719214737 +0000" stop="20250719222135 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>24 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Romina's resolve to fight back against Cindy and her underlings intensifies. While gaining more courage to protect herself, she begins to speculate that Cindy is conniving with Daniela. Meanwhile, Cassie finally decides to claim her part of the mansion creating another dispute amongst the Mondragons. Marga, on the other hand, revels at the updated rankings on Maxwell's leaderboard.</desc>
    <date>20190321</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_24_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719222135 +0000" stop="20250719225456 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>25 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on taking over Camila, Daniela follows Ms. Galvez's advice and gives her all in attracting more business for the company. However, a mishap occurs, putting her plans and her reputation in jeopardy. This propels Daniela to take her anger out on the innocent employees. Little does she know, Bonita and Neil are already gathering support to fight against her unreasonable leadership.</desc>
    <date>20190322</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_25_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719225456 +0000" stop="20250719232829 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>26 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>With enough persuasion from Bernard, the court lets Romina file a petition for bail. Daniela, on the other hand, refuses to accept the jury's decision and presses Atty. Cabrera to make sure Romina stays behind bars. Elsewhere, Carlos fails to contain his anger after much provocation from Hector. Meanwhile, Marga grows even more determined to reclaim everything Cassie took from her.</desc>
    <date>20190325</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_26_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719232829 +0000" stop="20250720000207 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>27 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After giving up her allowance to Marga, Cassie struggles to afford the materials she needs for a school project. Refusing to give up, she finds a way to earn her own money, but Marga pulls another stunt to thwart Cassie's plan. Meanwhile, Daniela orders Cindy to do something to prevent Romina from getting permission to bail. Elsewhere, Kulas gives Hector a piece of his mind for stepping on Carlos’ dignity.</desc>
    <date>20190326</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_27_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720000207 +0000" stop="20250720003611 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to clear his name from the allegations, Jacob enlists Atty. Balmaceda's help to track down his secret enemy. Perturbed by her husband's latest move, Jean relays this new information to Sonya. Unbeknownst to them, their hidden allegiance is on the verge of being discovered. Meanwhile, Anna finds herself in a life-threatening situation and Paco races against time to save her.</desc>
    <date>20180316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
