<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39">
    <display-name>Get.Factual</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d8ac3d3f-88be-4d2a-89f3-608f02e15728/GetFactual_Dark_Mode_Logordx.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705000000 +0000" stop="20250705010213 +0000">
    <title>Stalin's Daughter</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It is a sensation in the midst of the Cold War. Stalin's daughter Svetlana Alliluyeva flees to the West. During her childhood in the center of power, she was Joseph Stalin's favorite child. But death and violence overshadow her life. Her mother and brother die, relatives are killed, Stalin has her lover abducted.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/stalinsdaughter_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705010213 +0000" stop="20250705020358 +0000">
    <title>Operation Peter Pan - The Secret War against Cuba</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In 2016, a historic moment arrived when Barack Obama spoke in Cuba to the inhabitants of the island nation and promised a future together. For the first time in more than 50 years, an American president had entered the communist country and turned towards an erstwhile enemy. However, the US economic embargo against Cuba continues. It sanctions the socialist state – although the UN General Assembly recently again called it a violation of international law. Many Cubans are therefore sceptical about a new political future, despite the friendly words of the American President. Their distrust is deep. It is based on over fifty years of history and the policies of the United States towards their country. For years, the Cuban government has raised serious allegations against their big neighbour. The film "Operation Peter Pan" tracks these allegations.</desc>
    <date>20230529</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705020358 +0000" stop="20250705030207 +0000">
    <title>In Search of Santa Claus</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The amazing transformation of a holy man from Turkey into the world-wide symbol of Christmas cheer. He's one of the most widely recognized figures in the world; but what are the origins of St. Nicholas, and how did he become Santa Claus? With criminological acumen, this one-hour documentary sorts the myths from the facts to present the true story of the first multi-national saint, revered by the Catholic, Protestant and Orthodox churches alike.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/insearchofsantaclaus_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705030207 +0000" stop="20250705040000 +0000">
    <title>The Greater Caucasus</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The mountains of the Caucasus form a magical border between Europe and Asia. Film-maker Henry M. Mix and his crew spent over a year in Russia's highest mountains. The result is an impressive documentary about the natural wonders to be found between the Black and Caspian Seas. The wild mountain landscape with its extreme climate has created a unique world of flora and fauna and makes the Caucasus one of the world's 25 most significant centres of biodiversity. Mountain bison, Caucasus Snowcock and tur are only found here. In the rain shadow of the snow-covered main ridge live Saiga antelopes, long-eared hedgehogs and short-toed snake eagles. Epic footage, breath-taking aerial photography and hitherto unseen behaviour of rare animals - Greater Caucasus has its viewers spellbound from the first minute on.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/thegreatercaucasus_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705040000 +0000" stop="20250705050015 +0000">
    <title>The Kaiser's Pirates</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In November 1916, German raider SMS Wolf set out for a 15-month long voyage through the oceans finally reaching Australia and Papua New Guinea. The mission of this ship which was perfectly masked as a merchant vessel: capture, sink or destroy allied shipping.</desc>
    <date>20230316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_kaisers_pirates_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705050015 +0000" stop="20250705060031 +0000">
    <title>Gold for Kim - A Life for North Korea's Leader</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>North Korea is a country of stark contrasts. On the one hand, it presents real socialist stereotypes like cryptic messages from a frozen time loop, combined with shocking reports on shortages. On the other hand, polished Pyongyang lures with a futuristic skyline, flashy amusement parks and department stores with a range of goods equal to those in western consumer meccas.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/goldforkimalifefornorthkoreasleader_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705060031 +0000" stop="20250705070028 +0000">
    <title>The Secret of the Phaistos Code</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Is the Phaistos Disc a clever fake? The film follows the trail of possibly one of the greatest archaeological scandals ever. The search for the truth starts in the ancient Cretan palace complexes of Phaistos. The North American art dealer Jerome Eisenberg, one of the world’s foremost forgery experts, considers the “Phaistos Disc” to be a latter-day fake. In 1908, it was discovered by the Italian archaeologist Luigi Pernier. Since then, the disc has aroused the scientific ambition of countless linguists. The British academic Gareth Owens has analyzed new archaeological discoveries with unfamiliar characters and believes the disc to be genuine. But Eisenberg remains convinced that the disc cannot be deciphered at all. He claims that not only does it not reveal a text that has ever been decipherable, but also that is not even of ancient origin.</desc>
    <date>20230529</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705070028 +0000" stop="20250705075701 +0000">
    <title>The Lesser Caucasus - Between Ararat and the Caspian Sea</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The mountain worlds of the Greater and Lesser Caucasus mark the border between Europe and Asia. After their documentary about the Greater Caucasus, Henry J. Mix and his team have now prepared a second film about the impressive mountain world of this region. The species and landscape diversity of the lesser Caucasus are portrayed in Armenia, Georgia and Azerbaijan. Shielded from the more than 4000-metre-tall main ridge of the Greater Caucasus, a thermophilic flora and fauna was able to develop in the Lesser Caucasus. For the first time, the astonishing variety of the land bridge between Europe and Persia is portrayed comprehensively. From the mountains of Dagestan, down to the canyons of the Caspian Basin, through the steppes of Azerbaijan and up into the Armenian highlands, all before the majestic backdrop of biblical Mount Ararat.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/cf4636f3a80a4929660a75143c06ff2725f766e12ed0804bc6a4074d040637ff.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705075701 +0000" stop="20250705085716 +0000">
    <title>The Kaiser's Pirates</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In November 1916, German raider SMS Wolf set out for a 15-month long voyage through the oceans finally reaching Australia and Papua New Guinea. The mission of this ship which was perfectly masked as a merchant vessel: capture, sink or destroy allied shipping.</desc>
    <date>20230316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_kaisers_pirates_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705085716 +0000" stop="20250705095932 +0000">
    <title>Gold for Kim - A Life for North Korea's Leader</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>North Korea is a country of stark contrasts. On the one hand, it presents real socialist stereotypes like cryptic messages from a frozen time loop, combined with shocking reports on shortages. On the other hand, polished Pyongyang lures with a futuristic skyline, flashy amusement parks and department stores with a range of goods equal to those in western consumer meccas.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/goldforkimalifefornorthkoreasleader_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705095932 +0000" stop="20250705110129 +0000">
    <title>The Secret of the Phaistos Code</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Is the Phaistos Disc a clever fake? The film follows the trail of possibly one of the greatest archaeological scandals ever. The search for the truth starts in the ancient Cretan palace complexes of Phaistos. The North American art dealer Jerome Eisenberg, one of the world’s foremost forgery experts, considers the “Phaistos Disc” to be a latter-day fake. In 1908, it was discovered by the Italian archaeologist Luigi Pernier. Since then, the disc has aroused the scientific ambition of countless linguists. The British academic Gareth Owens has analyzed new archaeological discoveries with unfamiliar characters and believes the disc to be genuine. But Eisenberg remains convinced that the disc cannot be deciphered at all. He claims that not only does it not reveal a text that has ever been decipherable, but also that is not even of ancient origin.</desc>
    <date>20230529</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705110129 +0000" stop="20250705120000 +0000">
    <title>The Lesser Caucasus - Between Ararat and the Caspian Sea</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The mountain worlds of the Greater and Lesser Caucasus mark the border between Europe and Asia. After their documentary about the Greater Caucasus, Henry J. Mix and his team have now prepared a second film about the impressive mountain world of this region. The species and landscape diversity of the lesser Caucasus are portrayed in Armenia, Georgia and Azerbaijan. Shielded from the more than 4000-metre-tall main ridge of the Greater Caucasus, a thermophilic flora and fauna was able to develop in the Lesser Caucasus. For the first time, the astonishing variety of the land bridge between Europe and Persia is portrayed comprehensively. From the mountains of Dagestan, down to the canyons of the Caspian Basin, through the steppes of Azerbaijan and up into the Armenian highlands, all before the majestic backdrop of biblical Mount Ararat.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/cf4636f3a80a4929660a75143c06ff2725f766e12ed0804bc6a4074d040637ff.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705120000 +0000" stop="20250705130217 +0000">
    <title>Adventure Ocean Quest - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>Shark Paradise of Polynesia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>French Polynesia’s great hammerhead sharks are extraordinarily shy animals and still pose many questions, not least where they go during their annual migration. Freediver Frederic Buyle and cameraman Christian Petron team up with scientist Dr. Johan Mourir to investigate these bizarre predators.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/adventureoceanquest_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705130217 +0000" stop="20250705140430 +0000">
    <title>Adventure Ocean Quest - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>The Giants of Rurutu</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Humpback whales have come back from the brink of extinction, but they are still difficult to approach in the water and their behaviour and vocalisations pose many unsolved questions. Dr. Michael Poole wants to find out if the whales respond differently to a silent freediver compared to conventional divers, and has asked Frederic to dive with the whales and observe them.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/adventureoceanquest_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705140430 +0000" stop="20250705150844 +0000">
    <title>Font of Life</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Starting at Imbak Falls, wildlife photographer Cede Prudente together with boatman Rizal start their journey down Borneo’s longest river ­ the Kinabatangan. Cede is on a mission to photograph the varied wildlife along this river from source to sea. In this episode, we meet some modern day Dusun people, an ethnic group once notorious as headhunters.</desc>
    <date>20230529</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705150844 +0000" stop="20250705160916 +0000">
    <title>How the Greeks Changed the World</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Ascent of Civilization is a gripping landmark series with a twist – a fresh look at three ancient trailblazer cultures that have shaped all of our lives. Democracy, science, theatre, plumbing, modern roads, laws, the Olympics, conquering the seas, the discovery of America, and the onset of globalisation … you’d be hard-pushed to find a more eclectic list of achievements. They’re all at the heart of modern society, but their origins were passed down to us through the ages. It’s an inheritance that leads us back to the world of the Ancients – the world of the Greeks, the Romans and the Vikings.</desc>
    <date>20230525</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705160916 +0000" stop="20250705170734 +0000">
    <title>The First Victim</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Hitler’s Poland Campaign unleashed a “Blitzkrieg” lasting six weeks only. However, it was a war of unprecedented brutality resulting in a tremendous suffering of the Polish people in the long run. Jews were herded into Ghettos; other residents were imprisoned in camps for forced labor or displaced to make way for German settlers. Hundreds and thousands of them became victims of the Nazi murder machine. In part 2, “World War II” sheds light on some of their lives telling almost forgotten stories.</desc>
    <date>20230525</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/94b95009-759a-441e-884e-190db1f2b4c8/GetFactual_Vertical_Default_Artrdx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705170734 +0000" stop="20250705180950 +0000">
    <title>The Silicon Valley Revolution - How a few nerds did change the world</title>
    <sub-title>From the first Computer Trade Fair to the WWW</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The dream of personal computers slowly turns into Big Business. The dream of a few leftist visionaries took over the world in the 1980s: the now legendary Macintosh goes on sale, Bill Gates creates the foundation for his economic imperium, the world wide web connects billions of people all over the world, Google is founded.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/thesiliconvalleyrevolutionhowafewnerdsdidchangetheworld_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705180950 +0000" stop="20250705191203 +0000">
    <title>The Human Limits - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>Masters of the Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In this part, six talents prove their extraordinary abilities and show how they control their mind. There’s Lukas Irmler who’s slacklining in dizzying heights above the abyss, Shaolin monk Shi Yan Yao who has spent his whole life practicing meditation and can bend a steel bar with his neck and mathematical super brains Gert Mittring and Rüdiger Gramm who can solve nearly every arithmetic problem without a pocket calculator.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/thehumanlimits2_s02_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705191203 +0000" stop="20250705200357 +0000">
    <title>Alexander The Great - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>The Path to Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Part one of this stunning documentary focuses on Alexander the Great’s childhood and youth. Born in Macedonia in 356 BC as a member of the Argead dynasty, he succeeded his father Philip II to the throne at the age of twenty. But the kingdom Alexander inherited was volatile.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/alexanderthegreat_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705200357 +0000" stop="20250705205548 +0000">
    <title>Alexander The Great - Season 1</title>
    <sub-title>Until the End of the World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After the assassination of his father, the young king of Macedonia set out to conquer a massive empire. Against overwhelming odds, Alexander led his army to victories across the Persian territories of Asia Minor, Syria and Egypt finally reaching northwest India – all without suffering a single defeat.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/alexanderthegreat_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705205548 +0000" stop="20250705215656 +0000">
    <title>The Arabs</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Arabs have been bringing knowledge of the ancient world to Europe since the 8th century. In the fields of medicine, mathematics or philosophy, their scholars were far beyond their time and still affect our world today. For a long time the Arabs were estranged, not united by one nation or leader. They had little in common but a shared language.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/theascentofcivilization_s02_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705215656 +0000" stop="20250705225856 +0000">
    <title>The Carthaginians</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Carthaginians were sly merchants and cruel child killers – at least according to the Ancient Romans and Greeks. But research shows that they weren’t as bad as their reputation. The Carthaginians’ story began around 3,000 years ago, when settlers left their homes in what is now Lebanon to set up new colonies around the Mediterranean.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/theascentofcivilization_s02_7x10.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250705225856 +0000" stop="20250706000000 +0000">
    <title>The Silicon Valley Revolution - How a few nerds did change the world</title>
    <sub-title>From the first Computer Trade Fair to the WWW</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The dream of personal computers slowly turns into Big Business. The dream of a few leftist visionaries took over the world in the 1980s: the now legendary Macintosh goes on sale, Bill Gates creates the foundation for his economic imperium, the world wide web connects billions of people all over the world, Google is founded.</desc>
    <date>20230313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/thesiliconvalleyrevolutionhowafewnerdsdidchangetheworld_s01_thumbnail_16x9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6699937717c9985deeb74e39" start="20250706000000 +0000" stop="20250706010215 +0000">
    <title>The Kaiser's Pirates</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In November 1916, German raider SMS Wolf set out for a 15-month long voyage through the oceans finally reaching Australia and Papua New Guinea. The mission of this ship which was perfectly masked as a merchant vessel: capture, sink or destroy allied shipping.</desc>
    <date>20230316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_kaisers_pirates_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
