<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718233725 +0000" stop="20250719002406 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Kitchen Germs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E82</episode-num>
    <desc>Go LIVE in the O.R. and watch how surgeons perform a new valve replacement procedure! Are there hidden germs in your kitchen making you sick? The simple swaps to cut down on your sugar! Experts debate if it’s ever okay to yell at your kids!</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719002406 +0000" stop="20250719010744 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Why is This Happening to Me?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E90</episode-num>
    <desc>From bed wetting to plantar warts, The Doctors answer the big question: why is this happening to me? Don’t miss the simple procedure that eliminates crow’s feet, and find out Dr. Ordon’s tips to prevent them from forming!</desc>
    <date>20100126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02090.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719010744 +0000" stop="20250719014948 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Is Breast Implant Illness Real?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Find out why so many women are removing their breast implants. Could breast implant illness be to blame? Are you your own worst enemy? Do you get in your own way? Psychologist Dr. Judy Ho breaks down how to “Stop Self-Sabotage!” Could your favorite Boba drink put you at risk for intestinal blockage? Who says self-care has to be expensive? Find out how to self-care on a budget!</desc>
    <date>20190930</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719014948 +0000" stop="20250719023630 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The "L" Words</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E69</episode-num>
    <desc>From lips and legs to labor and libido, The Doctors explores the “L” words everyone loves or loathes and gives you the tools to start feeling and looking your absolute best! And find out the best ways to fight lethargy.</desc>
    <date>20091209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02069.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719023630 +0000" stop="20250719032304 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Embarrassing Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E97</episode-num>
    <desc>No question is too embarrassing for the The Doctors! Discover solutions for removing hair in odd places and if irregular genitals are cause for concern. Plus, The Doctors confess their most mortifying moments on the job!</desc>
    <date>20110208</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719032304 +0000" stop="20250719040901 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Smelling, Itching Problems Solved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E109</episode-num>
    <desc>What’s causing that foul odor? That nagging itch? No matter how gross or unusual, The Doctors solve your most annoying body problems from head to toe.</desc>
    <date>20120302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719040901 +0000" stop="20250719045514 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Unexpected Lumps and Bumps</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E116</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors help diagnose your body’s most mysterious lumps and bumps. Learn the warning signs of eye, brain and oral cancer. Plus, it’s an unsightly growth that can mimic melanoma, and most people will develop it in their lifetime. Find out what it is and how to treat it.</desc>
    <date>20130906</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719045514 +0000" stop="20250719054033 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Health Choices Caught on Tape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E125</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you cut corners when you think no one’s looking? The Doctors mounts a health sting with hidden cameras to see how many shortcuts people take with their health. And, find out which beauty treatments may do more harm than good!</desc>
    <date>20100507</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02125.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719054033 +0000" stop="20250719062541 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Preparing for Your First Time!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E84</episode-num>
    <desc>Witness a first for daytime TV; a mother-to-be delivers her first child by c-section Live on The Doctors! Plus, learn your first line of defense against America’s number one killer, and what you need to know before your first time going under the knife.</desc>
    <date>20110207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03084.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719062541 +0000" stop="20250719070315 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fixes for Funky Body Issues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>From stinky earwax to funky feet, The Doctors share solutions for the body issues you'd rather keep under wraps. Find fixes for nasty rashes, odor "down there" and more. Plus, "fifty shades of sex" secrets to try tonight!</desc>
    <date>20120918</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/eec225db0bef66144eafc9c146c6b534.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719070315 +0000" stop="20250719074814 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Biggest Health Dilemmas Solved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E65</episode-num>
    <desc>Tackle your health dilemmas! Get tips for younger looking hands, breathing better and more. Plus, one mom, two uteruses and a one-in-5 million chance of giving birth to twins. It's an exclusive interview you don't want to miss!</desc>
    <date>20120206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719074814 +0000" stop="20250719083315 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Most Embarrassing Questions Ever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E106</episode-num>
    <desc>From mysterious leaks to bad gas, no bodily function is off limits on THE DOCTORS. Get answers to your most embarrassing questions today. E! reality star Coco is notorious for her big booty – but is it real? Plastic surgeon Dr. Drew Ordon uncovers the truth with a real- time ultrasound. Pediatrician Dr. Jim Sears makes a stink about his stink! Learn why some people have stronger body odor than others. And, natural solutions to freshen your scent. Moms-to-be: You’re not alone. From prenatal gas to going number two in the delivery room, OB/GYN Dr. Lisa Masterson clears the air about the most embarrassing parts of pregnancy. Parents: Have your kids caught you in the act? Learn what to do if it happens to you. Plus, toenail biting, what corn in your stool means and more.</desc>
    <date>20120220</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04106.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719083315 +0000" stop="20250719091123 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Live Neck Procedure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS takes us “Inside the O.R.” for a LIVE neck lift procedure! 30 minute procedure to improve sex life and incontinence? Preacher’s brave interview about being addicted to pain medicine. Dr. Phil and Robin holiday exclusive! The artificial sweetener hack everyone is talking about!</desc>
    <date>20181212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719091123 +0000" stop="20250719095753 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Abduction Cases</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS looks into the criminal trend of baby abductions from someone else’s womb. Dr. Judy Ho discusses the disturbing psychology behind the Womb Raiders! Hepatitis A outbreak and what you need to know! Young girl battling anorexia for 16 years comes to THE DOCTORS, but is she willing to get better? Will THE DOCTORS give the new Beyoncé beauty trend a “Hack or Wack?”</desc>
    <date>20171120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719095753 +0000" stop="20250719104441 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bizarre ER Stories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Toxic shock mistake for flu. Bizarre in the ER: key lodged in head? Pen cap lodged in ear? Ask THE DOCTORS: plantar warts, UTI, yellow tongue diagnosis, and what causes dandruff? Is the fruity vagina a Buzz or Bust? Commando workout? Post work ritual for better sleep?</desc>
    <date>20181203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719104441 +0000" stop="20250719113123 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Man Survives 2,000 Foot Fall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E149</episode-num>
    <desc>In a THE DOCTORS exclusive, a young man falls 2,000+ feet and survives days in a blizzard…how did he do it? Are you paying different prices for the exact same medication? Why are more and more women turning to physical therapy for their private parts? Could loneliness be as deadly as cigarettes? Then, a husband and wife turn back the clock with facelifts … and reveal their new looks on set! We test magnetic eyelashes and tell you if they work! Plus, see what happens when bullfighting goes wrong … very wrong!</desc>
    <date>20170524</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09149.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719113123 +0000" stop="20250719121815 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Measures for Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E60</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go for beauty? A controversial surgery alters feet so women can wear heels. And, an acupuncture facelift that claims to take years off a woman's appearance. And, the latest in laser surgery that erases tattoos.</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01060.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719121815 +0000" stop="20250719130611 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Public Meltdowns &amp; More!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E62</episode-num>
    <desc>Caught on tape: a public meltdown at the gym! What to do when someone flies off the handle in public! Then, a 90-pound weight loss without surgery? Hear one woman’s personal tips that helped her get trim! And, The voice of beloved cartoon characters like Bugs Bunny, Ren and Stimpy, Doug and Futurama reveals his story of overcoming prostate cancer! The risk factors all men need to know! Plus, legendary Latin King of Comedy Paul Rodriguez opens up about his sister’s tragic diabetic death. Hear his heartache and his desire to improve his own personal health. Then, if you’re one of the 42 million Americans struggling with constipation, proctologist Dr. David Rosenfeld shares his top foods that can help you poop! Plus, a sweet trick for a bug-free BBQ!</desc>
    <date>20180912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719130611 +0000" stop="20250719134934 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Be Prepared</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Carbon monoxide can seep into your home while you sleep. Safeguard your family from this colorless, odorless and deadly gas. Plus, Dr. Lisa’s tips to prepare for menopause and how to lose those last 10 pounds!</desc>
    <date>20090921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719134934 +0000" stop="20250719143139 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bullied Because of My Skin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E105</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage girl is bullied because of her painful skin condition; will The Doctors be able to save her skin? Then, The Doctors discusses the latest health news. Could binge-watching your favorite shows trigger binge-drinking? Dr. Ordon reveals the latest nip-tuck trends, including a “No Downtime Neckline” procedure to help you say goodbye to your double chin! Plus, find out how you can fight wrinkles in your sleep!</desc>
    <date>20170327</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719143139 +0000" stop="20250719151840 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Body's Warning SIgns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Decipher the clues and warning signs your body is giving you. Witness a life-saving surgery that a mother and daughter underwent together! Plus, learn what kind of bruises can indicate a serious medical condition.</desc>
    <date>20091120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719151840 +0000" stop="20250719160504 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Weight Loss Extravaganza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E82</episode-num>
    <desc>The weight is over! From abuse victim to revenge body! From sickness to six packs! From bullied teen to inspirational hero! See story after story of incredible weight loss transformations without surgery that will blow your mind! Plus, meet the biggest weight loss success story in THE DOCTORS history!</desc>
    <date>20180108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719160504 +0000" stop="20250719165209 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>5 Cures in 5 Minutes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E109</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors present five-minute cures for common ailments. See a procedure that stops nasal allergy symptoms for good. And, cosmetic dentist Dr. Dorfman shares dental Dos and Don'ts, including an instant cure for canker sores.</desc>
    <date>20090223</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719165209 +0000" stop="20250719173804 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Miracles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E63</episode-num>
    <desc>When skin cancer destroyed one woman’s ear, see how doctors helped her grow a new one – on her arm! Then, a mom saves her child’s life with a fecal transplant. Plus, how one woman's breast milk is helping dozens of babies around the country.</desc>
    <date>20121115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719173804 +0000" stop="20250719182436 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Toenail Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Why does one woman have a 6th toenail? Watch as THE DOCTORS does a LIVE procedure in studio! Then, the Stool Squad is back to answer your burning questions! Want fast-food faster? A-list nutritionist Keri Glassman shares her kid-approved recipes! Next, would you change your future child’s eye color? Plus, do at-home bunion correctors really work? Then, why some people are turning to drinking vinegar for better gut health! Could it be doing more harm than good?</desc>
    <date>20181016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719182436 +0000" stop="20250719191024 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Common Medical Risks On The Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Behind the wheel, in a plane or on a train, learn how to avoid injuries and stay safe while on the go. And, Dr. Travis’ fun and safe workout tips for busy moms.</desc>
    <date>20100211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719191024 +0000" stop="20250719195845 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>A Test to Predict Cancer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>If you could take a test that would tell you whether or not you would get cancer, would you take it? And, is diet soda better for you than the than the real thing? Dr. Lisa says that everything should be consumed in moderation.</desc>
    <date>20080918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01005.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719195845 +0000" stop="20250719204549 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Drs: Why Does That Smell?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From foul gas to smelly ears, The Doctors answer your most pressing questions about the odors your body produces. And, editor-in-chief of Prevention, Liz Vaccariello, separates fact from fiction about a common medical myth.</desc>
    <date>20091027</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719204549 +0000" stop="20250719213159 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top Reasons People Call In Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Sore throat, upset stomach, aches and pains -- find out when you’re most contagious and when it’s safe to go back to school or the office. And, how to determine if your child is too sick for school.</desc>
    <date>20101213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719213159 +0000" stop="20250719221841 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Maureen McCormick &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, Maureen McCormick reveals new details of her shocking past! Then, one woman undergoes a live procedure for her resting “angry” face, did it work? Plus, what you need to know to protect your child from the super lice outbreak and a child abductor!</desc>
    <date>20160921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719221841 +0000" stop="20250719230440 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>I Donated My Husband's Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E141</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, a woman’s courage to donate her late husband’s face leads to a ground-breaking facial transplant with unbelievable results! In another exclusive, a mother reveals how the pressure to breastfeed her baby led her to accidentally starve her son. Reality star Laura Govan stops by for some advice on a personal health issue! Plus, the tweet that triggered a seizure … how’s that possible? And, a ssss-soothing massage by snakes? Meet Marnie The Dog!</desc>
    <date>20170509</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09141.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719230440 +0000" stop="20250719235050 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Can It Be Cured?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E63</episode-num>
    <desc>See a cure for chronic ear infections, a laser treatment that eliminates back pain and technology that guarantees less time in the dentist’s chair. And, at-home remedies that can cure a cold, calm a flu and quell motion sickness.</desc>
    <date>20091202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250719235050 +0000" stop="20250720003840 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Doctors: Body Sounds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>From a grumbling stomach, to a gassy gut to ringing ears, find out which body noises are hazardous, which are harmless and how to mute them.</desc>
    <date>20091006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
