<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709004254 +0000" stop="20250709012820 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>3 Amazing Medical Stories!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E43</episode-num>
    <desc>See why Doctors removed a part of a woman’s skull and placed it in her abdomen! Then, Lizzie was once labeled “the ugliest girl in the world” due to a rare facial disfigurement. Hear why she’s not letting cruelty slow her down. Plus, Kellie Pickler shaves her head in an exclusive clip.</desc>
    <date>20121029</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05043.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709012820 +0000" stop="20250709021354 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pimple Popper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Pimple Popper returns with her latest, greatest and grossest pops! Empire’s Ta’Rhonda Jones wants to gain a better smile without losing character…can it happen? Plus, a fertility doctor is accused of secretly impregnating patients with his own sperm? And, cocktails with health benefits – win!</desc>
    <date>20161005</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709021354 +0000" stop="20250709025824 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Breast Asymmetry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E119</episode-num>
    <desc>One is a “D” and The other an “A” - could one woman’s extreme breast asymmetry be fixed? Plus, proctologist Dr. David Rosenfeld make the world’s first colonoscopy rap called “The Bowel Prep Shuffle!” #AskTheDoctors! How to get rid of bikini blackheads? What to do if your kids “walk in” on you? At what age should you freeze your eggs? Does breast milk change color when baby is sick?</desc>
    <date>20180521</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10119.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709025824 +0000" stop="20250709034424 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Addicted to Exercise Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A previous guest who was addicted to exercise and referred to as the “sickest person ever on The show” returns with an unexpected update. Then, can cold medicine be used as a murder defense? The Doctors discusses the much buzzed about court case. Plus, our Stool Squad spins The “Wheel of Poop” and answers all your questions about… “Number Two”! And, The Doctors tackles the new research that points to the root cause of ADHD being sleep issues?</desc>
    <date>20171018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709034424 +0000" stop="20250709041729 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Caught On Tape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E53</episode-num>
    <desc>From politics to drugs, The Doctors cover headlines affecting your health. Should marijuana be legalized? Actress Roseanne Barr weighs in. Plus, why some doctors are being called drug dealers. And, what you must know about the peanut butter recall.</desc>
    <date>20121024</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05053.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709041729 +0000" stop="20250709050623 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Gross Anatomy: Oozing and Runny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E509</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors uncover the best treatments for your worst body conditions. Clear uncontrollable acne and treat embarrassing scars. Plus, a disintegrating teeth disorder and a debilitating problem “down there.” Are you at risk?</desc>
    <date>20120514</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04509.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709050623 +0000" stop="20250709055320 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Scare Experiment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E80</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors takes drastic measures to save the lives of three people before it’s too late. Will they change their destructive ways? And, easy steps to avoid becoming a health statistic!</desc>
    <date>20110117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709055320 +0000" stop="20250709063849 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Pregnant Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Three years ago, Thomas Beatie made headlines as the first legal man in history to give birth. After years under the radar, The Doctors uncover everything you didn’t know about the controversial pregnancy and delivery.</desc>
    <date>20111031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709063849 +0000" stop="20250709072533 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Skin Removal Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E123</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors checkup, we go inside the O.R. as a guest who lost 280 pounds gets skin removal surgery! Meet the biggest weight-loss loser of the #DropTheSugar Challenge! Dr. Travis’ skills are put to the test in the Baby Daddy Challenge! Could weekend brunch be causing us to put on weight.</desc>
    <date>20200506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12123.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709072533 +0000" stop="20250709081230 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What to Do if Disaster Strikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E56</episode-num>
    <desc>When disaster strikes, would you know what to do? Are you prepared for earthquakes, tornadoes, hurricanes, blizzards and more? Plus, five things you can do to increase your chance of surviving a plane crash.</desc>
    <date>20101108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03056.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709081230 +0000" stop="20250709085955 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Aaron Carter Exclusive - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Plagued by rumors of crack use, meth use, cancer and his HIV status, pop star Aaron Carter comes to The Doctors in a world exclusive to find out what’s really going. Can Aaron on be saved from The wreckage of superstardom?</desc>
    <date>20170913</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/88cae131125bd3805e3d308e7182b358.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709085955 +0000" stop="20250709094739 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Aaron Carter Exclusive - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E301</episode-num>
    <desc>Plagued by rumors of crack use, meth use, cancer and his HIV status, pop star Aaron Carter comes to The Doctors in a world exclusive to find out what’s really going. Can Aaron on be saved from The wreckage of superstardom? In Part 2 of our Aaron Carter exclusive, The Doctors is tasked with delivering the news to Aaron about his blood tests for HIV and meth use.</desc>
    <date>20170914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10301.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709094739 +0000" stop="20250709103428 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Feeds Children Dog Feces?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom accused of feeding her own kids dog feces? ASMR dandruff scraping? Why some are soothed by watching people scrape their scalps! Is elderly drinking on the rise? The medical trend that could be harming your grandparents! Woman celebrates massive excess skin removal! Cauliflower chocolate smoothie? Man’s penis turns to bone? Uncovering singer Camila Cabello's mental health tip is for a stress free day!</desc>
    <date>20191016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709103428 +0000" stop="20250709112059 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Grossest Moments Ever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E508</episode-num>
    <desc>The Embarrassing, Gross, and Wild Special brings you some of The Doctors’ most unforgettable moments! See “The Great Pop-Off”! Relive Dr. Pimple Popper’s biggest and best pops! Marvel at the courage of guests who shared Their most embarrassing problems to raise awareness! From the huge, painful keloids that isolated a school teacher to The severe birthmarks that tormented a young woman, These guests stepped out of the shadows for help. Don’t miss one man’s 315-pound transformation! Laugh and learn as Dr. Ordon and NBA star Jon Salley undergo prostate exams backstage! Score a simple fix for dry, chalky elbows.</desc>
    <date>20170908</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09508.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709112059 +0000" stop="20250709120738 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Build Your Best Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E133</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you suffer from migraine headaches? Learn about one surprising cure for your throbbing head! And, getting cavities filled used to be a painful process. Learn about a new, painless procedure that fixes your cavities.</desc>
    <date>20090325</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709120738 +0000" stop="20250709125335 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Try This At Home!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E78</episode-num>
    <desc>From kitchen catastrophes to workplace disasters, don’t miss the list of everyday health hazards that may surprise you. Learn when you can do it yourself and when you should call a professional.</desc>
    <date>20100106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709125335 +0000" stop="20250709134017 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top 5 Questions To Ask Your Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E43</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how to interview potential doctors, which tests you need and how to make the most of your next doctor’s visit. Plus, when you need to go to the emergency room – STAT.</desc>
    <date>20101215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03043.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709134017 +0000" stop="20250709142617 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Leave it On or Take it Off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E133</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it razor burn, pimples or something worse? Learn the difference between bumps down there. Plus, four tips for a smooth, sexy bikini line. Then, slash hundreds of calories with a simple breakfast swap. And, Dr. Travis turns up the heat at a sweat lodge!</desc>
    <date>20130424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709142617 +0000" stop="20250709151129 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Secrets to Never Getting Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Runny noses, sore throats, nasty coughs, vomiting: stop dreaded symptoms before they start! The Doctors reveal the top secrets to never getting sick. Find out when you should - and shouldn't - medicate, natural remedies in your kitchen and more!</desc>
    <date>20120217</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709151129 +0000" stop="20250709155612 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Legends' Top Age-Defying Tips</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E95</episode-num>
    <desc>Look and feel young at any age! Hollywood film stars Diahann Carroll, Dyan Cannon and Jacqueline Bisset reveal the secrets of Their eternal youth. And, see a new non-invasive skin smoothing treatment. Plus, an instant booty lifting procedure.</desc>
    <date>20130129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709155612 +0000" stop="20250709164249 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Large Fibroid Removal Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E95</episode-num>
    <desc>You won’t believe what happens when the show’s cameras go “Inside The O.R.” as a 51-year-old woman has a large fibroid removed, which left her looking 5 months pregnant! Controversial new study claims smart women should marry down if They want to start a family. E-cigarettes and vaping have been sold as a way for smokers to quit – new research on why it doesn’t work? The Doctors’ Court: woman arrested with five different types of drugs hidden…in her vagina?</desc>
    <date>20190123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709164249 +0000" stop="20250709173112 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>When Plastic Surgery Goes Wrong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Considering plastic surgery of any kind? Don't miss Krissy's story and Dr. Ordon's essential do's and don'ts to keep you safe. Watch several controversial potty training techniques in action and see if any of them are right for your child.</desc>
    <date>20081002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709173112 +0000" stop="20250709181804 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Measures for Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E60</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go for beauty? A controversial surgery alters feet so women can wear heels. And, an acupuncture facelift that claims to take years off a woman's appearance. And, the latest in laser surgery that erases tattoos.</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01060.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709181804 +0000" stop="20250709190336 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Improve Your Health From A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Get simple solutions for hiccups, nosebleeds, vertigo and 23 other ailments with The Doctors ABCs of medicine! Plus, learn how to how to last longer in bed. And, the number one mistake parents make when their kids get sick.</desc>
    <date>20101112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709190336 +0000" stop="20250709195016 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Investigate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E112</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors investigates lunchboxes! Could dangerous mold, fungus and bacteria be hiding in your child’s lunchbox? You may want to hit the brakes at the drive-thru … could cancer-causing chemicals be hiding in your fast food? An erotic website offers sex-ed for teens with a new “wellness” hub? A judge’s sentence is raising eyebrows: celibacy as punishment? Get your daily dose of gross with a viral earwax video! You might want to think twice before eating chicken with white stripes; find out why! And, how a penny could help you avoid sickness and save wads of cash in an emergency!</desc>
    <date>20121205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709195016 +0000" stop="20250709203713 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Fixes for Common Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E165</episode-num>
    <desc>From fighting flab, to stifling sneezes to quieting a crying baby, The Doctors reveals easy fixes for your most common problems! And, Oscar-winning actress Marisa Tomei shares her top secrets to a better body!</desc>
    <date>20100520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02165.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709203713 +0000" stop="20250709212354 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Kitchen Germs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E82</episode-num>
    <desc>Go LIVE in the O.R. and watch how surgeons perform a new valve replacement procedure! Are there hidden germs in your kitchen making you sick? The simple swaps to cut down on your sugar! Experts debate if it’s ever okay to yell at your kids!</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709212354 +0000" stop="20250709221043 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Howie Mandel &amp; OCD</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedian and television personality Howie Mandel confronts his OCD and germ phobia with THE DOCTORS! Our investigation reveals the filth on your hands and the most germ-infested places you’re touching! Restaurant horror stories you must see before you eat out again! Then, a mother’s excruciating jaw condition is destroying her life! Plus, a cure for garlic breath that’s right in your fridge!</desc>
    <date>20161031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709221043 +0000" stop="20250709225736 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Shape of Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E128</episode-num>
    <desc>Staying in shape isn’t only about muscle tone. From your lungs to your knees, improve your body from the inside out! Plus, flatten your tummy without surgery, and Alicia Silverstone’s secrets for healthy and sweet treats!</desc>
    <date>20110315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709225736 +0000" stop="20250709234417 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Weighs 6yo Daily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A mom is under fire for weighing her 6-year-old daughter every single day after she’s bullied for her weight! Is this mom doing the right thing the wrong way? Plus, the controversy over using marijuana for pain relief in the NFL continues! Do you think the drug should be allowed for players? Then, kids are so stressed out doing their homework they now need therapists? We discuss the new alarming trend! And, using oregano oil to stop a cold in its tracks – is it a buzz or a bust?</desc>
    <date>20181102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250709234417 +0000" stop="20250710002946 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Renew Your Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E160</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling burnt out and run down? The Doctors show you how to renew you life, body, mind and spirit. Learn the advantages to a little R&amp;R and the beauty benefits of steam. And, see what your eyes are saying about your health.</desc>
    <date>20110907</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250710002946 +0000" stop="20250710011618 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Tired? Here's Why</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E42</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling tired and worn down? The Doctors reveal the top four reasons you may feel fatigued -- and none are lack of sleep! Plus, take 10 years off your face without a scalpel or filler! Could it work for you?</desc>
    <date>20121107</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/547fc29b8780c7eddaeed643f4e3991d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
