<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704005958 +0000" stop="20250704020000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Holley Equipped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The '69 Daytona Charger returns from the media blaster and Mark gives Josh a history lesson on the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel Car before removing it's drive-train and suspension.</desc>
    <date>20130212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704020000 +0000" stop="20250704025959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car completely disassembled and off to the media blaster. Mark disassembles and restores the right-hand door to the 71' 440 Phantom Cuda. In addition, the headliner and vinyl top is installed in the 71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704025959 +0000" stop="20250704035959 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car completely disassembled and off to the media blaster. Mark disassembles and restores the right-hand door to the 71' 440 Phantom Cuda. In addition, the headliner and vinyl top is installed in the 71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704035959 +0000" stop="20250704050001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>You Win Some …</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The owner of the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car visits the shop and learns about assembly-line markings. Mark checks the paint on the body of the '70 Cuda 383 Automatic FE5 Rallye Red Car and discovers a major problem.</desc>
    <date>20130226</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704050001 +0000" stop="20250704060000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Cuda Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls receives a '70 Barracuda Convertible to get a full restoration. Despite improbability, Mark straightens the fender for the '71 440 Phantom Cuda and the crew continues the restoration of the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130305</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704060000 +0000" stop="20250704070001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Cuda Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls receives a '70 Barracuda Convertible to get a full restoration. Despite improbability, Mark straightens the fender for the '71 440 Phantom Cuda and the crew continues the restoration of the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130305</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704070001 +0000" stop="20250704080001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Flippin' the Bird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls detail and assemble the suspension of the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car. The owners of the '70 Plymouth Superbird, in the queue for resurrection, visit the shop and Daren convinces the crew to throw a birthday party for Mark.</desc>
    <date>20130312</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704080001 +0000" stop="20250704083006 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Family Truckster Restoration Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter provides tips and techniques for restoring dull, faded paint using a forced-rotation dual action polisher along with a graphene 3-in-1 ceramic polish, along with severe scratch and scuff removal.</desc>
    <date>20230802</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/DN230104H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704083006 +0000" stop="20250704090004 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Family Truckster Restoration Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter provides valuable tips and techniques for how super clean automotive upholstery, as well as the proper chemicals and detailing tools for deep cleaning vinyl and rubber surfaces.</desc>
    <date>20230802</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/DN230105H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704090004 +0000" stop="20250704093006 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>K5 Blazer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Time to get low with a K5 Blazer. Matt and Bruno are going to C-notch the frame and and this 73’ blazer while still using the factory wheels and tires.</desc>
    <date>00010117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704093006 +0000" stop="20250704100005 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>LS Blazer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A Blazer with an LS engine is cool, but the interior is far from ready. Matt and Bruno totally transform the interior with seats and door panels and have an almost drivable Blazer when we’re done.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704100005 +0000" stop="20250704103003 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Fleet F150</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E02</episode-num>
    <desc>This fleet F150 needs a kick into high gear. We’ll give the truck some needed stopping power with an upgraded brake kit and we’ll bolt on some power upgrades under the hood.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704103003 +0000" stop="20250704110008 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Buggy Maintenance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Last time this buggy was on the trail it broke. Matt and Bruno will give some tips on taking apart beadlock wheels, drain the fluids and check for metal scraps, and do some final repairs so the owner can get back on the trails.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704110008 +0000" stop="20250704113013 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Longbed to shortbed conversion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on Truck U, we’ll show you what it takes to convert a Longbed C10 into a shortbed. Couple of cuts, couple of sleeves and some welding and we’ve got an entirely new truck.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704113013 +0000" stop="20250704120018 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>7.3L Common Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Injector problems are common on these 7.3L engines, so we’ll show you how to swap them out and how to tell if your injector cup needs to be replaced in the process. We’ll also drop in a new transmission and get rid of the outdated one.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704120018 +0000" stop="20250704123019 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Propane Injection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Have you ever heard of using propane injection on a diesel truck? It has benefits for horsepower, EPA and most importantly for our 6.0 Powerstroke; miles per gallon!</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704123019 +0000" stop="20250704130019 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>New Jeep JL</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E07</episode-num>
    <desc>For the first time on TV, Matt and Bruno get to play with the new Jeep JL and there is already a ton of parts in the aftermarket for these Jeeps. They’ll bolt on a new suspension and change out the exhaust.</desc>
    <date>20221022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704130019 +0000" stop="20250704133018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 On The Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Season 13 is off and rumbling with Stacey showing off the new exhaust system for the SR-71 Rapid Tool Express project. From the headers to the tailpipes, this exhaust is going to scream! After that, it’s chassis details as Stacey lays out a plan for pedals, brakes and a fuel tank. Of course You can’t have an SR-71 inspired build without some killer wheels and wait ‘til you see what Stacey and our good friends at Neely Precision come up with. It’s all good, and it’s all here, this week on GearZ</desc>
    <date>20190105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0155.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704133018 +0000" stop="20250704140021 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Paint &amp; Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The biggest Toy in the shop is back... HEAVY METAL! Yes... Our old junk yard International Tow Truck rolls back into the garage as the freshly painted cab returns from the Hot Rot Institute. And it’s not just any paint, It’s Razzleberry from Axalta that’s so candy, you’ll want to take a bite! But there’s no time for that because Stacey jumps right in to putting a face and interior back in this old junkyard dog. The result will make you really glad that he rescued this one from the crusher! It’s recycling at it’s best... it’s GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0156.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704140021 +0000" stop="20250704143021 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Heavy Metal Dash &amp; Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re moving full steam ahead with the Interior of the Heavy Metal cab coming together and now’s the time to get the dash set up. We’ve got new gauges, old gauges and a bunch of empty holes where switches and knobs lived in this truck’s former life. Stacey lays out the dos and donts of getting your dash updated and a layout that makes sense before it gets installed. GearZ hits the road with a special delivery for the Hot Rod Institute for all they’ve done for us and the restoration industry. Feeling a little down about your project? Well, Stacey has a tool tech that’s sure to lift you up! All this and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0157.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704143021 +0000" stop="20250704150022 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The SR-71 Rapid Tool Express returns as Stacey digs into his old ’59 ford panel truck and shows how to convert it into a one-off tool delivery truck to show off a variety of Cornwell tools. From special shelves, lighting and floor, there are even a few surprises that are tucked away inside this rolling tool cart! Moving to the cab of the vehicle, Stacey addresses some of the issues people have when setting up seats and steering, and shows some simple tricks that make a huge difference in getting your seats and steering dialed in. Then it’s on the rear to lay out the gas tank, and then finally the SR-71 gets a new beak.... from a ’59 T-bird! ...What?!?.... how is that possible? Well, ya gotta watch GEARZ to find out!</desc>
    <date>20190309</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0158.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704150022 +0000" stop="20250704153025 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Topping the Jeep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jeep may be the single most modified vehicle out there. From winches to lights, doors and fenders, if you’ve got a Jeep, it probably has some accessories on it. But despite all that, one of the best things about a Jeep is the removable top. It also sparks one of the biggest debates... What is best: a soft top or a hard top? Stacey takes on the challenge by comparing a factory hard top with the new Bestop Trektop. The test will include everything from ease of install to styling, overall sound decibels and of course, how watertight it is. Hopefully you won’t get wet on this ride! Then it’s back to the shop where Stacey shows you that rotisseries aren’t just for chickens, and how an automotive rotisserie can make life in the shop a lot easier. Finally, it’s on to the right and wrong way to use weatherstrip adhesive to hold your rubbers on. Sound risqué? It’s not... it’s just GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190316</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0159.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704153025 +0000" stop="20250704160025 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s all about square body GM trucks, because The Stunt Double is back in the shop. First, we take a look back at the this awesome ‘86 Chevy 4x4 Silverado long bed build that pays tribute to the legendary Fall Guy TV truck. From its beginnings as a well-worn farm truck, you’ll see it get an upgraded suspension, interior, drivetrain, as we make it better than I was before... better... stronger... faster... wait, that was a DIFFERENT Lee Majors TV show! After that, we walk you through the paint job and show how it is similar to the Fall Guy truck, only different.... because It’s the Stunt Double!!! No hocus pocus... no movie magic... just a tough truck being built to handle the toughest stunts... only on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20190323</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0160.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704160025 +0000" stop="20250704163027 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Frame &amp; Body Assembly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The SR-71 Rapid Tool Express is back on the block and going back together for the last time. Stacey finishes up the frame into a rolling masterpiece with the suspension and drivetrain assembled for the last time. Then the body goes back on, and the interior starts to go together. We’re talking fitting the carpet, steering column and the new dash bezel and stuffing that bezel with custom SR-71 gauges. After that, Stacey shows some tricks on how to choose the right transmission and why rechargeable power tools are giving the tried and true air tools a run for their money! It's all here and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0161.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704163027 +0000" stop="20250704170029 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gas, Tops, Brushes &amp; Samurais</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the e85 market and flex fuel vehicles growing every day, Stacey dives into the myths and truths that surround ethanol and whether or not it’s a good choice for your vehicle. With a little help from Advanced Fuel Dynamics, Stacey installs a new fuel delivery system on a 2017 Mustang to show just how easy it is to up your performance and keep your engine safe at the same time. After that, Stacey and the crew head out west to tell the story of Bestop and how they’ve been making removable Jeep tops for decades. From rock-crawlers to the mall crawlers, Bestops unique past allows us to see what the future of the Jeep world will be. Finally, if you’re trying to decide between a stick or automatic transmission… hang out for a while as Stacey talks about converting your boring automatic to a lively manual transmission. We’ve got all this and more on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20190518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0162.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704170029 +0000" stop="20250704173027 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cornwell 100</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s rare for people to reach the age of 100. It’s ever rarer for a business, but that just what Cornwell Quality Tools has done! Take a trip through the last century as Stacey tracks the development of a tool company started by a blacksmith, to the tool truck empire that stresses quality over everything else. Speaking of 100 years…trucks have been around for over a century, and for over a century, truck owners have struggled to find the best way to lift their trucks. Stacey sheds some light on picking the right kind of lift for the truck you’re driving. We’ve got all of this and more on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190525</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0163.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704173027 +0000" stop="20250704180029 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Copperhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E10</episode-num>
    <desc>There’s nothing like a good mystery. One of our favorite GearZ mysteries is the whereabouts of Copperhead, the legendary C10 that Stacey built more than a decade ago. It seemed like the truck just disappeared. Well, it’s back! And Stacey was reunited with it at the C10 Nationals in Ft. Worth, TX. Tag along as Stacey gets a chance to get behind the wheel again and boil some tires. Back in the garage, Stacey tackles a fuel injection install on a Jeep Scrambler, then checks out the new Core Doors from Bestop. There’s a lot going on and plenty of smoke on the Texas Motor Speedway on this episode of GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190713</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0164.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704180029 +0000" stop="20250704183029 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>SR-71 Fins, Logo and Mystery Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As the SR71 Rapid Tool Express nears completion there are a couple of major things left on the plate before we can fire her up and get her down the road. First, every aircraft must have fins, and Stacey finally finds the fins he’s been looking for since the beginning of this build. Second, a cool logo design shows up at the shop. Third, what’s a stealthy tribute vehicle without stealthy paint? Believe it or not, Stacey’s got some paint that should keep the SR71 flying under the radar. Also, a slightly modified March Performance system will help Stacey get that much closer to putting some spark to this awesome build and stick around for plenty of other tech advice from America’s Gearhead… on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190720</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0165.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704183029 +0000" stop="20250704190028 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road - Squarebody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E12</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re on the road, again, as Stacey visits a truck enthusiast working on his first ground up restoration. It’s a sweet, clean, square body that’s in good enough condition that it might be on the road in a couple of months. But every build can use a little push, and GearZ On the Road does just that! After that, we dig into toolboxes. Hang out as Stacey talks with two engineers about what makes the new Cornwell Platinum boxes so tough. From rollers to welds, these might be the Ultimate box! Then the Cheetah is back in the garage, but only for a day or two before it heads out to get the body work finished and get some new color. It’s all here on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20190727</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0166.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704190028 +0000" stop="20250704193029 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>REVIVING THE SUR-TREK 8-WHEEL DRIVE ATV</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>STACEY DIGS INTO A PROJECT THAT SHOWS YOU JUST HOW MUCH FUN YOU CAN HAVE FOR ALMOST NO MONEY. BECAUSE HE’S TAKING A DERELECT 70’S ATV, STUFFING IN A JUNKYARD ENGINE, TOSSING IN SOME GOOD OL’ AMERICAN INGENINUITY AND ENDING UP WITH A REALLY COOL RIG. IT’S CHEAP! IT’S FUN! AND YOU’LL BE SURPRISED WHAT YOU LEARN ON A PROJECT LIKE THIS!</desc>
    <date>20070301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0001.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704193029 +0000" stop="20250704200028 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>What do you get when you cross the quentessential girl's car, the Mazda Miata, with the ultimate guy's car...the Shelby Cobra? Well, Gearz is the only place to find out as Stacey blows apart an innocent Miata to get it ready for its conversion into a V8 powered, screamin' machine called the "Banshee."</desc>
    <date>20070308</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0002.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704200028 +0000" stop="20250704203028 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Last week he made room, this week the transplant takes place as Stacey stuffs a 400 horsepower V8 into a Mazda Miata. If you've ever wondered if it's possible to actually build a blindingly fast car on a reasonable budget...The Banshee is the project you need to see. And Gearz is the olny place to see it.</desc>
    <date>20070315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0003.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704203028 +0000" stop="20250704210028 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>L.A.R.C.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Today on Gearz, Stacey takes you for a unique spin in one of the largest 4-wheel vehicles ever built...the LARC 60. Then it's back to the shop, where he digs into frame modifications so you can be sure the foundation is strong on your project. Then finally, he throws some cool fire-power into the back of Sgt. Rock that you are going to have to see to believe. Lock and load!</desc>
    <date>20070322</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0004.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704210028 +0000" stop="20250704213026 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Superbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>This is a show for all of you restorers out there, because Stacey not only shows you how to properly drive your hotrod by flogging on a '70 Superbird, but he also shows you some tips and tricks on restoring vintage parts like exhaust manifolds and steering wheels. If you're a Gearhead, then this Gearz id for you.</desc>
    <date>20070329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0005.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704213026 +0000" stop="20250704220025 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>32 Ford History and Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It's anniversary time. The '32 Ford is 75 years old and we take a look back at what made this car so popular for so long. But that's not enought, no...Stacey shows you that the deuce is not dead...it's just getting started as he walks you through the assembly and building of a brand new, steel '32 roadster body at Brookville Roadsters.</desc>
    <date>20070406</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0006.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704220025 +0000" stop="20250704223025 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Banshee is back on Gearz and rollin' down the final stretches as Stacey installs new suspension and brakes to help control this molten missile when he uncorks that nasty V8. Even if you are not putting a V8 in your Miata, this show is full of cool things you can do to any Miata to make it look, handle, and perform better.</desc>
    <date>20070413</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0007.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704223025 +0000" stop="20250704230022 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Banshee Part 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Banshee gets a major facelift as Stacey transforms it from a Mazda Miata into a ...well...uh...the Banshee! that's right, the body parts fly and the cutting continues until slowly, from the mayhem, a car appears that really does look as good and run as fast as a cobra or a corvette...except the Banshee is actually affordable...And only on Gearz</desc>
    <date>20070420</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0008.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250704230022 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title>Radford Reborn</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radford Reborn</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250705000000 +0000" stop="20250705010000 +0000">
    <title>Radford Reborn</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radford Reborn</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250705010000 +0000" stop="20250705015957 +0000">
    <title>Radford Reborn</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radford Reborn</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
