<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715001125 +0000" stop="20250715005927 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I'm a Slave to My Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E116</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil talks to controlling guests and the loved ones who feel trapped by them. Jeffrey hates that his wife of seven months, Mindy, goes out clubbing with her younger friends, who he says are a bad influence on her. Mindy leaves the kids with Jeffrey's 16-year-old daughter and parties until 6:00 a.m., while he works the night shift. Mindy calls Jeffrey “a warden,” and says if he had his way, she’d never leave the house. Then, Jason claims his wife, Terrie, is lazy. He says he has to clean the house, do chores, take care of the kids and balance two checkbooks! Terrie says her large chest and arthritis prevent her from doing household tasks. Can Jason get his wife to clean up her act?</desc>
    <date>20060320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715005927 +0000" stop="20250715014432 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Know It All In-Laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E130</episode-num>
    <desc>In-laws can be the kind who give unwanted advice, stop by unexpectedly and use guilt and manipulation to get what they want. But sometimes, they are loving parents who get caught in the middle of their child's relationship. Amanda calls her mother-in-law, Yolande, psychotic, controlling and meddling. She says Yolande speaks to her son, Pierre, in French so she can hide the hurtful words she’s using about Amanda. Yolande says Amanda is a drunk, and an uneducated woman who is wrecking her son's life. Why does Pierre say he can't choose a side? To test Amanda's theory of why Yolande and Pierre speak French to each other, Dr. Phil sets up a "special" dinner for the three of them. Be a fly on the wall, and find out if Amanda's right or just being paranoid. And, John and Chrissy's engagement is on hold because they say they can't stop fighting. They hit and slap each other, and call each other vulgar names — often in front of their 8-month-old son. John's mom, Charlene, who is often pulled into their fights, says they both need to grow up! After watching themselves scream and yell on tape, will this couple decide to drop their fists, close their mouths and work to make a peaceful home for their baby?</desc>
    <date>20070425</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715014432 +0000" stop="20250715023222 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Prophet or Pedophile?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>What happened to the victims of self-proclaimed FLDS prophet, Warren Jeffs?</desc>
    <date>20110927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715023222 +0000" stop="20250715032029 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Inside the FLDS</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E301</episode-num>
    <desc>A former FLDS spokesperson, Willie Jessop, comes face to face with critics.</desc>
    <date>20110928</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10301.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715032029 +0000" stop="20250715040546 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets Gone Wrong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Deborah was devastated when she went through her 17-year-old daughter, Miranda’s, cell phone and discovered a very disturbing photo. Miranda says she tried to tell her mom about her pregnancy but couldn’t bring herself to do it. Learn why Deborah says she was forced to turn her daughter in to the police, and how Miranda ended up in jail. Dr. Phil reaches out to the teen struggling to deal with guilt and loss, who faces backlash from a community she says doesn’t understand. Then, a family is torn apart after the father confesses the secret he’s kept for years. Find out why his girlfriend is now afraid for their 2-year-old daughter.</desc>
    <date>20110228</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715040546 +0000" stop="20250715045128 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Fiancé Believes He’s a Superhero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E74</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman says her fiancé made the decision to identify as "Goose Wayne Batman."</desc>
    <date>20190206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17074.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715045128 +0000" stop="20250715053910 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Co-Parenting Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Jared says his ex-wife, Chandra, is a deadbeat mom who has failed to pay her court-ordered child support in the last six months. He also accuses Chandra’s current husband, Jason, of physical abuse toward his two children when they’re in his care -- a claim Jason adamantly denies. Chandra accuses Jared of emotionally abusing her since their divorce five years ago, and she claims he’s determined to ruin her life with her new husband. Is Jared a concerned parent, or a bitter ex with an ulterior motive? And, with their children caught in the crossfire, can these exes stop pointing fingers and learn how to peacefully co-parent? Plus, why hasn’t Chandra paid child support? Then, don’t miss Dr. Phil’s tips on how to effectively co-parent with your ex!</desc>
    <date>20130307</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715053910 +0000" stop="20250715062657 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Butt Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you have someone in your life who's so annoying and frustrating that you just want him or her to go away? What do you do when you're co-parents with someone you can't get along with? And, what if your daughter secretly dated, and then married, a man you despise?</desc>
    <date>20080118</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715062657 +0000" stop="20250715071245 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Affair Accusation: Brother-In-Law &amp; Teen?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Bridget says she is worried that her 38-year-old brother-in-law Kevin may be having an inappropriate relationship with her 16-year-old daughter, Grace. Bridget says red flags went up when Grace told her that Kevin put whipped cream on his neck and asked her to lick it off, and then found a letter from Kevin hidden in Grace’s bedroom. Kevin strongly denies having an inappropriate relationship with Grace, and claims he’s just trying to be a father figure since Grace’s dad passed away. But is there something more?</desc>
    <date>20151102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715071245 +0000" stop="20250715075746 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Kevin Responds (Part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E303</episode-num>
    <desc>Bridget says she’s not sure what to believe about the relationship between her 38-year-old brother-in-law, Kevin, and 16-year-old daughter, Grace.Dr. Phil says Bridget is a parent in denial and in need of a wake-up call. He sits down one-on-one with Kevin. How does Kevin explain his actions?</desc>
    <date>20151103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14303.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715075746 +0000" stop="20250715084420 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In-Laws: Dirty Secrets Exposed!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Alan says he's being falsely accused of a heinous crime, and his accuser is his own mother-in-law! She claims he molested his 3-year-old daughter. Who's telling the truth? Find out when Dr. Phil reads the results of Alan's polygraph exam. Can this family heal and move on?</desc>
    <date>20061117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5014.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715084420 +0000" stop="20250715093038 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Big Time Moochers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E125</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents express frustration with their twin sons' disrespectful behavior.</desc>
    <date>20110519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9125.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715093038 +0000" stop="20250715101630 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Complicated Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E96</episode-num>
    <desc>Craig and Cherie say the last half of their 16-year marriage has been anything but happily-ever-after. Cherie says Craig is chauvinistic, verbally abusive and demands sex, which she admits she only gives him about three to four times a year. Craig says Cherie withholds sex to control him, and as a result, he has become a slave to his anger. Cherie fears the tension in their household is taking a toll on their 11-year-old daughter, who is often caught in the crossfire of their fighting. Dr. Phil challenges the couple to a communication test. Can they heal their wounds and rekindle their romance? Then, meet the couple who inspired the movie, The Vow. Shortly after Kim and Krickitt Carpenter were married, a terrible car crash changed everything. Krickitt lay in a coma for weeks, and awoke with no recognition of her husband. The couple shares their inspiring, though oftentimes heartbreaking, journey of falling in love all over again. How did they find their way back to each other? And what is it like seeing their lives played out on the big screen? If you’ve ever wondered whether love can survive the toughest of challenges, you won’t want to miss this show! This show contains strong sexual content. Viewer discretion advised.</desc>
    <date>20120306</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10096.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715101630 +0000" stop="20250715110447 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Finding Allene &amp; Mollie Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E123</episode-num>
    <desc>The dramatic international efforts to rescue two teen girls.</desc>
    <date>20060510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4123.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715110447 +0000" stop="20250715115048 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Finding Allene &amp; Mollie Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E210</episode-num>
    <desc>The tense family drama continues as Dr. Phil sends a private investigator through three countries to find two sisters abducted by their father.</desc>
    <date>20060510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4210.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715115048 +0000" stop="20250715123905 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Heaviest Woman On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E51</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother who is nealty 700 pounds struggles to gets her life on track.</desc>
    <date>20111123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715123905 +0000" stop="20250715132605 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bait and Switch Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E120</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben says his wife changed for the worse as soon as they got married; she says he is a narcissist and may be cheating on her.</desc>
    <date>20140418</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12120.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715132605 +0000" stop="20250715141112 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>From Top TV Newscaster to Drunken Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E86</episode-num>
    <desc>Christi says she was an Emmy-winning TV news reporter at the top of her career, but now her struggle with alcohol has left her jobless, sleeping in bushes and estranged from her two adult daughters, Heather and Haleigh. Christi faces her daughters for the first time in more than two years. Is she really ready to get clean? And, are they willing to give her another chance?</desc>
    <date>20150129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13086.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715141112 +0000" stop="20250715145752 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Queen Hits Rock Bottom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it possible for a former beauty queen to find sobriety?</desc>
    <date>20120209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715145752 +0000" stop="20250715154515 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Fugitive Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E86</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie, a divorced mother of four, says she has been a fugitive -- wanted for attempted murder -- for the past two months after attempting to attack her ex-husband with a hammer. What does she say caused her to carry out the violent act? And, is she ready to turn herself in?</desc>
    <date>20140219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12086.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715154515 +0000" stop="20250715163248 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Are My Children in a Cult?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E133</episode-num>
    <desc>A father is fighting for custody of his 4 children because his ex-wife is allegedly in a cult.</desc>
    <date>20130521</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715163248 +0000" stop="20250715171909 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Is My Sister a Drama Queen or Really Sick?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman believes her sister lied about being diagnosed with more than 70 health conditions.</desc>
    <date>20141110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715171909 +0000" stop="20250715180413 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Saving Shemida: What’s The Truth?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E304</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with a woman who says her sister lied about health diagnoses for attention.</desc>
    <date>20141111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715180413 +0000" stop="20250715185018 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Wife Enables Our Mooching Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother and stepfather express frustration with their unemployed, substance-abusing son's mooching behavior.</desc>
    <date>20171009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715185018 +0000" stop="20250715193659 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Our 7yo Threatens to Kill Us!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E75</episode-num>
    <desc>A 7-year-old boy's knives fascination and violent imaginary friend injured teachers.</desc>
    <date>20150310</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13075.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715193659 +0000" stop="20250715202635 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Moms Who Drink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E80</episode-num>
    <desc>There are killers among us, and they're not terrorists ... they're mothers who get drunk and then get behind the wheel, often with their kids in the car. More moms than ever are admitting to sneaking a drink or two while caring for their children. Learn how this epidemic may be affecting moms you know. This show just may be your call to action and help you save a life!</desc>
    <date>20100218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715202635 +0000" stop="20250715211331 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Controlling Husbands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Wives who say their husbands try to control every aspect of their lives.</desc>
    <date>20100203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715211331 +0000" stop="20250715220037 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Get Your Act Together</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E52</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil gives family freeloaders a wake-up call.</desc>
    <date>20080117</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6052.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715220037 +0000" stop="20250715224833 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Make It or Break It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A divorced couple secretly remarries, but did they make a mistake- again?</desc>
    <date>20080909</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715224833 +0000" stop="20250715233544 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Dilemmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E79</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple engage in a bitter custoday battle marred by allegations of violence and threats.</desc>
    <date>20070713</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250715233544 +0000" stop="20250716002314 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Generation Lazy!?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Moms confront freeloading children.</desc>
    <date>20111207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
