<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250706235955 +0000" stop="20250707013830 +0000">
    <title>Vengeance Valley</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A Colorado rancher contends with his two sons, one biological and the other adopted, who are fighting over control of the massive family property. Which brother will come out on top in this family battle for cash and cattle?</desc>
    <date>19510505</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yIiXDUWV2ka5116V4snpCBRsn0b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707013830 +0000" stop="20250707040000 +0000">
    <title>Sitting Bull</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A U.S. Cavalry officer begins to understand the plight of the Sioux and arranges a meeting between Chief Sitting Bull and President Grant.</desc>
    <date>19541006</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/eab893eb3f974487f6b2ad26bd500ee9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707040000 +0000" stop="20250707060000 +0000">
    <title>Christmas in the Pines</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ariel thought she bought the perfect cottage for Christmas, but, through a mix-up, two offers were accepted on the house. As she battles Mark, the other buyer, Ariel realizes she may not only have found the perfect house, but also the perfect love.</desc>
    <date>20211102</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b41729e6996cafaa9f43bed01bc0ce7d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707060000 +0000" stop="20250707070000 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Survivors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Buck continues to grieve over Ike's untimely death. Meanwhile, Cody falls for Julia, the widow of a gunrunner who has a young son named Danny. Cody helps them both adjust to life on their own.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707070000 +0000" stop="20250707072949 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>And the Devil Makes Five</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>While returning from a hunting trip, Lucas and Mark meet Marshal Micah Torrance who is escorting prisoner Scully Potter to trial. Later in camp, Lucas' life is suddenly in danger when a rattlesnake is found in his bedroll. Potter tries to escape.</desc>
    <date>19630211</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72515.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707072949 +0000" stop="20250707080000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End of the Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas wants to kill an old enemy, Reef Jackson, who is coming to North Fork. In the past, Jackson shot Lucas in the back and tried to steal his wife. Micah puts Lucas in jail to stop him from getting his revenge. Meanwhile, Mark wants to bag an elk.</desc>
    <date>19630218</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72516.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707080000 +0000" stop="20250707082945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Battle Beneath the Mountain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>For months, a thin wall of rock is all that keeps the peace between two rival silver mining companies 300 feet below the Idaho desert. When the barrier is finally breached, pickaxes give way to pistols and rifles, and the miners battle for five days.</desc>
    <date>20220901</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6477c29da2fc3fadb4c1306e/23d0b2d3-8f12-46ae-b13f-c3b169a7bbdbthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707082945 +0000" stop="20250707090000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Susie Goes Underground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After the suspicious death of a tunnel worker, and unconvincing answers from the project's lead engineer, Doc Susie goes on a covert mission to find out what happened. Deep underground, she finds her own life in peril when she's trapped by a cave-in.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/6477c327a2fc3fadb4de19df/ae03e037-8e14-49a2-b80f-56fafcb017acthumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707090000 +0000" stop="20250707100000 +0000">
    <title>Freedom on the Range</title>
    <sub-title>Freedom on the Range</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>From brave lawmen to rugged cowboys, discover the untold stories of African Americans' cultural significance in the Old West.</desc>
    <date>20240711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/23-fast-0046_ottera_deliverables_fotr_1920x1080-tt.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707100000 +0000" stop="20250707120000 +0000">
    <title>Christmas in Maple Hills</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Valerie Warrick is shocked to learn that her family's land is registered to a mysterious D Property Company. Days before Christmas, she teams with a handsome travelling doctor to unravel the mystery to her family's past and her heart's future.</desc>
    <date>20231123</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/72c156426718fe4f1967514f07f885ce.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707120000 +0000" stop="20250707133835 +0000">
    <title>Vengeance Valley</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A Colorado rancher contends with his two sons, one biological and the other adopted, who are fighting over control of the massive family property. Which brother will come out on top in this family battle for cash and cattle?</desc>
    <date>19510505</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yIiXDUWV2ka5116V4snpCBRsn0b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707133835 +0000" stop="20250707160000 +0000">
    <title>Sitting Bull</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A U.S. Cavalry officer begins to understand the plight of the Sioux and arranges a meeting between Chief Sitting Bull and President Grant.</desc>
    <date>19541006</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/eab893eb3f974487f6b2ad26bd500ee9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707160000 +0000" stop="20250707170000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <sub-title>Bulls on the Beach</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>While the cowboys are sorting the herd, Cody suffers a close call on the job that sets off a string of bad luck as he plans his annual rodeo, Bulls on the Beach. He struggles to impress a potential sponsor and the entire event is put in jeopardy when the bulls don't arrive as scheduled. Bubba heads to Mississippi to work for his father-in-law and try his hand at office life. Booger and Jaclyn enjoy learning the first dance for their wedding, but Booger finds himself awkwardly out of place as the only man at their bridal shower!</desc>
    <date>20180125</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/443b0f677c2469744d3b29db25db2767.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707170000 +0000" stop="20250707180000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <sub-title>Saddle Up or Settle Down?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba, Cody, and Booger have their work cut out for them removing a dangerous cow from a local rancher's herd. Bubba continues to shadow his father-in-law, making his first business pitch to a potential client. He begins to realize a life in Mississippi could prove to be very lucrative, but he isn't ready to hang up his spurs just yet. Misty convinces Cody to let her have his ranch horse for her new cattle business, requiring Cody and Booger to train a replacement colt for Cody. Booger and Jaclyn find wedding planning to be more troublesome than they anticipated.</desc>
    <date>20180201</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/2200d1b8e7f8b9fcf6e2e754a5ecc0b3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707180000 +0000" stop="20250707183017 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas' herd is wiped out by disease, he takes a job as an undercover agent for the U.S. government to raise money for new cattle. He travels to Wyoming to learn how renegade Cheyenne Indians are getting rifles illegally.</desc>
    <date>19610207</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72450.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707183017 +0000" stop="20250707190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas continues his investigation in Wyoming and makes contact with the local Indian agent, the source of the illegal gun-running operation. However, Lucas' life is put in danger when the town drunk reveals his true identity.</desc>
    <date>19610214</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72451.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707190000 +0000" stop="20250707210000 +0000">
    <title>County Line</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When his best friend, Sheriff Clint Thorne (Jeff Fahey, Texas Rising, Justified), is brutally gunned down, former neighboring county sheriff, Alden Rockwell (Tom Wopat, The Dukes Of Hazzard, Longmire) is left with many questions and no answers. After the investigation stalls and his replacement, Sheriff Preston (Grant Goodeve, Eight is Enough, Dynasty) turns a blind eye, Alden takes the case into his own hands. Uncovering a web of crime, deceit, and corruption that spreads through two counties, Alden is caught in a deadly criminal network with no backup, no badge, and local diner owner, Maddie (Patricia Richardson, Home Improvement, The West Wing) as his only ally. Seeking justice at any cost, Alden must find out who's behind this criminal enterprise, even if some lines must be crossed.</desc>
    <date>20170616</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/669ded19b7b7d5e81f7f6b72c99a5fc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707210000 +0000" stop="20250707230000 +0000">
    <title>The Proud Rebel</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A Confederate veteran battles prejudice and greed as he helps a woman save her ranch from a land grab, while searching for a cure for his mute son.</desc>
    <date>19580701</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/513fa20645a754aa04bbf13e4f34a9ac.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707230000 +0000" stop="20250707235647 +0000">
    <title>Buffalo Keepers</title>
    <sub-title>Buffalo Keepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Today, the buffalo is the quintessential symbol of strength, freedom, and the unspoiled American West. But in the late 1800s, the nation's buffalo were nearly wiped out by ruthless hide hunters. Those majestic herds, which once numbered in the tens of millions, were down to less than 500 animals. This is the story of the handful of determined men and women who mobilized to save the ones that were left in a last-ditch effort to stave off extinction. Ranchers like Charles and Mary Ann Goodnight rescued orphaned buffalo calves and built small herds. Former buffalo hunters like Buffalo Bill helped build public sympathy. And politicians like Theodore Roosevelt helped pass laws to protect the remaining animals. The effort would be a generational one, with buffalo herds carefully tended, bred, and passed down to new stewards when their old protectors passed away. Thanks to their efforts, there are an estimated 500,000 buffalo thundering across America's grasslands once again.</desc>
    <date>20240711</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/22-fast-1838_fcw_ottera_deliverables_june_buf-horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250707235647 +0000" stop="20250708002747 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finally captures a hawk that he has been chasing but he encounters a rattlesnake in the process. When a stranger quickly comes to his rescue, a grateful Mark invites the man to the ranch, unaware he is a fugitive on the run from the law.</desc>
    <date>19590414</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72383.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
