<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723">
    <display-name>Documentary+</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3bb2a1fe-7a16-4fa1-9db7-63b7fef3a376/documentaryplus_logo_dark_1_WHT.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704003431 +0000" stop="20250704013107 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 1- New York</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Though often overlooked, Latinos have been making contributions to the culture of NYC all along. Whether through food, dance, music or fashion, Latinos have helped make this city what it is: A cultural hub that the world looks to for inspiration. John begins his journey in Jackson Heights, Queens, the borough that shaped him as a man and as an artist, where he highlights the Latino spot that helps make every borough feel like home…the Bodega. He then meets up with DJ Tony Touch to discuss the many ways in which Latinos helped build Hip-Hop culture. Later, he visits the Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre to discuss the lack of access Latinos have to Broadway stages. He then shines a light on Luar, a fashion brand created, owned and operated by Raul Lopez, a true kid from the barrio, who unlike so many Latino designers before him is getting the recognition he deserves. John also pays tribute to salsa music and the people who keep it alive throughout the city. Lastly, John hosts one of his “Legends Dinners” with the help of Colombian chef, Stephanie Del Carmen who focuses on cooking and honoring indigenous food. Food that John, comedian Aida Rodriguez, DJ Tony Touch, Fat Joe and Broadway star Sergio Trujillo enjoy while discussing all things Latin.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/965c76c0p6z11ashduwti9kmu/original/965c76c0p6z11ashduwti9kmu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704013107 +0000" stop="20250704022711 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Episode 2.2</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s Friday morning, just after dawn in a secluded Cornish harbour and a member of public has reported seeing a tiny boat unload an unusual cargo into an awaiting Luton van.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/jr6vnlvzhylh16v6149d9al35/original/jr6vnlvzhylh16v6149d9al35.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704022711 +0000" stop="20250704032149 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 2- Miami</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John tours Miami’s historic sector, Little Havana, with community leader Marvin Tapia, and discusses the influence of the Cuban community in Miami. He then meets with the Borges family who through hard work and sacrifice have turned their dreams of owning a Cuban Coffee shop into a reality. John later meets with actor, playwright and activist Carmen Pelaez to discuss the stronghold the right wing has had on the Latino community and the future of Miami politics. John then visits the arts district of Miami which has earned that title largely due to the Latinx artists who have painted its impressive walls. He speaks with Evoca1, a muralist whose ideology has influenced him to tell complex Latinx stories through his art. Later, John meets up with singer/songwriter Elena Rose to discuss the current state of Latin music, Miami as its hub, and the future for her and other women in the industry. John also visits Peruvian chef Juan Chipoco at his flagship restaurant, Ceviche 105 to learn about his journey to becoming a mogul in the industry, by honoring the food of his homeland. Lastly, John meets up with comedian George Harris, who has built community and gives immigrants a safe place to laugh and rejoice in stories that reflect their personal experiences.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/570lljxleruu19fjda59a1yhd/original/570lljxleruu19fjda59a1yhd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704032149 +0000" stop="20250704041757 +0000">
    <title>Call The Cops: Episode 2.3</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>This is the story of two very different manhunts. One case involves a car, traveling at over 100mph which has flipped off the road and hit a tree.</desc>
    <date>20241128</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/16lyp94q84ywc1q6lfz184ow4/original/16lyp94q84ywc1q6lfz184ow4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704041757 +0000" stop="20250704051232 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 3- Washington D.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John first meets up with actor Diane Guerrero to chat about her experiences as an immigrant, author and activist over some of the best Latin food in town. He then meets up with Congressman Ritchie Torres from the Bronx to discuss the lack of Latinx representation in government and what can be done about it. John also speaks with Maria Teresa Kumar of Voto Latino to discuss the importance of voter registration within the Latinx community and how that will increase representation. And he goes canvassing to register potential voters with the help of activist and Vice President of Unidos US, Clarissa Martinez De Castro. John then takes a tour of the Smithsonian’s Latin American History exhibition with Founding Director of The National Museum of the American Latino, Jorge Zamanillo to discuss the need for a proper museum that more accurately tells the Latinx story in this country. Later, John meets up with poet/activist Quique Aviles, who has lived in D.C. since he was a child and fights against gentrification through the spoken word. Lastly, John visits the Gala Theater and the immigrant kids who find their voices and their strength through performance art.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1qyriafa984xw1s6mq7l9dlmk/original/1qyriafa984xw1s6mq7l9dlmk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704051232 +0000" stop="20250704060708 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 4- Chicago</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John meets up with renowned actor Michael Peña to learn about what it was like to grow up in the Midwest, while still attempting to retain his Mexican culture. By participating in a Peña family barbeque, John sees first-hand just how much family and friends who become family, help keep traditions alive and create safe spaces for those making a new home in a strange land. John also meets up with Congressman Chuy Garcia, who works tirelessly to bring about equity in government on behalf of the Latinx community. John then connects with Mario Hernández Jr. who shows him around the borough of Pilson, where political murals (a tradition started in Mexico) line the streets. He then talks with local artists who are passing on the tradition of political art to the community through printmaking. John has a chat with some of Chicago's queer youth activists who are actively working to provide education and a safe environment for their peers. Lastly, John gets the lowdown on Humboldt Park from community leader, Mike Oquendo. He introduces John to the Humboldt Park firemen who are entirely Latino and break all stereotypes through their community activism.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/cd8mv17tyr5m117s1pay0nwyw/original/cd8mv17tyr5m117s1pay0nwyw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704060708 +0000" stop="20250704070341 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 5- Puerto Rico</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John travels to the island of Puerto Rico to highlight the many ways in which the island and its people have influenced American culture and the ways in which America is influencing theirs. A hot topic: the issue of statehood, which John finds out, not everyone supports. John learns the deep roots of resistance that lives in the hearts and minds of the Puerto Rican people.</desc>
    <date>20250114</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7285030168667895979/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704070341 +0000" stop="20250704075816 +0000">
    <title>Leguizamo Does America: Ep. 6- Los Angeles</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John starts his trip by driving to east L.A. with native Angelino, George Lopez. While eating George’s favorite tacos, the two discuss George’s journey to becoming a star and the importance of allyship. He then shares a cup of coffee with legendary director, Robert Rodriguez who shares how he broke all the rules to forge his own path to success. John then meets up with the L.A. Opera’s new Resident Conductor, Lina Gonzalez-Granados who has broken through the fine arts glass ceiling and is making sure to bring her Latin flare to the world of Opera. John then sits down with one of the few Latina Showrunners in the television business, Gloria Calderón Kellett. They share laughs and discuss her professional journey, the lack of representation behind the camera and her continued fight to change the industry from within. John then heads to the Hollywood hills to meet up with Afro Latina, actress/producer, Gina Torres to discuss how colorism has affected her life and career. Finally, John takes some of today’s hottest Latinx powerhouses to a Michelin star Mexican restaurant in Inglewood to discuss all things Hollywouldn’t, and what needs to happen to truly address the industry’s representation problem.</desc>
    <date>20241001</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/ecrarfdewyhs1xgifuiauk8kf/original/ecrarfdewyhs1xgifuiauk8kf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704075816 +0000" stop="20250704082300 +0000">
    <title>A Swim Lesson</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A SWIM LESSON is an ode to an everyday hero: Bill Marsh, a swim teacher who helps children manage their fears and discover their own power when submerged in an overwhelming unknown.</desc>
    <date>20241228</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7278592812998081133/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704082300 +0000" stop="20250704100742 +0000">
    <title>The Hobby</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A McDonald’s Happy Meal shortage. A security guard escort. Guns pulled in a Target parking lot. All of these are caused by a common factor: trading cards. In 2020, a new BOOM began. For the first time, large hedge funds, celebrities like Logan Paul and Steve Aoki, nostalgic millennials, entrepreneurs like Josh Luber, and billionaires scrambled to add sports, Pokémon, and other hot item cards to their collections and portfolios. Over the next two years, the hobby exploded — even causing card grading services to shut down due to overwhelming customer service. This documentary is a character-driven feel good deep dive into the high-stakes, eccentric world of card collecting, following buyers, sellers, card shop owners, graders, online streamers, auctioneers, and more, who all participate in the hobby in their own unique ways. Directed by Morgan Jon Fox.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe/original/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704100742 +0000" stop="20250704112211 +0000">
    <title>Lewis Hamilton: The Winning Formula</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As the only black Formula One driver in history, Lewis' journey to becoming the most decorated Formula One driver in history, is one of dreams, courage, and determination. Directed by Piers Garland.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1/original/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704112211 +0000" stop="20250704122123 +0000">
    <title>Kobe Bryant: A Tribute</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The sudden and tragic passing of Kobe Bryant, alongside his young daughter Gianna left the world in a stunned silence. Never before has a sporting star held such high esteem outside of their profession… But Kobe Bryant was a superstar. Unmatched on the basketball court and cherished on the red carpet– Kobe’s dedication to his career, his family and his charity work led to him being adored the world over. Directed by Danielle Winter.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1hnwqz96frnvb149510harw2h/original/1hnwqz96frnvb149510harw2h.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704122123 +0000" stop="20250704132530 +0000">
    <title>The Taylor Swift Story: Dare To Dream</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The incredible journey of Taylor Swift all began with a girl, a guitar and a dream. Taylor Swift is a ten time Grammy winner, and the youngest recipient in history of the music industry’s highest honor, follow the story of an artist who turned a childhood dream into an empire. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/f8g1pm8w4tcv1ovtbgj3ztl9e/original/f8g1pm8w4tcv1ovtbgj3ztl9e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704132530 +0000" stop="20250704143532 +0000">
    <title>Beyonce: Queen B</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most recognizable figures in contemporary music. Get lost in the ultimate story of modern day superstardom as we take you through the incredible journey of Beyoncé. Directed by Billy Simpson.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1s6q5k9zm2p0z1jkxqauuehch/original/1s6q5k9zm2p0z1jkxqauuehch.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704143532 +0000" stop="20250704154715 +0000">
    <title>The Last 24 Hours: Amy Winehouse</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a very public battle with addiction the world was saddened to hear the shocking news that Amy Winehouse was found dead in her bedroom at the young age of 27. We investigate what really happened during the final 24 hours of the singer’s life, with exclusive interviews and testimonials. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240513</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1rwbqvysjtfeb1emjxae13yua/original/1rwbqvysjtfeb1emjxae13yua.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704154715 +0000" stop="20250704164015 +0000">
    <title>The Diana Story: Part I: The Young Princess</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the summer of 1980, a shy young girl arrives at Balmoral Castle. Two years later that girl became a royal princess. At just 20 years old, Lady Diana Spencer married HRH Prince Charles to become HRH Princess Of Wales. From her first steps into the royal world to the birth of her two sons and heirs, this tells the story of Diana's early years being part of the most famous family in the world. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/abovorg5cvls1sqc042hcn5t2/original/abovorg5cvls1sqc042hcn5t2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704164015 +0000" stop="20250704173315 +0000">
    <title>The Diana Story: Part II: Broken Hearts</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The marriage of Prince Charles and Princess Diana remains infamous for being one of the most turbulent royal weddings in modern history. As the cracks began to form the world watched. What should have been the fairytale couple could not hold any longer. Discover the truth of what really lead to the split, as the world behind palace gates is uncovered. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/16d6b15pdb87f14ygvjrh8fdp/original/16d6b15pdb87f14ygvjrh8fdp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704173315 +0000" stop="20250704184517 +0000">
    <title>Adele: Homecoming</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Adele is a Grammy Award-winning artist whose soulful sound has thrust her into the limelight. Her soulful voice, frank personality and chart-topping hits have made her one of the most successful artists of all time. Her authenticity in her work appeals to so many; there are no gimmicks with Adele. What you see is what you get. Through her own words, video and live performances, this documentary takes an incredible look at the life and times of one of the greatest artists of all time. Directed by Billy Simpson.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/vy7da8kxkn001b4vz74uw7dzq/original/vy7da8kxkn001b4vz74uw7dzq.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704184517 +0000" stop="20250704194550 +0000">
    <title>Meghan Markle: Changing Traditions</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>She's here, she's royal, and she's shaking things up. Meghan Markle has now become very much part of the most famous family in the world, but this strong and powerful woman is not stopping there. After a rollercoaster introduction to royal life, the now-Duchess of Sussex has made the most of her new role to spread a message of empowerment and acceptance across Great Britain and the Commonwealth. From the surprise engagement to the fairytale wedding, to starting a family and beyond, Duchess Meghan has been unstoppable. With Prince Harry by her side the pair have endured their fair share share of adoration and turmoil but they keep calm and carry on. This is Meghan's incredible journey as she redefines everything it means to be a royal. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r8oeebzqwrku1013cckjyhfj/original/1r8oeebzqwrku1013cckjyhfj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704194550 +0000" stop="20250704205558 +0000">
    <title>Taylor Swift: Superstar</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Taylor Swift completed her transition from country star to pop superstar. With exclusive interviews and footage, discover the remarkable story of the most powerful woman in Pop Music. Directed by Billy Simpson</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/13tdu4wen6u5s1sgi1gehei71/original/13tdu4wen6u5s1sgi1gehei71.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704205558 +0000" stop="20250704220146 +0000">
    <title>Selena Gomez: Devotion</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After returning from her five year break from music, Selena Gomez has blown the world away with her third studio album Rare. She has transformed over the years, from Disney pop star to award winning film and tv producer. She is one of the biggest stars in Hollywood and is certain one of the most devoted to her art. This is the life and career of Selena Gomez. Directed by Matt Salmon.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/994f38bje3u21i0sp32xebwrs/original/994f38bje3u21i0sp32xebwrs.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704220146 +0000" stop="20250704231346 +0000">
    <title>Britney Spears: Unbreakable</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Look into the glamorous and tumultuous life of pop sensation Britney Spears. From her incredible skyrocketing ascent into stardom to her personal troubles and downfalls, see the inside of the star's life with exclusive interviews. Directed by Sonia Anderson.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1gfqbszs1z1ns1hggf56nyuyr/original/1gfqbszs1z1ns1hggf56nyuyr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250704231346 +0000" stop="20250705000615 +0000">
    <title>The Barbie Story</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barbie is way more than just a 12-inches long piece of plastic, she is way more than a toy. The legendary blond bombshell has grown into a phenomenon and a children's sensation. Wildly revolutionary, Barbie broke barriers, shattered glass ceilings, and has inspired countless dreams, wonder and imagination. The history of the doll is a testament to its enduring appeal and impact. Things have changed for her the same way things changed for women. Whatever we may think about Barbie - love or loathe her - it is impossible to ignore her worldwide impact. Let's step into the beautiful world of Barbie and take a look at her cultural revolution through the decades. Directed by Roxane Schlumberger.</desc>
    <date>20241101</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/6njzqdmspnz11brw5q6s72oy7/original/6njzqdmspnz11brw5q6s72oy7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250705000615 +0000" stop="20250705005414 +0000">
    <title>Understory</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>“School of Fish” offers an intimate portrait inside one family's seasonal salmon rituals and their connection to the Bristol Bay Fly Fishing and Guide Academy, where local youth are empowered through fly fishing to serve as guides and conservationists. Can the next generation step up to defend the most prolific salmon run left on earth? Directed by Colin Arisman and Oliver Sutro</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7292680713127408031/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250705005414 +0000" stop="20250705025732 +0000">
    <title>After Antarctica</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After Antarctica follows legendary polar explorer Will Steger’s journey as an eyewitness to the greatest changes to the polar regions of our planet. Now, thirty years after his historic expedition across the coldest continent on Earth, Steger heads out on the ice once again, at a time when he is not only known for being the first in history to complete these historic feats - he is also the last. Directed by Tasha Van Zandt.</desc>
    <date>20250103</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7281052154789959068/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
