<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127">
    <display-name>Shout! TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/390674f3-43ef-4f52-95f9-0fdabd9b0269/S_TV_Logo_DARKRDX_2023__1_.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250719225959 +0000" stop="20250720010005 +0000">
    <title>City Hunter [Dubbed]</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jackie Chan stars as P.I. Ryu Saeba, who's been hired to find the runaway daughter of a publishing tycoon. Ryu's first impulse is to turn the job down…until he sees a picture of the beautiful girl, Shizuko.</desc>
    <date>19930101</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/5eb49bea-4f2e-4f6c-8fa8-ec626b6dd30d/ShoutTV_RDXVERT_-_Paige_Sherman.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720010005 +0000" stop="20250720030005 +0000">
    <title>Crime Story [Dubbed]</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jackie Chan stars in one of his grittiest roles ever as a police detective on the edge, who must race against time to solve a deadly kidnapping case. Based on the shocking true story of a billionaire abducted in a bold ambush, and filled with explosive martial-arts battles, Crime Story pulses with tension and excitement. Director Kirk Wong (The Big Hit) deftly combines acrobatic fight choreography with edge-of-your-seat action for this thrilling and dramatic tour-de-force for Jackie Chan.</desc>
    <date>19930101</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/5eb49bea-4f2e-4f6c-8fa8-ec626b6dd30d/ShoutTV_RDXVERT_-_Paige_Sherman.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720030005 +0000" stop="20250720050005 +0000">
    <title>The Protector</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Written and directed by James Glickenhaus (The Exterminator), The Protector stars Jackie Chan and Danny Aiello (Do the Right Thing) as a pair of NYPD cops sent to Hong Kong to catch a drug lord who has kidnapped the daughter of his former associate. Also starring martial-arts star Moon Lee (Angel Force) and Roy Chiao (Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom), this thriller features Hollywood-style action sprinkled with Chan's death-defying stunts.</desc>
    <date>19850615</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/34429e4bc67096dc254d3facd0becc3f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720050005 +0000" stop="20250720070005 +0000">
    <title>To Kill With Intrigue</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After the execution of his family by a gang, Lei Shao-feng is spared by its afflicting leader who stands in the way of him becoming reunited with his love, as does a traitorous friend, who takes advantage of their predicament.</desc>
    <date>19770722</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/951bf3ccb79df0cb046273dd32ce32a9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720070005 +0000" stop="20250720090005 +0000">
    <title>Karate Killer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Kiba is back again, but this time he has fallen from grace and sent to prison for all the violent acts he has committed. Once he's out, he begins working as a bodyguard in a club that is crawling with gangsters.</desc>
    <date>19731013</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/69c0797e6da6654013869dd9333c5251.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720090005 +0000" stop="20250720113005 +0000">
    <title>Samurai Reincarnation</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The villain is called Amakusa Shiro Tokaisada. He is actually based on a real christian samurai. The movie was one of the inspirations for the game called 'Samurai Shodown' (actual spelling)</desc>
    <date>19810606</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1RREOQRTYdjkzNxMv37winNPXFt.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720113005 +0000" stop="20250720140005 +0000">
    <title>Shogun's Shadow</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Iemitsu, Tokugawa Shogun III, hates his eldest son Takechiyo; all his love is given to his younger son Tokumatsu. One day, he orders Takechiyo to an initiation rite in Yedo (today's Tokio). Takechiyo lives far away under the surveillance of Hotta Masamori, head of the Skura clan, where he was also raised. Hotta does suspect some kind of treachery, but he can not ignore the direct command of the Shogun. Therefore, he starts on his travel with Takechiyo and seven accompanying samurais. A large army under the command of Iba Shoemon, a vassal of the Shogun, attacks their night camp in the vicinity of a copper mine. Hotta dies in this first battle, but Takechiyo and the samurai manage to escape. They are chased by the army, and several skirmishes between the small force and the larger army follow.</desc>
    <date>19890114</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uNjko2JANLETiXj7Q5PX2WNlfGV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720140005 +0000" stop="20250720160005 +0000">
    <title>True Legend</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <date>20100209</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/27140f6c535e648cff54bc0c2287b971.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720160005 +0000" stop="20250720180005 +0000">
    <title>Fong Sai Yuk [Subbed]</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This Hong Kong martial-arts extravaganza tells of evil emperors and true love. The secret Red Lotus Flower Society is committed to the overthrow of the evil Manchu Emperor and his minions. One of his Governors is sent on a mission to retrieve a list of members of that secret society. Meanwhile, Canton kung fu practitioner Fong Sai-Yuk falls in love with the beautiful daughter of a rich merchant, recently moved to Canton.</desc>
    <date>19930304</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pFqTVNWseJbikSGXEbIKk5ninbo.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720180005 +0000" stop="20250720200005 +0000">
    <title>Fong Sai Yuk 2 [Subbed]</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Cantonese hero Fong Sai Yuk becomes involved in the secret brotherhood "The Red Flower", who are trying to overthrow the Manchurian emperor and re-establishing the Ming dynasty. The social upheaval is combined with Sai Yuk's personal moral conflict about how to conform to the rigid regime of the brotherhood and on top of that sort out his difficult love life, saddled with two presumptive wives</desc>
    <date>19930925</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c97fdf8d86ee46990661b986ae23d7f7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720200005 +0000" stop="20250720215959 +0000">
    <title>Shaolin Wooden Men</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After witnessing the murder of his father, Little Mute trains in Shaolin Temple for revenge and is taught by various teachers, one of which is clandestine.</desc>
    <date>19761110</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0bf5072820e11b42b7a649fba0f38c89.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-60d4edd6b2fdec002c141127" start="20250720215959 +0000" stop="20250721000005 +0000">
    <title>Winners And Sinners</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Fresh from prison, five friends try to stay crime free but inadvertently find themselves caught in a Triad war.</desc>
    <date>19830707</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kpK9R3x7F4zYO9g5ZQejFQrmNki.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
