<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817">
    <display-name>Waypoint TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/waypointtv_logo_dark.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723000016 +0000" stop="20250723003015 +0000">
    <title>Dirty 30</title>
    <sub-title>"Big BASS, Big DRAMA, Big HEART: Lake Hartwell"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Folks at home, folks at home! - We’re back with another Dirty 30 — and this one takes us to the legendary Lake Hartwell, where things didn’t exactly go as planned… - This stop on the Bassmaster Elite Series pushed me to my limit. From unpredictable conditions to tough decisions and pressured fish, this one had everything. But that’s what this series is all about — showing you the real highs and lows of professional bass fishing.</desc>
    <date>20250613</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723003015 +0000" stop="20250723010015 +0000">
    <title>Fishing With Jay</title>
    <sub-title>"Shark Bite Capital of the World"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>We sent Jay to the shark bite capital OF THE WORLD, it just so happens to be in our backyard. Watch Jay get shark bit in the scariest episode yet.</desc>
    <date>20250605</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723010015 +0000" stop="20250723013004 +0000">
    <title>The Green Way Outdoors</title>
    <sub-title>"The Great Eastern Turkey"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Green meets up with his friends at the National Wild Turkey Federation to dive into turkey conservation, and hunt the largest subspecies of wild turkey. Kyle finishes off this episode with his most favorite wild game recipe, boneless wild turkey wings.</desc>
    <date>20250401</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723013004 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title>The Reel American Road Trip</title>
    <sub-title>"Fishing Cape San Blas for Reds and Trout"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Danny is joined by Ryan Sheffield for some fishing on Cape San Blas. They meet up with Mark Moore to go fishing for Reds and Trout. Later, they cook up the catch.</desc>
    <date>20250107</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723023011 +0000">
    <title>Stomping Grounds</title>
    <sub-title>"Florida' Highway on the Water"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>From country music star Brian Kelley’s big 56’ Sunny Briggs Sportfishing Yacht, to getting caught in a storm aboard a small Hurricane deck boat in the Gulf of Mexico, this episode of Stomping Grounds has host Ryan McVinney exploring boat culture in Florida’s Panhandle region, from the Emerald Coast to The Big Bend and the Forgotten Coast. Brian Kelley, aka “Beach Cowboy”, or BK for short, makes up one half of the country music group Florida Georgia Line (FGL) and has just released his own solo album Sunshine State of Mind. Kelley invites viewers aboard his vessel the “Brittney Marie” which was named after his wife, for a look at the couple’s Stomping Grounds. Songs from his album play on the boat’s sound system - including a tune about shopping for a boat on Boat Trader</desc>
    <date>20220407</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723023011 +0000" stop="20250723030002 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Exploring New York City's Hidden Culinary Gems: Cooking Goat Brains, Lobster &amp; MORE"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>New. York. City. That’s where our host Josh Rosen kicks off his journey in Episode 4—and where he lived for 16 years and started up the surf-centric apparel brand, Saturdays NYC. Back in his old stomping grounds, Josh first meets up with the award-winning chef and Mumbai native, Chintan Pandya, currently blowing up the New York food scene with his unapologetic and authentic Indian cuisine (pro tip: try the goat brains). Next, Josh travels through the boroughs, heads upstate, and along the coast to source local ingredients—from sake brewers and pig farmers to catching fresh lobster just 100 miles from Wall Street. As always the adventure will end with a feast, right back in Chintan’s kitchen.</desc>
    <date>20240604</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723030002 +0000" stop="20250723033002 +0000">
    <title>Duck Camp Dinners</title>
    <sub-title>"In a Camp Down by the River"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Duck Camp Dinners crew leaves the bayous and heads down river to Venice, Louisiana where they prepare for their first duck hunt in the delta.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723033002 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title>Goin' Coastal</title>
    <sub-title>"Family Day"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and his wife Anna celebrate the first day of summer by taking their daughters out for a fun-filled day on the water.</desc>
    <date>20250626</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723042045 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Border Bucks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Every year, hunters from across the country flock to various parts of Texas to extend their hunting season. This year, our friends from Struttinbuck did just the same. Matt and Clede make the long drive to Del Rio to hunt South Texas bucks right on the Mexico border.</desc>
    <date>20221109</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723042045 +0000" stop="20250723043616 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Once In A Lifetime"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>This week our team visits the G2 Ranch along with life time TTHA member Owen West.  Owen has been a member and volunteer for Texas Trophy Hunters for 46 years and was invited to share camp with us.  It was a hunt he never dreamed would happen in his lifetime.</desc>
    <date>20220126</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723043616 +0000" stop="20250723050019 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Run-N-Gun Adventures"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Texas Gulf Coast offers an array of opportunities to experience the outdoors. From fishing to waterfowl, we have found that every hunt gives us a chance to experience other people's stories. On this hunt, we learned not only about the incredible adventures that take place at Run-N-Gun, but also about a Texas based organization changing the lives of young people.</desc>
    <date>20211117</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723050019 +0000" stop="20250723053016 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Louisiana's Wild Food &amp; Award-Winning Cuisine | Hog Hunting, Swamp Fishing &amp; MORE"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 2: New Orleans, Josh links up with Mason Hereford (owner of award-winning sandwich shop Turkey and the Wolf) and then hits the road for some epic hog hunting, swamp fishing, crawfish and oyster harvesting, and exploring Louisiana’s only water buffalo dairy farm. It all culminates in one incredible feast featuring unique regional dishes prepared by Mason with the help of some local friends.</desc>
    <date>20240604</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723053016 +0000" stop="20250723060016 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Alaskan Fishing, Foraging, &amp; Mountainside Cooking with Local Legends"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hop in the float plane—a new episode of DIRT just dropped. The DIRT crew made their way to Alaska, “the land of earth, sea, and sky.” All feast, no sleep is the name of the game as Josh makes the most of Alaska’s abundant and legendary daylight alongside local guides, fishermen, and even a couple grizzlies. There’ll be plenty of time to hibernate in winter. But for now—join us—there are halibut to filet, rainforest ’shrooms to forage, and mountainside meals to cook up.</desc>
    <date>20240604</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723060016 +0000" stop="20250723063003 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Clowning with Peacocks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ryan Miller targets exotic fish in Lake Ida with local guide Kevin Cannon in Episode 2 of FinQuest. Catching peacock bass and clown knife fish, Ryan also enjoys family fun with a skimboarding session in Jupiter, Florida.</desc>
    <date>20241015</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723063003 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Ambers &amp; Kings"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 3 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller joins Captain Alex from Supremacy Fishing Charters for an offshore adventure targeting big fish off shore. Starting at the Palm Beach Inlet, the team uses planar fishing techniques to hook wahoo and other catches like kingfish and amberjack. Along the way, firefighter Johnny Bennett shares his journey from fishing to starting a popular fish dip business. The day wraps up with thrilling doubleheader catches and a conservation message, showcasing the importance of sustainable fishing practices.</desc>
    <date>20241125</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723073000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Snook On Board"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 4 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller explores Jupiter’s Inner Coastal Waterway, blending fishing, paddleboarding, and community engagement. With the help of Matthew from Jupiter Live Bait, Ryan showcases bait preparation techniques before catching snook in the vibrant ICW. He highlights Jupiter's community spirit by joining a local clean-up initiative with Jeremy from Blue Line Paddleboards. The episode features paddleboarding adventures with Ryan’s family, connecting with nature and marine life, and ends with a conservation message about preserving Jupiter’s pristine environment.</desc>
    <date>20241202</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723073000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Ocean Mixed Bag"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 5 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller dives into the vibrant world of offshore fishing off the coast of Palm Beach County. Joined by Cabo Mike, they showcase expert bait techniques and strategies, reeling in a variety of catches, including bonita and a stunning mahi mahi. The duo shares insights into their fishing setup, explains the use of daisy chains, and celebrates their exciting day at sea. With breathtaking views of the ocean and a colorful array of fish, Ryan’s passion for saltwater fishing shines through. The episode wraps up with a reflection on the beauty and bounty of Palm Beach County waters.</desc>
    <date>20250117</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723083001 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>“The Veteran”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Every spring brings a new opportunity to take a step forward &amp; recall the memories of seasons past. World War II Veteran and retired Judge Arden Hill has spent most of his life chasing turkeys in the hills of Tennessee. Now in his 90’s, Arden doesn’t let age stand in the way of his love for spring turkey hunting. Also: patterning turkey shotguns and hunting spring gobblers.</desc>
    <date>20240410</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723083001 +0000" stop="20250723090002 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Let’s Shoot United"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester introduces the Shoot United brand aimed at offering useful information and tips to the millions of new shooters entering the shooting sports. New York native and Midland University competitive shotgun shooter Amy Cawley and her journey as a student-athlete is followed. Also: Theo Ribbs gives shooting tips for competition and Foster Bartholow reviews Winchester AA Diamond Grade.</desc>
    <date>20240410</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723090002 +0000" stop="20250723093000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"The Rabbit Hunter"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Rodney’s relationship with his hunting dogs, passion for field-to-table living and connection to the land make his love for chasing rabbits contagious while the heritage of Winchester’s small game ammunition makes this beloved pastime accessible for generations to come. Also: a Model 42 collection for the ages and hunting Kansas coyotes with the Keefer Brothers.</desc>
    <date>20240410</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723093000 +0000" stop="20250723095959 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>“Deer Season”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Deer season — the sights, the sounds and the smells stick with you. It’s about remembering those who came before us and setting the right example for those who look up to us. It’s about protecting the tradition, so they always have something to look forward to. When communities come together, we see the real reason for this special time of year.</desc>
    <date>20240410</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723095959 +0000" stop="20250723103000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Pontoon Deck Upgrade"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team is at  - John’s lake house on Tupper Lake, NY. They are checking out some of the damage done to John’s pontoon decking from freezing weather they received. John and the team are upgrading the material, and adding carpeting to the pontoon decking. We also get some information on SPX-Johnson bilge pumps and the ease of access they provide.</desc>
    <date>20250320</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723103000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Repairing Rotten Deck &amp; Restoring Antique Outboard"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team  - highlighted deck repair and antique motor restoration, including storage solutions and structural enhancements.</desc>
    <date>20250211</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723111615 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Hunting Next To A Haunted House"+</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we take you to historic Saint Francisville, Louisiana. We closed on a couple of real estate properties in this area and want to show you why this area is so unique from a recreational standpoint. This place holds the “old south” feel that is ever so fleeting. We hunt on a property I sold to a client last year in Saint Francisville and manage to get a beautiful longbearded turkey on the ground. This episode is one you definitely don’t want to miss.</desc>
    <date>20221101</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723111615 +0000" stop="20250723113016 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Missouri Turkey Tour!!"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On this episode of Hunting Land Man, Slade, Ryan and Bearcub take on the midwest! After some tough hunting, the group is able to make a move to get in position on a BIG midwestern gobbler! Bearcub was able to harvest him after working the bird for almost 45 minutes! Slade and Ryan also do some Pre-Deer season work, and establish where the fall food-plots will be!</desc>
    <date>20250602</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723113016 +0000" stop="20250723114619 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Duck Land Man"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode Slade takes Bentley on his very first duck hunt. Slade also gets to take a trip to duck hunting paradise with some great buddies of his. This episode is all about having a great time with great friends.</desc>
    <date>20240318</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/kspeuyYO/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723114619 +0000" stop="20250723120014 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Turkeys Vs. Real Estate"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, Slade and the new producer (Tim Guidroz) go out on their first turkey hunt together, and even though the weather is not ideal, they get the job done on a Wilkinson County gobbler. We also get a look at what the United Country - Southern States Realty office looks like during turkey season, with interviews from Scott Lindsey and Caleb Armstrong, and three big properties closing in Baton Rouge.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723120014 +0000" stop="20250723123014 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Tarpon Producer"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>With Meredith McCord halfway around the world, Capt. Justin Leake gives show producer Chris Hermans his first shot at landing a tarpon after filming them for 9 seasons. Does art imitate life?</desc>
    <date>20250131</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723123014 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Billfish Tourney"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Justin Leake joins some old friends on board the Fall Line in hopes of scoring big in the Bay Point Billfish Open. This trip will test the limits of all the anglers as the skilled captain and crew do the impossible in hopes of bringing home the prize.</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723133002 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Electric Deep Drop"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Justin and Florida WaterSports pro Jeff Lange go deep off Panama City Beach to test the limits of a new battery powered reel. The results are surprising.</desc>
    <date>20250616</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723133002 +0000" stop="20250723140002 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Once Upon a Wahoo"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When tarpon don’t cooperate, it’s time for Capt. Justin and friend Ethan Register to have a competition for dinner options in the gulf’s grocery store.</desc>
    <date>20250703</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/UfzOy2Mm/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723140002 +0000" stop="20250723142959 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Nine Lives"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Will Cooper finally trades 3 years of tough times for triumph in his quest to tag an out-of-state buck with a bow.</desc>
    <date>20231031</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723142959 +0000" stop="20250723150003 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Coach"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Join Will Cooper on an unforgettable adventure in the Colorado mountains, where he dedicated three years chasing elusive bull elk without success. Determined to turn the tide, Will enlists the expertise of his good friend Jermaine Hodge, prior World Elk Calling Champion and Wrestling Coach for the United States Army World Class Athlete Program. Together, they face challenges and overcome adversity during a thrilling public land over-the-counter rifle hunt. Experience the highs and lows of their journey against the stunning backdrop of Colorado's wilderness.</desc>
    <date>20231218</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723150003 +0000" stop="20250723153000 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Prize Of The Plan"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In the wide world of western big game, pronghorn antelope hunting in Wyoming is unmatched in its accessibility and excitement. It’s an active pursuit, typically ripe with plenty of opportunities to spot and stalk black-horned bucks. This makes it an ideal forum for riflemen looking to scratch their western itch.</desc>
    <date>20231227</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723153000 +0000" stop="20250723160005 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"The Muley Freak"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After several years of shifting focus back to his native whitetails, Dahlke returns to mule deer country with the Muley Freak, Erik Van Woerkom. Follow along on this Utah mule deer hunt.</desc>
    <date>20241121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723160005 +0000" stop="20250723163001 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Doe Patrol"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, hunting season swiftly coming to an end. With - the real estate world getting busier, Slade and his family set out - to fill some tags, and fill up the freezer. It’s time to go on a Doe - Patrol!</desc>
    <date>20240301</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723163001 +0000" stop="20250723170014 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Kansas Year 15"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>We are in Kansas again chasing monster whitetails. This season makes 15 years that we have been going to Kansas and this year was special. But first we had to show you this amazing listing in South Louisiana that’s a little different for the Hunting Land Man.</desc>
    <date>20230816</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723170014 +0000" stop="20250723173000 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Thunder"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 2024 turkey season has arrived. Slade and Bentley are already off to a great start. Bentley managed to take one down opening weekend for youth hunt. And Slade took one down opening day. This episode features an inside look into Slade’s life filled with real eastate and the great outdoors.</desc>
    <date>20240327</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723173000 +0000" stop="20250723180007 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Mule Deer Dilemma"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting are taking turns filming and hunting Mule Deer in Colorado where they both harvest big mature Colorado bucks with Browning 6.8 Westerns at long range. They leave Colorado and go to Nebraska to hunt with Heritage Outfitters and double up on two great spots and stalk bucks.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723180007 +0000" stop="20250723183000 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Western Turkey Tracks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting team up with a crew from Simmons Sporting Goods and head west to chase the Wild Turkey! Good times, Good Friends and Great Hunting make for an awesome Spring hunting trip.</desc>
    <date>20250319</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723183000 +0000" stop="20250723185959 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"2 Limits Of Ducks And 2 Swamp Bucks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting work on moving a duck blind in September before duck season then hunt it later that season for a two man limit in a flooded rice field. After that hunt Kyle heads to the deer stand where he is able to catch up with a big buck a friend had missed a couple days earlier. On the way to look for the buck he shot he comes across some buzzards that lead him to a different dead buck equal in size. Two Limits of ducks and two Swamp bucks is a hard couple of hunts to top.</desc>
    <date>20250619</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723185959 +0000" stop="20250723193001 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"The Magic of Malta Part 1"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon Simmons goes to the magical Island nation of Malta to explore the secrets buried beneath the waters.</desc>
    <date>20241115</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/9UXPTzDB/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723193001 +0000" stop="20250723200005 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"The Magic of Malta Part 2"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon Simmons goes to the magical Island nation of Malta to explore the secrets buried beneath the waters.</desc>
    <date>20241115</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/6PMXFC6s/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723200005 +0000" stop="20250723203000 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Fishing with Styles"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a trip out to God's Grocery Store with country star Styles Haury as - he and Brandon look for Tuna and Snapper to bring home to the family.</desc>
    <date>20250205</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/GQUdtLVR/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723203000 +0000" stop="20250723205959 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Sailfish Time"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon Simmons is passionate about catching the mighty Sailfish, and - goes out with his tournament partner and former MLB star, Doug Mankietwicz. Doug has won a World Series and Olympic Gold medal, and now is in search of some Sails.</desc>
    <date>20250205</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/cP5RBqbA/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723205959 +0000" stop="20250723213008 +0000">
    <title>Destination Dive</title>
    <sub-title>"Dive like a Native"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, we will explore where the locals dive and experience the underwater gems where the natives love to hang out in the Florida Keys.</desc>
    <date>20250221</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723213008 +0000" stop="20250723220004 +0000">
    <title>Destination Dive</title>
    <sub-title>"Wrecks - Where Locals Love to Dive"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>We will take you to some of the wrecks in the Florida Keys that locals love to dive and share their rich history and the stories held deep aboard these sunken ships. We will also take a deep dive and discuss how these wrecks are critical to the environment.</desc>
    <date>20250221</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723220004 +0000" stop="20250723223000 +0000">
    <title>Destination Dive</title>
    <sub-title>"Volunteering to help our Oceans"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>We will follow people rethinking how they can make a difference by volunteering to help the environment in the Florida Keys. Whether you are traveling to the Keys on vacation or you live there, people are making a difference by giving back.</desc>
    <date>20250221</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723223000 +0000" stop="20250723230001 +0000">
    <title>Destination Dive</title>
    <sub-title>"Groups working to restore our vital ecosystems"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>We highlight organizations and programs making a difference in the Florida Keys. Learn how they help protect and restore these vital ecosystems.</desc>
    <date>20250221</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723230001 +0000" stop="20250723233000 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"Love Thy Neighbor"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether you're hunting 10 acres or 1,000, how you handle boundaries, buck movement, and communication with neighboring hunters can make or break your season. The team shares real-world scenarios and proven strategies to foster cooperation, avoid conflict, and build relationships that lead to better deer hunting for everyone.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250723233000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"Stages of Antler Development"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E01</episode-num>
    <desc>From fuzzy velvet to hardened bone, antlers are more than headgear—they're nature’s calendar. In this episode of Deer &amp; Deer Hunting, we explore the fascinating stages of whitetail antler development, what they reveal about a buck’s age and health, and how understanding this process can help you become a better hunter. Join us as we break down the biology, bust myths, and show real examples from the field.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250724000000 +0000" stop="20250724003000 +0000">
    <title>Spring Thunder</title>
    <sub-title>"Two First Osceolas for the Boys | South Florida At Its Finest | "</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Spring Thunder crew heads southward to Florida for round No 2. They're meeting up with good friends Chris Seaton and Chris Quarrels. Plus, Michael Pitts from Hunt Club and Drake Lamb both take their first ever Osceolas.</desc>
    <date>20210719</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
