<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703093950 +0000" stop="20250703102559 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Mooching Kyle Finally Move Out?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E318</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents get help to deal with a mooching son.</desc>
    <date>20180313</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L16318.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703102559 +0000" stop="20250703111004 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Son Believes He’s a Cyborg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E67</episode-num>
    <desc>Can Dr. Phil convince a 24 yo NYU grad that he’s not a cyborg from the future?</desc>
    <date>20200131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18067.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703111004 +0000" stop="20250703115636 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Is This Marriage Really Over?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E320</episode-num>
    <desc>From the outside, Jason and Shani had the perfect marriage " a big, beautiful house on the lake and three adorable boys " but recently Jason was crushed to learn that Shani's been having an affair with a mutual friend. Now, Shani is torn between her husband and her lover. What would you do?</desc>
    <date>20080508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6320.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703115636 +0000" stop="20250703124153 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teenage Wasteland</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E86</episode-num>
    <desc>A self destructive teen or a bad role model for a Mom? Who is telling the truth?</desc>
    <date>20130128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11086.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703124153 +0000" stop="20250703132509 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Teen Can’t Stand Her Stepfather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E104</episode-num>
    <desc>When he last appeared on Dr. Phil, Kip’s brazen and outrageous tirade toward his 17-year-old stepdaughter, Tory, shocked audience members and viewers. But the married father of two refused to back down. When Tory broke down in tears, Kip finally agreed to find a calmer way to express his frustration. Just weeks later, Tory’s mother, Vicky, says the surly relationship has not only gotten worse, the hostility has escalated, and her patience is running thin. She says both Tory and Kip refuse to seek help, and now there is a new bombshell that is making their home life virtually unbearable. What does Kip say is his biggest issue with his stepdaughter? And, will this family finally agree to accept help and repair what’s left of their relationship? Then, Joe, 34, became an instant father to two teenage daughters. One of the girls has run away, and the other feels that he treats her like a slave. Can they resolve their disputes and come together as one? (FOLLOW UP FROM 9093)</desc>
    <date>20110531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9104.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703132509 +0000" stop="20250703141245 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Brides</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E76</episode-num>
    <desc>A newlywed wife does not trust her husband plus a follow-up with popular past Shamika and Marlon.</desc>
    <date>20060116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703141245 +0000" stop="20250703145819 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Family Court Battles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E100</episode-num>
    <desc>Stalking allegations, surveillance cameras, restraining orders. This is the real-life drama of a mother and daughter who have declared war on each other! Rita claims her daughter, Lisa, is alienating her from her 13-year-old grandson, Koal, and is brainwashing him to hate her. Lisa says Rita is crazy and is using Koal as a weapon to hurt her.</desc>
    <date>20080221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703145819 +0000" stop="20250703154310 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>17 And Out Of Control</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you struggling to tame your rebellious teen? Chris and Barbara say their 17-year-old daughter, Courtney, is out of control! The teen proudly admits she bullies, steals, drinks and does drugs and is consumed with anger. Can Dr. Phil set her straight? Parents: If you know a teen who’s heading down a dangerous path, this is one show you can't afford to miss!</desc>
    <date>20120125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703154310 +0000" stop="20250703162939 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mom: Let Us Speak to Our Dying Dad!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Four adult siblings say they have been blacklisted by their mother from seeing their dying father.</desc>
    <date>20141112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13027.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703162939 +0000" stop="20250703171700 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Nasty Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Feuds between neighbors are examined.</desc>
    <date>20070919</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703171700 +0000" stop="20250703180219 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Rude Relatives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E51</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you know someone who turns your stomach or makes you cringe the minute he or she walks into the room? Dr. Phil talks to guests who say their relative's rude behavior keeps them on edge.</desc>
    <date>20061122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703180219 +0000" stop="20250703185019 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The New Generation of Moochers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Meet the "Boomerang Generation" - children who go to college and then move back in with their parents after leaving the nest, sometimes multiple times. Dr. Phil shares advice for parents and their adult children who want to end this cycle.</desc>
    <date>20051109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4032.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703185019 +0000" stop="20250703193904 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Dr. Phil &amp; Robin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>From a bride-to-be who's becoming obsessed about the wedding to a guy who says he's so good-looking that women seem to run the other way, Dr. Phil and Robin answer these guests' questions.</desc>
    <date>20041011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703193904 +0000" stop="20250703202349 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Saving Hannah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Crystan turn to Dr. Phil, desperate for help with their 14-year-old daughter, Hannah. They say their beautiful, sweet girl has turned into an angry, out-of-control teen, and they think their family is on the brink of disaster. Hannah has been caught shoplifting, accused of arson, has run away for weeks, pulled a knife on her father and threatened to have her parents killed. These frustrated parents say they’re forced to call the police for help several times a month. Hannah says her father is abusive and frequently hits her. Why does Robert say he’s had to “whoop” his daughter? Can Dr. Phil intervene before someone gets seriously hurt, and can this family heal?</desc>
    <date>20110427</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9027.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703202349 +0000" stop="20250703211131 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Troubled Teens Turnaround</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E75</episode-num>
    <desc>Why do some teens feel so hopeless that they’ll risk their lives by turning to gangs and drugs? Dr. Phil and Father Greg Boyle, executive director of Homeboy Industries and author of Tattoos on the Heart, discuss strategies to help troubled kids overcome their darkest demons. April says her 14-year- old son, Isaac, is a drug dealer, a member of the Bloods street gang and is obsessed with knives and guns. She says the teen has missed countless days of school since August, and she found a shotgun and a 9mm in his room, along with a bag of cocaine. Isaac says he joined the gang because he was bored, but now he’s in it for the money. Will the teen get a wake-up call about his dangerous behavior before he gets arrested or worse? Then, Tracie says her 3-year-old son was killed, and she was shot five times in a drive-by shooting. She says she has no gang affiliation; she was simply standing in her brother’s front yard when the neighborhood erupted in a hail of gunfire. Hear her strong message for Isaac. Plus, best-selling rapper Young Jeezy explains how he went from dealing drugs to encouraging kids to pursue their dreams.</desc>
    <date>20101215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9075.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703211131 +0000" stop="20250703215715 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teens Dividing Families</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Two families send desperate pleas asking Dr. Phil to help their teen daughters. First, Deanna and Michael say their 15-year-old daughter, Miranda, is out of control. They say they’ve discovered that she’s engaging in cybersex, sending and receiving nude photos on her phone, and has even run away four times -- once to meet up with a 29-year-old man, with whom they say she had a sexual relationship. In an effort to tame the teen, they say they've taken away her phone and iPod and revoked Internet privileges. Deanna says she even quit her job to stay home and keep tabs on Miranda, but nothing has helped. Miranda says she wants to be loved by an adult male, and if she has to have sex to feel loved, then she will. How is Michael's role in his daughter’s life influencing her decisions? Dr. Phil gives the teen's dad a wake-up call. Then, Dawn and John say that their adopted 13-year-old daughter lies, steals and shows no remorse for her actions. Among her offenses, they say she ordered 77 adult movies and was playing a sexually inappropriate game with her 7-year-old brother. In an effort to protect their other children, the couple sent her to a facility for troubled teens. John says he doesn’t want her to come home after her treatment, but Dawn disagrees, and it’s tearing their marriage apart. How can they save their daughter without destroying their marriage?</desc>
    <date>20111019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703215715 +0000" stop="20250703224455 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Stabbed In The Heart… By My Teen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Beka is a mom of three teenage girls who she says are angry, violent and out of control. She says an argument with her oldest daughter Arielle escalated to a life-threatening altercation when the 16-year-old stabbed her with a kitchen knife. Arielle was arrested and sent to juvenile detention for the incident, but is she remorseful? And are her 15-year-old identical twin sisters following in her footsteps? Beka says they are "evil" and have threatened to kill her too. But the twins tell a different story, claiming Beka is the one who is manipulative and abusive. They say she drinks excessively, has choked them and has even tried to take her own life. Can Dr. Phil get to the root of the real problem in this tumultuous household? Beka's husband, Jody, weighs in. Plus, Dr. Phil delivers a shocking message to this family in crisis -- Don't miss it.</desc>
    <date>20120307</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703224455 +0000" stop="20250703233126 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brutal Beauties (Pt.1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nicky, 17, says she loves to fight and proudly posts the videos of the brawls on the Internet. The teen brags that she once cracked a girl’s head on the concrete, has broken cheekbones and noses, and has had so many confrontations, she's lost count. She says the police have been called to her home as many as 80 times, and she’s been arrested monthly since she was 13 years old. What’s at the root of her rage? Dr. Phil delves deep into Nicky’s past to find the source of her pain. And, Nicky’s mom, Yvette, says she feels helpless and fears her daughter will end up dead or in prison, but is she modeling bad behavior? An anonymous letter to the show makes shocking allegations against Yvette. Can Dr. Phil get this family help -- before someone gets really hurt -- or worse?</desc>
    <date>20120926</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250703233126 +0000" stop="20250704001724 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brutal Beauties Pt.2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E301</episode-num>
    <desc>Levi and Bob say their once-perfect, honor roll student, Tiffani, has changed into someone they don’t know, and she is terrorizing the family. Levi says the 15-year-old is mean and evil, drinks, steals and fights with her every day. In one altercation, Levi says Tiffani spit in her face, punched her and threatened to push her off a balcony, and now she’s afraid for her life. Bob says Tiffani doesn’t respect discipline or any authority -- including the police. Tiffani has been in juvenile detention three times, and Bob says each time she's released, her behavior only escalates. Dr. Phil takes a look into their family dynamics. How might Bob and Levi be contributing to Tiffani's recklessness? Plus, hear from Tiffani. You may be surprised to hear why she says she acts out.</desc>
    <date>20120927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11301.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704001724 +0000" stop="20250704010234 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>America's Teen Mental Health Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E51</episode-num>
    <desc>The Surgeon General’s Advisory stated, before the COVID-19 pandemic, mental health challenges were the leading cause of disability and poor life outcomes in young people. The pandemic shutdown further exacerbated the mental challenges, and youth mental health is trending in the wrong direction across the country. Why is this happening? How do parents and schools play a role? Some experts believe young people were never taught how to fend for themselves because they were raised in a bubble by “concierge parents“ who protected them from learning about life and developing resiliency. Twenty-four-year-old Gracelyn says she describes her childhood just that way. She admits she was overprotected in some ways growing up, which she believes led to struggles with anxiety and depression for the past six years. What does she reveal for the first time? Also, parents of teens with mental health struggles talk about their frustrations. This is a life-saving episode you won’t want to miss.</desc>
    <date>20221122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L21051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704010234 +0000" stop="20250704014635 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Teen’s Near Fatal Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E313</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation about the rise in mental health issues among young people continues. Dr. Phil speaks with 22-year-old Emma, who says she was a cheerleader and “picture-perfect American girl” who appeared happy on the outside but was secretly struggling with severe anxiety and depression, which led her to make a near-fatal decision that changed her life forever. Ross Szabo, the wellness director at Geffen Academy at UCLA, the CEO of the Human Power Project, and co-author with Melanie Hall of Behind Happy Faces: Taking Charge of Your Mental Health, says he has ideas to implement more mental health education in schools. And, Massachusetts's Congressman Seth Moulton shares his latest project: the new 9-8-8 National Suicide Prevention Lifeline. Americans experiencing a mental health crisis or who are concerned about the mental health of a loved one are now able to dial 9-8-8 and get rapid, free, trained and confidential help from a network of 200+ local crisis centers nationwide.</desc>
    <date>20221123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L21313.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704014635 +0000" stop="20250704023501 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>That's Rude!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>From bad table manners to public spitting, Dr. Phil is determined to bring an end to the rudeness epidemic.</desc>
    <date>20031010</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L2034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704023501 +0000" stop="20250704032003 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Arrested for Keying Ex-Boyfriends Car (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Autumn claims her ex-boyfriend, D’Andre, abused her, which he denies. Why does she defend him to her parents?</desc>
    <date>20181112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704032003 +0000" stop="20250704040625 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Dad Confronts Daughter’s Abuser (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E306</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with D’Andre, who blames his abusive relationship with his ex-girlfriend, Autumn, on her upbringing.</desc>
    <date>20181113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17306.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704040625 +0000" stop="20250704045110 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Dr Phil Catfish Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E92</episode-num>
    <desc>A concerned daughter seeks Dr. Phil’s help to rescue her mother from a deceptive online relationship.</desc>
    <date>20200518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18092.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704045110 +0000" stop="20250704053655 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Catfish Inv. Pt2: Inside Lois’ Safe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E313</episode-num>
    <desc>An investigation uncovers the secrets of a woman’s mysterious safe. What hidden truths and surprises lie inside?</desc>
    <date>20200519</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18313.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704053655 +0000" stop="20250704061409 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Catfish Inv Pt3: Where’s Paul Shaw?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E314</episode-num>
    <desc>The final part of a gripping investigation to track down a woman’s elusive fiancé whom she has never met.</desc>
    <date>20200520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18314.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704061409 +0000" stop="20250704065827 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>We Survived a Cult</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E402</episode-num>
    <desc>30 years after being forced into a religious sect full of sexual abuse, some of its victims share their stories for the first time.</desc>
    <date>20201026</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19402.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704065827 +0000" stop="20250704074619 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lover, My Abuser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah is a pretty, intelligent, successful woman with everything going for her — so why won't she leave her abusive boyfriend, Robert? She says he punches her, chokes her, spits in her face, and has even threatened to kill her, but she believes he can be rehabilitated. Is she in over her head? If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic violence, don’t miss Dr. Phil's exit action plan for safely leaving an abusive partner</desc>
    <date>20120221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704074619 +0000" stop="20250704083350 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>DP Mystery: Morgan’s Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E55</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents suspect foul play in their daughter's alleged death by suicide.</desc>
    <date>20121112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704083350 +0000" stop="20250704092050 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s 1000 Lies and Counting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E115</episode-num>
    <desc>Melisa claims her estranged husband, Chris, is a pathological liar. Chris admits he has a problem and insists he wants to change -- but does he really? Should Melisa stay with him or call it quits?</desc>
    <date>20150330</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13115.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704092050 +0000" stop="20250704100753 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Slaughtered for Teen Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E77</episode-num>
    <desc>Did 21 yo Erin Caffey plot to have her family killed, or was she the victim of puppy love gone terribly wrong? In a Dr Phil Exclusive, she speaks out from prison about the brutal killing.</desc>
    <date>20140203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12077.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250704100753 +0000" stop="20250704105432 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teen Daughter Killed for Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E315</episode-num>
    <desc>What was 21 yo Erin Caffey’s role in the brutal slayings of her mother and 2 brothers?And will Erin’s father forgive his daughter after listening to Dr Phil’s exclusive prison interview?</desc>
    <date>20140204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12315.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
