<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250705223221 +0000" stop="20250706002153 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Things That Go Bump In The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Undertaker Patrick Pennyman is found dead in the village of Fletcher's Cross, in his own chapel of rest, by his wife. Barnaby and Scott start looking into a spiritualist church in the village that had been heavily controversial. Elizabeth, a friend of Joyce, who had attended their meetings, tells her that she was suspicious of both the spiritualist church and the undertaker and believed they were acquiring information and stealing from the dead.</desc>
    <date>20041010</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tY6TFJ4AV4ejYj3v08E8ths6sbG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706002153 +0000" stop="20250706020937 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dead In The Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Down at the Midsomer Regatta, the day is interrupted by the body of Guy Sweetman, Chairman of the local rowing club, resurfacing midway through a race. Barnaby and Scott learn that Guy was a ladies' man with many past conquests. He had been in secret meetings with a few other members. The two detectives uncover lies, blackmail, jealousy and a planned robbery, before the latest woman Guy was planning to marry is attacked and almost killed.</desc>
    <date>20041017</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8sAALv8ji1bvo2xxipY8MnAGI4q.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706020937 +0000" stop="20250706040109 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Orchis Fatalis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a local handyman finds a female classics teacher and a member of a group of orchid enthusiasts poisoned in her own home, DCI Barnaby finds himself heading back to Midsomer Malham, the day after he and Joyce had helped out during the village's annual garden show. It is discovered that the victim had a secret lover and had helped to smuggle a rare one-of-a-kind orchid, the Yellow Roth, out of Borneo.</desc>
    <date>20050109</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nPJV8S2WTqMjyaOgs21JL7X7aq5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706040109 +0000" stop="20250706055234 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Bantling Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A successful day at the races for the racehorse, Bantling Boy, the previous day, it is not long before one of the horses' owners is found murdered in the horses' stables. The victim, Bruce Hartley, had been in dispute with the other owners of Bantling Boy, the night before his murder had had a rather heated argument with them and had refused to let them acceptance of an offer to buy the horse. It seems to make things a whole lot worse of the others in the syndicate.</desc>
    <date>20050116</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/my5qDAUXcskpIfhUPQIfacTyLko.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706055234 +0000" stop="20250706074327 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Second Sight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John Ransom gets thrown out of the village pub in Midsomer Mere, for fighting with his brother-in-law, and a short while later he is found dead on the green. It is discovered that John had been used as a guinea pig for scientific experiments by his brother Max, who suspected he had the ability of 'Second Sight'. Barnaby and Scott soon discover that another family possesses the same talent. They have to delve deeper to unravel many secrets within the village to find the truth.</desc>
    <date>20050123</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nwxJeRBaxKCFYUoBXLBbHuC7B6A.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706074327 +0000" stop="20250706093450 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Depths</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When solicitor Nick Turner apparently commits suicide by walking off the roof of his home in Midsomer Magna, then Nick's neighbour Jack Wilmot mysteriously disappears that same day, it starts a series of unexplained events. Barnaby and Scott soon discover that a large amount of money has gone missing from the account of one of Nick's clients. Shortly afterwards, Nick's rival gets murdered in an elaborate ritual, by his own model of a medieval catapult, while his wife is forced to watch.</desc>
    <date>20050313</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7zOnVVREkoGM2RQQr441JFGKOrw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706093450 +0000" stop="20250706112847 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Sauce For The Goose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The body of a visitor is found on-site at the famous relish factory of Plummer &amp; Son in the village of Little Upton. When the detectives begin investigating the Plummer family and its staff, it turns out that the victim, Dexter Lockwood, was known to the family and had been on a guided tour of the factory the day before his body was found. It is not long before legal documents, family resentments and mysterious sightings add to the complexity of the case.</desc>
    <date>20050403</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4KKc9KhfSaDDFxQGZeTMQRgtqjg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706112847 +0000" stop="20250706131631 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Midsomer Rhapsody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Retired music teacher Arthur Leggott is murdered after disturbing an intruder at his home in Badger's Drift. It is discovered that a musical manuscript by the late composer Joan Alder has since gone missing before being sent to auction. When the manuscript shows signs that it has been written by another hand, a handwritten letter by Joan Alder turns up indicating the manuscript is a forgery. Where the manuscript goes more murders follow.</desc>
    <date>20051002</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7SgXUsAJVaJqE1uCbQ64Ghyf3PV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706131631 +0000" stop="20250706150215 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Blacktrees Prophecy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Deep in Blacktrees Forest is a bombproof shelter, at which a doomsday prepper group meets weekly.</desc>
    <date>20240414</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uSgOttgUCU326xejwt1o4tjpJ9z.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706150215 +0000" stop="20250706164626 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt Of Lies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is called in when a new arrival to a tight-knit community for retired police officers is found dead.</desc>
    <date>20240716</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7e1vYNhILjkq2GRzYGwu3oErKx6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706164626 +0000" stop="20250706183017 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Grain Of Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A trendy organic bakery in a restored mill is at the centre of a local dispute which leads to a death.</desc>
    <date>20240723</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A46qINlyqkUk0hHGNKhFArBz1DW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706183017 +0000" stop="20250706201428 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dressed To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Parish chairwoman is found dead in a local theatre, possibly because of her hostility toward a drag show.</desc>
    <date>20241110</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wzfWPAJj1DKlug0H7PQ4vinMl2j.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706201428 +0000" stop="20250706220053 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Village That Rose From The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young man is found murdered during its grand reopening, DCI Barnaby and DS Winter must unravel a sinister web of lies from both past and present in order to catch the killer.</desc>
    <date>20161218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xQEjIX0ux5AOjrMmRWJwP3eMwwH.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706220053 +0000" stop="20250706234707 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Crime And Punishment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bleakridge Watch patrols the streets of their remote village, exposing anyone who steps outside the law.</desc>
    <date>20170104</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1oLR8XAJ2drZK4VyvW1g9nb2nag.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250706234707 +0000" stop="20250707013328 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Last Man Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a star cricketer dies during a tournament, DCI Barnaby and DS Winters investigation draws them into a dangerous game with a surprise visitor from Barnabys past.</desc>
    <date>20170111</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vqicA9MVtmqSnIaHDUFBCaYh19V.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
