<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250712235915 +0000" stop="20250713003644 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>07 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>As the Alipios rejoice over Jacob's imprisonment, the latter laments on Atty. Balmaceda's incapacity to keep him out of jail. The lawyer proves otherwise by resorting to dirty means to fulfill his client's demand. The move apparently sends Sonya and Jean in utmost disbelief, who are well aware that Jacob has no power to file petition for bail. Meanwhile, Nessa's suspicions pave the way to save Domeng from danger. Elsewhere, Jean gets the chance to finally reunite with her dear Anna.</desc>
    <date>20180306</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_07_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713003644 +0000" stop="20250713010946 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>08 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob and Insp. Asuncion plot another scheme to kill Domeng. As Domeng is about to be transferred to another hospital, Dindo shockingly takes over the ambulance without anyone's knowledge. Unfortunately for the gunman, Rizalina stays alert and halts his assassination attempt. Sonya grows fearful after failing to get updates regarding her son's transport. Atty. Vega's camp finally discovers the identity of the fake nurse who tried to kill Domeng.</desc>
    <date>20180307</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_08_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713010946 +0000" stop="20250713014457 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob and Dindo clash anew after the latter failed to kill Domeng for the second time. True to Mr. Montecillo's fears, Domeng finally regains consciousness and immediately reveals the one behind the murder attempts on him and Paco. This sends his older brother fuming for revenge. While Domeng remains traumatized by what happened, Atty. Vega and Sonya prevent Paco from giving in to his rage. Elsewhere, Jean finds a way to keep an eye on her dear Anna despite their separation.</desc>
    <date>20180308</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713014457 +0000" stop="20250713022121 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In her earnest desire to save the Alipios from impending danger, Jean offers a refuge for Sonya and her sons. Though hesitant at first, Sonya deems it necessary to ensure Domeng's safety while he is still recovering. Meanwhile, Atty. Vega begins searching for evidence that might change the track of the investigation. This move makes Jacob worried. Elsewhere, Anna comes full circle as she realizes that her deep-seated feelings for Paco are still lingering in her heart.</desc>
    <date>20180309</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713022121 +0000" stop="20250713025652 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Paco chances upon a piece of evidence that confirms Sonya's innocence. Atty. Vega then exhorts her allies to devise a plan to deliver the evidence to the crime lab safely. Armed with renewed hope, Sonya resolves to ensure Domeng's safety by transferring her to Jean's house. Later, Anna catches sight of a heartbreaking scene between Paco and Georgette. This prompts Georgette to ask a tough favor from Paco's ex-girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>20180312</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713025652 +0000" stop="20250713032945 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob plots another wicked scheme, this time to stop Atty. Vega from transporting the evidence against him to the crime lab. The following day, Atty. Vega's camp departs, but not until pulling off a masterful plan that catches Jacob's gunmen off guard. Dindo and SPO3 Asuncion remain adamant to get the dirty job done. Their harmful attempts to nab the evidence are countered by a couple of tactical moves. The trickery of Atty. Vega's camp soon comes at an ally's expense.</desc>
    <date>20180313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713032945 +0000" stop="20250713040544 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Atty. Vega's camp finally lays Georgette to rest. As such, the feisty lawyer commends her fallen ally for an outstanding job in the investigation. Furthermore, Anna expresses gratitude to the late attorney for her help in seeking justice for Edward. Soon, things take a turn for the better when they receive great news about Sonya. Meanwhile, Domeng is finally showing signs of improvement in his post-traumatic condition.</desc>
    <date>20180314</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713040544 +0000" stop="20250713043535 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The court finds Sonya not guilty of murdering Edward Lamoste. Now that his mother is acquitted, Paco shifts his focus to attaining justice for his bereaved girlfriend, Georgette. While the Alipios celebrate the ruling, Jacob confronts them with another stern warning. The joke is on him, however, as his role in EduCare's downfall gets uncovered in public. This pushes him to go after the one who, he believes, is behind the exposé.</desc>
    <date>20180315</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713043535 +0000" stop="20250713070000 +0000">
    <title>Once a Princess</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Erin Almeda, a member of an all-girl clique consisting of the most glamorous and richest, plays with the innocent heart of resident class geek, Leonard Jamieson. Seven years later, they meet again, this time being Erin's turn to feel the pain.</desc>
    <date>20140806</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/gbl_onceaprincess_portrait.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713070000 +0000" stop="20250713073044 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Carlos’ happiness fades when he learns Roman granted Gabriel’s request. Meanwhile, Jay-Jay decides to run away, and Steph visits him, unknowingly revealing their location to her sister. Bianca and Isabel argue over their younger siblings. After Gabriel resolves the conflict, he invites Bianca on an outing, where she receives a long-awaited sign.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713073044 +0000" stop="20250713075943 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabriel and Bianca are officially together, but Bianca makes a request about their relationship. Meanwhile, Rigor's relentless pursuit of Victoria leads to Carlos discovering the truth about his identity. Isabel then offers Carlos a tempting deal against his rival in exchange for his love. Later, Roman finds Rigor in Victoria’s office.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713075943 +0000" stop="20250713082834 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Devastated by his discovery, Carlos vows to hide the truth and remain a dela Vega. Meanwhile, Isabel continues to pressure him about Tiger Shark’s plans for Bianca and Gabriel. Bianca struggles to tell her family about her relationship with Gabriel, while Gabriel celebrates with his family. Elsewhere, Roman grows suspicious of Rigor.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713082834 +0000" stop="20250713085733 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rigor learns about Gabriel and Bianca’s relationship and openly voices his disapproval. Victoria also tries to turn Carlos against Bianca, prompting him to question her reasons. Carlos later confronts Bianca, but someone steps in to defend her. Meanwhile, Rigor finds a reminder of his crime, and Roman uncovers his link to Victoria.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713085733 +0000" stop="20250713092508 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabriel and Bianca learn their training in Batangas falls on Lydia’s birthday. Gabriel upsets Carlos by requesting a reschedule. Meanwhile, Maila confronts Rigor over his treatment of Bianca. Hoping to ease tensions, Lydia plans to invite the Agbayanis to her birthday celebration.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713092508 +0000" stop="20250713095312 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Agbayanis convince Maila to attend Lydia’s birthday, where she’s reminded of her broken dreams. Meanwhile, Victoria receives a romantic surprise from Roman. Carlos continues striving to prove himself, and his efforts are finally recognized by his father.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713095312 +0000" stop="20250713102202 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lydia grows suspicious of Rigor after noticing Maila’s initials on the wallet he gave her. She confronts him, prompting Rigor to devise a plan to avoid exposure. Meanwhile, Victoria tells Carlos he’s finally making a good impression on Roman. Elsewhere, Steph tells Jay-Jay she wants to leave the country.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713102202 +0000" stop="20250713105112 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Maila, troubled by Rigor’s possible involvement in her assault, turns to Victoria for answers. Victoria rebukes Rigor, but he threatens her in return. Meanwhile, Bianca and Gabriel arrive at the triathlon camp. Carlos, now in control of Tiger Shark, shifts the brand’s campaign focus. Lydia grows suspicious of Rigor.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713105112 +0000" stop="20250713111908 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While Bianca and Gabriel train in Batangas, Rigor claims his son’s allowance from Tiger Shark and runs into Roman, who confronts him about his past with Victoria. Victoria later faces trouble after learning of their exchange. Meanwhile, Lydia searches for answers, and Maila confronts Rigor about her robbery.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713111908 +0000" stop="20250713115311 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassie goes out of her way to seek the answers she has long been looking for and goes to a hospital to get her birth records. Meanwhile, hoping to save face, Marga uses Cassie's absence as an opportunity to talk ill about the other Mondragon. Unaware of what is happening to his daughter, Robert decides to finally confront the man behind the mysterious letters. Carlos, on the other hand, begins to notice Daniela's unusual behavior.</desc>
    <date>20190115</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713115311 +0000" stop="20250713122753 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Unable to contain his curiosity, Carlos decides to confront his wife about her suspicious actions. However, Daniela refuses to budge and continues to feign innocence. Meanwhile, Robert pulls some strings in order to prevent Alvin from getting anywhere near his daughter. Cassie, on the other hand, becomes the laughing stock of her class due to a rumor circulating at school. An unsettling discovery prompts Romina to question her husband's intentions.</desc>
    <date>20190116</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713122753 +0000" stop="20250713130122 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Cassie fails to restrain her anger after finding out Robert’s plan to get rid of Alvin. However, her rage quickly turns into horror as she witnesses another side of her father she has never seen before. The students of Maxwell continue to ridicule the young Mondragons. Sick of all the bullying, Kristoff decides to put an end to his classmates' childish actions. Marga, on the other hand, carries on with her facade and pretends that she still has everything under control.</desc>
    <date>20190117</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713130122 +0000" stop="20250713133729 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep her dark secrets from being exposed, Daniela resolves to get rid of Alvin as soon as possible and goes out of her way to prevent Alvin from getting near her family. Cassie, on the other hand, has something different in mind and insists on inviting the janitor to her 16th birthday party. Later, Cassie and Robert try to settle their misunderstanding. Romina, meanwhile, cannot help but suspect that her husband is hiding something from her.</desc>
    <date>20190118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713133729 +0000" stop="20250713141403 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It is Cassie's long-awaited 16th birthday party, but despite everyone's excitement, she continues to spend the day with a long face. Witnessing this, Marga grows even more annoyed over how the other Mondragon keeps takinge verything for granted. Seeing that his efforts to cheer up his daughter is not effective, Robert decides to focus on securing the safety of the party's venue. However, no matter how much he tries to be cautious, danger continues to lurk around the corner.</desc>
    <date>20190121</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713141403 +0000" stop="20250713144742 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Fearing for their respective daughters' lives, Romina and Daniela both find it hard to keep calm. Robert takes matters into his own hands and carefully makes use of his resources to satisfy the kidnappers' demands. Kulas, on the other hand, disregards the possible consequences of his actions and takes one step ahead. Meanwhile, Marga attempts to get past her abductors in desperation to escape. However, this only puts her and Cassie in even more danger.</desc>
    <date>20190122</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713144742 +0000" stop="20250713152135 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kulas' careless act pisses off the kidnappers and drives them to demand more money from the Mondragons. With double the amount to gather and less time to deliver, Robert struggles to keep his composure. Cassie, on the other hand, remains brave in the face of danger. Using her wits, she creates an opportunity to outsmart and escape her abductors. However, instead of finding a way out, she receives a revelation that shakes her to the core.</desc>
    <date>20190123</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713152135 +0000" stop="20250713155559 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Unable to do anything to help save their respective daughters, Romina and Daniela can only pray. Robert refuses to adhere to the kidnappers’ demands. As he heads out to deliver the ransom money in exchange for Cassie and Marga, he discreetly conspires with his allies to plot against the criminals. However, Alvin's sudden appearance jeopardizes the success of his plans. Will the Mondragon patriarch be able to bring Cassie and Marga back to safety and come back alive?</desc>
    <date>20190124</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_19_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713155559 +0000" stop="20250713163031 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing Cassie confront Robert for the truth, Romina is left with no choice but to recount her bitter past. This deeply upsets Marga, who is being plagued by guilt after accidentally spilling the truth to Cassie. Daniela, on the other hand, begins to suspect Alvin for orchestrating the abduction. Meanwhile, Hector and Alvin continue their plan to exact revenge on Robert. Carlos also questions Daniela over the unexplained withdrawals from their bank account.</desc>
    <date>20190125</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713163031 +0000" stop="20250713170456 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniela finds herself in a bind after Carlos discovers her suspicious transactions. Afraid to be exposed, she scrambles to find a way to cover up her secrets. Meanwhile, the kidnapper's call keeps haunting Romina and triggers her most painful memories. Instead of cowering in fear, she finally decides to seek the justice she truly deserves. Cassie struggles to move on from the traumatic events that happened to her and her family as Marga continues to give her a hard time.</desc>
    <date>20190128</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713170456 +0000" stop="20250713190000 +0000">
    <title>Bekis on the Run</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A hoodlum and his gay brother rob a construction site, but when things don't go as planned, they have not choice but to go on the run.</desc>
    <date>20210917</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/bekisontherun_v.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713190000 +0000" stop="20250713193511 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>09 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob and Dindo clash anew after the latter failed to kill Domeng for the second time. True to Mr. Montecillo's fears, Domeng finally regains consciousness and immediately reveals the one behind the murder attempts on him and Paco. This sends his older brother fuming for revenge. While Domeng remains traumatized by what happened, Atty. Vega and Sonya prevent Paco from giving in to his rage. Elsewhere, Jean finds a way to keep an eye on her dear Anna despite their separation.</desc>
    <date>20180308</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_09_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713193511 +0000" stop="20250713201135 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>10 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In her earnest desire to save the Alipios from impending danger, Jean offers a refuge for Sonya and her sons. Though hesitant at first, Sonya deems it necessary to ensure Domeng's safety while he is still recovering. Meanwhile, Atty. Vega begins searching for evidence that might change the track of the investigation. This move makes Jacob worried. Elsewhere, Anna comes full circle as she realizes that her deep-seated feelings for Paco are still lingering in her heart.</desc>
    <date>20180309</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_10_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713201135 +0000" stop="20250713204706 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>11 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Paco chances upon a piece of evidence that confirms Sonya's innocence. Atty. Vega then exhorts her allies to devise a plan to deliver the evidence to the crime lab safely. Armed with renewed hope, Sonya resolves to ensure Domeng's safety by transferring her to Jean's house. Later, Anna catches sight of a heartbreaking scene between Paco and Georgette. This prompts Georgette to ask a tough favor from Paco's ex-girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>20180312</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_11_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713204706 +0000" stop="20250713211959 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>12 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob plots another wicked scheme, this time to stop Atty. Vega from transporting the evidence against him to the crime lab. The following day, Atty. Vega's camp departs, but not until pulling off a masterful plan that catches Jacob's gunmen off guard. Dindo and SPO3 Asuncion remain adamant to get the dirty job done. Their harmful attempts to nab the evidence are countered by a couple of tactical moves. The trickery of Atty. Vega's camp soon comes at an ally's expense.</desc>
    <date>20180313</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_12_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713211959 +0000" stop="20250713215558 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Atty. Vega's camp finally lays Georgette to rest. As such, the feisty lawyer commends her fallen ally for an outstanding job in the investigation. Furthermore, Anna expresses gratitude to the late attorney for her help in seeking justice for Edward. Soon, things take a turn for the better when they receive great news about Sonya. Meanwhile, Domeng is finally showing signs of improvement in his post-traumatic condition.</desc>
    <date>20180314</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713215558 +0000" stop="20250713222549 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>14 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The court finds Sonya not guilty of murdering Edward Lamoste. Now that his mother is acquitted, Paco shifts his focus to attaining justice for his bereaved girlfriend, Georgette. While the Alipios celebrate the ruling, Jacob confronts them with another stern warning. The joke is on him, however, as his role in EduCare's downfall gets uncovered in public. This pushes him to go after the one who, he believes, is behind the exposé.</desc>
    <date>20180315</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_14_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713222549 +0000" stop="20250713225953 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to clear his name from the allegations, Jacob enlists Atty. Balmaceda's help to track down his secret enemy. Perturbed by her husband's latest move, Jean relays this new information to Sonya. Unbeknownst to them, their hidden allegiance is on the verge of being discovered. Meanwhile, Anna finds herself in a life-threatening situation and Paco races against time to save her.</desc>
    <date>20180316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713225953 +0000" stop="20250713233643 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Paco falls into police hands upon accidentally ending Dindo's life. With Paco's back against the wall, a trusted ally comes to his aid. Jean, on the other hand, goes to great lengths to earn Jacob's trust. Later, her efforts pay off when Jacob lays some of his cards on the table. Meanwhile, a witness offers to testify against Jacob.</desc>
    <date>20180319</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250713233643 +0000" stop="20250714001245 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean remains committed to play mind games with Jacob despite his confession on the embezzlements within EduCare. However, she reaches her boiling point upon learning about his hideous plan against Anna. Anna, on the other hand, learns that someone has been protecting her without her knowledge. Meanwhile, Domeng insists on testifying against Jacob. Unfortunately, his post-traumatic condition hinders his request.</desc>
    <date>20180320</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250714001245 +0000" stop="20250714004553 +0000">
    <title>Magpahanggang Wakas</title>
    <sub-title>13 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While Aryann remains unconscious at the hospital, Waldo decides to cut their ties for good. Tristan finds himself in hot water as he gets blamed for the attempt on Waldo's life.</desc>
    <date>20160919</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/magpahanggang_wakas_s1_13_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
