<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707001438 +0000" stop="20250707010103 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Weight Loss Extravaganza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E82</episode-num>
    <desc>The weight is over! From abuse victim to revenge body! From sickness to six packs! From bullied teen to inspirational hero! See story after story of incredible weight loss transformations without surgery that will blow your mind! Plus, meet the biggest weight loss success story in THE DOCTORS history!</desc>
    <date>20180108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707010103 +0000" stop="20250707014633 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>TV Star's Cancer Battle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a THE DOCTORS exclusive, Growing Pains star Joanna Kerns talks for the first time about her secret breast cancer battle and the double mastectomy surgery she had one week before co-star Alan Thicke’s death! Then, our cameras go “inside the OR”’ as a young woman undergoes cervical artificial disc replacement surgery after years of chronic shoulder and neck pain! Plus, Bar Rescue star Jon Taffer returns to give us some of his grossest dirty bar and restaurant secrets! And, are you hitting a roadblock with your diet? A THE DOCTORS prescription that could help knock off those unwanted pounds.</desc>
    <date>20171005</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707014633 +0000" stop="20250707023304 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fattest Woman In The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E130</episode-num>
    <desc>She was the heaviest woman in the world, tipping the scales at over 1100 pounds … can a new bariatric surgery save her life? Then, the inspiring story of a Saved by The Bell star who started going blind at age 13 and now thinks it’s the best thing to ever happen to him! A breast cancer survivor turns to The Doctors after her reconstruction goes wrong! Can she be healed? And, one of our most infamous guests - “The Sperminator” – is back with baby news!</desc>
    <date>20170329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707023304 +0000" stop="20250707031226 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bizarre Medical Headlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E42</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS takes on bizarre medical headlines, from blowing your nose for mind-blowing sex … to the health benefits of smelling farts! Author Dr. Jeremy Howick shares his research on how you can heal your body from within without modern medicine. Comedian Ms. Pat opens up on how laughter was her prescription from selling crack … to cracking jokes! Surprising cure for Rheumatoid Arthritis that can be found in your kitchen pantry!</desc>
    <date>20181206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707031226 +0000" stop="20250707035914 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Embarrassing Body Questions Answered</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Nothing is off limits as The Doctors address your most embarrassing body problems. Learn why you get tongue-tied at the most inconvenient of times, and how to get rid of back hair. And, what your bowel movements tell you about your health.</desc>
    <date>20091119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707035914 +0000" stop="20250707044542 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Unhealthy Lady-Like Habits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E85</episode-num>
    <desc>Women are taught to always cross their legs, never pass gas in front of anyone, and many never leave the house without makeup. The Doctors reveal why these old-fashioned expectations and other lady-like habits can harm your health!</desc>
    <date>20110121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03085.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707044542 +0000" stop="20250707053245 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing's Off Limits!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E49</episode-num>
    <desc>If it oozes, aches or makes you blush, we’re talking about it today! From one woman’s excruciating pain “down there” to a pill-free fix for erectile dysfunction, The Doctors answers your most embarrassing questions! Could you leak breastmilk years after childbirth? The most embarrassing questions come out of our “Medical Confessional”! A celebrity stylist opens up about an embarrassing secret he’s kept under wraps for years! And, the athlete’s foot fix you can gargle with! Then, an unconventional way to relieve sinus pain that actually could work!</desc>
    <date>20171113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707053245 +0000" stop="20250707061938 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>600lb Health Intervention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS assembles a medical dream team to save a 600+ pound man! But first, there’s a new type of school bully with a serious health threat! THE DOCTORS takes a closer look at the wrongful death suit filed against Jim Carrey and reveals a major flaw in healthcare! Then, the hot trend in Hollywood —chlorophyll water— is it an A-List health secret or hype? And, a surprising risk to your baby and what to look for!</desc>
    <date>20161017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707061938 +0000" stop="20250707070559 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hoarder Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoarder update from social media star Glozell. Skin removal surgery shocker! Eyelid popping! Can fish oil improve your sperm count?</desc>
    <date>20200430</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707070559 +0000" stop="20250707075140 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What Every Woman is Afraid to Ask</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E42</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors answer the questions you’re too embarrassed to talk about – even with your best friend! Find out how to improve your love life, eliminate body odor and more!</desc>
    <date>20091105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707075140 +0000" stop="20250707083817 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Mistakes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>People know that smoking causes cancer and continue to puff anyway, but could you be doing something you didn’t know was bad for you? The Doctors reveals some of the health mistakes you never knew you were making.</desc>
    <date>20091002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02021.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707083817 +0000" stop="20250707092452 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Wants Biggest Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E36</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS exclusive: “Plastic surgery intervention” for a woman who has had three Brazilian butt lifts but says she won’t stop until she has the biggest butt in the world! Plus, he’s been called “the sexiest doctor in America” – Dr. Mike drops by to break hearts and give the latest update on his love life! Then, it’s a shocking viral video you have to see to believe – a 7-year-old girl whose heart beats outside of her chest due to a rare congenital condition! And, THE DOCTORS takes on the hottest viral challenge on YouTube – the spicy noodle challenge!</desc>
    <date>20180111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10036.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707092452 +0000" stop="20250707101137 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Embarrassing Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E67</episode-num>
    <desc>Answers to your most embarrassing questions. Young woman reaches out to THE DOCTORS for help with her painful skin condition. Could your clicking jaw be causing irreparable damage? Is daily nosebleed the sign of something serious? How young is too young for breast reduction? Special chair promises incontinence cure? Surprising way to prevent your baby from developing a flat head?</desc>
    <date>20190214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11067.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707101137 +0000" stop="20250707105818 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Night Health Risks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E102</episode-num>
    <desc>Bursting bladders, hacking coughs, pounding headaches -- what keeps you up at night? The Doctors put your nighttime symptoms to bed. Solve night blindness, night sweats and more. Plus, why fevers skyrocket when the sun goes down</desc>
    <date>20120223</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04102.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707105818 +0000" stop="20250707114506 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Beating Medical Odds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E75</episode-num>
    <desc>Exclusive: Watch the story of Joey, who was born without legs and abandoned by his family in Romania. The Doctors give him a life changing surprise. Then, the story of 9-year-old Briana, who must sleep under a blue light every night to stay alive.</desc>
    <date>20130225</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05075.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707114506 +0000" stop="20250707123145 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets to Transform Your Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E118</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitness expert Jillian Michaels goes toe-to-toe with Dr. Travis in The Doctors’ Brains vs. Brawn Challenge! And, surprising recipes that spice up your sex life and transform your body!</desc>
    <date>20100303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02118.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707123145 +0000" stop="20250707131817 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E114</episode-num>
    <desc>A domestic violence survivor is nominated by her daughter for the ultimate Hollywood makeover and you won’t believe the transformation! The Dahm triplets put at-home ancestry kits to the test! The results will shock you! One yogi showcases her menstrual stain to the world … is her bold decision gross or empowering? Meet the record-breaking martial artists people are calling the modern-day Bruce Lee! Score Rosie Mercado’s must-have tips for full-figure fashion! If given the choice, would you choose a million dollars or true love? Find out why seniors are having the best sex! Plus, a simple way to move forward from emotional pain … today!</desc>
    <date>20170303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09114.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707131817 +0000" stop="20250707140459 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Frustrating Body Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Plagued by persistent and frustrating body problems like dandruff, blackheads or excessive sweating? The latest installment of Ask Our Doctors shows you how to get rid of pesky ailments for good!</desc>
    <date>20090128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707140459 +0000" stop="20250707145157 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Live In The OR</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors go Live in the OR to witness a knee replacement surgery! Woman finds out if she’s been catfished! Viral TikTok star talks about her life living with alopecia! Missouri woman fights to keep pet monkeys she claims helps her with PTSD!</desc>
    <date>20191003</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707145157 +0000" stop="20250707153905 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Transplants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E59</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother hears her son’s voice for the very first time. See the cutting edge procedure that restored her hearing after 15 years of silence. Then, should your child take a break from ADHD medicines? Plus, are you overtreating your skin and hair?</desc>
    <date>20121203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707153905 +0000" stop="20250707162540 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Best Treatments From Head To Toe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E135</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share treatments from head to toe. Brooke Burke reveals how to regain your pre-pregnancy figure. And, Olympic champion Steve Holcomb shares how eye surgery helped him win gold.</desc>
    <date>20100426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707162540 +0000" stop="20250707171226 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask The Docs: Permanent Cures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Backaches, allergies and toothaches are among the most common recurring health problems. Find out how to keep your chronic medical issues from coming back, and learn to keep body odor and bad breath at bay.</desc>
    <date>20091013</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02026.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707171226 +0000" stop="20250707175928 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>50 Ways to Improve Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you want to better your health, but can’t seem to find the time? The Doctors reveal 50 ways to improve your health, and each takes just five minutes or less! And, learn simple housecleaning tips that don’t cost a dime.</desc>
    <date>20090918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707175928 +0000" stop="20250707184753 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Singer's Spine Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E58</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors Exclusive: Gloria Gaynor’s major spine surgery. Gloria and her surgeon, Dr. Hooman Melamed explains the risky procedure. Tips to protect your family this flu season! Testing new non-surgical procedure to rid you of saggy skin and those dreaded jowls. The man behind some of Hollywood’s biggest superheroes shares his top workout moves anyone can do at home. The surprising germy spots in your kitchen!</desc>
    <date>20191213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707184753 +0000" stop="20250707193442 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eat, Sleep, Poop at Every Age</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E87</episode-num>
    <desc>Eat, sleep, poop; we all do it! The Doctors answers your questions about the three most common bodily functions! Get clear on food allergy rumors, discover the risks of snoring and learn how to combat the dangers of constipation.</desc>
    <date>20110125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03087.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707193442 +0000" stop="20250707202012 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Race to Erase 10 Years Makeover!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors “Race to Erase 10 Years” on a lucky audience member! Just wait until you see The jaw-dropping results! Candle explosion: could it happen to you? People are suing The major cereal companies over “nutritious” and “wholesome” claims! Guest loses 170 pounds but it isn’t enough! Find out what still is weighing her down. The Doctors discusses a new study that claims going vegan leads to depression! Product claims to whiten teeth 6 shades lighter in just 3 days? Does it work or is it 50 shades of disappointment? We’re putting it to The test! Plus, The water bottle danger you haven’t heard!</desc>
    <date>20171012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707202012 +0000" stop="20250707210701 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Body Quirk or Something Worse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E150</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedienne Niecy Nash goes on assignment to uncover mystifying body quirks and what you can do about them. And, a new, minimally invasive procedure promises to put an end to heavy periods. Plus, common sex mistakes men make.</desc>
    <date>20090422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01150.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707210701 +0000" stop="20250707215259 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>20 Fast Fixes For Loads Of Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E148</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how maple syrup reduces the risk of cancer, the advantages of vinegar and treat five ailments for one dollar. Plus, if you think vodka is only good for making cosmos, think again! Discover the health benefits behind the bar.</desc>
    <date>20110510</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03148.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707215259 +0000" stop="20250707223948 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Uncooked Pasta Addiction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman addicted to eating uncooked pasta for 30 years writes in to THE DOCTORS to save her life! Could her obsession with macaroni noodles be cured? Then, a body builder dies … from a protein overdose? And, why the internet has everyone cringing over the callus removal videos? Plus, could the hormones in fast food be to blame for one boy’s “A” cup breast? THE DOCTORS discusses the startling links between hormones and your health. And, caught on tape: a crazy calf cramp that seems to have a mind of its own! Then, see what happens when the “Yum Yuck Crew” kids give their critiques on avocado ice cream … will they like it? And, breast surgeon Dr. Kristi Funk gives you the “Breast Case Scenario” on your most embarrassing nipple issues.</desc>
    <date>20250324</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707223948 +0000" stop="20250707232640 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. G Medical Examiner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E78</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. G: Medical Examiner says that the dead don’t keep secrets. Watch a simulated autopsy, and learn ways to keep premature death and disease from your doorstep. And, a procedure that can shrink you six sizes in less than six hours.</desc>
    <date>20090119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707232640 +0000" stop="20250708000845 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E73</episode-num>
    <desc>A celebrity hairstylist that’s groomed some of the hottest men in Hollywood changes the lives of homeless people with a haircut! The Doctors first wedding for a couple whose story went viral! What’s The Real Deal with a wearable device that relieves headaches? Does it work? Infant sleeping dangers every parent must hear! Simple trick for a perfect burger!</desc>
    <date>20181127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11073.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250708000845 +0000" stop="20250708005508 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Spray Tanned Toddlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E76</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors discusses the wackiest health headlines! Hilarious photos of toddlers in a fake tan mess and how to safely clean up a bad tan! Which state has the most psychopaths? The best beauty buys all for under $10! The Doctors diagnoses your toilet dilemmas in a segment called, “What The Flush!” Instant treatment to reverse tremors?</desc>
    <date>20190503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
