<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250716234800 +0000" stop="20250717003503 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>50 Ways to Improve Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you want to better your health, but can’t seem to find the time? The Doctors reveal 50 ways to improve your health, and each takes just five minutes or less! And, learn simple housecleaning tips that don’t cost a dime.</desc>
    <date>20090918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717003503 +0000" stop="20250717011731 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Potluck Poop Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E90</episode-num>
    <desc>Party crashed by unwelcome visitor – poop bacteria? New study may lead way to offset Alzheimer’s. Bizarre in the ER – you won’t believe what one patient got tangled up in and how another patient’s throat became rotted. Could trauma be healed through sex work? One survivor shares her story. Why woman was denied a manicure? When you’re under the knife, do you know what’s going on in the OR? The secret ingredient to take your smoothies to the next level!</desc>
    <date>20190225</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11090.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717011731 +0000" stop="20250717015548 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ladylike Habits to Stop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E44</episode-num>
    <desc>Suppressing your sneezes? Holding back your gas? Learn how ladylike manners could be hazardous to your health. Plus, shocking perfume dangers. Know the risks before you spritz! And, why your skin may be aging overnight.</desc>
    <date>20121109</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/cb7f0d6e5402209bf43c2832c8601426.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717015548 +0000" stop="20250717024342 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Gross Anatomy: Worst Body Conditions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E508</episode-num>
    <desc>Parasites, freaky feet, piercings gone wrong -- no one is immune to gross anatomy. Witness how modern medicine can solve painful and unsightly problems on a special edition of The Doctors. Relief is possible –change your life today</desc>
    <date>20111121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04508.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717024342 +0000" stop="20250717033016 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Emergency: How to Save A Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Could you save someone's life in a dire situation? The Doctors give you must have info for medical emergencies. Learn how to react if someone you love is bleeding from the mouth, nose or ears. Find out what to do when someone is having a seizure, how to decipher an allergy from anaphylactic shock and more.</desc>
    <date>20121025</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bb5e16bf5fd5a0856bde806d78aedd0e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717033016 +0000" stop="20250717041643 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Twin Sisters Get Twin Facelifts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E120</episode-num>
    <desc>We go “inside the O.R.” for an amazing update as two identical twin sisters get the “twinning” facelifts they’ve always wanted! The RefrigerDATEr’s back to help another single bachelorette find a man – by looking through the contents of his refrigerator! Is viral “60 second rule” to a clearer face legit? Is the mental workload of running a house harming moms’ health?</desc>
    <date>20190219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11120.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717041643 +0000" stop="20250717050317 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Most Embarrassing Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E166</episode-num>
    <desc>Reboot your sex drive and learn how to get more connected with your partner! And, get the skinny on going bare down there. Plus, Dr. Travis reveals the best time to have sex!</desc>
    <date>20100517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02166.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717050317 +0000" stop="20250717054934 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Biggest Makeover Show Ever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>All summer long, teams of plastic surgeons, cosmetic dentists and dozens of stylists worked around the clock. Now, The Doctors presents a makeover show so big, a call had to be made to The Guinness Book of World Records!</desc>
    <date>20090914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02016.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717054934 +0000" stop="20250717063507 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Women’s Body Complaints Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Tone, tighten and sculpt your booty with celebrity trainer David Kirsch’s signature exercises! And, how to get rid of adult acne, eliminate crow’s feet and look a size smaller in less than 60 seconds!</desc>
    <date>20091029</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02035.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717063507 +0000" stop="20250717072039 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>All Shook Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you get body tremors? Does your butt jiggle? Do you tremble when you get a high fever? Learn why your body shakes, shimmies and shivers! And, shake your way to a better physique.</desc>
    <date>20101022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717072039 +0000" stop="20250717080738 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom's Alcohol Intervention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E144</episode-num>
    <desc>A family fed up with their mother’s years of alcohol abuse turns to THE DOCTORS for help! Will she finally quit her drinking and accept that she needs to go to rehab? Then, do you believe in past lives? We meet a mom who says her son is the reincarnation of Major League Baseball player Lou Gehrig! Plus, elementary school drop-off lines are stressful, but why would a mom pull a gun on another mom? A woman disfigured by her ex when he threw acid in her face receives a life-changing facial procedure! Don’t miss her transformation!</desc>
    <date>20170522</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09144.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717080738 +0000" stop="20250717085423 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Why Do I Itch and Smell Like That?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E63</episode-num>
    <desc>Get the lowdown on bug, mosquito and spider bites, tickles in the back of your throat and more! And, why bad breath may indicate a more serious problem. Plus, see the latest at-home technology to relieve itchy skin.</desc>
    <date>20101207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717085423 +0000" stop="20250717094034 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors 911</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E122</episode-num>
    <desc>A female fan reaches out to THE DOCTORS about her addiction to exercise leading to an extreme health intervention! Then, a 64-year-old woman gives birth to twins after IVF, but should she have been able to have the babies after a previous child was taken away from her? Plus, actress Marcia Gay Harden reveals a health crisis affecting her family! And, it’s the shocking viral video you have to see to believe – sex on the freeway on the back of a motorcycle?</desc>
    <date>20170321</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09122.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717094034 +0000" stop="20250717102651 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Pooper on the Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman who poops and runs is labeled the “Mad Pooper”! Then, father tried to discipline daughter by chasing her around with a clown mask? Next, Dr. Ordon gives young girl a life changing surgery after being attacked by the family dog! How is she doing today? Don’t miss when the Yum Yuck Crew tries Keri Glassman’s healthy treats! What will they think? Then, one mom refuses to send her daughter to daycare with overweight teachers? Then, an HOA tries to ban the shed where a young girl does her breathing treatments? Do they have a case? Next, could this rash happen to your kid and how can you prevent it? Don’t miss the secret to better sex for parents!</desc>
    <date>20171218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717102651 +0000" stop="20250717111316 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Medical Survival Stories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E79</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors exclusive: After an electrical fire burned Dallas’ face, doctors said he’d never eat, walk or talk again. Today, Dallas shares his incredible story as the first American ever to receive a full face transplant. Plus, meet a 6-year-old hero.</desc>
    <date>20130114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717111316 +0000" stop="20250717115958 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Crisis Survival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E109</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you prepared for life’s imminent health obstacles? Learn to manage infertility, how to respond when someone faints and discover the silent killer that takes more lives than breast cancer and AIDS combined.</desc>
    <date>20110302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717115958 +0000" stop="20250717124502 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Manic Mom Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A stressed out mom has a “manic mom makeover!” Plus, a reality star using coffee enemas to cure his cancer? Then, a paralyzed man walks again by using his brain to move his legs! And one woman’s dramatic reveal after having life changing surgery for her scarred face.</desc>
    <date>20151019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D08033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717124502 +0000" stop="20250717133124 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eye Whitener Scars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A company is accused of pushing opioids on patients for profit! One patient shares her story, and a whistleblower speaks out! A popular TV actress gets a procedure to reverse her scarred eyes, but does it work? Then, our kid taste testers taste favorite foods made healthy! Why some doctors are treating patients with hydrogen peroxide injections! Then, a man has the world’s largest bladder stone removed! And, a secret beauty tip from Molly Sims.</desc>
    <date>20171010</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717133124 +0000" stop="20250717141641 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Surprising Health Dangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrible accidents and life-threatening conditions can happen to anyone at any time, even you! Learn how to prevent a critical head injury, E.coli poisoning, severe dehydration and more. And, spot the hazards in your home!</desc>
    <date>20101011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717141641 +0000" stop="20250717150254 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Treat It Now or Pay Later?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Actress Sally Field joins The Doctors to raise awareness about osteoporosis, a bone-thinning disease that affects four times more women than men. Learn steps to take to preserve the health of your bones.</desc>
    <date>20091109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717150254 +0000" stop="20250717154939 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Skin Infection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E101</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s The Doctors’ “What The Health” show. Can farting thwart flirting at the gym? Can shellfish cause a deadly skin infection? Once considered barbaric, why is electroshock therapy being used in treatment today? Bizarre skincare treatment reportedly used by Meghan Markle. Health risks with DIY eyebrow microblading. How to increase your strength without increasing your workouts!</desc>
    <date>20180220</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10101.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717154939 +0000" stop="20250717163729 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Habits That Harm Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E111</episode-num>
    <desc>Are your beauty habits more fashionable than rational? Discover the dangers of carrying heavy handbags, why strutting in stilettos can lead to funky feet and how applying the wrong makeup can actually magnify blemishes.</desc>
    <date>20110301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03111.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717163729 +0000" stop="20250717172427 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>140 Pound Tumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E128</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman struggles to lose weight for years, only to learn she has a 140 pound tumor! Why is a young man spending thousands of dollars to become a genderless alien? It’s snake season; hear The poisonous snake warning signs from the experts! Can The Doctors solve a guest’s medical mystery? Find out which nutrition fads are trending up or trending down! Plus, how the color of your outfit could determine the outcome of key life situations! A product promises perfect eyebrows in seconds … we’re putting it to the test!</desc>
    <date>20170503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717172427 +0000" stop="20250717181221 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Against All Odds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E111</episode-num>
    <desc>The most inspiring health stories of Season 5! Meet the “Couple of the Year” and see why people compare them to “The Notebook.” Plus, the Lifetime Achievement Award, Best Supporting Spouse, Nurse of the Year, the Viewer’s Choice Award and much more!</desc>
    <date>20130221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05111.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717181221 +0000" stop="20250717190129 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Jersey Shore Star's 6 Pack Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E308</episode-num>
    <desc>Jersey Shore star undergoes 6-pack surgery! Housewives on drug-spiked cheese? The benefits of cow cuddling? DIY facial! Are women happier with younger men? Autistic man’s amazing weight loss. New fitness trend: crawling emotional support alligator. The fruit you need to eat!</desc>
    <date>20190517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11308.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717190129 +0000" stop="20250717194933 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Become a Medical Statistic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E53</episode-num>
    <desc>Get the facts about women's heart disease with singer and philanthropist Barbra Streisand, founder of the eponymous cardiovascular research program. And, cardiologist Dr. Noel Bairey shares vital tests every woman must take.</desc>
    <date>20091116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02053.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717194933 +0000" stop="20250717203450 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Clues: Face, Fingers &amp; Toes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E100</episode-num>
    <desc>They’re the subtle symptoms only a doctor can spot – until now. From head to toe, The Doctors reveal signs, signals and prevention tips for your health. Plus, the latest on actress Demi Moore’s health crisis.</desc>
    <date>20120215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717203450 +0000" stop="20250717212142 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Strep Throat to Limb Amputation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E151</episode-num>
    <desc>In a THE DOCTORS exclusive, meet the father who had to have his hands and feet amputated after an extremely rare case of strep throat! Don’t miss the moment his family gets the surprise of a lifetime! Then, reality TV star and model Courtney Stodden reaches out to THE DOCTORS for help with depression and drugs and speaks out about her controversial marriage and rocky relationship with her mother! Plus, a doctor’s fight to save his brother’s life requires he become a donor! Then, a guest who was addicted to eating clay pots returns; has she kicked her strange habit for good?</desc>
    <date>20170518</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09151.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717212142 +0000" stop="20250717220836 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>How Can I Cure That?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E116</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share quick fixes for common body problems! Learn how to reduce hair loss, heal bruises faster and get rid of acne – even in embarrassing areas!</desc>
    <date>20100302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717220836 +0000" stop="20250717225547 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>40 Ways to Fight the Flu</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E65</episode-num>
    <desc>Runny noses, stuffy heads and aching bodies can only mean one thing: cold and flu season is in full swing. Find out 40 ways to fight the flu and outsmart a cold! Plus, the latest technology to keep your gadgets germ-free.</desc>
    <date>20101209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717225547 +0000" stop="20250717234341 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>A Purse’s Shocking Health Dangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Discover the top five dangers lurking in your purse, including a surprising PMS medicine risk. Plus, can ice cream can be addictive? And, top beauty mistakes women make when trying to avoid acne and wrinkles.</desc>
    <date>20120327</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717234341 +0000" stop="20250718002918 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Call the Docs Stat!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS tackles one of the most difficult interventions yet - a 19-year-old with anorexia and heroin and marijuana addictions. Plus, the crazy story of a married couple with two kids who woke up one early morning to a unique experience – the surprise birth of their third baby! Then, the viral video of two young women who took the “hot pepper challenge” and how it went totally wrong!</desc>
    <date>20161028</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
