<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250715234151 +0000" stop="20250716013828 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blue Herrings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice Bly arrives at Lawnside, a nursing home in Aspern Tallow to rest after having hospital treatment. She soon suspects something is not right when a fellow resident dies the night after her arrival. It is also discovered that the lady's valuable Cartier watch has also gone missing. Alice's nephew DCI Barnaby agrees to look into things despite having a week's leave. It is not long before two more deaths quickly follow the first and a mysterious visitor is seen lurking around at night.</desc>
    <date>20000122</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/M5TbKaW4qBUhZ7cYMRnxKduylz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716013828 +0000" stop="20250716033658 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Judgement Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of Midsomer Mallow are preparing for the 'Perfect English Village' competition even though a few days earlier saw the murder of local thief and lothario, Peter Drinkwater (Orlando Bloom). Barnaby and Troy discover that he had been stabbed with a pitchfork while squatting at an abandoned farm. The detectives must deduce if one of his burglary victims, his accomplice in the robberies or another disgruntled villager may have been the killer.</desc>
    <date>20000129</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ySqSxGTn2ssjtBEXWQM16WjRXR1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716033658 +0000" stop="20250716053615 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Shortly before his retirement, Superintendent Pringle arrests a local poacher for the murder of a tramp during a fox hunt in woodland close to the village of Upper Marshwood. DCI Barnaby is unsure that the poacher was the killer. Upon returning from holidaying in France, Barnaby is proved right, when the poacher's father is murdered with his own shotgun. As they reopen the investigation, they find many hidden secrets amongst the villagers.</desc>
    <date>19991231</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iu9fV001rhwyTKw0CR8DZndRWZV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716053615 +0000" stop="20250716072547 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Things That Go Bump In The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Undertaker Patrick Pennyman is found dead in the village of Fletcher's Cross, in his own chapel of rest, by his wife. Barnaby and Scott start looking into a spiritualist church in the village that had been heavily controversial. Elizabeth, a friend of Joyce, who had attended their meetings, tells her that she was suspicious of both the spiritualist church and the undertaker and believed they were acquiring information and stealing from the dead.</desc>
    <date>20041010</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tY6TFJ4AV4ejYj3v08E8ths6sbG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716072547 +0000" stop="20250716091332 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dead In The Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Down at the Midsomer Regatta, the day is interrupted by the body of Guy Sweetman, Chairman of the local rowing club, resurfacing midway through a race. Barnaby and Scott learn that Guy was a ladies' man with many past conquests. He had been in secret meetings with a few other members. The two detectives uncover lies, blackmail, jealousy and a planned robbery, before the latest woman Guy was planning to marry is attacked and almost killed.</desc>
    <date>20041017</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8sAALv8ji1bvo2xxipY8MnAGI4q.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716091332 +0000" stop="20250716110504 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Orchis Fatalis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a local handyman finds a female classics teacher and a member of a group of orchid enthusiasts poisoned in her own home, DCI Barnaby finds himself heading back to Midsomer Malham, the day after he and Joyce had helped out during the village's annual garden show. It is discovered that the victim had a secret lover and had helped to smuggle a rare one-of-a-kind orchid, the Yellow Roth, out of Borneo.</desc>
    <date>20050109</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nPJV8S2WTqMjyaOgs21JL7X7aq5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716110504 +0000" stop="20250716125629 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Bantling Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A successful day at the races for the racehorse, Bantling Boy, the previous day, it is not long before one of the horses' owners is found murdered in the horses' stables. The victim, Bruce Hartley, had been in dispute with the other owners of Bantling Boy, the night before his murder had had a rather heated argument with them and had refused to let them acceptance of an offer to buy the horse. It seems to make things a whole lot worse of the others in the syndicate.</desc>
    <date>20050116</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/my5qDAUXcskpIfhUPQIfacTyLko.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716125629 +0000" stop="20250716144722 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Second Sight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John Ransom gets thrown out of the village pub in Midsomer Mere, for fighting with his brother-in-law, and a short while later he is found dead on the green. It is discovered that John had been used as a guinea pig for scientific experiments by his brother Max, who suspected he had the ability of 'Second Sight'. Barnaby and Scott soon discover that another family possesses the same talent. They have to delve deeper to unravel many secrets within the village to find the truth.</desc>
    <date>20050123</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nwxJeRBaxKCFYUoBXLBbHuC7B6A.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716144722 +0000" stop="20250716163845 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Depths</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When solicitor Nick Turner apparently commits suicide by walking off the roof of his home in Midsomer Magna, then Nick's neighbour Jack Wilmot mysteriously disappears that same day, it starts a series of unexplained events. Barnaby and Scott soon discover that a large amount of money has gone missing from the account of one of Nick's clients. Shortly afterwards, Nick's rival gets murdered in an elaborate ritual, by his own model of a medieval catapult, while his wife is forced to watch.</desc>
    <date>20050313</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7zOnVVREkoGM2RQQr441JFGKOrw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716163845 +0000" stop="20250716183241 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Sauce For The Goose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The body of a visitor is found on-site at the famous relish factory of Plummer &amp; Son in the village of Little Upton. When the detectives begin investigating the Plummer family and its staff, it turns out that the victim, Dexter Lockwood, was known to the family and had been on a guided tour of the factory the day before his body was found. It is not long before legal documents, family resentments and mysterious sightings add to the complexity of the case.</desc>
    <date>20050403</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4KKc9KhfSaDDFxQGZeTMQRgtqjg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716183241 +0000" stop="20250716202026 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Midsomer Rhapsody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Retired music teacher Arthur Leggott is murdered after disturbing an intruder at his home in Badger's Drift. It is discovered that a musical manuscript by the late composer Joan Alder has since gone missing before being sent to auction. When the manuscript shows signs that it has been written by another hand, a handwritten letter by Joan Alder turns up indicating the manuscript is a forgery. Where the manuscript goes more murders follow.</desc>
    <date>20051002</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7SgXUsAJVaJqE1uCbQ64Ghyf3PV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716202026 +0000" stop="20250716220722 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Dogleg Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Down at the prestigious Whiteoaks Golf Club, there is much rivalry and snobbery amongst its members. When Alistair Kingslake is coerced into the thicket to look for his ball on the notorious 13th hole, known as Crisp's Folly, he soon gets bludgeoned to death. There's many suspects, from fellow members, several villagers who only have limited time on the course and the club's staff. It is not long before another member is found stabbed in woodland close to the course.</desc>
    <date>20090722</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h3gpjWH14hPYVYoMGNyFSwuV5Yk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716220722 +0000" stop="20250716235430 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When a newly discovered treasure by the 19th-century landscape artist Henry Hogson, makes an impression, it is later sold at auction for 400,000. Shortly after the previous owner of the artwork is tortured and killed. The following day another Hogson is stolen in a burglary and Barnaby finds himself having to investigate both. In order to get success, he needs to become an expert on Hogson with the help of art teacher Matilda Simms, they uncover many hidden secrets, deception and more.</desc>
    <date>20090805</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qGjxLzPUrZdk90lhTbXJyGKw0t0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716235430 +0000" stop="20250717014635 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets And Spies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Former secret agent Geoffrey Larkin arrives in the village of Midsomer Parva and heads for a visit to Allenby House, a country manor run by former spies, the Frazer family as a safe house. With an air of hostility towards Geoffrey, it is not long before he is murdered, by some who blame the 'beast of Midsomer', who believe the creature exists. Barnaby, a former spy himself, gets involved in the case.</desc>
    <date>20090729</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vHfe8ppjSF0mRgOp6qjKLy4z3Rp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
