<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716010000 +0000" stop="20250716013000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E12 - Bears Ears National Monument</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore how Native American Tribes of the past lived in the vast, desolate high desert of Utah thousands of years ago. They’ll route find their way to hidden ancient cliff dwellings deep in the canyons of Bears of Ears.</desc>
    <date>20180210</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6539827.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716013000 +0000" stop="20250716020000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E13 - Santa Fe National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton meet up with up with friend and Forest Ranger Rourke McDermott to learn the skills necessary to survive in the New Mexico desert.</desc>
    <date>20180217</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6551267.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716020000 +0000" stop="20250716023000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E14 - Florida Parks: Hurricane Recovery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head back to Biscayne National Park and the Everglades to see the effects of hurricanes on the parks ecosystems and wildlife. They also lend a hand to help with debris clean-up.</desc>
    <date>20180224</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6567212.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716023000 +0000" stop="20250716030000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E15 - Best Of Caves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Caves come in all shapes, sizes, and locations. Jack and Colton look back on their most epic cave adventures on the water, underground, and under ice.</desc>
    <date>20180303</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6583281.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716030000 +0000" stop="20250716033000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E16 - Cayman Islands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are in the Cayman Islands to swim with stingrays and scuba dive a sunken Russian Frigate called the Captain Keith Tibbets. They also caving on the Island of Cayman Brac.</desc>
    <date>20180310</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6593721.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716033000 +0000" stop="20250716040000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E17 - Jean Lafitte National Historical Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head south to New Orleans, Louisiana to travel in the footsteps of well-known pirate turned patriot Jean Lafitte. Stops include: The French Quarter, Chalmette Battlefield and boating through the bayou of this national historic park.</desc>
    <date>20180317</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6605503.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716040000 +0000" stop="20250716043000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E18 - Best of Rivers and Waterfalls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>From waterfall meditation in Japan to rafting Class V rapids in New River Gorge, Jack and Colton are looking back on waterfalls that challenged them, and rivers that earned their respect.</desc>
    <date>20180407</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6631437.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716043000 +0000" stop="20250716050000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E19 - Best of Conservation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton pitch in to protect the places we all love, and the creatures who live in them.  Included: Endangered sea turtles of Padre Island, the bats of Mammoth Cave, and sorting visitor trash in Yellowstone.</desc>
    <date>20180414</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6652264.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716050000 +0000" stop="20250716053000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E20 - Best of the Rockies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether they’re cycling up, hiking down, or canyoneering into the Rocky Mountains, Jack and Colton prove there are endless ways to explore the national parks, forests, and monuments of the Rockies.</desc>
    <date>20180421</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6652265.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716053000 +0000" stop="20250716060000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E21 - Northern California</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore Northern California. Stops include Point Reyes National Seashore, the Golden Gate Bridge, and Alcatraz Island.</desc>
    <date>20180428</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6662998.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716060000 +0000" stop="20250716063000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E22 - Grand Canyon National Park: Rim to Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>For the 100th episode of Rock the Park, Jack and Colton experience the Grand Canyon in a way less than 1% of visitors do: They’re hiking rim-to-rim.</desc>
    <date>20180505</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6676906.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716063000 +0000" stop="20250716070000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E23 - Denali: Dog Sledding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Sophia Bush joins Jack and Colton as the guys head back to Denali National Park in Alaska. This trip is going to the dogs as the three immerse themselves in all things dog mushing.</desc>
    <date>20180512</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6687286.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716070000 +0000" stop="20250716073000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E24 - Nevada: The Loneliest Road in America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are traveling the “The Loneliest Road in America” and discovering the natural history of Nevada.</desc>
    <date>20180519</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6694160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716073000 +0000" stop="20250716080000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E25 - Santa Catalina Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack explore this island paradise off California’s coast. They check out the island by bike, search for free-roaming bison that inhabit the island and attempt their first solo shore dive.</desc>
    <date>20180526</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6703098.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716080000 +0000" stop="20250716083000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E26 - Superior National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are back in their home state to experience a true Minnesota winter. Adventures include fat biking, and cross-country skiing to frozen waterfalls.</desc>
    <date>20180602</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6711304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716083000 +0000" stop="20250716100000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E01 - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>If you were tasked to race across the world with limited cash and nothing in the way of modern technology, how do you think you’d fare?  This Spring, BBC2’s Race Across the World returns, as five teams attempt just that.  This series takes viewers on the trip of a lifetime, following our contestants as they embark on an epic and adrenaline-fuelled adventure, travelling into the unknown without the trappings of modern life.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303796533459208627/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716100000 +0000" stop="20250716113000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E02 - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Five teams have been set the challenge to travel from the top to the bottom of Latin America - leaving behind smartphones, internet access and credit cards and armed with only the cash equivalent of a one-way airfare from Mexico City to Ushuaia.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303718448085622934/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716113000 +0000" stop="20250716130000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E03 - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this next leg on the race to Ushuaia, Argentina - the most Southerly city in the world- there are just four teams left to battle it out for the £20,000 prize.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303753706154528841/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716130000 +0000" stop="20250716143000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E04 - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>As the 25,000 km race to Ushuaia approaches the half-way mark, the four teams compete not just with each other, but with the extreme altitudes of Peru.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303691754044875836/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716143000 +0000" stop="20250716160000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E05 - Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The four teams have reached the half-way mark in the 25,000 km race to Ushuaia and with only 8 ½ hours between them - the race is on. To reach the next checkpoint - Cafayate in Argentina - teams must choose to travel through either Bolivia or Chile. But an unstable political climate in both countries puts everyone’s journeys at risk. And with half the race still to complete, emotions are pushed to breaking point.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303588370006604217/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716160000 +0000" stop="20250716173000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E06 - Episode 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With three teams at the checkpoint – Cafayate in Argentina - one team is yet to arrive. Dom and Lizzie are over 24 hours behind their competitors and after a disastrous last leg, they must rely on all their ingenuity to claw their way back into the race.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303698302174150414/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716173000 +0000" stop="20250716190000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E07 - Episode 7</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>With two teams at the checkpoint –Ilha Grande in Brazil – the two remaining teams are engaged in a frantic race to avoid finishing the leg in last place. Dom and Lizzie are on foot, running through the jungle whilst Jo and Sam are paddling furiously in a canoe across the bay. It’s a nail-biting ending and the siblings just manage to edge out their rivals and sign into the book.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303577303681157553/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716190000 +0000" stop="20250716203000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E08 - Episode 8</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After twenty-one thousand kilometres, two continents and seventeen countries. The teams embark on the final leg of their epic journey. However, a mammoth 4800km still stands between them and the finish line of Ushuaia, Argentina, the most southerly city in the world.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303810640975003352/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716203000 +0000" stop="20250716220000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S02 E09 - Episode 9</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Over 54 days, five pairs of ordinary Brits took on the challenge of a lifetime and attempted to travel, at ground level, the entire length of Latin America: from Mexico City to Ushuaia, Argentina, the most southerly city in the world – with no planes, no credit cards and no smartphones in sight. They came across extreme weather, states of emergency, evacuations, challenging budgets as well as life-changing encounters, incredible acts of generosity and dramatic landscapes. Most of all, they had to survive each other.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303641855111305847/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716220000 +0000" stop="20250716233000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E01 - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Our five pairs must race across the breadth of Canada, passing through seven checkpoints, taking them from the Pacific coastline, to the edges of the Arctic and the shores of the Great Lakes, to reach their final destination on the Atlantic Ocean; St. John’s on the island of Newfoundland, the most easterly town in North America. As they experience beautiful scenery, bonds will be formed across cultural divides and relationships will be tested as never before.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303659003455659614/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716233000 +0000" stop="20250717010000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E02 - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Our five teams have been set the challenge to race across the breadth of Canada, passing through seven checkpoints, taking them from the Pacific coastline, to the edges of the Arctic and the shores of the Great Lakes, to reach their final destination on the Atlantic Ocean; St. John’s on the island of Newfoundland, the most easterly town in North America. As they experience beautiful scenery, bonds will be formed across cultural divides and relationships will be tested as never before.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303763279160536391/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717023000 +0000">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <sub-title>Race Across the World S03 E03 - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>‘Race Across the World’ is back, this time on BBC One and iPlayer, as five teams attempt to race sixteen thousand kilometres through the second largest country in the world – Canada. Without smartphones, internet access and credit cards, and armed only with the cash equivalent of the airfare to fly the route, our teams travel this extraordinary journey at ground level.  Their skill, ingenuity and determination will be tested to the extreme as they race through some of the world’s most remote regions, where they must also rely on the kindness of strangers in order to stand the best chance of reaching the finish line. This series takes viewers on the trip of a lifetime, following our racers as they embark on an epic and adrenaline-fueled adventure, traveling into the unknown without the trappings of modern life.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303683693704512338/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
