<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250714233000 +0000" stop="20250715004500 +0000">
    <title>Walks of Life</title>
    <sub-title>Walks of Life S01 E05 - Kent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mehreen Baig explores the gorgeous Kent countryside as she walks in the footsteps of the county’s most famous son, Charles Dickens.</desc>
    <date>20190414</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1p8fvk8v8k5g614wft5x2hmgj/original/1p8fvk8v8k5g614wft5x2hmgj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715004500 +0000" stop="20250715020000 +0000">
    <title>Walks of Life</title>
    <sub-title>Walks of Life S01 E06 - Edinburgh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>JB Gill heads North of the Border to explore the hidden secrets that can be found amongst the familiar tourist sites of Edinburgh.</desc>
    <date>20190421</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1q46jhz035j1b1cxhlnlyrwdl/original/1q46jhz035j1b1cxhlnlyrwdl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715020000 +0000" stop="20250715031500 +0000">
    <title>Walks of Life</title>
    <sub-title>Walks of Life S01 E07 - Lichfield</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mehreen Baig is in stunning Staffordshire, walking the final section of the Two Saints Way, an ancient pilgrim trail that ends at the Shrine of St Chad near the magnificent Lichfield Cathedral.</desc>
    <date>20190505</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/31okuzspy8z81p3y3zdhrg18l/original/31okuzspy8z81p3y3zdhrg18l.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715031500 +0000" stop="20250715043000 +0000">
    <title>Walks of Life</title>
    <sub-title>Walks of Life S01 E08 - Cornwall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>JB Gill explores the beautiful county of Cornwall to find out how the dramatic landscape shapes the lives and beliefs of the people who live there.</desc>
    <date>20190512</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1l95gff514gh11s62qug3ypxr/original/1l95gff514gh11s62qug3ypxr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715043000 +0000" stop="20250715054500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa  - The Kingdom of Asante</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Asante in West Africa was a kingdom that was built on gold and slaves, which ensured its important place in an economy that linked three continents.</desc>
    <date>20100105</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/watkGlYrLMsfERoIyUxGxUzthaY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715054500 +0000" stop="20250715070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa  - The Zulu Kingdom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In South Africa, Gus Casely-Hayford visits evocative sites in Zulu history and searches for the secrets behind the Zulu's cultural power and military strength.</desc>
    <date>20100112</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/G9EBeTkyN5pENIOX8D3WY62Cn3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715070000 +0000" stop="20250715081500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa - The Berber Kingdom of Morocco</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Gus Casely-Hayford visits Morocco, once the centre of a vast kingdom created by African Berbers that stretched from northern Spain to West Africa.</desc>
    <date>20100119</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fTeCMO0QCGzNqQawtrYHtkkSsbp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715081500 +0000" stop="20250715093000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Africa - Bunyoro and Buganda</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Gus Casely-Hayford visits Uganda to explore how Bunyoro saw its dominance challenged by the rise of Buganda, a neighboring kingdom on the shores of Lake Victoria.</desc>
    <date>20100126</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/68oo8T6QiBO4m2xbHjAjkUHvCcc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715093000 +0000" stop="20250715104500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America - Kingdom of the Jaguar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Jago Cooper journeys through Southern Mexico to investigate the rise and fall of America's oldest civilization, the Olmec, who thrived over 3000 years ago.</desc>
    <date>20140915</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k2NbhPtcILo0CssDjAvw9WCvd3T.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715104500 +0000" stop="20250715120000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America - The People Who Greeted Columbus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taino, the first people of the Americas to greet Christopher Columbus, had an amazing multicultural society complete with drug infused rituals, strange skulls and amazing navigation.</desc>
    <date>20140922</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lM6jWIFVfBcGjWjQ5x2CzOkn20S.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715120000 +0000" stop="20250715131500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America - Between Oceans and Empires</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Jago explores the forgotten people of ancient Costa Rica, who built a series of spectacular settlements amongst the rivers and volcanoes of Central America.</desc>
    <date>20140929</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sbwWwcHgcq79rQHgJV8oZ0zWmQ8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715131500 +0000" stop="20250715143000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of Central America - The Place Where Time Began</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Jago Cooper explores the ancient civilization of Teotihuacan that exploded into a position of dominance in the ancient Americas almost 2000-years ago.</desc>
    <date>20141006</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oaVLFoYJBg9NXBqQUcvPpjwhZg9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715143000 +0000" stop="20250715154500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - The Stone at the Centre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Deep in the Bolivian Andes at the breathtaking height of 13000ft stands Tiwanaku, the awe inspiring ruins of a monolithic temple city.  Built by a civilisation who dominated a vast swathe of South America, it was abandoned 1000 years ago.  For centuries it has been a mystery: how did a civilisation flourish at such an altitude and why did they vanish?  Archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper journeys through Bolivia's spectacular landscape to investigate the origins of Tiwanaku and finds evidence of an ancient people with amazing understanding of their environment whose religion was based on collective effort and ritual beer drinking.</desc>
    <date>20130114</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cFGhImYsngUFg0R5gJib4Ut1aaG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715154500 +0000" stop="20250715170000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - Kingdom of the Desert, Peru</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In the spectacular deserts of coastal Peru, archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper explores the dramatic rise and fall of Chimor, the first empire of South America.  His journey begins among the ruins of a vast lost city once home to an all-powerful monarchy, whose subjects transformed the desert landscape, created gold and silver treasures, and believed so strongly in the power of their gods that they made the most shocking of sacrifices.  Chimor thrived despite facing some of the most extreme climate conditions in the world – but not even this powerful empire could withstand the forces that eventually destroyed it.</desc>
    <date>20130121</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vWvxRx1CVnazn4FDg4a9mLJ8Ybh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715170000 +0000" stop="20250715181500 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America - People of the Clouds, Peru</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper embarks on an epic journey into the remote Peruvian Andes in search of the mysterious Chachapoya people.  Once numbering half a million, they were known as 'The People of the Clouds'.  Dr Cooper reveals how they developed sophisticated methods of recording stories, traded in exotic goods found hundreds of miles from their territory, and had funeral traditions that challenge assumptions about ancient human behaviour.  His search for evidence takes him to astonishing cliff tombs untouched for 500 years, and one of the most spectacular fortresses in South America, where the fate of the Chachapoya is revealed.</desc>
    <date>20130128</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g3pvdK7NoLk5r1EtHxOu3FsZJIg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715181500 +0000" stop="20250715193000 +0000">
    <title>Lost Kingdoms of South America</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Kingdoms of South America S01 E04 - Lands of Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Through the mountains and jungles of Colombia, archaeologist Dr Jago Cooper goes in search of the truth behind one of the greatest stories ever told: the legend of El Dorado.  His journey takes him from Bogota to the Caribbean coast, through territories once dominated by two cultures, the Muisca and Tairona, who flourished for centuries before the arrival of the Spanish in the 16th century.  Dr Cooper reveals forgotten peoples who valued gold in a way the Western world still struggles to understand, travelling to an astonishing lost city and meeting the last survivors of an ancient civilisation.</desc>
    <date>20130204</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQGtqLSrbWqHjobNjowdehAfcRb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715193000 +0000" stop="20250715200000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E01 - New River Gorge National River</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton are exploring one of the oldest rivers in North America and one of the biggest bridges in the country. After that, they hit the crazy whitewater of the New River.</desc>
    <date>20171007</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6339081.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715200000 +0000" stop="20250715203000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E02 - NYC: National Parks Of New York Harbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack visit the parks of New York Harbor to learn about immigration and their own family history. Stops include Ellis Island and kayaking to the Statue of Liberty.</desc>
    <date>20171014</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6353244.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715203000 +0000" stop="20250715210000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E03 - Biscayne National Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton check out the underwater world of Biscayne and help the park fight a dangerous invasive species.</desc>
    <date>20171021</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6353245.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715210000 +0000" stop="20250715213000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E04 - Glacier: Back In Big Sky Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack are back in one of their favorite parks and bringing along their buddy, Joe Stone. Joe introduces them to a new way of biking Going-to-the-Sun Road and then it’s a trip into the backcountry to camp.</desc>
    <date>20171028</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6365385.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715213000 +0000" stop="20250715220000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E05 - Jasper National Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton travel through the heart of the Canadian Rockies while exploring the famous Icefields Parkway. Then they try a new adventure… canyoneering.</desc>
    <date>20171104</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6376210.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715220000 +0000" stop="20250715223000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E06 - Churchill, Canada</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack head north to Manitoba, Canada hoping to spot their first ever polar bear in the wild. Then After a night of camping in a historic fort on Hudson Bay, they kayak with beluga whales.</desc>
    <date>20171111</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407235.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715223000 +0000" stop="20250715230000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E07 - Coconino National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton take on a section of the Arizona Trail as they bike-pack their way through ancient lava fields in the Coconino National Forest. They’ll also explore a lava tube cave that’s hundreds of thousands of years old.</desc>
    <date>20171118</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407242.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715230000 +0000" stop="20250715233000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E08 - San Juan National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack are heading deep into the San Juan National Forest in Colorado to climb their first 14,000-foot mountain.</desc>
    <date>20171125</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6407243.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250715233000 +0000" stop="20250716000000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E09 - Katmai: Return To The Valley Of 10,000 Smokes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack and Colton return to Katmai National Park in Alaska to find one of the last remaining known volcanic steam vents in the Valley of 10,000 Smokes.</desc>
    <date>20180120</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6516886.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250716000000 +0000" stop="20250716003000 +0000">
    <title>Rock The Park</title>
    <sub-title>Rock the Park S04 E10 - White Mountain National Forest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colton and Jack set out to hike the nine peaks of the Presidential Traverse in White Mountain National Forest in New Hampshire. It’s a place known for the worst weather in the world, and this trip proves to be no exception.</desc>
    <date>20180127</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/301828/6523656.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
