<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708001149 +0000" stop="20250708020813 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Tale Of Two Hamlets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At the family home of actor Larry Smith in the village of Upper Warden, a crowd has gathered to watch the promotion for the sequel to his hit film 'The House of Satan', when Larry walks into a summerhouse house in the grounds, it suddenly explodes. His family quickly suggest that it was someone from the rival village of Lower Warden. When Larry's director; another member of his family is also murdered, electrocuted while using an exercise bike.</desc>
    <date>20030124</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5jygVAhMdKM9726eSXpEOilrAzu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708020813 +0000" stop="20250708040430 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Of Prey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the village of Midsomer Magna, the body of a man is found who had apparently drowned himself. It is discovered later that he was desperately seeking a way out of bankruptcy after visiting a local millionaire to get back his money from a scheme he had invested in. The post-mortem says that he was indeed murdered. Whilst DS Troy assists a pretty wildlife liaison officer with an investigation into the illegal sale of protected birds eggs.</desc>
    <date>20030131</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8D9yxp3s8Wfc87jz8bS06vtDrln.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708040430 +0000" stop="20250708060349 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Eleven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Fletcher's Cross are preparing for their team match against Midsomer Worthy. Tara Cavendish, the second wife of local landowner and cricket captain Robert Cavendish, has since gone missing after taking their dog for a walk. When her body is later discovered nearby in a disused quarry, with the weapon, a cricket bat lying, next to her.</desc>
    <date>19990912</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nYo00SJRLJcIgftyqkNgE3H31AT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708060349 +0000" stop="20250708080026 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blue Herrings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice Bly arrives at Lawnside, a nursing home in Aspern Tallow to rest after having hospital treatment. She soon suspects something is not right when a fellow resident dies the night after her arrival. It is also discovered that the lady's valuable Cartier watch has also gone missing. Alice's nephew DCI Barnaby agrees to look into things despite having a week's leave. It is not long before two more deaths quickly follow the first and a mysterious visitor is seen lurking around at night.</desc>
    <date>20000122</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/M5TbKaW4qBUhZ7cYMRnxKduylz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708080026 +0000" stop="20250708095856 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Judgement Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of Midsomer Mallow are preparing for the 'Perfect English Village' competition even though a few days earlier saw the murder of local thief and lothario, Peter Drinkwater (Orlando Bloom). Barnaby and Troy discover that he had been stabbed with a pitchfork while squatting at an abandoned farm. The detectives must deduce if one of his burglary victims, his accomplice in the robberies or another disgruntled villager may have been the killer.</desc>
    <date>20000129</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ySqSxGTn2ssjtBEXWQM16WjRXR1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708095856 +0000" stop="20250708115814 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Shortly before his retirement, Superintendent Pringle arrests a local poacher for the murder of a tramp during a fox hunt in woodland close to the village of Upper Marshwood. DCI Barnaby is unsure that the poacher was the killer. Upon returning from holidaying in France, Barnaby is proved right, when the poacher's father is murdered with his own shotgun. As they reopen the investigation, they find many hidden secrets amongst the villagers.</desc>
    <date>19991231</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iu9fV001rhwyTKw0CR8DZndRWZV.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708115814 +0000" stop="20250708134524 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As preparations are underway for Cully Barnaby's wedding, Ned Fitzroy and Beth Porteous are married in Bledlow village. At the gorgeous reception at Bledlow Hall, the maid of honour, Marina Fellowes, is found by a couple of guests murdered in an upstairs room. With the honeymoon postponed, the newlyweds and their guests find themselves being interrogated by the police.</desc>
    <date>20080510</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mhESsfxwBmjh8wSnmRbrLkxaK3U.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708134524 +0000" stop="20250708153237 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Shot At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When the name of Tommy Hicks, who was executed for cowardice and desertion during World War I, is added to the war memorial in Midsomer Parva, the Hicks family are very glad. The son and grandson, Lionel and Mayor Dave Hicks, revel in the occasion. The Hammond family are much more displeased. Henry, the patriarch, is infuriated by the move, having sustained a long-running feud with the Hickses.</desc>
    <date>20080101</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LCIvKnzwkQfnTrGSMResopWTGz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708153237 +0000" stop="20250708172200 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Left For Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The village of Dunstan, leads Barnaby and Jones to investigate the deaths of reclusive couple, Ron and Libby Wilson. Early on in the case, they learn that their son Michael had been killed in a hit and run. Not too far away a fiery dispute is in full swing, between a builder who has a very short fuse and a group of road protesters, protesting about plans for a bypass. With hostilities almost at breaking point, it is not long before another death rocks the village.</desc>
    <date>20080524</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fgnerGKRvOSICEtNfOhENwi8Wo7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708172200 +0000" stop="20250708191115 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Midsomer Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When the body of Charlie Finleyson is found in woodland in Midsomer Sonning. Barnaby and Jones begin to scrutinise the employees at the offices of Midsomer Life magazine. It is discovered that Mr Finleyson was married to the ex-wife of Guy Sandys, the wealthy owner of the magazine. The detectives also become aware of a dispute between Guy and the owner of the Morecroft Hotel. With tensions starting to rise between the locals and visitors from London.</desc>
    <date>20080531</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ew618rTr6XYkfDrhg4R3RFn9UCG.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708191115 +0000" stop="20250708205835 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Magician's Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>During a children's magic show, a performer assisting with a trick, is poisoned whilst on stage. It is found that the poison came from a species of Ecuadorean frog. Barnaby and Jones discover that conflict is once again brewing between a village occult guide and enthusiast Ernest Baillol and famous writer Aloysius Wilmington who are both searching for a treasured antique book on the subject.</desc>
    <date>20080614</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mO3WpqHBKIJwgwjjJKzTmVp1PrB.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708205835 +0000" stop="20250708224549 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Days Of Misrule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A team building exercise is imminent planned by a new acting Chief Superintendent John Cotton and Barnaby and Jones are very reluctant to take part. Following an explosion in a truck at a haulage yard, both the detectives see the opportunity as a distraction to investigate. It is not long after that a body is discovered, when a trunk resurfaces from the nearby lake. It is identified as Alec Grainger, a man who had been arguing with James Parkes, the son of Colonel Matt Parkes.</desc>
    <date>20080705</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dAw5JF8lyYPZ5kSBHUJBRXeBBlQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250708224549 +0000" stop="20250709003503 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Talking To The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In the village of Monks Barton, two couples seemingly disappear from their cottages. When Barnaby and Jones arrive and learn of the legendary, mysterious haunted woods, they remain sceptical. Shortly after a body is found in a shallow grave, answering to the description of one of the 'missing'. The detectives have to delve much deeper into the woods and beyond to find out if ghosts are really to blame or something else.</desc>
    <date>20080805</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/juPnY9Mf7cU9WIes42qLd92iQY6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250709003503 +0000" stop="20250709023351 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Green Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>During a canal restoration project near Midsomer Worthy, on which Joyce is working as a volunteer, several skeletons are discovered shortly after a tunnel collapse. DCI Barnaby begins his investigations when it is found that one skeleton had modern dental work. Meanwhile, DS Troy, having been promoted to Inspector has his last case in Midsomer, to look into the murder of a youth, Simon Mayfield (Henry Cavill), who had caused problems for many in the village.</desc>
    <date>20031102</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nhfabQSsoGFCTT09gx1rzwm8Vq7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
