<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250717234341 +0000" stop="20250718002918 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Call the Docs Stat!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS tackles one of the most difficult interventions yet - a 19-year-old with anorexia and heroin and marijuana addictions. Plus, the crazy story of a married couple with two kids who woke up one early morning to a unique experience – the surprise birth of their third baby! Then, the viral video of two young women who took the “hot pepper challenge” and how it went totally wrong!</desc>
    <date>20161028</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718002918 +0000" stop="20250718011608 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Body Quirk or Something Worse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E150</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedienne Niecy Nash goes on assignment to uncover mystifying body quirks and what you can do about them. And, a new, minimally invasive procedure promises to put an end to heavy periods. Plus, common sex mistakes men make.</desc>
    <date>20090422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01150.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718011608 +0000" stop="20250718020151 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Docs: Hot and Cold Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E81</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors reveals the best hot and cold remedies for ailments. And, surprising ways the weather can sabotage your health. From winter storm warnings to heat waves, learn how to keep your family safe.</desc>
    <date>20100112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02081.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718020151 +0000" stop="20250718024946 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Decapitated and Survived!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E114</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, meet a woman who was internally decapitated and survived. Plus, positions to help blood pressure, migraines and cramps. And, how to determine your baby’s sex, erase varicose veins and more!</desc>
    <date>20120229</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04114.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718024946 +0000" stop="20250718033640 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>My Breast Implants Made Me Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E136</episode-num>
    <desc>In an exclusive interview, a former Playboy Playmate claims her implants made her sick and says she’s not the only one! Derek Hough reveals how he stays fit and gives the inside scoop on his new show! Find out why some parents are potty training their kids … in public! A young man with a family history of early-onset Alzheimer’s turns to The Doctors! What will be revealed? Get the warning signs you need to know! Plus, a hoarder finally finds freedom … how did she do it?</desc>
    <date>20170412</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09136.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718033640 +0000" stop="20250718042317 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>My Mom Made Me Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E41</episode-num>
    <desc>I am a Munchausen by Proxy victim! Woman breaks her silence on medical abuse after several medical records and Doctors suggest her own mother intentionally kept her sick! Could the allegations be true? Win big prizes with The Word of The Day Giveaway!</desc>
    <date>20191031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12041.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718042317 +0000" stop="20250718050940 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Pimples to Pop? And "Scromiting"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E88</episode-num>
    <desc>A person posts a Craigslist ad looking for pimples to pop! Then, mysterious “scromiting” condition hits marijuana smokers! What is causing this? Next, a viral video shows The dramatic effects of post-partum hair loss! And, Facebook messenger for kids? Also, Viral Beauty Trends: are these up-and-coming trends healthy? An Arkansas mom introduces her child to life of crime! We have the shocking video! Mother accused of medical abuse? Don’t miss this shocking story! Man gets lip fungus from woodworking blade? Don’t miss the shocking way Gabrielle Union tried to cure a yeast infection!</desc>
    <date>20180122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718050940 +0000" stop="20250718055633 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Shot in the Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E125</episode-num>
    <desc>A daughter puts herself in the line of fire to save her father’s life. Hear her remarkable story! An accident leaves a young woman paralyzed but she turns tragedy into triumph becoming a popular beauty vlogger! Watch as she meets the person who saved her life! Parents are outraged as a drama teacher gives an assignment on how to make and inject crystal meth! An aspiring politician publishes his own sexual history online; is he a refreshing dose of honesty? For $25,000, a DNA screening and tests could predict your future health? Plus, THE DOCTORS tries the hottest new cocktail trend … fat flavored cocktails! See the father-daughter pep talk that has gone viral for all the right reasons! The simple trick to clean stained coffee mugs!</desc>
    <date>20170307</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09125.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718055633 +0000" stop="20250718064412 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The United States of Addiction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E45</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors highlights the other side of addiction: recovery. Witness the powerful life transformation of a man who lost his legs to heroin. Then, can a breakthrough brain treatment for pain and addiction offer hope to so many sufferers? Then, The Doctors investigates drug addicted healthcare workers who put the patients they are treating at risk. Hear a harrowing story of a mother who contracted a deadly disease at the hands of a drug-addicted hospital worker. Plus, find out how you can protect yourself from becoming a victim of a medical mistake at the hands of a drug-addicted provider. And, learn the key to harnessing hope when things feel hopeless.</desc>
    <date>20171121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718064412 +0000" stop="20250718072301 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Amputates Leg to Save Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E84</episode-num>
    <desc>Inspiring story of a mom who decided to amputate her leg after a motorcycle crash to save her unborn baby. #DropTheSugar Dollar Store challenge proves you can eat healthy on a budget! Hundreds of women getting scammed with pregnancy congratulations cards? CBD vending machines coming to a convenience store near you!</desc>
    <date>20200511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12084.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718072301 +0000" stop="20250718080855 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask The Doctors: Sex &amp; Menopause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E125</episode-num>
    <desc>Ask The Doctors: can sex help menopause! Dr. Batra’s fix for greasy hair. Is it safe to dye a young child’s hair? Safe ways to break up dog fights. Is it safe to smoke pot while dealing with depression? Dr. Travis’ favorite exercises to prevent slouching. The Bachelor's Dr. Chris Strandburg reveals his top 3 tips to stop teeth grinding! Can sleep apps actually diagnose sleep apnea?</desc>
    <date>20180501</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10125.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718080855 +0000" stop="20250718085524 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Drs Set The Record Straight!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E76</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors debunk common health myths. Do dairy products really produce mucus? And how often should you really have a bowel movement? Plus, what actress Anne Heche wants you to know about sun protection. And, how robots are assisting weight loss.</desc>
    <date>20130102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05076.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718085524 +0000" stop="20250718094140 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Sex, Drugs &amp; Rock N Roll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E62</episode-num>
    <desc>Live fast, die young, party all night – rock and roll’s infamous lifestyle is in the spotlight. Learn how to stay safe while you have fun! Plus, the daughter of shock rocker Alice Cooper shares stories from life on the road.</desc>
    <date>20101206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718094140 +0000" stop="20250718102700 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>How to Get it Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Whether it’s a tick, a cyst, phlegm or dirt, or if you’ve got something stuck in your eye or ear, get tips to get it out! Plus, are you ready to give birth? Get the safest ways to speed up labor and delivery.</desc>
    <date>20101110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718102700 +0000" stop="20250718111423 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hottest Plastic Surgery Trends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E49</episode-num>
    <desc>t’s the plastic surgery show! Heidi Montag reveals her latest plastic surgery procedures and her regrets! GG from Shahs of Sunset dishes on her plastic surgery obsession and reality star Tiffany Pollard shares how cosmetic surgery completely changed her life. Plus, see how the Kardashian’s doctor boosts the booty without a scalpel in just 30 minutes! Go inside the OR to see the surgeries to give you sexy bedroom eyes, a perfect pout, and the ideal hourglass figure!</desc>
    <date>20241017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718111423 +0000" stop="20250718120127 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Drs: Why Does That Smell?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From foul gas to smelly ears, The Doctors answer your most pressing questions about the odors your body produces. And, editor-in-chief of Prevention, Liz Vaccariello, separates fact from fiction about a common medical myth.</desc>
    <date>20091027</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718120127 +0000" stop="20250718124808 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Weighs 6yo Daily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A mom is under fire for weighing her 6-year-old daughter every single day after she’s bullied for her weight! Is this mom doing the right thing the wrong way? Plus, the controversy over using marijuana for pain relief in the NFL continues! Do you think the drug should be allowed for players? Then, kids are so stressed out doing their homework they now need therapists? We discuss the new alarming trend! And, using oregano oil to stop a cold in its tracks – is it a buzz or a bust?</desc>
    <date>20181102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718124808 +0000" stop="20250718133350 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Blame This, Not That!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E152</episode-num>
    <desc>Think you know what’s to blame for what’s ailing you? Bad skin? Must be the chocolate. Acid Reflux? Probably spicy food? Not so fast – The Doctors shed new light on common problems. Plus, how to get your body back after baby!</desc>
    <date>20110422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03152.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718133350 +0000" stop="20250718142031 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Investigate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E112</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors investigates lunchboxes! Could dangerous mold, fungus and bacteria be hiding in your child’s lunchbox? You may want to hit the brakes at the drive-thru … could cancer-causing chemicals be hiding in your fast food? An erotic website offers sex-ed for teens with a new “wellness” hub? A judge’s sentence is raising eyebrows: celibacy as punishment? Get your daily dose of gross with a viral earwax video! You might want to think twice before eating chicken with white stripes; find out why! And, how a penny could help you avoid sickness and save wads of cash in an emergency!</desc>
    <date>20121205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718142031 +0000" stop="20250718150514 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Legends' Top Age-Defying Tips</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E95</episode-num>
    <desc>Look and feel young at any age! Hollywood film stars Diahann Carroll, Dyan Cannon and Jacqueline Bisset reveal the secrets of Their eternal youth. And, see a new non-invasive skin smoothing treatment. Plus, an instant booty lifting procedure.</desc>
    <date>20130129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718150514 +0000" stop="20250718155210 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Fixes for Common Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E165</episode-num>
    <desc>From fighting flab, to stifling sneezes to quieting a crying baby, The Doctors reveals easy fixes for your most common problems! And, Oscar-winning actress Marisa Tomei shares her top secrets to a better body!</desc>
    <date>20100520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02165.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718155210 +0000" stop="20250718163740 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Renew Your Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E160</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling burnt out and run down? The Doctors show you how to renew you life, body, mind and spirit. Learn the advantages to a little R&amp;R and the beauty benefits of steam. And, see what your eyes are saying about your health.</desc>
    <date>20110907</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718163740 +0000" stop="20250718172604 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>When Plastic Surgery Goes Wrong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Considering plastic surgery of any kind? Don't miss Krissy's story and Dr. Ordon's essential do's and don'ts to keep you safe. Watch several controversial potty training techniques in action and see if any of them are right for your child.</desc>
    <date>20081002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718172604 +0000" stop="20250718181135 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Improve Your Health From A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Get simple solutions for hiccups, nosebleeds, vertigo and 23 other ailments with The Doctors ABCs of medicine! Plus, learn how to how to last longer in bed. And, the number one mistake parents make when their kids get sick.</desc>
    <date>20101112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718181135 +0000" stop="20250718185735 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Leave it On or Take it Off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E133</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it razor burn, pimples or something worse? Learn the difference between bumps down there. Plus, four tips for a smooth, sexy bikini line. Then, slash hundreds of calories with a simple breakfast swap. And, Dr. Travis turns up the heat at a sweat lodge!</desc>
    <date>20130424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05133.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718185735 +0000" stop="20250718194428 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Shape of Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E128</episode-num>
    <desc>Staying in shape isn’t only about muscle tone. From your lungs to your knees, improve your body from the inside out! Plus, flatten your tummy without surgery, and Alicia Silverstone’s secrets for healthy and sweet treats!</desc>
    <date>20110315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718194428 +0000" stop="20250718203104 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Large Fibroid Removal Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E95</episode-num>
    <desc>You won’t believe what happens when the show’s cameras go “Inside The O.R.” as a 51-year-old woman has a large fibroid removed, which left her looking 5 months pregnant! Controversial new study claims smart women should marry down if They want to start a family. E-cigarettes and vaping have been sold as a way for smokers to quit – new research on why it doesn’t work? The Doctors’ Court: woman arrested with five different types of drugs hidden…in her vagina?</desc>
    <date>20190123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718203104 +0000" stop="20250718211747 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top 5 Questions To Ask Your Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E43</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how to interview potential doctors, which tests you need and how to make the most of your next doctor’s visit. Plus, when you need to go to the emergency room – STAT.</desc>
    <date>20101215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03043.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718211747 +0000" stop="20250718220344 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Try This At Home!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E78</episode-num>
    <desc>From kitchen catastrophes to workplace disasters, don’t miss the list of everyday health hazards that may surprise you. Learn when you can do it yourself and when you should call a professional.</desc>
    <date>20100106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718220344 +0000" stop="20250718225033 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Howie Mandel &amp; OCD</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedian and television personality Howie Mandel confronts his OCD and germ phobia with THE DOCTORS! Our investigation reveals the filth on your hands and the most germ-infested places you’re touching! Restaurant horror stories you must see before you eat out again! Then, a mother’s excruciating jaw condition is destroying her life! Plus, a cure for garlic breath that’s right in your fridge!</desc>
    <date>20161031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718225033 +0000" stop="20250718233725 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Measures for Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E60</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go for beauty? A controversial surgery alters feet so women can wear heels. And, an acupuncture facelift that claims to take years off a woman's appearance. And, the latest in laser surgery that erases tattoos.</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01060.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250718233725 +0000" stop="20250719002406 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Kitchen Germs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E82</episode-num>
    <desc>Go LIVE in the O.R. and watch how surgeons perform a new valve replacement procedure! Are there hidden germs in your kitchen making you sick? The simple swaps to cut down on your sugar! Experts debate if it’s ever okay to yell at your kids!</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
