<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250724225152 +0000" stop="20250725004332 +0000">
    <title>The Jealous Son</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Seduced by her boyfriend's charming son, a woman soon finds herself trapped in a dangerous obsession that will push her to her limits.</desc>
    <date>20250304</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/8/gracenote/8f547a2d1a491063d4ea5e44c1efab19.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725004332 +0000" stop="20250725021908 +0000">
    <title>Kiss Me Once</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Gabrielle, a delusional romantic, fixates on anyone who shows her the slightest interest. Her obsession turns dangerous when her feelings aren't reciprocated.</desc>
    <date>20240426</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5e7310bb932d100335aba8d38b7f601b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725021908 +0000" stop="20250725042618 +0000">
    <title>Nowhere to be Found</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Two sisters go on a senior trip to Mexico, led by Ava’s boyfriend Trent. Meanwhile, journalist Jessica Vandross is going to the same Mexican town in search of her sister’s killer after escaping a sex trafficking ring. These stories collide, in a thrilling fight for their lives.</desc>
    <date>20241231</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0a41aefac4b6f8785f9bad9ce4cb30c8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725042618 +0000" stop="20250725060236 +0000">
    <title>The Wait Game</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Yolanda Hills, a woman deeply in love with her longtime partner Jonas Jones, has been patiently awaiting their wedding day. Their idyllic relationship takes a terrifying turn when a home intruder invades their peaceful sanctuary. Held captive in her own home, Yolanda is confronted with a shocking revelation that will forever alter the course of their lives.</desc>
    <date>20240314</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c30dbb3d5fd9eda9ec1a676a8142da71.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725060236 +0000" stop="20250725074135 +0000">
    <title>Garrett Morris and Michael Schultz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The story of the careers of legendary actor Garrett Morrison and legendary movie director Michael Schultz. Follow their life and career from their early beginnings to adulthood and becoming worldwide legendary artists from Broadway to Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>20241007</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODliYjQ3ZjgtNjUyNi00ZTI4LWJjNDEtOTMyNzFjMDI1MzQ1XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725074135 +0000" stop="20250725093513 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of Glynn Turman</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The life story and career of legendary actor Glynn Turman. At 12 years old he made his Broadway debut in the classic and original production of “A Raisin in the Sun” opposite all-time great, Sidney Poitier. For the last 6 decades he has graced the silver screen, television, and stage with performances of brilliance and excellence. The film chronicles his childhood, born in New York to his journey to Hollywood, becoming one of the world’s best actors.</desc>
    <date>20220830</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/ccdb7e0fce863d0cccbe2161427b8dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725093513 +0000" stop="20250725111235 +0000">
    <title>Shadows of Redemption</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ares, a ruthless criminal, seeks to reclaim his family's underworld empire. Betrayal and deception haunt his path as he battles former allies and lovers. Determined to avenge his father's murder and reunite his family, Ares faces his toughest challenge yet: uncovering the truth behind the chaos.</desc>
    <date>20241110</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0dd6a1678052c99753672c491aa0d6c2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725111235 +0000" stop="20250725124247 +0000">
    <title>Carmen and Magic</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Carmen meets a new friend at school named Magic, she helps raise her spirits and allows her to stand up for herself. When her single father Drew starts seeing the school principal, Magic convinces Carmen to disrupt their relationship, pulling the veil on Magic’s sinister nature.</desc>
    <date>20250120</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/04bbfb0cfcd743d16af923cf8795b3c2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725124247 +0000" stop="20250725151623 +0000">
    <title>Bloodline of the Jewel</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Bride to be, Nahdulay Ncala’s world is turned upside down as she finds herself in the middle of someone's dangerous and deadly quest for a royal jewel. Traveling from Africa to America, Nahdulay connects with an unsuspecting driver, Oliver, who vows to help her get answers. Nahdulay is faced with revlations from her past and newly surfaced feelings, as a series of mysterious and deadly events connected to her family unfold.</desc>
    <date>20250114</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rNbmhPncQ5cEU6LyXwi40ly0Jvj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725151623 +0000" stop="20250725165535 +0000">
    <title>Scandalous</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Lady Watts, a bestselling author, reveals secrets about her affairs with those closest to her in her latest memoir. At her launch party, a heated argument turns violent, and she's left unconscious. As detectives investigate, secrets, love triangles, and betrayal emerge. The search for the attacker leads to twists and turns, involving everyone from her talent manager to her labelmate. The truth about the night of the attack is slowly revealed, with unexpected consequences for all involved.</desc>
    <date>20241231</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1fc9eff8f4132009b56b7d944b04aee.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725165535 +0000" stop="20250725182351 +0000">
    <title>Back Home</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Drug kingpin Jay looks to expand his drug empire with the help of his business partners, and his girlfriend Passion. However, Polo and Marco have their own agenda’s, which could lead to chaos, as a potential drug war descends upon Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/609aa989726588d38d523bfe3705d83f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725182351 +0000" stop="20250725200130 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725200130 +0000" stop="20250725221702 +0000">
    <title>Troublesome</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Veteran homicide detective Michael reluctantly partners with rookie Derrick. Witnessing a double homicide, they survive a deadly chase, but Derrick is wounded. The suspects are linked to the kingpin, who retaliates by ordering murders across the city. As chaos erupts, the FBI joins the case, revealing the kingpin's identity. Michael finds a weak link, offering a chance to finally catch him.</desc>
    <date>20250609</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bba572182a25acd3645156c83fc0e787.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725221702 +0000" stop="20250725235220 +0000">
    <title>All the Love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young woman begins her journey to adulthood, navigating love and self-discovery, while being haunted by a mysterious past that she can’t fully remember. As murders and violence swirl around her, she wonders who she can trust. Will she find love or suffer the same mysterious fate as her birth parents?</desc>
    <date>20250225</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6589e799a5ad0a6e19fa52d1d64f0025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725235220 +0000" stop="20250726012524 +0000">
    <title>Kingdom Men</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Pastor Gerald’s job is on the line if he doesn’t increase the attendance of the men in the church. He decides to have a men’s retreat hoping it will fix everything. Little did he know that he’s in for the fight of his life. He realizes God didn’t call him to increase the men at the church but help them.</desc>
    <date>20200320</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5faa3e6babb4d76418dc26807622e35c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
