<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711001520 +0000" stop="20250711014916 +0000">
    <title>Induced</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An expectant couple heads to a remote cabin to have a natural childbirth, but comes under attack from a predatory midwife who will stop at nothing to snatch their unborn child from them.</desc>
    <date>20221018</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/9d406aface68c8cc3dbef34038f8d0b6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711014916 +0000" stop="20250711035426 +0000">
    <title>Trapped in the Game</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Polo is a young desperate hustler looking to make some quick cash. However, the only way he knows how to make cash quickly, is pimping out young women with the help of his crew. When of his crew starts taking girls off the street, the heat threatens to bring down his whole operation.</desc>
    <date>20241015</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d2c5ce7b27554d531a4d54779b038354.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711035426 +0000" stop="20250711061108 +0000">
    <title>Surviving the Storm</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A twenty-eight year old single mother hears the unsettling news of stage three breast cancer; causing two estranged sisters to confront family secrets and stop the silence.</desc>
    <date>20230704</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/coC17hMotPZJAnocrNy95QgOOKz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711061108 +0000" stop="20250711073200 +0000">
    <title>She Time</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Krystal, a devoted wife and mother, finds herself trapped in the routine of a her daily life and a fading marriage. Longing for excitement and passion, she embarks on a girls’ night out that unexpectedly reignites an old flame from her past.</desc>
    <date>20231002</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/fa23a8d45becb7c00cec4e20a06eae2b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711073200 +0000" stop="20250711102237 +0000">
    <title>SistAhood</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jordyn Dixon returns home to the city of Augusta to reunite with loved ones, but she quickly finds out that things are not the same as she left them years ago. This story follows Jordyn and her circle of friends, who are each on different walks of life in their professions and relationships, but each of their stories and paths are intertwined as each woman must deal with situations in their individual lives that could disrupt their bonds with one another.</desc>
    <date>20210525</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/afc9df457e908d28734e37ca9e127cfa.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711102237 +0000" stop="20250711131446 +0000">
    <title>SistAhood 2: Calling All Lovers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jordyn Dixon and her group of girlfriends are working to better themselves and each other; however, secrets from the past and grudges in the present will test the future of their sisterhood circle.</desc>
    <date>20240924</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b6223cf24cfd1236f24fa559dda3b92e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711131446 +0000" stop="20250711145713 +0000">
    <title>Killer Zaddy</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Naomi Anderson is struggling financially when she meets a successful, handsome, older gentleman.</desc>
    <date>20231212</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lQ0sRwb2SqkLZKhCO23bE7rsX78.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711145713 +0000" stop="20250711165822 +0000">
    <title>Hidden Agenda</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jessica is the smartest girl on campus tutoring the most popular football player, Ryan. He is loved by many but he also has a few enemies. After the football team wins the championship game, Ryan decides to throw an after party at his house. When campus police find Ryan’s dead body, multiple people have a motive to want him dead. Will Jessica and her friend uncover the truth before it’s too late?</desc>
    <date>20230709</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/30ZApQjC28XNAGGiqgHvFp4PyUT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711165822 +0000" stop="20250711184411 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Score</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After starting their new record label, Donica Blair and Shequell Harris have entered a dangerous arena full of guns, lies, and deceit. Now they are racing against time to right their wrongs and save their own lives before they are next in a string of murders. Meanwhile their partner Seven, has fallen victim to the deadliest of them all; the Black widow.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711184411 +0000" stop="20250711202903 +0000">
    <title>Runway of Shadows</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters Ivy and Zara are separated at a very young age due to their father’s deceit. When Ivy and Zara unexpectedly cross paths at a prestigious runway show, the stage it set for a series of mysterious and unsettling events.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711202903 +0000" stop="20250711220332 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711220332 +0000" stop="20250711233147 +0000">
    <title>Back Home</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Drug kingpin Jay looks to expand his drug empire with the help of his business partners, and his girlfriend Passion. However, Polo and Marco have their own agenda’s, which could lead to chaos, as a potential drug war descends upon Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/609aa989726588d38d523bfe3705d83f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711233147 +0000" stop="20250712011942 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Dawn</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Having platinum records and superstar rosters seem like easy work to music industry legends Donica Blair and Shequell Harris, but when they want to start their own label, they become targets in more ways than they are prepared for. Adding Seven to the mix in an already uneven playing field leads to unorthodox measures to protect Don and save her life. Quell, on the other hand, may have gotten exactly what she asked for when she calls Silk to help them out.</desc>
    <date>20250520</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
