<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703092220 +0000" stop="20250703110631 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt Of Lies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is called in when a new arrival to a tight-knit community for retired police officers is found dead.</desc>
    <date>20240716</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7e1vYNhILjkq2GRzYGwu3oErKx6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703110631 +0000" stop="20250703125021 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>A Grain Of Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A trendy organic bakery in a restored mill is at the centre of a local dispute which leads to a death.</desc>
    <date>20240723</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A46qINlyqkUk0hHGNKhFArBz1DW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703125021 +0000" stop="20250703143432 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dressed To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S23E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Parish chairwoman is found dead in a local theatre, possibly because of her hostility toward a drag show.</desc>
    <date>20241110</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wzfWPAJj1DKlug0H7PQ4vinMl2j.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703143432 +0000" stop="20250703161930 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Haunting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Its Christmas and new detective Charlie Nelson moves into Midsomer. Hes thrown straight into an intriguing mystery in the village of Morton Shallows. A man is fatally stabbed with an antique sword.</desc>
    <date>20131224</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8tABWVupBYiM3rn1NRCUEOkkq5S.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703161930 +0000" stop="20250703180428 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Let Us Prey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of murders in Midsomer St Claire seem to be inspired by macabre images on a medieval fresco.</desc>
    <date>20140108</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1kIZ9xpDDe4U5qwgL1F9iNJzqpA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703180428 +0000" stop="20250703194917 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Harvest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When wealthy farmer Martin Strickland is covered in truffle oil and mauled to death by a wild boar, the investigation leads to restaurant Wyvern House and its tyrannical celebrity chef Ruth Cameron.</desc>
    <date>20140129</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zeliFzcL6KDIJeeADWXf5eDjfJ1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703194917 +0000" stop="20250703213456 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Flying Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a body is discovered in a reservoir dropped out of a plane, Barnaby and Nelson find the world of stunt pilots and military heroes hides many dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>20140205</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kB5krKKTBLoDrpEvWt0qC4V8Xvn.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703213456 +0000" stop="20250703232047 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Killings At Copenhagen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When the boss of Calders Biscuit Company is murdered in Copenhagen, Barnaby and Nelson join forces with two female Danish detectives, the abrasive and astute Poulsen and the charming and cool Degn.</desc>
    <date>20140212</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uXCntd4N3rH5m9iiAxS9KpRFD77.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250703232047 +0000" stop="20250704010523 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Made To Measure Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Milton Cross depend on lord of the manor Edward Milton, for their jobs and income. When Sonia Woodley is found murdered in the churchyard, two years after the death of her abusive husband Gerald, the murder weapon is discovered to be tailor's shears, but which one of villagers is responsible? Barnaby and Jones arrive at Woodley and Woodley, the tailors to find out, to discover that the vicar had received a letter from Sonia a few days before.</desc>
    <date>20100512</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tXZ7Zqn1wMQZbXoJJnnSSB8ZdP5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704010523 +0000" stop="20250704025017 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword Of Guillaume</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>During a council meeting, Mayor Dave Hicks announces plans to awaken an annual trip to Brighton. Barnaby suspects his proposal to buy coastal land there is a fraud. Barnaby reluctantly joins the party, but during their time in Brighton, hated property developer Hugh Dalgleish is beheaded on a ghost train ride. The detectives together with Tom's cousin DCI John Barnaby gather who from the party or someone else could have been responsible before other murders occur and secrets are uncovered.</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3vsfoPqqRENM97cx6wVGBFMLcb7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704025017 +0000" stop="20250704043513 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Saddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ford Florey is anything but quiet, when the Wild West Society bring their show and fair, consisting of many stalls and a shooting re-enactment. The witch on the 'Dunk the Witch' stall, gets truly dunked and goes horribly wrong, when the water starts turning red. Barnaby and Jones have to be alert with a shooter in their midst. With many grudges, jealousies and a dispute over wasteland, known as 'the swamp', as possible motives, it is not long before more people turn up dead.</desc>
    <date>20100908</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8DFMFTMHAc9gjZoFswWVd0jrAaQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704043513 +0000" stop="20250704061941 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On a dark night in the village of March Magna, Joyce Barnaby swerves her car and narrowly misses a shadowy figure in the road. Shortly after a body is found in the local old cemetery. The victim Gerald Ebbs was a member of the council and of the village's library. It is discovered from the villagers that Gerald had had a strange fixation on both the old hospital and cemetery; in particular a grave from within.</desc>
    <date>20100922</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qXbun3EZ9GMJvqNlUAyznQ8VtwY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704061941 +0000" stop="20250704080438 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Master Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Devington Manor Winter School led by internationally renowned musician Sir Michael Fielding, is a magnet for many aspiring piano students. Amongst the latest batch of students is Zoe Stock, a gifted young lady. Whilst in the grounds of the manor and by the riverbank, Zoe sees a woman jump from the bridge and disappear underwater. When Barnaby and Jones start their enquiries into the possible drowning, they discover many shady connections to the past.</desc>
    <date>20101006</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ab8nTnZk7hjjfUoZsaRVyfamFZp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704080438 +0000" stop="20250704094907 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Noble Art</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When boxer John Kinsella wins a world title in New York, the village of Midsomer Morchard are overjoyed at his success. Shortly afterwards a solicitor is found dead by his assistant and Kinsella's manager. Barnaby and Jones start to investigate and come across infidelity, anger, betrayals and blackmail. When a Victorian prize-fight re-enactment turns nasty and Kinsella's manager is found murdered in his home's gym.</desc>
    <date>20101013</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cn661RGTLE6sjtH9yuZcR8glQal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250704094907 +0000" stop="20250704113401 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Not In My Background</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Midsomer Conservation Society are up in arms, when a recent new build, called Swanscombe House is a highlight of an open garden day. It leads to an ugly confrontation between a couple of its members and those responsible for the planning application, design and build. The people of which are suspected of involvement in a money-making scam. Political squabbles, burglaries and sexual liaisons all come to the fore in picturesque Great Pelfe.</desc>
    <date>20110112</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LCr4F0wC54rJDCkmKNQuJZe3w1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
