<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721005957 +0000" stop="20250721012954 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenger VS The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Some of the biggest news to come down the automotive pipeline in a long time is the fact that Dodge is making the Challenger again. But how does it stack up against the legendary Challengers of old? Well, Stacey decides to find out! First, by “grabbing” a Challenger in a most unorthodox way and then comparing it head-to-head with a 70’ 440 six-pack car. But that’s not all… Then Stacey decides to take the new car beyond the legend by sticking on a supercharger and really blowing the doors off of the competition! If you are a Mopar nut, or have just wondered what all the fuss was about concerning the new Challenger…this is one show you’ve got to see!</desc>
    <date>20090424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0034.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721012954 +0000" stop="20250721015955 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>GEARZ Stimulus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>With the price of gas going up, down, and all over the place, people are becoming more and more concerned about fuel economy, and GEARZ is asked time and time again what products we recommend that really give you better economy and performance. Well, ask no more…because Stacey not only addresses that question, but also goes through the top 6 upgrades that ANYBODY can do to a vehicle! That’s right; these are inexpensive AND easy to do! After that, Stacey takes on the subject of alternative fuels by demonstrating that you can actually make a diesel engine run, and run well, on old used cooking oil! Now there is yet another reason to eat French fries! So pass the ketchup and put the hammer down!!!</desc>
    <date>20090501</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0035.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721015955 +0000" stop="20250721022956 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt. Rock Motor Mounts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Every once in a while, there comes a point in your project where there are no parts available to help you, and your only choice is to make something yourself… but how do you do that? Stacey walks you through the steps of how to lay out an engine swap, and how to hand fabricate motor mounts, so you can stick an engine into a vehicle that it was never intended to go into. It’s hard-core, down and dirty how-to, but somebody has to do it… and it needs to be YOU. The good news is, with Stacey walking you through the process and showing you how to solve problems, it CAN be you! Now you just need to get out in the garage and start working!!</desc>
    <date>20090508</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0036.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721022956 +0000" stop="20250721025957 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Straight Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everybody knows that the engine is a central key component to ANY Hot Rod project. But is a V8 the only way to go? NO WAY! Stacey takes a vintage straight six engine that has been sleeping in a crate for almost 40 years and he puts on the right pieces. He shows you why the straight six was a force to be reckoned with in the early days of hot rodding. After that, Stacey jumps into the tips and tricks of how to paint your own true Kandy paint job. If you are into vintage Hot Rods, Kandy paint, and multi-carbs… you don’t need to go on a diet… you just need to watch GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20090515</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0037.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721025957 +0000" stop="20250721033000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Knucklebuster Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The “KnuckleBuster” is back on GearZ, and Stacey is putting the final touches on this ’73 Chevy pickup. After a quick look at the new paint slathered on its flanks, Stacey gives the truck a face lift with grille, bumpers, and all that other cool trim stuff. Then it’s on to the bed where he lays in some oak to give the former “beater” some class and style. Finally, it’s underneath to stick in a new exhaust system to keep the bad gas blowing out the back. If you have ever wondered if you could really build something cool yourself… all you have to do is check out the finished “KnuckleBuster” and be willing to bust YOUR own knuckles… the rest will take care of itself!</desc>
    <date>20090522</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0038.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721033000 +0000" stop="20250721040000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Wheels Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>POP QUIZ… what are the 16 most influential cars ever made? If you answered Ford, Chevy, VW, Honda, or any other car manufacturer, you are close…but wrong! The 16 most influential cars ever made were the 16 original Hot Wheel cars that Mattel rolled out in 1968. Stacey walks you through the fascinating and unique story of how those little metal cars came to be and how they changed American car culture in a HUGE way. Young or old, you will love the story about the cars that turned living rooms across the country into huge racetracks. Matter-of-fact, we’ll bet you not only remember these cars, but you probably owned a few of them over the years. So, dig out the toy box and put the chores on hold because it’s time to do some Hot Wheels racin’!</desc>
    <date>20090529</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0039.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721040000 +0000" stop="20250721043002 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Gamma Goat/ Welding Safety</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to off-road vehicles, more is usually better. This is especially true when tires are involved. Today on GEARZ, Stacey takes you through the nuts and bolts of one of the most incredible off-road vehicles ever built…the Gamma Goat. What!?! You’ve never heard of it? Well that’s probably because you were not in the military. Because only the military could dream up an articulating, six-wheel-drive, amphibious monster like this, and still keep it street legal! After that, Stacey walks you through some important safety tips and tricks that you need to know if you are going to be welding in your shop…so lock and load and strap in ‘cuz it’s all coming at you today on GEARZ!</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0040.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721043002 +0000" stop="20250721050001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Reviving a Junkyard Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey goes where all of us have been before to pull an old derelict SEMI TRUCK(’69 International) out of a quiet junkyard to demonstrate the steps necessary to get an old, neglected vehicle running again. From rat’s nests to chicken poop, it’s all here as Stacey slowly coaxes the old truck back to life. This show definitely drives the point home that if something like this can be revived, there’s NOTHING that you should be afraid to tackle as long as you are armed with a set of tools and a sense of adventure! Go get ‘em !</desc>
    <date>20220831</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0041.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721050001 +0000" stop="20250721060000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Factory Correct</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the Ghoulz use their brand new Shop Crane to lower the body of the '71 Cuda 340 Triple Black 'Phantasm' Tribute car onto its restored suspension and its drive-train is assembled and installed.</desc>
    <date>20130205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721060000 +0000" stop="20250721070001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Holley Equipped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The '69 Daytona Charger returns from the media blaster and Mark gives Josh a history lesson on the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel Car before removing it's drive-train and suspension.</desc>
    <date>20130212</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721070001 +0000" stop="20250721080000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car completely disassembled and off to the media blaster. Mark disassembles and restores the right-hand door to the 71' 440 Phantom Cuda. In addition, the headliner and vinyl top is installed in the 71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721080000 +0000" stop="20250721090001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls get the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car completely disassembled and off to the media blaster. Mark disassembles and restores the right-hand door to the 71' 440 Phantom Cuda. In addition, the headliner and vinyl top is installed in the 71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721090001 +0000" stop="20250721100003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>You Win Some …</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The owner of the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car visits the shop and learns about assembly-line markings. Mark checks the paint on the body of the '70 Cuda 383 Automatic FE5 Rallye Red Car and discovers a major problem.</desc>
    <date>20130226</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721100003 +0000" stop="20250721110002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Cuda Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls receives a '70 Barracuda Convertible to get a full restoration. Despite improbability, Mark straightens the fender for the '71 440 Phantom Cuda and the crew continues the restoration of the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130305</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721110002 +0000" stop="20250721120002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Cuda Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls receives a '70 Barracuda Convertible to get a full restoration. Despite improbability, Mark straightens the fender for the '71 440 Phantom Cuda and the crew continues the restoration of the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car.</desc>
    <date>20130305</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721120002 +0000" stop="20250721130003 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Flippin' the Bird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls detail and assemble the suspension of the '70 AAR Cuda 340 Six Barrel car. The owners of the '70 Plymouth Superbird, in the queue for resurrection, visit the shop and Daren convinces the crew to throw a birthday party for Mark.</desc>
    <date>20130312</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721130003 +0000" stop="20250721140005 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Fish n' Chips</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark takes some time for himself and leaves Daren in charge of the shop. The crew gets the newly painted panels installed on the '70 Cuda 383 Automatic FE5 Rallye Red Car. And Mark discovers a chip on the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car and no one will own up to it.</desc>
    <date>20130319</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E11_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721140005 +0000" stop="20250721150006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Game Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The fuel and brake lines are installed in the '71 'Phantasm' Tribute car. Daren quits and won't return until Mark begins the restoration of his '70 Plum Crazy Challenger. A phone-call from the Phantasm car owner forces Mark to make a promise he might not be able to keep.</desc>
    <date>20130326</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E12_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721150006 +0000" stop="20250721160008 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Phantasm ‘Cuda</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The GYC crew is under the gun to get the '71 Cuda 340 Triple Black 'Phantasm' Tribute car finished by the end of the week. With the exhaust, ornamation, and the engine start still ahead of them, will they be able to finish the car before the director of the 'Phantasm' movie franchise arrives?</desc>
    <date>20130402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S02_E13_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721160008 +0000" stop="20250721170008 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Back in Triple Black</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the team rush to complete the triple-black, '71 Cuda, Phantasm homage car. The director and star of Phantasm, Don Coscarelli and A. Michael Baldwin, visit Graveyard Carz to check out the homage car and hopefully, drive it around town.</desc>
    <date>20140107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721170008 +0000" stop="20250721180009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>AAR You Ready for This?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The team tears down Mike Hill's '70 Superbird and finishes up final touches on Chris Driscoll's '70 AAR Cuda. Daren confronts Mark about stealing parts from his car and Mark gets a rematch on Chris Driscoll's race track.</desc>
    <date>20140114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721180009 +0000" stop="20250721190007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Go for It!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Holly asks Mark if she can work on cars. Mark Cain from Bad Boy Blasters brings the crew a huge gift. The '70 Barracuda Convertible is torn down and sent to the dipper, progress is made on the '70 Sunroof Challenger and Mark gets a surprise from one of his favorite actors.</desc>
    <date>20140121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721190007 +0000" stop="20250721200008 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Get Your Hands Dirty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark installs the hood decal on the '70 Sunroof Challenger, Holly helps Josh disassemble the Barracuda suspension, Mark and Daren work on the 440 engine for the Challenger, and the team assembles one of the rarest Mopar options, the sunroof for the '70 Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20140128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E04_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721200008 +0000" stop="20250721210009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>W-O-M-A-N, Mark Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The team rushes to ready the '69 Dodge Daytona for Tom Partridge and his family's visit. The guys settle a leadership dispute the old fashioned way, the Graveyard Carz van gets a face lift, and Daren retaliates when Mark won't let him sign for deliveries.</desc>
    <date>20140204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E05_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721210009 +0000" stop="20250721220012 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Pop Secrets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Holly helps Mark on the '70 Challenger, Daren annoys everyone with his popcorn and causes Mark to damage a very rare car. Tony D'Agostino, from Tony's Mopar Parts, visits and lends a hand on the '70 sunroof Challenger. Mark lets Holly in on the big secret and Daren reveals a secret of his own.</desc>
    <date>20140211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E06_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721220012 +0000" stop="20250721230010 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Let the Sunshine In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark gets a portable showroom, the '70 Hemi Charger is dissembled and the team finishes the 1970 Sunroof Challenger. Mark finally reveals his big secret project to the Graveyard Carz team and Royal makes a video tribute to the Sunroof Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20140218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E07_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250721230010 +0000" stop="20250722000000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Royal Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the ghouls build out the 440 Super Commando engine for their '70 Plymouth Superbird and install the suspension for the '69 Daytona Charger. Daren finally has enough of Mark's foolishness.</desc>
    <date>20140225</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E08_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250722000000 +0000" stop="20250722010000 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Grand Torino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Body man Derrick becomes an official Graveyard Carz crew member and assists in the disassembly of the rare '67 Plymouth Hemi GTX Convertible. Josh and Daren play "the game" with Mark.</desc>
    <date>20140304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250722010000 +0000" stop="20250722020001 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>The Waltons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and the Ghoulz get a massive sheet-metal order from AMD for their '70 Plymouth Superbird. Meanwhile, the owners of the '72 Charger visit and talk about what made their car so special. Daren gets the offer of a lifetime on his '70 Challenger R/T.</desc>
    <date>20140311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S03_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
