<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250705233615 +0000" stop="20250706002328 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Contagious or Not? Are You at Risk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E137</episode-num>
    <desc>Find out the 10 most common ailments, and which ones are contagious. Plus, a dangerous virus that often masquerades as a rash. Is your child at risk? And, quick cures for urinary tract infections and the stomach flu.</desc>
    <date>20090330</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01137.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706002328 +0000" stop="20250706010915 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Docs Investigate: Adderall Epidemic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E69</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors investigates Hollywood’s Adderall epidemic. Former Hollywood “It-girl” says Adderall destroyed her life. What’s behind the increase in adult ADHD and is it a valid diagnosis? Safer alternatives for stimulant drugs. A procedure that gives a keyhole pout.</desc>
    <date>20191114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12069.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706010915 +0000" stop="20250706015339 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Desperate to Save A Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E97</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go to save your life or the life of someone you love? Meet a family who has taken drastic steps to prevent the cancer that runs rampant in their genes. And, Survivor star Ethan Zohn in the battle of his life.</desc>
    <date>20100201</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706015339 +0000" stop="20250706024020 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Investigate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E112</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors investigates lunchboxes! Could dangerous mold, fungus and bacteria be hiding in your child’s lunchbox? You may want to hit the brakes at the drive-thru … could cancer-causing chemicals be hiding in your fast food? An erotic website offers sex-ed for teens with a new “wellness” hub? A judge’s sentence is raising eyebrows: celibacy as punishment? Get your daily dose of gross with a viral earwax video! You might want to think twice before eating chicken with white stripes; find out why! And, how a penny could help you avoid sickness and save wads of cash in an emergency!</desc>
    <date>20121205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706024020 +0000" stop="20250706032613 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Gross Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn why IBS can wreak havoc on your stomach and your sex life! Gunk in your eyes? Find out how to get rid of it. Plus, how to heal hemorrhoids. And, surprising ways to increase your man’s sperm count.</desc>
    <date>20121113</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d5527404ae5a786aa4d62b74df5c2239.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706032613 +0000" stop="20250706041300 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Post Surgery Skin Removal &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Massive skin removal reveal post weight loss! Break up battle plan with Dr. Ish. Does beer make men more fertile? “Morgue Mom” Mysteries! The ABC’s of cancer and what you need to know today! Viral superstar “Sancho” the therapy dog! Fridge hacks you must have!</desc>
    <date>20180927</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706041300 +0000" stop="20250706045936 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Insta-Famous "Peach Booty"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E109</episode-num>
    <desc>Insta-famous fitness star Abby Pollock is known for her “peach booty” that’s so perfect some say it’s fake! A live glute ultrasound reveals the truth, while Abby shares a shocking admission about her past. When a bad habit becomes debilitating, a woman turns to The Doctors for help! Special correspondent Rosie Mercado joins The Doctors and is shocked to hear that people are putting apple cider vinegar… down where? Is there any truth to the internet rumor urging women to try DIY “tightening”? Could a contraceptive gel for men change birth control forever? Should you stay friends with your ex? Hear what The Doctors has to say! Then, Dr. Travis tears up as he talks about his beloved dog, Nala, and her health struggles. A 97-year-old record-breaking sprinter … how does he do it? And, the easiest way to peel garlic, ever!</desc>
    <date>20170315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706045936 +0000" stop="20250706054507 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>DIY Baby Delivery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mom’s at-home delivery story you won’t believe! Could fruit flies be the key to figuring out the male sex drive? Treating face shingles. Newly engaged couple in need of serious weight loss help. The shocking new dating trend! DIY shoe polish hack you need to know! The new “String Test” to determine if you’re obese!</desc>
    <date>20180928</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706054507 +0000" stop="20250706063147 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Stool Squad Answers Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Stool Squad is back to answer your most embarrassing poop-related questions! Disturbing Kim Kardashian look-a-like plastic surgery! Shocking celebrity beauty trend! Toddler hospitalized after using a toy makeup kit!</desc>
    <date>20181009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11004.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706063147 +0000" stop="20250706071748 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Let It Happen to You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E108</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors are joined by home improvement guru and safety expert, Eric Stromer, to share important tips about home, flood and fire safety. Learn what to do if you find yourself in a dangerous situation. And, kitchen safety rules to live by.</desc>
    <date>20100224</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02108.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706071748 +0000" stop="20250706080320 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>All Shook Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you get body tremors? Does your butt jiggle? Do you tremble when you get a high fever? Learn why your body shakes, shimmies and shivers! And, shake your way to a better physique.</desc>
    <date>20101022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706080320 +0000" stop="20250706085005 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Why Do I Itch and Smell Like That?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E63</episode-num>
    <desc>Get the lowdown on bug, mosquito and spider bites, tickles in the back of your throat and more! And, why bad breath may indicate a more serious problem. Plus, see the latest at-home technology to relieve itchy skin.</desc>
    <date>20101207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706085005 +0000" stop="20250706093637 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Gastric Band Nightmare!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Is allowing your child to play youth football the same as child abuse? Famed neuropathologist played by Will Smith in the film Concussion and a former NFL player join the controversial debate on America’s pastime! Plus, should your children be learning about gender identity … in kindergarten? Then, doctors are removing gastric bands now more than ever! One woman shares her weight loss surgery nightmare! Plus, how does weed affect your heart? One mom claims her son’s marijuana use caused his death. And, America is having a “Constipation Crisis!” We have solutions to get your poop back on track!</desc>
    <date>20171002</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/256b7d1464c2321dcd6a4f650a15b9f0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706093637 +0000" stop="20250706102154 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Surprising Health Dangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrible accidents and life-threatening conditions can happen to anyone at any time, even you! Learn how to prevent a critical head injury, E.coli poisoning, severe dehydration and more. And, spot the hazards in your home!</desc>
    <date>20101011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706102154 +0000" stop="20250706110853 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom's Alcohol Intervention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E144</episode-num>
    <desc>A family fed up with their mother’s years of alcohol abuse turns to THE DOCTORS for help! Will she finally quit her drinking and accept that she needs to go to rehab? Then, do you believe in past lives? We meet a mom who says her son is the reincarnation of Major League Baseball player Lou Gehrig! Plus, elementary school drop-off lines are stressful, but why would a mom pull a gun on another mom? A woman disfigured by her ex when he threw acid in her face receives a life-changing facial procedure! Don’t miss her transformation!</desc>
    <date>20170522</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09144.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706110853 +0000" stop="20250706115511 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Pooper on the Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Woman who poops and runs is labeled the “Mad Pooper”! Then, father tried to discipline daughter by chasing her around with a clown mask? Next, Dr. Ordon gives young girl a life changing surgery after being attacked by the family dog! How is she doing today? Don’t miss when the Yum Yuck Crew tries Keri Glassman’s healthy treats! What will they think? Then, one mom refuses to send her daughter to daycare with overweight teachers? Then, an HOA tries to ban the shed where a young girl does her breathing treatments? Do they have a case? Next, could this rash happen to your kid and how can you prevent it? Don’t miss the secret to better sex for parents!</desc>
    <date>20171218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706115511 +0000" stop="20250706124200 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Howie Mandel &amp; OCD</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedian and television personality Howie Mandel confronts his OCD and germ phobia with THE DOCTORS! Our investigation reveals the filth on your hands and the most germ-infested places you’re touching! Restaurant horror stories you must see before you eat out again! Then, a mother’s excruciating jaw condition is destroying her life! Plus, a cure for garlic breath that’s right in your fridge!</desc>
    <date>20161031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706124200 +0000" stop="20250706132904 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Drs: Why Does That Smell?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>From foul gas to smelly ears, The Doctors answer your most pressing questions about the odors your body produces. And, editor-in-chief of Prevention, Liz Vaccariello, separates fact from fiction about a common medical myth.</desc>
    <date>20091027</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706132904 +0000" stop="20250706141609 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>5 Cures in 5 Minutes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E109</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors present five-minute cures for common ailments. See a procedure that stops nasal allergy symptoms for good. And, cosmetic dentist Dr. Dorfman shares dental Dos and Don'ts, including an instant cure for canker sores.</desc>
    <date>20090223</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706141609 +0000" stop="20250706150236 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Vegetarian Diet Increase Strokes?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Can a vegetarian diet really increase the risk of a stroke? Are fake meat burgers the same as dog food? Should everyone be screened for Hepatitis C? Moms get help with sleepless toddlers! Are cold-pressed skin care and spray-on skin really a thing? Is your mouthwash raising your blood pressure? Plus, do emojis encourage more dates and sex?</desc>
    <date>20191008</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706150236 +0000" stop="20250706154831 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Miracles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E63</episode-num>
    <desc>When skin cancer destroyed one woman’s ear, see how doctors helped her grow a new one – on her arm! Then, a mom saves her child’s life with a fecal transplant. Plus, how one woman's breast milk is helping dozens of babies around the country.</desc>
    <date>20121115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706154831 +0000" stop="20250706163441 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Can It Be Cured?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E63</episode-num>
    <desc>See a cure for chronic ear infections, a laser treatment that eliminates back pain and technology that guarantees less time in the dentist’s chair. And, at-home remedies that can cure a cold, calm a flu and quell motion sickness.</desc>
    <date>20091202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02063.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706163441 +0000" stop="20250706172051 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top Reasons People Call In Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Sore throat, upset stomach, aches and pains -- find out when you’re most contagious and when it’s safe to go back to school or the office. And, how to determine if your child is too sick for school.</desc>
    <date>20101213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03066.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706172051 +0000" stop="20250706180413 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Be Prepared</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Carbon monoxide can seep into your home while you sleep. Safeguard your family from this colorless, odorless and deadly gas. Plus, Dr. Lisa’s tips to prepare for menopause and how to lose those last 10 pounds!</desc>
    <date>20090921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02019.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706180413 +0000" stop="20250706185114 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Body's Warning SIgns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Decipher the clues and warning signs your body is giving you. Witness a life-saving surgery that a mother and daughter underwent together! Plus, learn what kind of bruises can indicate a serious medical condition.</desc>
    <date>20091120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706185114 +0000" stop="20250706193320 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bullied Because of My Skin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E105</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage girl is bullied because of her painful skin condition; will The Doctors be able to save her skin? Then, The Doctors discusses the latest health news. Could binge-watching your favorite shows trigger binge-drinking? Dr. Ordon reveals the latest nip-tuck trends, including a “No Downtime Neckline” procedure to help you say goodbye to your double chin! Plus, find out how you can fight wrinkles in your sleep!</desc>
    <date>20170327</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706193320 +0000" stop="20250706202115 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Public Meltdowns &amp; More!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E62</episode-num>
    <desc>Caught on tape: a public meltdown at the gym! What to do when someone flies off the handle in public! Then, a 90-pound weight loss without surgery? Hear one woman’s personal tips that helped her get trim! And, The voice of beloved cartoon characters like Bugs Bunny, Ren and Stimpy, Doug and Futurama reveals his story of overcoming prostate cancer! The risk factors all men need to know! Plus, legendary Latin King of Comedy Paul Rodriguez opens up about his sister’s tragic diabetic death. Hear his heartache and his desire to improve his own personal health. Then, if you’re one of the 42 million Americans struggling with constipation, proctologist Dr. David Rosenfeld shares his top foods that can help you poop! Plus, a sweet trick for a bug-free BBQ!</desc>
    <date>20180912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11062.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706202115 +0000" stop="20250706210714 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>I Donated My Husband's Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E141</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, a woman’s courage to donate her late husband’s face leads to a ground-breaking facial transplant with unbelievable results! In another exclusive, a mother reveals how the pressure to breastfeed her baby led her to accidentally starve her son. Reality star Laura Govan stops by for some advice on a personal health issue! Plus, the tweet that triggered a seizure … how’s that possible? And, a ssss-soothing massage by snakes? Meet Marnie The Dog!</desc>
    <date>20170509</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09141.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706210714 +0000" stop="20250706215301 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Common Medical Risks On The Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E103</episode-num>
    <desc>Behind the wheel, in a plane or on a train, learn how to avoid injuries and stay safe while on the go. And, Dr. Travis’ fun and safe workout tips for busy moms.</desc>
    <date>20100211</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02103.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706215301 +0000" stop="20250706223944 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Maureen McCormick &amp; More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, Maureen McCormick reveals new details of her shocking past! Then, one woman undergoes a live procedure for her resting “angry” face, did it work? Plus, what you need to know to protect your child from the super lice outbreak and a child abductor!</desc>
    <date>20160921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706223944 +0000" stop="20250706232617 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Toenail Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Why does one woman have a 6th toenail? Watch as THE DOCTORS does a LIVE procedure in studio! Then, the Stool Squad is back to answer your burning questions! Want fast-food faster? A-list nutritionist Keri Glassman shares her kid-approved recipes! Next, would you change your future child’s eye color? Plus, do at-home bunion correctors really work? Then, why some people are turning to drinking vinegar for better gut health! Could it be doing more harm than good?</desc>
    <date>20181016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250706232617 +0000" stop="20250707001438 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>A Test to Predict Cancer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>If you could take a test that would tell you whether or not you would get cancer, would you take it? And, is diet soda better for you than the than the real thing? Dr. Lisa says that everything should be consumed in moderation.</desc>
    <date>20080918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01005.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250707001438 +0000" stop="20250707010103 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Weight Loss Extravaganza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E82</episode-num>
    <desc>The weight is over! From abuse victim to revenge body! From sickness to six packs! From bullied teen to inspirational hero! See story after story of incredible weight loss transformations without surgery that will blow your mind! Plus, meet the biggest weight loss success story in THE DOCTORS history!</desc>
    <date>20180108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
