<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250716235430 +0000" stop="20250717014635 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets And Spies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Former secret agent Geoffrey Larkin arrives in the village of Midsomer Parva and heads for a visit to Allenby House, a country manor run by former spies, the Frazer family as a safe house. With an air of hostility towards Geoffrey, it is not long before he is murdered, by some who blame the 'beast of Midsomer', who believe the creature exists. Barnaby, a former spy himself, gets involved in the case.</desc>
    <date>20090729</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vHfe8ppjSF0mRgOp6qjKLy4z3Rp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717014635 +0000" stop="20250717033843 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Glitch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>George Jeffers, a professor of Midsomer University and cycling enthusiast, threatens to go public, he is found with his state-of-the-art invention Kernel Logic. This angers American software boss Clinton Finn and fears he will lose millions if the truth is exposed. When schoolteacher Emily Harte is killed in a hit and run, things become more complicated. With someone known as 'the Bucketman' throwing red paint over cars belonging to employees of a local computer firm, among others.</desc>
    <date>20090923</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/afTP5yk79dy4gbEptEMKaBOHU1n.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717033843 +0000" stop="20250717052550 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Small Mercies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In Little Worthy, model maker Bob Moss was just going to open his beloved model village, when he stumbled across the body of young Richard Tanner. He had been stabbed and his corpse tied down like Gulliver in the stories of Lilliput. Barnaby and Jones start questioning all the villagers and discover many quirky characters in the process. When the girl Richard was secretly meeting in the grounds of the model village, is murdered during the Crazy Craft Race.</desc>
    <date>20091028</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ul1WbnrnL6fq12EhKE7EeN6h4H.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717052550 +0000" stop="20250717071501 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Creeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A cat burglar known as 'the Creeper' could be responsible for murder, not just burglaries. When a writer friend David Roper is found smothered in bed on the Chettham family estate, a few days after arriving. The police soon learn that Mr Roper had been planning to write a book that could have exposed many Chettham family secrets of years past. That would make someone quiet uneasy and edgy. The mystery deepens when a second victim who knew the family is shot in woodland.</desc>
    <date>20100127</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/67pfleWseGdwgfoyaz7lkXU9Trl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717071501 +0000" stop="20250717090157 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Great And The Good</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A school teacher Connie Bishop, Nancy Carroll, who is known to sleepwalk, begins to believe that she has slit the throats of her mentor and a local handyman. Her friends are not convinced that she is to blame; neither does Barnaby. A local philanthropist and his social climbing wife are planning the annual Frobisher night -- will it go ahead without a hitch? The detectives begin to piece the puzzle together and catch the killer.</desc>
    <date>20100414</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pokyn3NiCdIF76a3yNBkRNxoWHZ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717090157 +0000" stop="20250717104825 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Point Of Balance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Midsomer is buzzing with excitement at the arrival of the annual Paramount Dance Extravaganza.</desc>
    <date>20200121</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/27Ax9f8gXjF6OrRsjXzleYTvXHZ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717104825 +0000" stop="20250717123454 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Miniature Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Prolific real estate agent Alexander Beauvoisin is murdered in front of a crowd.</desc>
    <date>20200204</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1m4K5twN6vzz9ZJTAdqLbmvSpdR.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717123454 +0000" stop="20250717142135 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Sting Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Deddingtons thriving bee Empire has put Granville Norton on the map.</desc>
    <date>20200211</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rlsRe6wl0UcXmYOb25YuPgTNV7g.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717142135 +0000" stop="20250717160752 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>With Baited Breath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Fishermen and women flock to catch a giant fish that is said to lurk in the lake.</desc>
    <date>20200218</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g7gUcuBy8bqcLt7jdyoKy0qynVH.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717160752 +0000" stop="20250717180748 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Garden Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Midsomer Deverell are angered over plans by the Inkpen family to convert the public memorial garden into a tea shop. When Elspeth Inkpen's daughter 'Fliss' is found murdered in the garden, shortly after a village meeting, Barnaby and Troy suspect that someone may be determined to stop the destruction. As their investigations continue, they discover a web of snobbery, greed, illegitimacy and mourning.</desc>
    <date>20000910</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wJ5m7R7576zeEsXefNCnjI5Yt0j.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717180748 +0000" stop="20250717200641 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Destroying Angel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gregory Chambers, manager of the Easterly Grange Hotel, goes missing just before the funeral of Karl Wainwright, his employer, after venturing into the woods to collect wild mushrooms. His wife tells everyone, including the police, that nothing is untoward. During a search of the woods, a severed hand is found. The case becomes more complex when the beneficiaries of Wainwright's will start receiving death threats.</desc>
    <date>20010826</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gnSefZ3VHWU2eAXp6qOQT0f72iT.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717200641 +0000" stop="20250717220509 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Electric Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Not only do Midsomer Parva's wheat fields include crop circles, they also contain an added mystery element, when the naked body of a dead man is found. It is later discovered that he was first electrocuted, has puncture marks on his back, and a chunk of his hair missing. Barnaby and Troy have their work cut out with rivalries, secret affairs and loves, jealousies and hatred.</desc>
    <date>20010902</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/otd1IjvygEXA3skbVhZNPVCUhhA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250717220509 +0000" stop="20250718000356 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Who Killed Cock Robin?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The village doctor of Newton Magna involves the police after he accidentally hits a man in the road following a party; however, the injured man is nowhere to be found. Then the body of Robin Wooliscroft, who disappeared over a year before, is pulled up from a well. The detectives come up against suspicions, lies, disapproving families, resentments and hidden secrets before another victim is found and they get to the truth.</desc>
    <date>20010909</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eJYOgPrqzQiuvr63lelb4c4d3aw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250718000356 +0000" stop="20250718020249 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Autumn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the remote hamlet of Goodman's Land, local postman and casanova Dave Cutler gets murdered whilst doing his early postal delivery. Barnaby and Troy, with WPC Jay Nash, start investigating. They discover Dave had slept with many women in the village. A witness later recalls having heard strange 1950s dance music before the murder. When others become victims to the killer, the detectives need to find a possible link to connect the murders before Jay gets into a perilous situation herself.</desc>
    <date>20010916</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vIBCvCqI7Iz9pgStgDfD9M5XNgj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
