<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4">
    <display-name>Made It Myself TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/89dc782a-d85c-468c-8e3c-a5973d824ec6/MIMTV_Logo_1500x1000_LightBackgrounds.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721010428 +0000" stop="20250721012017 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Lace Trim</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Add a simple lace trim to anything!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929355-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721012017 +0000" stop="20250721030202 +0000">
    <title>Fabric to Fashion Episode 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Fabric to Fashion is a reality show featuring designers and sewist from all over the world. Designers are given a challenge, then we follow the guests designing in their own sewing spaces. Angela Wolf mentors and guides the designers throughout each challenge, and often throws in a few extra twists!</desc>
    <date>20241103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/161787699-0.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721030202 +0000" stop="20250721031912 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Happy Halloween! - My Digital Art Process PLUS SpeedPaint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What’s up guys! Are you ready for a brand new Frog Food? Today we are going through a total breakdown of this Halloween themed piece. From sketches to final touches, we’ve gotcha covered!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928498-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721031912 +0000" stop="20250721040558 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Draw With Me - Paper Dolls</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! For today's Frog Food we are making paper dolls from start to finish. From poses to clothing we've got ya covered, so sit back, relax and enjoy!!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928496-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721040558 +0000" stop="20250721043423 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: How to Draw Hands Tutorial</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! for this Frog food we are going to learn how to draw hands! Thats right, it's a tutorial! You asked for it, and I delivered. Well, to the best of my abilities. I am by no means an expert but I am happy to show you all how I learned.</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928495-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721043423 +0000" stop="20250721044400 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Re-Drawing My Old Art From When I Was 5 Years Old!</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! In this Frog Food i'm redrawing my old art from when I was 5 years old!! I know right, it's been a long time. Check out how far i've come in an ALL NEW Frog Food</desc>
    <date>20220106</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928490-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721044400 +0000" stop="20250721050219 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Drawing Commentary - Do you Actually NEED an Art Style</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up folks, for this Frog Food we are imagining Toya &amp; Bella as Secret Agents in this moody, monochromatic vibe. So get ready for another Speed Paint and Commentary!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928508-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721050219 +0000" stop="20250721052059 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Balancing Art and Life - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In today's video we'll be discussing the balancing act between art and life. From our personal struggles to solutions we cover it all! Sit back, relax and enjoy!!</desc>
    <date>20200103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928504-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721052059 +0000" stop="20250721053819 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: DIY Anime Poster "METRO" - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This is our first Frog Food of 2021 so let's hit the ground running and try something new: A detailed background! But not too detailed ... remember, baby steps. Join me for a little speed drawing and commentary!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928500-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721053819 +0000" stop="20250721054938 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: I Turned My Dog Into An Anime Character</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Time for another frog food today we’re gonna turn my Dog Bowie into an anime character with a pop punk style. From inspo to highlights we got it covered. So sit back, relax, and enjoy!</desc>
    <date>20200103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928507-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721054938 +0000" stop="20250721060338 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Attempting Comics - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What’s up guys, for today’s Frog Food we’re exploring new horizons in this cool comic style piece. From inspiration to workflow we gotcha covered, so sit back, relax, and enjoy.</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928494-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721060338 +0000" stop="20250721065942 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 17</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929267-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721065942 +0000" stop="20250721075525 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 18</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929266-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721075525 +0000" stop="20250721085100 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 19</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929265-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721085100 +0000" stop="20250721085725 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Butterfly DIY Wall Decor</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Decorate your walls with handmade butterfly decor!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928694-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721085725 +0000" stop="20250721090254 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Pretty Pendant Charm Necklace Wine Cork Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a pretty pendant charm necklace out of a simple wine cork!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928691-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721090254 +0000" stop="20250721090842 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Rainbow Perler Bead Pattern</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to create a rainbow perler bead pattern.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928686-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721090842 +0000" stop="20250721091406 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Spring Wood Slice Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a spring wood slice wreath.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928684-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721091406 +0000" stop="20250721091909 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage China Flower Display</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a vintage Chinese flower display.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928682-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721091909 +0000" stop="20250721092352 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage Plate DIY Cake Stand</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a beautiful vintage plate cake stand.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928680-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721092352 +0000" stop="20250721092813 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Cute Scrap Paper Garland</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ready for an excuse to use up those scrap paper pieces that have been lying around? This Cute Scrap Paper Garland is the perfect craft that can clear up some of those extra paper pieces. Plus, you get a really cute DIY home decor garland that you can make and use for all different kinds of occasions. No matter where you hang this homemade garland, it is sure to get complimented. Plus, using die cuts make creating this DIY garland super quick and easy!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928558-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721092813 +0000" stop="20250721093504 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage Inspired DIY Barrette Hair Accessories</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make vintage inspired barrette hair accessories.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928681-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721093504 +0000" stop="20250721094303 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Ribbons DIY Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a ribbons wreath.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928685-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721094303 +0000" stop="20250721095251 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Candy Drawer DIY Party Favor</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This cute Candy Drawer DIY Party Favor is an excellent, customizable DIY favor for just about any occasion. Fill the tiny drawer with candy and leave them on tables as a DIY wedding favor, or fill them with kind notes and hand out to your friends the next time you host girls' night. No matter what you use it for, this free paper craft idea is a great little project! Check out this video tutorial to learn how to make them.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928561-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721095251 +0000" stop="20250721095847 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Adorable Flower Pencil Toppers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This Adorable Flower Pencil Toppers is such a quick and cute craft that is perfect for the back to school season. Make your pencils stand out this year, or just brighten up your day by creating these tissue paper flowers. Everyone is going to love your DIY paper flowers and ask how you made your pencils. Whether you are decorating gel pencils or just regular #2 pencils, these die cut flowers are guaranteed to add a fun and pretty touch to your school supplies!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928562-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721095847 +0000" stop="20250721100530 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Cherry Blossom Tissue Paper Flower</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Subtle spring accents, like this Cherry Blossom Tissue Paper Flower branch, can add some lovely touches to your home. This free flower craft idea shows you how to make small tissue paper flowers and attach them to a branch for a realistic-looking faux flower. Once you create this cute DIY flower craft, you can add them to a vase, hang them on the wall, or combine them with other floral ideas for a unique DIY bouquet. These tissue paper cherry blossoms make excellent springtime decorations!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928560-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721100530 +0000" stop="20250721101458 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Coffee Filter Bouquet</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This Coffee Filter Bouquet is a gorgeous paper flower tutorial for your big day. Make a DIY bridal bouquet out of coffee filters with this free crafting video. Combining dyed coffee filters and die cutting techniques, this forever flower bouquet is a charming and secretly cheap way to make a wedding bouquet. Consider making this homemade bouquet idea for a wedding, baby shower, or for spring accents in your home. You never have to worry about it wilting!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928559-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721101458 +0000" stop="20250721102159 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Felt Flower Corsage Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Watch this video tutorial to learn how to make a colorful Felt Flower Corsage Craft. Adding a chic and cute DIY corsage to your event can really make your quirky and crafty nature stand out. This craft tutorial shows you how to create felt flowers and combine then with a pipe cleaner to make a charming DIY corsage. This felt craft idea would be a fantastic wearable craft to make for bridal shower guests or the flower girl at your wedding.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928557-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721102159 +0000" stop="20250721102922 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Fleece Flower DIY Headband</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sometimes it can really be a challenge finding the exact style you want from a headband. This Fleece Flower DIY Headband shows you how you can make the perfect floral headband just the way you want. This DIY headband project is the perfect flirty and girly headband that makes a great DIY gift too. If you have a friend that loves flowers, or are even contemplating what to get your flower girl in your wedding make them this handmade headband and they will be in love!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928556-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721102922 +0000" stop="20250721103438 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Make a Spring Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Watch this DIY video tutorial to learn How to make a Spring Wreath. Adding colorful spring wreaths to your home is a fabulous way to make your space blossom with very little effort. Follow along with this home decor craft tutorial to create a stunning and bright project. This DIY craft is easy to make, and you can use just about any fabric you would like. Get started on your own DIY wreath for the most cheerful of seasons!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928555-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721103438 +0000" stop="20250721104427 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Make Wedding Invitations and Programs</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Many brides-to-be are asking How to Make Wedding Invitations and Programs that are unique enough to reflect their style but don't cost an arm and a leg. That's where this DIY wedding video tutorial comes in. Learn how to use embossing and die cutting techniques to make absolutely adorable and spring-themed wedding invitations and programs. Wedding crafts like the ones featured in this DIY craft video help you save money while still adding a personal touch to your big, beautiful day.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928554-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721104427 +0000" stop="20250721105537 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Mother's Day Card Box</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Any mom or grandma likes presents that are made by hand. This box of cards is a perfect size to carry in your purse and bring out when someone asks to see the kids. The box also holds gift cards, business cards and small gifts- style it to fit any occasion! The Mothers Day Card Box is the perfect way to show mom you care all the while giving her something practical to use. Whether she uses this adorable box to hold keepsakes or important business card, it is sure to keep her smiling for days to come.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928552-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721105537 +0000" stop="20250721110529 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Use the Sizzix Twist and Style Tool</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ready to start making perfect flower stems and friendship bracelets? This How to Use the Sizzix Twist and Style Tool guide shows you just how easy using this tool is. Plus, this is a great tool you can use for all different kinds of crafts that require a little extra twist. Whether you are making flowers and need a stem, or you are working with wire on some DIY jewelry projects, this tool can become your go to! This Sizzix tool is worth giving a try if you want to expand your craft tools collection!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928553-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721110529 +0000" stop="20250721111314 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Personalized DIY Luggage Tag</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Going on a trip? Need a gift tag? Looking for a cute purse accessory? This Personalized DIY Luggage Tag is the perfect craft that can serve a number of purposes. Not only is this the perfect die cut craft that you can completely personalize and make your own, but you can also complete this craft in less than an hour. If you really need a new luggage tag for a trip but don't want to run to the store and buy one, this craft video can show you how easy it is to make your own!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928551-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721111314 +0000" stop="20250721112947 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Potted Faux Flower Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Learn how to make a Potted Faux Flower Craft as a DIY centerpiece for springtime, bridal showers, baby showers, and more! This video tutorial shows you how to make a faux flower as well as a vase for your brand new bloom. This easy die cut craft is perfect for spring decorating, and unlike real plants, this flower craft is low maintenance and can go anywhere in your home! Be sure to watch this DIY craft tutorial for a spring craft idea you'll love. "</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928550-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721112947 +0000" stop="20250721114610 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Toolbox Father's Day Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>While picking out the perfect gift for dad can be tempting, sometimes a gift card is an even better idea. As they say, it is the thought that counts! With this Toolbox Fathers Day Craft, you can learn how to make the perfect gift for dad. By creating a DIY craft to keep the gift card tucked into, you give your dad some handmade love and something useful at the same time. Plus, you could easily use this homemade box to wrap up some homemade candies, as well.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928548-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721114610 +0000" stop="20250721115308 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Table Top Tree Decoration</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>You will not believe how easy it is to make this adorable Table Top Tree Decoration. Whether you are making it for a summer party or for the holidays this is a great quick and easy decor craft. Plus, this is such an easy craft project that you can get your kids in on making them too. Now, you have a great indoor DIY kids craft, and you are making some fun and adorable center pieces for your next party. There are so many different reasons and ways you could make your own tree!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928549-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721115308 +0000" stop="20250721115905 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Fizzy Lavender Homemade Bath Soak Recipe</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a fizzy lavender bath soak.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928692-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721115905 +0000" stop="20250721120409 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: DIY Spa Gifts in a Jar</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a cool spa gifts collection in a jar.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928693-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721120409 +0000" stop="20250721120743 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Beachy Driftwood DIY Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a beachy driftwood wreath.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928696-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721120743 +0000" stop="20250721122224 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Jacket Sleeves</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Angela gives advice on how to make jacket sleeves.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929356-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721122224 +0000" stop="20250721123705 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Jeans &amp; Pants That Fit</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Want a better fit on your favorite pair of pants? Check out this video to learn how!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929360-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721123705 +0000" stop="20250721125321 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Kimono</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a stylish kimono!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929342-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721125321 +0000" stop="20250721130757 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Knit Necklines</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Angela teaches how to make a neckline with knit fabrics.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929349-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721130757 +0000" stop="20250721132346 +0000">
    <title>It's Sew Easy: Lace Trim</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Add a simple lace trim to anything!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929355-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721132346 +0000" stop="20250721150532 +0000">
    <title>Fabric to Fashion Episode 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Fabric to Fashion is a reality show featuring designers and sewist from all over the world. Designers are given a challenge, then we follow the guests designing in their own sewing spaces. Angela Wolf mentors and guides the designers throughout each challenge, and often throws in a few extra twists!</desc>
    <date>20241103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/161787699-0.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721150532 +0000" stop="20250721152241 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Happy Halloween! - My Digital Art Process PLUS SpeedPaint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What’s up guys! Are you ready for a brand new Frog Food? Today we are going through a total breakdown of this Halloween themed piece. From sketches to final touches, we’ve gotcha covered!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928498-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721152241 +0000" stop="20250721160928 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Draw With Me - Paper Dolls</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! For today's Frog Food we are making paper dolls from start to finish. From poses to clothing we've got ya covered, so sit back, relax and enjoy!!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928496-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721160928 +0000" stop="20250721163752 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: How to Draw Hands Tutorial</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! for this Frog food we are going to learn how to draw hands! Thats right, it's a tutorial! You asked for it, and I delivered. Well, to the best of my abilities. I am by no means an expert but I am happy to show you all how I learned.</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928495-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721163752 +0000" stop="20250721164729 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Re-Drawing My Old Art From When I Was 5 Years Old!</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up guys! In this Frog Food i'm redrawing my old art from when I was 5 years old!! I know right, it's been a long time. Check out how far i've come in an ALL NEW Frog Food</desc>
    <date>20220106</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928490-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721164729 +0000" stop="20250721170548 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Drawing Commentary - Do you Actually NEED an Art Style</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What's up folks, for this Frog Food we are imagining Toya &amp; Bella as Secret Agents in this moody, monochromatic vibe. So get ready for another Speed Paint and Commentary!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928508-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721170548 +0000" stop="20250721172429 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Balancing Art and Life - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In today's video we'll be discussing the balancing act between art and life. From our personal struggles to solutions we cover it all! Sit back, relax and enjoy!!</desc>
    <date>20200103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928504-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721172429 +0000" stop="20250721174149 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: DIY Anime Poster "METRO" - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This is our first Frog Food of 2021 so let's hit the ground running and try something new: A detailed background! But not too detailed ... remember, baby steps. Join me for a little speed drawing and commentary!</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928500-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721174149 +0000" stop="20250721175307 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: I Turned My Dog Into An Anime Character</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Time for another frog food today we’re gonna turn my Dog Bowie into an anime character with a pop punk style. From inspo to highlights we got it covered. So sit back, relax, and enjoy!</desc>
    <date>20200103</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928507-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721175307 +0000" stop="20250721180708 +0000">
    <title>Digital Painting - Frog Food: Attempting Comics - Speed Paint</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>What’s up guys, for today’s Frog Food we’re exploring new horizons in this cool comic style piece. From inspiration to workflow we gotcha covered, so sit back, relax, and enjoy.</desc>
    <date>20210105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928494-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721180708 +0000" stop="20250721190311 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 17</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929267-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721190311 +0000" stop="20250721195854 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 18</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929266-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721195854 +0000" stop="20250721205430 +0000">
    <title>For What It's Worth: Episode 19</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>For What It's Worth is an exciting and compelling new quiz show hosted by Fern Britton who is assisted by a different BBC antiques expert each day.</desc>
    <date>20160101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929265-1.jpeg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721205430 +0000" stop="20250721210055 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Butterfly DIY Wall Decor</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Decorate your walls with handmade butterfly decor!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928694-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721210055 +0000" stop="20250721210624 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Pretty Pendant Charm Necklace Wine Cork Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a pretty pendant charm necklace out of a simple wine cork!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928691-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721210624 +0000" stop="20250721211212 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Rainbow Perler Bead Pattern</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to create a rainbow perler bead pattern.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928686-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721211212 +0000" stop="20250721211735 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Spring Wood Slice Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a spring wood slice wreath.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928684-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721211735 +0000" stop="20250721212239 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage China Flower Display</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a vintage Chinese flower display.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928682-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721212239 +0000" stop="20250721212721 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage Plate DIY Cake Stand</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a beautiful vintage plate cake stand.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928680-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721212721 +0000" stop="20250721213143 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Cute Scrap Paper Garland</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ready for an excuse to use up those scrap paper pieces that have been lying around? This Cute Scrap Paper Garland is the perfect craft that can clear up some of those extra paper pieces. Plus, you get a really cute DIY home decor garland that you can make and use for all different kinds of occasions. No matter where you hang this homemade garland, it is sure to get complimented. Plus, using die cuts make creating this DIY garland super quick and easy!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928558-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721213143 +0000" stop="20250721213833 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Vintage Inspired DIY Barrette Hair Accessories</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make vintage inspired barrette hair accessories.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928681-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721213833 +0000" stop="20250721214632 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Ribbons DIY Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a ribbons wreath.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928685-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721214632 +0000" stop="20250721215621 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Candy Drawer DIY Party Favor</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This cute Candy Drawer DIY Party Favor is an excellent, customizable DIY favor for just about any occasion. Fill the tiny drawer with candy and leave them on tables as a DIY wedding favor, or fill them with kind notes and hand out to your friends the next time you host girls' night. No matter what you use it for, this free paper craft idea is a great little project! Check out this video tutorial to learn how to make them.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928561-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721215621 +0000" stop="20250721220216 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Adorable Flower Pencil Toppers</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This Adorable Flower Pencil Toppers is such a quick and cute craft that is perfect for the back to school season. Make your pencils stand out this year, or just brighten up your day by creating these tissue paper flowers. Everyone is going to love your DIY paper flowers and ask how you made your pencils. Whether you are decorating gel pencils or just regular #2 pencils, these die cut flowers are guaranteed to add a fun and pretty touch to your school supplies!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928562-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721220216 +0000" stop="20250721220859 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Cherry Blossom Tissue Paper Flower</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Subtle spring accents, like this Cherry Blossom Tissue Paper Flower branch, can add some lovely touches to your home. This free flower craft idea shows you how to make small tissue paper flowers and attach them to a branch for a realistic-looking faux flower. Once you create this cute DIY flower craft, you can add them to a vase, hang them on the wall, or combine them with other floral ideas for a unique DIY bouquet. These tissue paper cherry blossoms make excellent springtime decorations!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928560-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721220859 +0000" stop="20250721221828 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Coffee Filter Bouquet</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>This Coffee Filter Bouquet is a gorgeous paper flower tutorial for your big day. Make a DIY bridal bouquet out of coffee filters with this free crafting video. Combining dyed coffee filters and die cutting techniques, this forever flower bouquet is a charming and secretly cheap way to make a wedding bouquet. Consider making this homemade bouquet idea for a wedding, baby shower, or for spring accents in your home. You never have to worry about it wilting!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928559-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721221828 +0000" stop="20250721222529 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Felt Flower Corsage Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Watch this video tutorial to learn how to make a colorful Felt Flower Corsage Craft. Adding a chic and cute DIY corsage to your event can really make your quirky and crafty nature stand out. This craft tutorial shows you how to create felt flowers and combine then with a pipe cleaner to make a charming DIY corsage. This felt craft idea would be a fantastic wearable craft to make for bridal shower guests or the flower girl at your wedding.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928557-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721222529 +0000" stop="20250721223252 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Fleece Flower DIY Headband</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sometimes it can really be a challenge finding the exact style you want from a headband. This Fleece Flower DIY Headband shows you how you can make the perfect floral headband just the way you want. This DIY headband project is the perfect flirty and girly headband that makes a great DIY gift too. If you have a friend that loves flowers, or are even contemplating what to get your flower girl in your wedding make them this handmade headband and they will be in love!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928556-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721223252 +0000" stop="20250721223808 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Make a Spring Wreath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Watch this DIY video tutorial to learn How to make a Spring Wreath. Adding colorful spring wreaths to your home is a fabulous way to make your space blossom with very little effort. Follow along with this home decor craft tutorial to create a stunning and bright project. This DIY craft is easy to make, and you can use just about any fabric you would like. Get started on your own DIY wreath for the most cheerful of seasons!</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928555-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721223808 +0000" stop="20250721224756 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Make Wedding Invitations and Programs</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Many brides-to-be are asking How to Make Wedding Invitations and Programs that are unique enough to reflect their style but don't cost an arm and a leg. That's where this DIY wedding video tutorial comes in. Learn how to use embossing and die cutting techniques to make absolutely adorable and spring-themed wedding invitations and programs. Wedding crafts like the ones featured in this DIY craft video help you save money while still adding a personal touch to your big, beautiful day.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928554-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721224756 +0000" stop="20250721225906 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Mother's Day Card Box</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Any mom or grandma likes presents that are made by hand. This box of cards is a perfect size to carry in your purse and bring out when someone asks to see the kids. The box also holds gift cards, business cards and small gifts- style it to fit any occasion! The Mothers Day Card Box is the perfect way to show mom you care all the while giving her something practical to use. Whether she uses this adorable box to hold keepsakes or important business card, it is sure to keep her smiling for days to come.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928552-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721225906 +0000" stop="20250721230859 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: How to Use the Sizzix Twist and Style Tool</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ready to start making perfect flower stems and friendship bracelets? This How to Use the Sizzix Twist and Style Tool guide shows you just how easy using this tool is. Plus, this is a great tool you can use for all different kinds of crafts that require a little extra twist. Whether you are making flowers and need a stem, or you are working with wire on some DIY jewelry projects, this tool can become your go to! This Sizzix tool is worth giving a try if you want to expand your craft tools collection!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928553-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721230859 +0000" stop="20250721231644 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Personalized DIY Luggage Tag</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Going on a trip? Need a gift tag? Looking for a cute purse accessory? This Personalized DIY Luggage Tag is the perfect craft that can serve a number of purposes. Not only is this the perfect die cut craft that you can completely personalize and make your own, but you can also complete this craft in less than an hour. If you really need a new luggage tag for a trip but don't want to run to the store and buy one, this craft video can show you how easy it is to make your own!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928551-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721231644 +0000" stop="20250721233316 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Potted Faux Flower Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>"Learn how to make a Potted Faux Flower Craft as a DIY centerpiece for springtime, bridal showers, baby showers, and more! This video tutorial shows you how to make a faux flower as well as a vase for your brand new bloom. This easy die cut craft is perfect for spring decorating, and unlike real plants, this flower craft is low maintenance and can go anywhere in your home! Be sure to watch this DIY craft tutorial for a spring craft idea you'll love. "</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928550-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721233316 +0000" stop="20250721234940 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Toolbox Father's Day Craft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>While picking out the perfect gift for dad can be tempting, sometimes a gift card is an even better idea. As they say, it is the thought that counts! With this Toolbox Fathers Day Craft, you can learn how to make the perfect gift for dad. By creating a DIY craft to keep the gift card tucked into, you give your dad some handmade love and something useful at the same time. Plus, you could easily use this homemade box to wrap up some homemade candies, as well.</desc>
    <date>20160105</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928548-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721234940 +0000" stop="20250721235637 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Table Top Tree Decoration</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>You will not believe how easy it is to make this adorable Table Top Tree Decoration. Whether you are making it for a summer party or for the holidays this is a great quick and easy decor craft. Plus, this is such an easy craft project that you can get your kids in on making them too. Now, you have a great indoor DIY kids craft, and you are making some fun and adorable center pieces for your next party. There are so many different reasons and ways you could make your own tree!</desc>
    <date>20170101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928549-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250721235637 +0000" stop="20250722000234 +0000">
    <title>FaveCrafts: Fizzy Lavender Homemade Bath Soak Recipe</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Learn how to make a fizzy lavender bath soak.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153928692-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250722000234 +0000" stop="20250722003009 +0000">
    <title>She's Crafty: Crafty Idol</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Wine racks, custom dinnerware, and photo edits!</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929506-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250722003009 +0000" stop="20250722005748 +0000">
    <title>She's Crafty: Crafty Do Over</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A groovy use for blah bar stools. Make them into chic seating or even tables. Turn a tuna can into a trendy time piece.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929511-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-65b80306e5cf85050598aba4" start="20250722005748 +0000" stop="20250722012526 +0000">
    <title>She's Crafty: Crafty Flashback</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Wendy takes you through some craft projects of the past.</desc>
    <date>20230101</date>
    <icon src="https://ingest-assets.wurl.com/429429/153929512-1.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
