<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722011216 +0000" stop="20250722015934 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And Illegal?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Thirty-year-old mother of four Melissa Dilan-Hernandez made headlines when she was charged with unlawful sexual activity with certain minors, stemming from her relationship with her fiancé, T.J., who is 17 years old and the father of her 4-month-old child. Melissa is facing up to 15 years in prison and may have to register as a sex offender, yet she says she still doesn’t consider their relationship a crime. How does she justify her love affair with a minor -- and planning a pregnancy with him? T.J. says he wants to spend the rest of his life with Melissa -- but is he willing to wait for her if she goes to jail? And, could their romance stand in the way of his aspirations of becoming a U.S. Marine or police officer? T.J.’s father, Ed, and stepmother, Sea, weigh in with their thoughts on the relationship. Do they approve? Plus, don’t miss Dr. Phil’s stern advice for Melissa and T.J. -- and for any teen who may be blindsided by love.</desc>
    <date>20121120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722015934 +0000" stop="20250722024637 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Slaughtered for Teen Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E77</episode-num>
    <desc>Did 21 yo Erin Caffey plot to have her family killed, or was she the victim of puppy love gone terribly wrong? In a Dr Phil Exclusive, she speaks out from prison about the brutal killing.</desc>
    <date>20140203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12077.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722024637 +0000" stop="20250722033315 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Teen Daughter Killed for Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E315</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his exclusive interview with Erin Caffey, who was sentenced to two life sentences in prison plus 25 years for the murders of her mother and two little brothers in 2008. What does she say was her role in the brutal slayings? And, Erin’s father, Terry, says he has forgiven his daughter -- will her revelations to Dr. Phil cause him to have a change of heart?</desc>
    <date>20140204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12315.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722033315 +0000" stop="20250722041949 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Nanny Affair (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Affairs, fights, lies and dark secrets threaten a marriage</desc>
    <date>20070912</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6001.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722041949 +0000" stop="20250722050809 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Nanny Affair (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E302</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his look into the nanny affair that shattered a marriage</desc>
    <date>20070913</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6302.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722050809 +0000" stop="20250722054748 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Exclusive: Co-Eds and the Catfish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E416</episode-num>
    <desc>Seven college students recount their harrowing experience of being deceived by an online predator.</desc>
    <date>20150424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13416.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722054748 +0000" stop="20250722063510 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Most Unusual Love Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E98</episode-num>
    <desc>One-time high school sweethearts Tracey and Doug started having marriage problems when Doug admitted to having an affair with a transgender female, Essence.</desc>
    <date>20120222</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10098.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722063510 +0000" stop="20250722072221 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Dads</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E105</episode-num>
    <desc>They threaten, scream, intimidate and even bite. They’re not tantrum-throwing tots, but bullying dads.</desc>
    <date>20070502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722072221 +0000" stop="20250722080646 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Deadly Love Affair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E130</episode-num>
    <desc>A headline making story of a husband’s affair with a co-worker that led to murder. Now the wife and the mistress come face to face for the first time.</desc>
    <date>20150423</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722080646 +0000" stop="20250722084706 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting With Pills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The first line of treatment for the millions of kids who are diagnosed with Attention Deficit Disorder (ADD) or Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) is often drugs. Is medication the best treatment?</desc>
    <date>20040928</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722084706 +0000" stop="20250722093418 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Drew Peterson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E51</episode-num>
    <desc>The case of missing Stacy Peterson is discussed.</desc>
    <date>20081110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722093418 +0000" stop="20250722102221 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>What Happens To Peterson's Children?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E404</episode-num>
    <desc>The children of Drew Peterson deal with the reality of their father's suspected involvement in their mother's murder and stepmother's disappearance.</desc>
    <date>20090521</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7404.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722102221 +0000" stop="20250722110836 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Pregnant for 3 Years and 7 Months?!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Guests claim their pregnancies have lasted well over 9 months– Shayna for one year and Zona for more than three-and-a-half years.</desc>
    <date>20181031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17035.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722110836 +0000" stop="20250722115546 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Children Caught in the Crossfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Drug use, faking a heart attack, parental alienation – can these exes stop making accusations and come together for the sake of their children?</desc>
    <date>20131113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722115546 +0000" stop="20250722124344 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Living on the Edge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E74</episode-num>
    <desc>How can you change a racist's thinking? How can someone who has had a racist viewpoint his entire life learn to accept a biracial granddaughter? Catch up on Charlie's story.</desc>
    <date>20060112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4074.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722124344 +0000" stop="20250722133036 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Family On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Suzanne says her sister, Jennifer, is a neglectful parent, and she's considering taking action to gain custody of Jennifer’s three children. Suzanne says when the family's home caught fire, Jennifer saved her daughter's friend's baby and left her own children to fend for themselves. Jennifer's 16-year-old daughter, Alyssa, suffered a broken ankle after jumping from the second story, and her 12-year-old son ran back into the burning house to save his 9-year-old sister. Jennifer maintains she is a good mom, and says there was too much smoke and fire to go back for her kids. Was there more she could have done? Is there truth behind Suzanne's accusations? Then, hear Alyssa's emotional plea to Jennifer. Will it make an impact? Don't miss this compelling, all-new Dr. Phil.</desc>
    <date>20121101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722133036 +0000" stop="20250722141644 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Affairs of the Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Can married people be friends with someone of the opposite sex without sex getting in the way? At what point does a friendly relationship become an affair of the heart or emotional infidelity? Meet Randy, who says his wife, Amanda, has crossed that line.</desc>
    <date>20090304</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722141644 +0000" stop="20250722150446 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Brat-Proof Your Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The challenge of taming tantrums in young children is examined.</desc>
    <date>20101202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722150446 +0000" stop="20250722155448 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Munchausen Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil takes goes inside the unthinkable: making your own child sick to fulfill a disturbing need for attention. The idea might sound unimaginable, but for people with a psychological disorder called Munchausen by Proxy, it's irresistible. Note: Viewer discretion is advised.</desc>
    <date>20071011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6013.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722155448 +0000" stop="20250722164204 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Fight Over Your Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E86</episode-num>
    <desc>"Let me take a moment to read a few lines of a heartbreaking letter of a 10-year-old boy caught in the middle of an ugly, ugly custody battle between his parents" Dr. Phil says. He reads, “I'm bawling my eyes out with the tears of sadness. Dad, I never thought I would say this, but I always think that you're with another girl or sleeping with another girl. Question for dad: Mom says she still loves you and misses you. Do you still love her? Put a check in one of the boxes: yes or no.”</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8086.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722164204 +0000" stop="20250722172927 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Why Is My Mom Faking Cancer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jessica says her mother, Patricia, claims she is defying the odds by becoming a record-setting weight lifter while simultaneously battling Stage 3 brain cancer. But Jessica insists her mother isn’t sick at all and that she is lying about her health to gain sympathy and attention. She says Patricia has been spinning stories about various medical ailments for as long as she can remember -- and it’s time to come clean. Patricia strongly denies her daughter’s accusations and insists her diagnosis and incredible survival story are real. Why does she claim Jessica is out to get her? Emotions run high when mother and daughter meet on Dr. Phil’s stage. Do Patricia’s claims hold up? And, can this mother and daughter repair their fractured relationship?</desc>
    <date>20150115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722172927 +0000" stop="20250722181656 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bullies Beware!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E106</episode-num>
    <desc>A self-proclaimed adult bully is confronted.</desc>
    <date>20110516</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9106.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722181656 +0000" stop="20250722190327 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bullies Beware Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E311</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with a self-admitted adult bully.</desc>
    <date>20110517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9311.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722190327 +0000" stop="20250722195051 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Young and Wild!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E57</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother's concern escalates as her daughter's party lifestyle spirals into substance abuse and reckless behavior.</desc>
    <date>20110201</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722195051 +0000" stop="20250722203749 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Craze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Demi Moore did it. So did Madonna and Halle Berry. This trend of older women dating younger men is called the Cougar Craze, and it’s sweeping the country. Recently, at a New York speed-dating event, "Sugar Mamas and Boy Toys," good-looking 35-year-old men wooed women over 35 who made at least $500,000 a year. Jeremy organized the event and says he was just answering a demand from affluent ladies. Was he sincere in his matchmaking or just out to make a buck? Dr. Phil talks to two women who participated in the event -- Gail, 44 and Nancy, 50. Their experiences might surprise you. Then, 51-year-old Kat says she’s no cougar; she just likes to date younger guys because men her age are set in their ways. She says her 23-year-old ex-boyfriend, Ryon, was loving, passionate and had a much higher libido than older men. Her friend, Nancy, says Kat has a great head for business, but a bad one when it comes to the opposite sex. She says young men just see dollar signs when they see Kat. Is Kat dating down, or should Nancy just butt out? And, Bobbi had an 11-year relationship with a man who was 17 years her junior, but she says once she turned 50, he saw her as too old. She wants to be in a relationship again, but not with an older man. Her son, Nathan, says someone still wet behind the ears can’t appreciate all Bobbi has to offer. Does Nathan have the right to put his foot down with his mother? Do you think it's OK for older women to date younger men? Take our poll!</desc>
    <date>20080502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722203749 +0000" stop="20250722212250 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Regret Marrying Older Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E59</episode-num>
    <desc>Brenda says she fell in love with and married her husband, Don – despite their 26-year age gap. But soon after, she claims her “Prince Charming” turned “crazy” and “temperamental.” Is their age difference at the root of their issues? Then, Bev says she’s concerned for her sister, Melanie, who married her much younger man, Devar, after meeting him on a Jamaican vacation. Is Devar in it for love, or for a green card and money? And, Dr. Phil catches up with best-selling author Mitch Albom.</desc>
    <date>20151210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722212250 +0000" stop="20250722220006 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>49-Year-Old Dad Dating Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Joni claims that Gina used to be one of her besties and that they were inseparable, from spending birthday trips out of town to girls’ nights out, often ending in Gina crashing at Joni’s house. Joni says all that changed when 23- year-old Gina began dating Joni’s 49-year-old father, David, behind her back and giving birth to David’s child. Joni says she feels betrayed by Gina and her father, even going as far as sharing her dislike for her former friend and father’s newfound romance on TikTok. Gina says the picture Joni paints of them being best friends is all a lie, but in any event, Joni needs to accept her relationship with Joni’s father. David says despite his daughter’s disapproval, he is going to continue being in a committed relationship with Gina, but that doesn’t mean he can’t also have a relationship with his daughter.</desc>
    <date>20201019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722220006 +0000" stop="20250722224253 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marrying Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E88</episode-num>
    <desc>Sixty-two-year-old Bill and his 23-year-old girlfriend, Bri, are one of the couples featured on Lifetime’s television series Marrying Millions. Bill and Bri say not only do they come from two different worlds, but they have a 39-year age gap and are at different stages of their lives – Bri wants a family and children, and Bill has been divorced twice. Bill’s first ex- wife claims Bill has a history of cheating, as she says he cheated on her and has warned Bri it could happen to her. While Bill and Bri have been together for four years, they say they are at a crossroads: what happens when he turns 70 and she is only 31? Also, they say their families don’t see eye-to-eye, which impacts their daily lives. How “healthy” is their relationship? The couple takes Dr. Phil’s “Relationship Health Profile Test” and learns the results. Plus, Dr. Phil speaks with superfans from across the U.S. and has a special announcement for them. One superfan even gets his own “Dr. Phil” tattoo ... live! You won’t want to miss this episode!</desc>
    <date>20210126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722224253 +0000" stop="20250722232220 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Dramas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Imagine your pregnant teen daughter running away to be with the baby's father -- an older man whom she met online. For Heidi, this became reality when her 15-year-old daughter, Brittney, went missing for five weeks. Dr. Phil put private investigator and former FBI Agent Harold Copus on the case to find the missing teen. See the confrontation when Harold finally locates her and her 34-year-old boyfriend. Then, find out why Brittney was even more upset when she found out what was in store for her. It's been two months; has Brittney's relationship with her mother improved? Next, Kim, 15, has run away six times in the last year, most recently making it halfway across the country to be with her married boyfriend. Why didn't her parents look for her, and why does she say she'll do anything to get away from them? Can this family learn to get things back on track? Think your child is being targeted by a sexual predator? Don’t miss Dr. Phil’s warning signs!</desc>
    <date>20061016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250722232220 +0000" stop="20250723000726 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cougars And Sugar Daddies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to dating, they say age is just a number. But what happens when the man is more than two decades older than his girlfriend, or the woman is 15 years older than her young lover? Forty-year-old Sanjay is a wealthy cosmetic surgeon who met 18-year-old Jacqueline on the Web site SugarDaddie.com. They’ve only been together for four months and are already talking marriage. Sanjay’s friend, Mike, is convinced that Jacqueline will put him right in the poorhouse! Is there a chance that Sanjay has found true love, or is Jacqueline just in it for the money? Then, 24-year-old Ryan is engaged to Angela, a woman 15 years his senior. Ryan’s friend, Donovan, fears that Angela is alienating Ryan from his buddies. Will Ryan have to choose between his college friends and his soon-to-be wife?</desc>
    <date>20061108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723000726 +0000" stop="20250723005346 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Does Age Matter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Can May-December romances really last? Christopher Knight, famous for his role as Peter on The Brady Bunch, and Adrianne Curry, winner on America's Next Top Model, began their relationship when they starred together on the reality show The Surreal Life 4, and the public watched as they planned their wedding on their own show, My Fair Brady. Now they both say their 24-year age difference is a huge problem in their chaotic marriage. Adrianne says Christopher treats her like an employee, and Christopher says if she worked for him, she would’ve been fired a long time ago. Can these two work out their generational differences? Then, 38-year-old Shelly wants to know if it’s wrong to be in a relationship with an 18-year-old friend of her son. She says he makes her feel beautiful, but wonders if she’s causing him or her children harm. Dr. Phil doesn’t mince words when he tells her his opinion.</desc>
    <date>20070921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6006.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250723005346 +0000" stop="20250723014112 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Controversy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil explores the controversial trend of older women dating much younger men. Is age really just a number? First, Pie, a 58-year-old self-admitted cougar, has been dating 24-year-old Oleg for four months -- and her best friend, Terese, strongly disapproves. Could Pie be headed for heartbreak? Then, 52-year-old divorcée Bella says her relationship with 32-year-old Eddie is the best she has ever had. Eddie says he loves Bella and doesn’t mind that she’s the same age as his mother. Does this couple see a long-term future together? And, 76-year-old Aalsa -- former Miss Cougar America -- says after 40, men go downhill! After dating younger men for four decades, what advice does she have for fellow cougars? Tune in and decide for yourself: Can a relationship really survive a significant age gap?</desc>
    <date>20141210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
