<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146">
    <display-name>Runtime</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/2bad1dfc-bfda-46ae-bd0d-36b1e07ccb47/runtime-logo_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716000000 +0000" stop="20250716014022 +0000">
    <title>7 Below</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of strangers are trapped in a time warp house where a terrible event transpired exactly 100 years prior.</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/below_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716014022 +0000" stop="20250716032059 +0000">
    <title>Cloned: The Recreator Chronicles</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Duplicates. Doubles. Recreations. They are exact copies of Craig, Tracy and Derek, three friends on a camping trip who accidentally trigger a deadly experiment left by the Recreator, a mysterious scientist with a passion for cloning. Threatened by a superior enemy who knows everything about them, will the teenagers out-smart and escape their dangerous duplicates before they are replaced?</desc>
    <date>20241011</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/cloned_the_recreator_chronicles_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716032059 +0000" stop="20250716050232 +0000">
    <title>Making Contact</title>
    <sub-title>Be Inspired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Join one man's mission to explore, document, and ultimately work towards understanding the evolving mythology of UFOs in today's world.. How far would you be willing to go, in body, mind, and heart to make contact?</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/making_contact_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716050232 +0000" stop="20250716060000 +0000">
    <title>The Insider: Reggie Yates</title>
    <sub-title>Reggie Yates in a Refugee Camp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Since the war in Syria first began, nearly 11 million people have fled their homes in search of safety. The news has been dominated by those trying to cross into Europe, but some five million people ended up in refugee camps. But what is it really like to be a 21st-century refugee?</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_insider_reggie_yates_s2_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716060000 +0000" stop="20250716074707 +0000">
    <title>The Breed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of five college kids are forced to match wits with unwelcoming residents when they fly to a "deserted" island for a party weekend.</desc>
    <date>20210819</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_breed_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716074707 +0000" stop="20250716092957 +0000">
    <title>Final Draft</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An aspiring screenwriter (James Van Der Beek) is faced with a career-altering opportunity to write a new horror script. After isolating himself for days in his apartment to finish the assignment, he starts blending reality with his subconscious, but he is determined to finish: even if it kills him.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/final_draft_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716092957 +0000" stop="20250716102045 +0000">
    <title>Celebs on the Ranch</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nine budding cowboys and cowgirls arrive in deepest Arizona at the remote Ranch they will call home. Once unpacked they meet Rancher Rick, the man they need to impress. He’ll judge, set challenges, and decide who must leave the Ranch and who makes it into the Final. The 1st challenge is a Treasure Hunt - a chance for the celebs to work together and meet their 4-legged partner for the stay.</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebs_on_the_ranch_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716102045 +0000" stop="20250716111129 +0000">
    <title>Celebs on the Ranch</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Despite jetlag, the celebs wake in good spirits and ready for the day. Their 1st challenge - identifying their horse after yesterday’s short intro. Rancher Rick briefs the celebs on grooming and bonding. Later, the celebs learn lassoing - techniques and success rates vary, but they all get into the cowboy spirit. Who will have roped themselves the first horseshoe of the competition?</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebs_on_the_ranch_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716111129 +0000" stop="20250716120000 +0000">
    <title>Celebs on the Ranch</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Day three begins with the celebs given an additional challenge to work on - the girls are pitched against the boys in a Line-Dance Off. In the Paddock, the celebs are shown how to ‘Tack-Up’ (or Saddle Up) their horses. Eventually, the celebs attempt a group lap of the arena on their four-legged friends. In the evening, the Line Dance-Off brings the house down. But who has won a horseshoe today?</desc>
    <date>20240415</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/celebs_on_the_ranch_thumbnail_16x9_widescreen_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716120000 +0000" stop="20250716134144 +0000">
    <title>Finding Love in Big Sky, Montana</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>An independent country girl takes on the task of upholding her adored grandfather's ranch. After being denied the funding needed to refurbish the ranch, she is reintroduced to her ex-boyfriend, a big-time marketing executive stationed in Denver. Admitting to herself that she needs the help, Paisley agrees to work with Josh while he is town to come up with ideas on how to raise money for the farm.</desc>
    <date>20211101</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/3d506c86cd32bfd736ee2a2e5eec4753.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716134144 +0000" stop="20250716151851 +0000">
    <title>Farm to Fork to Love</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Alice, a young and talented sous chef at NY's top restaurant, receives an invitation to judge a food competition for a prestigious annual fundraiser. Despite the dismay of Bret, her boss who is also her boyfriend, she accepts the invitation. Once she arrives in Kansas, Alice is surprised to find her former boyfriend in college, CHRISTIAN, is amongst the judges.</desc>
    <date>20210501</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a8c72d2ada6f0940435233a0815ecdbe.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716151851 +0000" stop="20250716165322 +0000">
    <title>The Penalty</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The human cost of the death penalty in America comes in for timely, gripping examination in The Penalty, the vital new documentary from British filmmakers Will Francome &amp; Mark Pizzey (One for Ten). Embedding themselves in the stories of three fascinating people affected by the American capital punishment system, the filmmakers follow the stories of a man wrongly convicted who spent 15 years on death row, a lawyer fighting against increasingly inhumane, botched executions, and a mother battling against the state’s pursuit of the death penalty for her daughter’s murderer. With recent controversial news about executions across the USA, and support for the death penalty at an all-time low, The Penalty is a riveting, forensic examination of the weightiest of issues.</desc>
    <date>20240706</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_penalty_thumbnail_7x10_poster_us.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716165322 +0000" stop="20250716184807 +0000">
    <title>Ba'al: The Storm God</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A terminally ill archaeologist attempts to cure his cancer by retrieving the ancient amulets of the storm god Ba'al.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/baal_the_storm_god_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716184807 +0000" stop="20250716203931 +0000">
    <title>Earthstorm</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A massive asteroid impact on the moon begins causing storms on earth due to the sudden changes in ocean tides. When a further examination is conducted, it's discovered that the moon's structure is now entirely unstable threatening all life on earth. With time running out, a team of scientists turn to one man, demolitions expert John Redding, in an effort to find a solution and secure the moon.</desc>
    <date>20240808</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/earthstorm_thumbnail_7x10_poster_en.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716203931 +0000" stop="20250716222813 +0000">
    <title>Icetastrophe</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>It's Christmas and everything is quiet in a peaceful town while snow covers every corner. However, the tragedy begins when a terrifying meteorite crashes and threatens to crystallize the entire population.</desc>
    <date>20221127</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/69f3fcac8bc5a6a45c438d52666cc22a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250716222813 +0000" stop="20250717000000 +0000">
    <title>Jurassic Galaxy</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the near future, a spaceship crashes on an unknown planet. Soon they encounter some of their worst fears when they discover that the planet is inhabited by monstrous dinosaurs.</desc>
    <date>20240808</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/jurassic_galaxy_thumbnail_7x10_poster_en.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f47b0b87cb6a400422f9146" start="20250717000000 +0000" stop="20250717014707 +0000">
    <title>The Breed</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A group of five college kids are forced to match wits with unwelcoming residents when they fly to a "deserted" island for a party weekend.</desc>
    <date>20210819</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/run/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_breed_thumbnail_7x10_poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
