<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250725235220 +0000" stop="20250726012524 +0000">
    <title>Kingdom Men</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Pastor Gerald’s job is on the line if he doesn’t increase the attendance of the men in the church. He decides to have a men’s retreat hoping it will fix everything. Little did he know that he’s in for the fight of his life. He realizes God didn’t call him to increase the men at the church but help them.</desc>
    <date>20200320</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/5faa3e6babb4d76418dc26807622e35c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726012524 +0000" stop="20250726030521 +0000">
    <title>Killer Baby Mama</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Calvin and Erica's tumultuous relationship takes a turn when Erica discovers she's pregnant. Unhappy with the news, Calvin decides to break up with her, moving on to date Candace. Meanwhile, Erica befriends Calvin's sick mother to gather information about his new relationship. Tragedy strikes as Candace is found murdered, and Calvin becomes a suspect. To add to his troubles, he learns that Erica manipulated his mother into changing her will.</desc>
    <date>20231002</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/gracenote/54451021ddc6abdd94161a548ecb1329.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726030521 +0000" stop="20250726044633 +0000">
    <title>Mahogany</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mo, a young woman growing up in the trenches of an urban neighborhood, faces drugs, crime, violence, and poverty. All become driving factors that will test Mo’s decision to rise above her circumstances as danger grows beyond her control.</desc>
    <date>20221111</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d7f3d28b5a2675efbf06f2ac578f7bd7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726044633 +0000" stop="20250726065905 +0000">
    <title>Heavier</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After a tragic night in the city, lovers, friends and family are forced to take on the dominating forces. Many are left to choose life or death.</desc>
    <date>20231201</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/3/gracenote/34207401145afe3f419b272900bb5a54.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726065905 +0000" stop="20250726090457 +0000">
    <title>Guns Down</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Ten criminals are invited to the estate of one of the most major drug lords in the US for the chance to win $5 million dollars and leave the drug game. However, the game could risk their lives and everything they built.</desc>
    <date>20231228</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1d64aukhIBf24Bzxl3IQ3skTWUt.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726090457 +0000" stop="20250726104845 +0000">
    <title>Gutta Mamis</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Shinette and Tierra have always vowed to ride-or-die for one another. So when opportunity knocks, it's time to do what they do best — get to the bag! It was supposed to go down like all of the others, except this time, they walk away from the scene with a body on their hands. As long as Tierra sticks to the script and doesn't utter a word, there's nothing to worry about. But once fear and desperation seep in, it's not long before she finds herself confiding in her on-again-off-again boyfriend, Duke — breaking her pact and setting off a chain of events that leaves every woman for herself. Their chase to get the bag, just might land them inside of one!</desc>
    <date>20201103</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oHPnrR8PIXO7UTllMatllptXkEp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726104845 +0000" stop="20250726121134 +0000">
    <title>Gold Digga</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Maxine is a thriving maneater that lives a lavish life based on the gifts and material things her string of wealthy men gift to her. When she finds her next sugar daddy, she encounters a big problem; his wife.</desc>
    <date>20240910</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/00f2be7e7613bf2b743216fe3360b081.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726121134 +0000" stop="20250726134850 +0000">
    <title>Hail Mary</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mary went from having everything to losing it all within a blink of an eye. She taps into her inner hustle to help her get back on her feet. What starts off as a temporary hustle leads to a path of destruction.</desc>
    <date>20240227</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/5/plex/54cfd33b-81df-4266-b0bb-657bf5d25443.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726134850 +0000" stop="20250726154926 +0000">
    <title>Fractured</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When a woman stumbles upon undeniable proof of her husband's infidelity, reality takes an unexpectedly bizarre turn and the truth becomes stranger than fiction. This thrilling narrative is skillfully woven through the perspectives of multiple characters. With each character's viewpoint, fresh layers of information are unveiled, gradually unraveling a shocking twist that will leave viewers stunned, defying all expectations.</desc>
    <date>20240528</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4Ft9aJ1vHDixLTvdkGhPlswqMW5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726154926 +0000" stop="20250726173205 +0000">
    <title>For the Gram</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Fired from her corporate job, Brandi moves to live with her cousin, who works as an internet model. Brandi follows in her footsteps and becomes successful overnight. Brandi craves the attention from social media and the lifestyle it affords her, but begins to lose sight of who she is. One decision could change your life for better or for worse.</desc>
    <date>20230519</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a70f363c50d3a572aae10d90284054f9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726173205 +0000" stop="20250726185351 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726185351 +0000" stop="20250726203338 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726203338 +0000" stop="20250726215723 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWVkNzQ1MjAtYmNjZS00NDc0LTg0YzktNzVlNGViODYyMmUxXkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726215723 +0000" stop="20250726233240 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250623</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250726233240 +0000" stop="20250727010644 +0000">
    <title>Sweet Mahogany: Pure Indulgence</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mahogany Andrews appears to be in the fight for her life as she is battling Tony Hawkins for custody of their daughter, Rachel. However, another fight is beginning to ensue as Cassie Pearson is doing whatever it takes to keep her entire family, which includes Mahogany, together and Khalil Pearson is battling internally to figure out what he truly wants and needs out of life and his marriage.</desc>
    <date>20210223</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/c00ce2ef9b3709b77599172190cab0ee.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
