<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724010026 +0000" stop="20250724013030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Games - Fun with Reading</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop has trouble following the rules and taking turns while playing games. Barney and Riff help her learn how to follow the rules and Baby Bop learns that rules make games fun for everyone! BJ hurts his toe while pretending to be Captain Pickles. When Barney suggests he rest in the caboose, BJ becomes frustrated, as hed rather be outside playing. Barney reminds him of the wonderful world of books, and the little dinos decide to write a book of their ownbased on the exciting true-life adventures of Captain Pickles!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029601_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724013030 +0000" stop="20250724020022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making Mistakes - Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>BJs enthusiastic efforts to decorate the park go awry when he accidentally paints the caboose several different colors. Barney helps BJ learn that everyone makes mistakes. Together with his friends, BJ cleans up the mess he made on the caboose. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers she misses them more than she expected and the more time that goes by, the more she misses them! Barney shows Baby Bop ways to keep friends close in our hearts while theyre away.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029602_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724020022 +0000" stop="20250724023027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Days of the Week - Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ, Baby Bop and Riff can hardly wait for the petting zoo that is coming to the park. Barney helps them pass the time while teaching them about the days of the week. When the animals finally do arrive, everyone realizes that it was all worth the wait! Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029603_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724023027 +0000" stop="20250724030024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724030024 +0000" stop="20250724033030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724033030 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724043009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword in the Sandbox - A Storybook Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel fails miserably when he tries to join the others in jump rope. Convinced that he's too little to do anything right, Barney tells him the story of The Sword in the Sandbox. Through the legend of King Arthur, Daniel learns there are many things he can do... if he tries hard enough.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029632_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724043009 +0000" stop="20250724050003 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Riff to the Rescue! - A Wild West Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Riff is asked to be captain of a baseball team, he doesnt think he can do it. But Barney gives him the courage to try, by recounting the tale of his great-great-grandfather Riffle the Wild West hero!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029633_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724050003 +0000" stop="20250724053001 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lights! Camera! Action! - A Movie Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Melanie comes up with the perfect idea to get people to donate to Grace's food drive - put on a movie premiere in the caboose! Barney and friends pitch in to help, but they all have different ideas about what kind of movie to make. Everything they try falls apart. It's curtains for Melanie's movie until she comes up with a blockbuster idea of her own.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029634_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724053001 +0000" stop="20250724060004 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch a Thief - A Mystery Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Detective BJ is on the case when several sports balls suddenly disappear. Determined to find the mysterious ball thief, BJ falsely accuses Riff of being the thief. BJ learns he cannot jump to conclusions and must find the whole story to see who the thief really is.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029635_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724060004 +0000" stop="20250724063003 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Lamp - A Travel Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrating her birthday in the park with friends, Layla is more interested in hot dogs than her mother's Middle Eastern food. When Barney reads the story of Aladdin and the Magic Lamp, Layla is transported to a Middle Eastern marketplace where she learns different cultures have many exciting foods and customs to offer.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029636_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724063003 +0000" stop="20250724070011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Amazing Captain Pickles - A Hero Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Pickles and Wonder Princess both wanted to be the super-est superheroes. When Captain Pickles said he could jump over the moon, everyone wanted to see. BJ knew he couldn't really jump that high, but he could jump high enough to save Emma's balloon. Everyone was proud of him, even if he couldn't jump over the moon. BJ was a hero.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029637_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724070011 +0000" stop="20250724073012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Game for Everyone - A Sports Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes up with the idea to have a sports day in the park. All day, they play games like soccer and hopscotch among others, all for fun. Meanwhile, Baby Bop meets a girl with special needs named Jill, as well as her mom. As Baby Bop gets to know Jill more, she encourages her to play hopscotch with the others. In the end, Baby Bop and Jill win the trophy for hopscotch and she and her mother leave.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029638_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724073012 +0000" stop="20250724080005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Dragon - A Fairy Tale Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After the kids judge a spider by its creepy looks, Barney tells them the story of The Reluctant Dragon where a shepherd became friends with a dragon, who was judged by her appearance.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029639_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724080005 +0000" stop="20250724082818 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bienvenido, Barney!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop's friend Monty the butterfly passes through the park with a flock of friends on their way to Mexico. When Monty gets left behind, Barney takes everyone on a visit to Mexico to return Monty to his insect friends and family and give Baby Bop the chance to say goodbye to her butterfly friend.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029640_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724082818 +0000" stop="20250724090009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Big Brother Rusty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's excited to find out that Rusty's family is adopting a new baby sister from China; however, Rusty's not sure if he's going to be a good brother, and he doesn't know much about China. Barney shows Rusty and the others some info China on the computer and BJ and Baby Bop talk about siblings. Through Barney's Travel Book, Barney takes Rusty, BJ and Baby Bop on an adventure to China where he can learn more about his new sister's heritage. When they get there, the people are celebrating Chinese New Year. From lion dances and talented performers to tasty treats, making lanterns and puppet shows, the celebration never runs out of fun. By the time he returns to the park, Rusty excitedly meets his new baby sister, named Mei Ling, and realizes he will be the best big brother ever.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029641_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724090009 +0000" stop="20250724093008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Ahora Mismo!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is late to the park and is disappointed to realize he missed his chance at riding a real pony. He has waited his whole life for this, and now it looks as if hes missed his opportunity. Luckily, Barney takes Ben to Spain where they meet Regalo, a dancing horse with Riff and Baby Bop. Ben and Barney return to the park just in time for him to ride the pony after all! Ben is thrilled to ride a horse and learned an important lesson about patience and waiting.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029642_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724093008 +0000" stop="20250724100013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Venice, Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Emma is stuck with a school project and can't play soccer with Joshua. Having to interview her parents and get info about an interesting ancestor, she is frustrated with the assignment. Barney helps her discover that her ancestors were from Venice, Italy. Using his Travel Book, Barney takes Joshua, Emma, and Riff to Venice, Italy. He gives his friends a gondola ride as well as telling them about famous explorer Marco Polo. Barney's friend, Anna Maria tells Emma that she knew her great grandfather and takes her to his shop, where they try on masks and make some of their own. Emma learns that if she makes the mask in parts, she'll get it done. Barney reminds her of this lesson, so she will do the same for her school project.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029643_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724100013 +0000" stop="20250724103012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Sweeter Than Candy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, Baby Bop, and BJ are helping the kids get ready for a school play. Barney tells everyone that putting on shows began in Greece. Of course, the little dinos and kids want to visit the country, so off they go! While there, they meet some friends and decide to put on a play in an amphitheatre. Barney knows a great story that originated in Greece called King Midas. By the end of the day, everyone has learned that wanting too much is not a good thing, especially BJ!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029644_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724103012 +0000" stop="20250724110017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Music Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ben accidentally includes Kioko's prized music box from Switzerland in a cardboard box of yard sale items-the music box is sold! Kioko is sad and Ben wants to make things right, so he and Barney travel to Switzerland in search of a replacement gift. While there, they sample Swiss food, customs and games-but no music box! Luckily when Ben returns the music box is returned!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029645_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724110017 +0000" stop="20250724113009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Making Mistakes - Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>BJs enthusiastic efforts to decorate the park go awry when he accidentally paints the caboose several different colors. Barney helps BJ learn that everyone makes mistakes. Together with his friends, BJ cleans up the mess he made on the caboose. Baby Bop cant wait for BJ and Riff to go on their camping trip so she can have Barney and the park all to herself! But, once theyre gone, she discovers she misses them more than she expected and the more time that goes by, the more she misses them! Barney shows Baby Bop ways to keep friends close in our hearts while theyre away.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029602_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724113009 +0000" stop="20250724120013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Days of the Week - Sharing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ, Baby Bop and Riff can hardly wait for the petting zoo that is coming to the park. Barney helps them pass the time while teaching them about the days of the week. When the animals finally do arrive, everyone realizes that it was all worth the wait! Riff feels terrible when he accidentally wrecks BJs beloved scooter. BJ loved that scooter more than almost anything! Riff and Baby Bop decide to have a sale in the park to raise money to buy BJ a brand-new scooter.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029603_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724120013 +0000" stop="20250724123010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724123010 +0000" stop="20250724130016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724130016 +0000" stop="20250724133017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724133017 +0000" stop="20250724140019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724140019 +0000" stop="20250724143021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724143021 +0000" stop="20250724150015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724150015 +0000" stop="20250724153017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724153017 +0000" stop="20250724160019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724160019 +0000" stop="20250724163021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724163021 +0000" stop="20250724170016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724170016 +0000" stop="20250724173022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724173022 +0000" stop="20250724175842 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724175842 +0000" stop="20250724182824 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724182824 +0000" stop="20250724185831 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724185831 +0000" stop="20250724193022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724193022 +0000" stop="20250724200020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724200020 +0000" stop="20250724203024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724203024 +0000" stop="20250724210025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724210025 +0000" stop="20250724213023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724213023 +0000" stop="20250724220025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724220025 +0000" stop="20250724223029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724223029 +0000" stop="20250724230021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724230021 +0000" stop="20250724232846 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724232846 +0000" stop="20250724235828 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250724235828 +0000" stop="20250725002834 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725002834 +0000" stop="20250725005839 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Boss Barney - Get Happy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Three children try to build a pretend farm, but have a hard time working together. Barney takes them to a ranch to show them how all the people there have to work together to keep things running smoothly. Riff invents a Happiness Machine to try to cheer up a sad little girl. But it's her friends, not the machine, that make her happy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029618_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250725005839 +0000" stop="20250725013033 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>For the Fun of It - Starlight, Star Bright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ wants to learn Terry's fancy basketball moves. He tries hard, but just can't seem to do it! More importantly, he's not even having fun anymore. After some advice from Barney and Terry, BJ has fun while doing his best! On a campout, Baby Bop sees a falling star and wants to return it to the sky. With a little imagination and help from Barney and friends, she replaces the star that fell.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029619_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
