<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23">
    <display-name>Midsomer Murders</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3e052da1-c8b1-4f8d-a770-ca6998bbcbee/Wurl_MidsomerMurders_ChannelLogoDark_1500x1000_Jack_Archer.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250713234712 +0000" stop="20250714013148 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Made To Measure Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The villagers of Milton Cross depend on lord of the manor Edward Milton, for their jobs and income. When Sonia Woodley is found murdered in the churchyard, two years after the death of her abusive husband Gerald, the murder weapon is discovered to be tailor's shears, but which one of villagers is responsible? Barnaby and Jones arrive at Woodley and Woodley, the tailors to find out, to discover that the vicar had received a letter from Sonia a few days before.</desc>
    <date>20100512</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tXZ7Zqn1wMQZbXoJJnnSSB8ZdP5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714013148 +0000" stop="20250714031642 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Sword Of Guillaume</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>During a council meeting, Mayor Dave Hicks announces plans to awaken an annual trip to Brighton. Barnaby suspects his proposal to buy coastal land there is a fraud. Barnaby reluctantly joins the party, but during their time in Brighton, hated property developer Hugh Dalgleish is beheaded on a ghost train ride. The detectives together with Tom's cousin DCI John Barnaby gather who from the party or someone else could have been responsible before other murders occur and secrets are uncovered.</desc>
    <date>20100210</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3vsfoPqqRENM97cx6wVGBFMLcb7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714031642 +0000" stop="20250714050138 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Saddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ford Florey is anything but quiet, when the Wild West Society bring their show and fair, consisting of many stalls and a shooting re-enactment. The witch on the 'Dunk the Witch' stall, gets truly dunked and goes horribly wrong, when the water starts turning red. Barnaby and Jones have to be alert with a shooter in their midst. With many grudges, jealousies and a dispute over wasteland, known as 'the swamp', as possible motives, it is not long before more people turn up dead.</desc>
    <date>20100908</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8DFMFTMHAc9gjZoFswWVd0jrAaQ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714050138 +0000" stop="20250714064606 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On a dark night in the village of March Magna, Joyce Barnaby swerves her car and narrowly misses a shadowy figure in the road. Shortly after a body is found in the local old cemetery. The victim Gerald Ebbs was a member of the council and of the village's library. It is discovered from the villagers that Gerald had had a strange fixation on both the old hospital and cemetery; in particular a grave from within.</desc>
    <date>20100922</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qXbun3EZ9GMJvqNlUAyznQ8VtwY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714064606 +0000" stop="20250714083103 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Master Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Devington Manor Winter School led by internationally renowned musician Sir Michael Fielding, is a magnet for many aspiring piano students. Amongst the latest batch of students is Zoe Stock, a gifted young lady. Whilst in the grounds of the manor and by the riverbank, Zoe sees a woman jump from the bridge and disappear underwater. When Barnaby and Jones start their enquiries into the possible drowning, they discover many shady connections to the past.</desc>
    <date>20101006</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ab8nTnZk7hjjfUoZsaRVyfamFZp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714083103 +0000" stop="20250714101532 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Noble Art</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When boxer John Kinsella wins a world title in New York, the village of Midsomer Morchard are overjoyed at his success. Shortly afterwards a solicitor is found dead by his assistant and Kinsella's manager. Barnaby and Jones start to investigate and come across infidelity, anger, betrayals and blackmail. When a Victorian prize-fight re-enactment turns nasty and Kinsella's manager is found murdered in his home's gym.</desc>
    <date>20101013</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cn661RGTLE6sjtH9yuZcR8glQal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714101532 +0000" stop="20250714120026 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Not In My Background</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Midsomer Conservation Society are up in arms, when a recent new build, called Swanscombe House is a highlight of an open garden day. It leads to an ugly confrontation between a couple of its members and those responsible for the planning application, design and build. The people of which are suspected of involvement in a money-making scam. Political squabbles, burglaries and sexual liaisons all come to the fore in picturesque Great Pelfe.</desc>
    <date>20110112</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5LCr4F0wC54rJDCkmKNQuJZe3w1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714120026 +0000" stop="20250714134507 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Fit For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A spa weekend at Swavely Manor, proves far from relaxing, when Tom and Joyce Barnaby arrive. It starts stressful and goes rather downhill when a female client is found dead in the flotation chamber, by Joyce. Barnaby takes a break from his treatment to investigate alongside Jones. The mystery deepens when the woman's husband disappears in the night shortly afterwards. Tom's worries about his future seem to distract him from the case.</desc>
    <date>20110202</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xMsFlyngsDpKDuAth8KlQHXDTtx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714134507 +0000" stop="20250714153157 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Dance With The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A disused airfield at Cooper's Cross is where Simon Bright's vintage car is found by Frances Kirby. Inside she finds Simon dead, as the evening before his death had been on a romantic date with his girlfriend Laura Sharp. Laura is nowhere to be found, both Barnaby and Jones, newly promoted to DS, need to work out if it was a suicide pact gone wrong or whether it was murder and track down Laura.</desc>
    <date>20061111</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qF4KWvjCBaLCP7fnwGNNWCUChlA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714153157 +0000" stop="20250714171902 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Animal Within</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Faith Alexander arrives in Midsomer to meet her long-lost uncle Rex Masters. She receives a real shock, when she discovers that Rex's friends had been told she had died in a plane crash. Things become complicated when Rex's body is found in the nearby river. Barnaby and Jones quickly turn up trying to workout who would wish Rex harm. Several friends of Rex come forward with multiple 'new' wills each being sole beneficiary.</desc>
    <date>20070118</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/djHyhDeVbHaPzznei6mX2Ku9MGx.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714171902 +0000" stop="20250714190748 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>King's Crystal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Whilst on a business trip to China, Alan King suddenly dies. The family firm, King's Crystal is in financial uncertainty, including plans to close its factory in Midsomer Magna. Six months later Alan's widow Hilary and his brother Charles are married, much to the chagrin of Alan's son Ian. With family feuds and factory workers angered by the loss of their jobs, there's many motives in the mix. When Peter Baxter, the firm's accountant is found dead, stabbed with a Masonic dagger.</desc>
    <date>20070126</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tvIc7wolHlehggXyS7gQuwzc1HA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714190748 +0000" stop="20250714205454 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>The Axeman Cometh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Midsomer Rocks festival is due to take place and music fans descend on neighbouring fields to enjoy the fiesta. The recently reformed band Hired Gun, are one of the headline acts and during their opening performance, the bands vocalist Mimi Clifton is electrocuted on stage whilst holding on to her microphone stand, that had an added mystery wire. Barnaby and Jones soon discover other band members could be targets.</desc>
    <date>20070202</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/38G2QX72T4hcsZ3jtGMcEWS0sUh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714205454 +0000" stop="20250714224201 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Death And Dust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When popular GP, Doctor Alan Delaney borrows fellow Dr. James Kirkwood's new car to do an evening call-out. He is mysteriously killed in a hit and run during a drive through woods in a thunderstorm. Barnaby and Jones start investigating in Midsomer Market and discover that James may have been the intended victim. The case leads them to North Walesformer home of Delyth Mostyn, James's fiance to delve further.</desc>
    <date>20070508</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d16oDfe5xRkqz6X3wCqLSh63uA0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-63d6fc71a9e88ee909e7ee23" start="20250714224201 +0000" stop="20250715003058 +0000">
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <sub-title>Picture Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In the pretty village of Luxton Deeping, there's fierce conflict between the traditional film and modern digital photographers. When their societies committee decide not to accept digital images at the annual photographic exhibition, it appears to make things worse. It leads to a confrontation at the private view. The following day Lionel Bell is found murdered in woodland, strangled with the cord of his light meter.</desc>
    <date>20070603</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hYiCsblCms9LmSXTev4jua63cC8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
