<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250711233147 +0000" stop="20250712011942 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Dawn</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Having platinum records and superstar rosters seem like easy work to music industry legends Donica Blair and Shequell Harris, but when they want to start their own label, they become targets in more ways than they are prepared for. Adding Seven to the mix in an already uneven playing field leads to unorthodox measures to protect Don and save her life. Quell, on the other hand, may have gotten exactly what she asked for when she calls Silk to help them out.</desc>
    <date>20250520</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712011942 +0000" stop="20250712032149 +0000">
    <title>The Forbidden Daughter</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When tragedy happens at a young age Demetrius loses her way, until an angel comes to rescue her and gives her the strength to face her fears.</desc>
    <date>20230301</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/ab078f3127e3f6ce5bb2eb33b036408b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712032149 +0000" stop="20250712043527 +0000">
    <title>The Co-Signer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Released from prison, Mark makes the decision to change his ways. Kane has other plans in store for him.</desc>
    <date>20180307</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/c/gracenote/ce03b7366ce3a100a0eeea822c120c23.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712043527 +0000" stop="20250712061554 +0000">
    <title>The Aftermath</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After the new guy botches a perfectly planned armored car heist, 4 crafty criminals are left trapped with the police closing in on them. Tensions rise as they try to find a way out with a hard-nosed detective hot on their trail. Will the risk be worth the reward?</desc>
    <date>20200907</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/95e3ae1fc5958e908edc256fde4c6100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712061554 +0000" stop="20250712074535 +0000">
    <title>Keisha Takes the Block</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Keisha is a woman down on her luck with no money, who finds out her sick mother is in need of expensive medical care. After a brief stay in jail, she decides to form an all-female street gang to take over the city, and get the money she needs for her mother. Keisha begins taking down rival drug dealers to build her empire. When the leader of a gang on the northside of town tries to take down Keisha and her crew, Keisha must kill him before he can kill her first.</desc>
    <date>20230905</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/leukTs63TE7bz1m4MjI9QHzZqGS.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712074535 +0000" stop="20250712093803 +0000">
    <title>In Transit</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In New York City, friends Leon and Rollo, live a fast life of drugs and women. From an unexpected mistake in their past, they owe a debt to a well-known drug kingpin. They soon find out the fast money is more than they bargained for, but leaving it behind, will prove to be even more challenging.</desc>
    <date>20240331</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjFmMGU3MzUtN2ZlYS00MTIzLWEzMzgtMGZkOWVlZmRhOTU3XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712093803 +0000" stop="20250712112913 +0000">
    <title>He'll Never Let Go</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Candace's life takes an unexpected turn when she crosses paths with the charismatic Karlton Moore. At first glance, Karlton seems like the epitome of perfection—his looks, charm, and achievements paint an irresistible picture. However, as their relationship deepens, Candace begins to unearth a chilling truth. Karlton harbors a sinister darkness and an overwhelming fear of commitment. What initially appeared as a dreamy romance soon transforms into a harrowing nightmare.</desc>
    <date>20240423</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/acb893993bde3d68b046ad26aeee17da.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712112913 +0000" stop="20250712125620 +0000">
    <title>Have You Seen My Man?</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After a long night of partying, Niecey's man Chase is nowhere to be found. Just when things couldn’t get any worse, here comes the exes and their drama. The tables turn and the finger pointing begins, Niecy knows there's no turning back now, she has to find the truth and her man.</desc>
    <date>20240131</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/9b113e8529d6ac8d541ac27fa2916319.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712125620 +0000" stop="20250712143552 +0000">
    <title>Forever Single</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Dawkins Brothers are back! 3 Brothers living together are in a wild adventure when Hercules has a crazy baby mama who gets her detective dad to force Hercules to take care of his responsibilities by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>20230710</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/248962ede43bb26fbfa7905d35a48713.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712143552 +0000" stop="20250712162155 +0000">
    <title>Flew'd Out</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Tiara is an up and coming social media influencer after going viral for posting a mans reaction online after denying him sex. In an attempt to grow her online profile, she accepts a date from a man named Josiah for an out of town excursion. Over time, Josiah's intentions become more elaborate, deranged, and sinister. Will Tiara make it out alive?</desc>
    <date>20240909</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/a7488c4f4e1e117311e9d8781bd439bf.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712162155 +0000" stop="20250712190740 +0000">
    <title>Family Over Everything</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After being set up to get jumped, West now owes the biggest Street hustler in Syracuse, Gunzo $50,000. But when Gunzo’s crew shows up at West’s family home, his older sibling’s step in to protect the family from his wrath.</desc>
    <date>20231101</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pDK3h3pxJAB0RqnqqBMHXAqRftc.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712190740 +0000" stop="20250712204519 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Friendz</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When an average, anti-social, woman gets tired of going through the motions of her daily life, she reluctantly decides to attend her company’s Halloween Party. As the night goes along, debauchery ensues, revealing secrets and revelations about herself. Reality blurs, friendships shatter, but who’s the real villain?</desc>
    <date>20250610</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712204519 +0000" stop="20250712230051 +0000">
    <title>Troublesome</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Veteran homicide detective Michael reluctantly partners with rookie Derrick. Witnessing a double homicide, they survive a deadly chase, but Derrick is wounded. The suspects are linked to the kingpin, who retaliates by ordering murders across the city. As chaos erupts, the FBI joins the case, revealing the kingpin's identity. Michael finds a weak link, offering a chance to finally catch him.</desc>
    <date>20250609</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bba572182a25acd3645156c83fc0e787.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250712230051 +0000" stop="20250713002237 +0000">
    <title>Crush</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Haunted by her past, a young woman's life is complicated by love, self-discovery, and surrounding violence.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e1859f3cb8a9be85453d30f134daa833.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
