<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37">
    <display-name>SPEEDVISION</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/9653867c-6eb1-4c68-a494-4d4897c22b96/SV_4C_LOGO_LIGHT_1500x1000.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711010001 +0000" stop="20250711020002 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Investigation O.E.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Two rare Mopars, a Daytona survivor and early Hemi Charger, are analyzed for authenticity and restoration.</desc>
    <date>20151223</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E09_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711020002 +0000" stop="20250711030005 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Chally vs. Chally</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The ghouls complete the 1970 V-Code Challenger and make a side-by-side comparison with Mark's 2014 Shaker-hood Challenger.</desc>
    <date>20151230</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E10_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711030005 +0000" stop="20250711040006 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>HEMI FK5 Alive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A 1970 Hemi Charger is restored.</desc>
    <date>20160106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E11_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711040006 +0000" stop="20250711050007 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Pitch and Rides</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The 1970 Hemi Charger project is completed in the season finale.</desc>
    <date>20160113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S05_E12_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711050007 +0000" stop="20250711060009 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>General Assemble Lee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Graveyard Ghouls return with the final assembly of the legendary General Lee which so happens to also be the official screen-used, record holding, freeway jump-car from the 2005 Dukes of Hazzard film.</desc>
    <date>20171115</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E01_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711060009 +0000" stop="20250711070011 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>Put Up Your Dukes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark isolates himself in the machine-shop and begins the assembly of the 440 4BBL for the 1970 Plum Crazy Challenger previously owned by a former cast member.</desc>
    <date>20171122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E02_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711070011 +0000" stop="20250711080014 +0000">
    <title>Graveyard Carz</title>
    <sub-title>General Deliver Lee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s a delivery day at Graveyard Carz! We jump back and show you every moment in the restoration of our legendary, screen-used, record holding, General Lee from the 2005 Dukes of Hazzard film. It all builds to a reveal the Duke Boys would be proud of.</desc>
    <date>20171129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GC_SPEED_WURL_S08_E03_Episode_Still.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711080014 +0000" stop="20250711083018 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Interior Car Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter provides valuable tips and techniques for cleaning and rejuvenating your cars interior</desc>
    <date>20221102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/RDG-EP-1-Title.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711083018 +0000" stop="20250711090022 +0000">
    <title>Rutter's Detailin Garage</title>
    <sub-title>Exterior Car Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick Rutter provides valuable tips and techniques for properly washing your vehicle to avoid instilling swirl marks</desc>
    <date>20221102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/RDG-EP-2-Title.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711090022 +0000" stop="20250711093007 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Ford Common Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Not all trucks are perfect. Matt and Bruno dissect some common Ford problems in the engine and suspension.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711093007 +0000" stop="20250711100011 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Air Bag It Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruno and Matt improve the ride quality and tow capacity on our Ford Super Duty tow project by installing an adjustable airbag system.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711100011 +0000" stop="20250711103011 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Air Bag It Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>We finish the Air Bag kit on our Super Duty tow project and put it to the test on the road.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711103011 +0000" stop="20250711110011 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Street Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruno and Matt install some upgrades on a 2010 Ford F 150 to make it more roadworthy</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711110011 +0000" stop="20250711113011 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>King of the Hammers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt heads out west to find out what makes the King of the Hammers one of the fastest growing races in the world.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711113011 +0000" stop="20250711120010 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>See It Made-Surf City Garage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruno Massel takes a trip to Huntington Beach, California to see a garage of Dream Cars that inspired a company.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711120010 +0000" stop="20250711123010 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Rock Racer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Chassis for the Rock Racer is almost done, so Matt and Bruno add a Speedwire System and install the torque converter.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711123010 +0000" stop="20250711130013 +0000">
    <title>Truck U</title>
    <sub-title>Small Engine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt and Bruno replace a small engine on a go kart and get some help from some kids on a special project.</desc>
    <date>00010110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/TruckUWurl.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711130013 +0000" stop="20250711133013 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt Rock Interior Other Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A custom build can lose some power if the theme doesn’t stay consistent. Stacey shows how to do that by taking you through the process of how to make door and kick panels that keep the rugged military WWII bomber vibe flowing throughout the interior of Sgt. Rock. After that, its some tips on how to fit a radiator and that all-important cooling fan in a place where space is limited. Finally, the gas tank and battery placement are critical on a custom vehicle and Stacey goes through the steps in doing that as well. If you’ve always wanted to build a custom vehicle, this episode is sure to get your fabrication gearZ turning.</desc>
    <date>20160311</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0117.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711133013 +0000" stop="20250711140012 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Asessing Unfinished Project</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Two things are certain in life: death and taxes. We all know what to do with taxes, but what happens when a loved one passes and leaves behind an unfinished project vehicle? How do you know what’s sitting in your garage? And how can you find out? Stacey tackles these questions and takes you on a thorough inventory of an almost finished restoration that was left to a widow when her husband suddenly died. A new dash going into your vehicle? A gauge tech should keep you from crossing your wires. And we’ve got tips that should help with battery relocation and lining up your vehicle’s body panels.</desc>
    <date>20160318</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0118.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711140012 +0000" stop="20250711143012 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Gearz On The Road - Basic Tools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The GearZ crew mount up and head out to visit a young gear-head whose love of wrenching started with 4-wheelers and has grown to include 4-wheel drive pick ups. Young Adam has a few surprises in store as Stacey visits him in his Dad’s garage and discusses tools, storage and tearing apart things to see how they work. Then, it’s back in the shop as Stacey takes on the big question every gear-head has: What OTHER tools should I have in my box? A look beyond the typical wrenches, hammers and clamps will show you what you may need and what you may not, depending on your project.</desc>
    <date>20160325</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0119.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711143012 +0000" stop="20250711150015 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Body Work Latches Custom Exhaust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The son of legendary car builder, Bill Thomas, talks shop about wrenching, racing and his father’s Cobra Killer…the Cheetah. Then Stacey heads over to Stainless Works to check out how the Cheetah’s custom side pipes, headers and mufflers came together. A Gauge Tech explains the pros and cons of mechanical vs. electric gauges. After that, a Quick Tip explains the proper way to use some of those mystery tools laying around in your tool box.</desc>
    <date>20160401</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0120.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711150015 +0000" stop="20250711153014 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Old Dog New Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ever wonder why your wife or best buddy won’t step foot in your late model truck? It could be that crusty interior. Tag along as Stacey takes on the sights and smells of an ’83 Chevy in dire need of some attention. From new dash to leather on the bench seat and new carpet in the floor, Stacey shows you what a difference a weekend and some parts from LMC can make. Speaking of trucks, Stacey raises the bar with a bed lifter that will make you the most popular guy in your neighborhood. A new buffer is going to help add some shine to your vehicle and a creeper that’s simply “Magic” is sure to raise an eyebrow or two. Big things are happening in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160408</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0121.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711153014 +0000" stop="20250711160014 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Reviving An Old Snowcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Through the years, we’ve had some amazing vehicles featured on GearZ—from elite racecars to the insanity of a V-8 barstool. Well, here we go again! Stacey hauls in a Thiokol Imp that needs some…attention. First things first with this crazy snowcatmobile; we’ve got to see if we can make it run. Follow along as Stacey takes you through the ins and outs of getting a neglected vehicle up and running again. For you performance BMW guys, a tuner from Dinan is going add the horses you’ve been looking for. We’ve got sparks flying, fuel splashing and all kinds of garage mayhem this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160415</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0122.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711160014 +0000" stop="20250711163013 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Wiring Sgt Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>In the world of car building there are few things more ominous than missing titles or VIN numbers. But there is one task that stands out, one that brings grown men to tears, one that is usually lurking behind 100 yards of electrical tape…WIRING. Well hold on tight as Stacey dives head first into wiring Sergeant Rock. That’s right; see how painless Stacey can make wiring the big old truck. Follow along as Stacey moves front to back and gets the Rock one step closer to hitting the road!</desc>
    <date>20160422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0123.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711163013 +0000" stop="20250711170015 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>New AC Old Chevy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>With summer in full swing, it’s time to cool down that classic truck of yours. That’s right, roll those windows up and feel the cool breeze as Stacey shows just how easy it is to install this complete AC system from LMC Truck. Now that you’re done sweatin’, let’s take a look at headers and intakes and get that motor performing the way it should. And don’t miss out on the ins and outs of turbos and super-chargers…which one fits your needs? All this and plenty of sparks in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0124.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711170015 +0000" stop="20250711173015 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Building A Better Tool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the GearZ crew heat things up as they head to the Cornwell forges to watch molten steel be expertly transformed into America’s best ratchet. Get ready to see sparks fly. But the trip doesn’t stop there. Tag along as the crew follows what it takes for a ratchet to end up on a Cornwell truck. Back in the garage, Stacey talks maximizing boost and the role of intercoolers when it comes to super-chargers and turbos. The wheels keep turning and the rubber keeps burning, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0125.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711173015 +0000" stop="20250711180017 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On The Road - 67 Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheetah lovers will be excited to see Stacey’s solution to keeping the headers both cool and looking red hot. Want to keep using your stock tank after converting to fuel injection? Get psyched, because Holley has a new fuel pump that’s going to make your life a whole lot easier. Think your car is buttoned up tight? Stacey and some friends from Redline Detection blow smoke at the old soap and water test and show you how to really test for leaks in your vehicle. It’s a world of problems out there, but Stacey’s got you covered in the garage. All this and more, this week, on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0126.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711180017 +0000" stop="20250711183019 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Novas BBQ</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>This week Stacey and crew head to Memphis, TN to help out a local BBQ pitmaster who’s deep into a ground up rebuild of a ’72 Nova. The big challenge here?...Can you swap out an automatic transmission with a manual without losing your mind? Well, Stacey is always up for a good challenge and he’ll show you just how simple this swap can be. A new tuner from Super chips will make your Jeep life easier, and replacement dashes for Chevy owners are going to light up their eyes. There’s a lot going on in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20160520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0127.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711183019 +0000" stop="20250711190018 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Cheap Fuel Injection Snow Cat Bed TN Electric Guitar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re winding up the tenth season of GearZ, and what a season it’s been! But we’ve got some business to take care of before we move onto season eleven. First things first…Holley just made an EFI even easier to install on your carbureted vehicle, and Stacey will show you just how on target the Sniper is. The Thiokol Imp gets a suspension upgrade to keep it on track. And there’s a new kind of off-roading that’s sweeping the nation…see what RC4WD has going on. And what season would be complete without guitars? Check out Tennessee Electric Company as Stacey introduces a new guitar-maker whose custom guitars are hotter than the asphalt at the drag strip.</desc>
    <date>20160527</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0128.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711190018 +0000" stop="20250711193020 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The SL-C’s Hit the Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re back and taking it to the streets! Season 11 comes roaring back with a look at Super Lite Cars on the road and the track! Stacey recalls and earlier SLC build and introduces two SLC builders who took a very hands-on approach to putting their cars together. These street/race cars are sure to catch your eye and get your racing blood flowing. If there’s one thing Stacey preaches on every episode, it’s paying attention to the details. His quick tip is no exception, getting rid of those sharp edges and nasty welds to give your project the small details that people will notice. Side mirrors for a muscle car, building a better battery, and keeping your air flowing through carbon fiber vents fill out the parts bin. We’ve got all this and more as Stacey kicks of his 11th season of GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20170107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0129.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711193020 +0000" stop="20250711200019 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Sgt. Rock Lives!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>This is the moment you’ve been waiting for! Master car builder, Stacey David, shows off the truck that’s had the nation talking for ten years! Take a look back at the kid with the dream. Follow the design and fabrication. See what happens when the military tribute vehicle rolls out and conquers the road! This episode is gonna be epic. It’s been a long road, but anything worth doing well is worth the wait. This week, the wait is over. Sergeant Rock Lives!</desc>
    <date>20170114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0130.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711200019 +0000" stop="20250711203021 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>On the Road &amp; Unicure Spray Booths</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Things are rockin’ and rollin’ in and out of the GearZ garage. Stacey hits the road to find a project build that will get gear heads buzzing. He ends up with an ’81 Camaro and some awesome stories from the seller. If you’re talking project vehicles, you’ve got to talk paint! And Stacey does just that with folks from Unicure, who specialize in paint booths and helping you get set up for that all important paint job. The V-8 Interceptor is back from a trip to Stainless works, where a custom exhaust system was made for the big Boss Nine engine. Things are about to get loud, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0131.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711203021 +0000" stop="20250711210022 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>The Return of Heavy Metal &amp; Snowcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey and the GearZ crew roll in an old favorite: Heavy Metal. The coolest hotrod tow truck is back in the garage and ready for a facelift. Our good friends at the Hot Rod Institute drop by and talk shop with Stacey about his plans for the paint and fab work needed to get this bad boy looking good and back on the road. Fresh from the sandblaster, the snowcat reveals the scars that were under the skin. And with the drive train out, Stacey walks through the importance of replacing gaskets, seals and checking for wear and tear before stuffing that engine, transmission and skid steer rear end back into the cat. There’s a whole lot going on this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0132.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711210022 +0000" stop="20250711213020 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Every gear head has a secret: they all want to drive like McQueen in Bullitt, or Vin Diesel in The Fast And The Furious. But when the heat gets turned up, even some really good drivers can’t keep up. That’s when you bring in the Stunt Double! This week Stacey sits down with legendary Hollywood stunt man Ian Quinn to talk crashing cars and keeping actors out of harms way. There’s also a new project in the garage: The Stunt Double, a build inspired by the 80’s tv show The Fall Guy, and sure to get all four wheels off the ground before Stacey’s done with it. Sparks are going to fly and you know we’re gonna have a good time this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170401</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0133.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711213020 +0000" stop="20250711220024 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Nose Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Seems like you can’t go more than a block these days without running into someone whose had some work done on their face. Well, here at the GearZ garage, Stacey believes in facelifts too. Just to prove it, he’s taken on a 1981 Camaro and sharpened his scalpel to perform an automotive nose job. Just wait till you see him whack of the old rubber nose and replace it with a 71’ rally sport front end! Now that’s what we call a facelift. Plenty of people said it couldn’t be done, but that’s just the kind of challenge Stacey is up for. Plenty of sparks are gonna fly, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170408</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0134.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711220024 +0000" stop="20250711223022 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Interior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>They say that true change comes from within… Well, this week Stacey turns his attention to the interior of the Stunt Double. The old, crusty junk hits the floor and our Fall Guy inspired build gets a new look: from painting trim and door panels, to a new bench seat. Man o’ man, this truck is starting to look completely different. A shower of sparks lights up the garage as Stacey demonstrates how to make a bracket that mounts our new bench seat to the truck while using the stock seat adjustment. It’s a tour de force of aftermarket parts and salvaging what we’ve got, this week on GearZ!</desc>
    <date>20170415</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0135.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711223022 +0000" stop="20250711230022 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Gets a Lift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When you’re putting together a project that’s inspired by a high-flying stunt truck, you know you’ve got to add some lift, and our Stunt Double gets the goods this week. The front and rear suspension get treated to a 6” lift to get that rig up in the air. But a good lift won’t do any good if the steering and frame can’t hold up, so Stacey shows you how Offroad Design has fixed some serious issues that many late model four-wheel drives encounter. Bed need to come off your truck, but the carriage bolts are rusted and spinning? Stacey’s got a fix for that too. There’s a lot going on, and we’ve got you covered, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0136.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711230022 +0000" stop="20250711233020 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Ram Gets a Procharger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone needs a little boost here and there. For some people, coffee does the trick. But here in the GearZ Garage we take our boost seriously. And we like ours packing 160 HP. Hang on to your seat as Stacey adds a bolt on Supercharger to a Ram 1500 breathes a little excitement into a daily driver. And speaking of things going on in the garage, you’ll definitely want to stick around as Stacey talks shop with the guys at Rebuilding Generations. Learn all about how this mentoring program is teaching the next generation about working on cars and sharing plenty of life lessons. We’ve got a lot going on this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0137.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250711233020 +0000" stop="20250712000000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Stunt Double Drivetrain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>We’re running full steam ahead as the Stunt Double rolls back into the shop this week! First, Stacey reveals the wheels and tires that are going to accentuate that 6” lift, then He dives headlong into the drivetrain of this beast and comes up with a hot crate engine and a high-performance transmission to get the Stunt Double ready for the road. But that’s not all…. We also take some time out for a visit with the guys from American Powertrain and so much more. Check out the sparks flying in the garage this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170715</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0138.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712000000 +0000" stop="20250712003000 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Catalog Camaro Front Suspension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s business as usual in the garage this week. We’re back at work on the Catalog Camaro and really diggin’ into the front end. You know what they say, “out with the old and in with the new,” and that’s exactly what Stacey’s doing. The old sub frame, drivetrain, and suspension are hitting the garage floor in favor of a much-needed updated suspension system that’ll keep this awesome Camaro hugging the road at high speeds—From the wheels to the sub frame, Stacey’s replacing it all. And he’s not going to break the bank while doing it, either. Follow the GearZ crew as they hit the road and visit Cornwell Tools to see their latest and greatest tool box being manufactured. From powder coat to knuckle bustin’ bolts, we’ve got you covered this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170722</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0139.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712003000 +0000" stop="20250712010001 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Procharger Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>We head out of the garage to visit one of the premiere supercharger manufacturers in the world… ATI Pro Charger. Follow along for the ride as Stacey walks through the entire process of how they have raised the bar on how a supercharger is built and what it does. From bulk metal to dyno runs, we’ve got it covered. Back in the garage, a young Gearhead drops by to learn how to install an air intake and cowl induction hood on his pick-up. After the wrench turning is done, he and Stacey have enough time to hit a few licks on their guitars. From massive horsepower increases with state-of-the-art tools and machinery, to simple intake and hood installs,….. it’s all here, this week on GearZ.</desc>
    <date>20170729</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0140.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6349ed0eb1adc4cfa571fd37" start="20250712010001 +0000" stop="20250712012959 +0000">
    <title>Stacey David's Gearz</title>
    <sub-title>Recaps &amp; Catchups</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stacey is in full hot rod mode as he unveils a wicked LS engine and Tremec 6spd tranny and stuffs it into the Catalog Camaro. If 600hp and a 6spd in a Camaro doesn’t get you going, the update on the Stunt Double will! It’s old school cool as Stacey shows off the stainless light bar, side steps and cutout flairs to give the truck that “Fall Guy” vibe. After that we introduce you to the amazing world of scale R/C that is sure to have you re-thinking what you want for Christmas! Finally we roll in some updates on the Cheetah and the Junkyard Jag too. If you’re a gearhead, you’re gonna find a whole lot to love about this show!......and that’s GEARZ!!!</desc>
    <date>20170805</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/speedvision/GRZSV0141.png" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
