<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817">
    <display-name>Waypoint TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/waypointtv_logo_dark.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716010013 +0000" stop="20250716013007 +0000">
    <title>The Green Way Outdoors</title>
    <sub-title>"Alaska Sockeye Salmon"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Green Way Outdoors team heads to Alaska to target sockeye salmon. The beautiful color of these harvested fillets will blow your mind.</desc>
    <date>20250401</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716013007 +0000" stop="20250716020003 +0000">
    <title>The Reel American Road Trip</title>
    <sub-title>"Fishing Cape San Blas for Reds and Trout"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Danny is joined by Ryan Sheffield for some fishing on Cape San Blas. They meet up with Mark Moore to go fishing for Reds and Trout. Later, they cook up the catch.</desc>
    <date>20250107</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716020003 +0000" stop="20250716023001 +0000">
    <title>Stomping Grounds</title>
    <sub-title>"Florida' Highway on the Water"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>From country music star Brian Kelley’s big 56’ Sunny Briggs Sportfishing Yacht, to getting caught in a storm aboard a small Hurricane deck boat in the Gulf of Mexico, this episode of Stomping Grounds has host Ryan McVinney exploring boat culture in Florida’s Panhandle region, from the Emerald Coast to The Big Bend and the Forgotten Coast. Brian Kelley, aka “Beach Cowboy”, or BK for short, makes up one half of the country music group Florida Georgia Line (FGL) and has just released his own solo album Sunshine State of Mind. Kelley invites viewers aboard his vessel the “Brittney Marie” which was named after his wife, for a look at the couple’s Stomping Grounds. Songs from his album play on the boat’s sound system - including a tune about shopping for a boat on Boat Trader</desc>
    <date>20220407</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716023001 +0000" stop="20250716030000 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Alaskan Fishing, Foraging, &amp; Mountainside Cooking with Local Legends"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hop in the float plane—a new episode of DIRT just dropped. The DIRT crew made their way to Alaska, “the land of earth, sea, and sky.” All feast, no sleep is the name of the game as Josh makes the most of Alaska’s abundant and legendary daylight alongside local guides, fishermen, and even a couple grizzlies. There’ll be plenty of time to hibernate in winter. But for now—join us—there are halibut to filet, rainforest ’shrooms to forage, and mountainside meals to cook up.</desc>
    <date>20240604</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716030000 +0000" stop="20250716033000 +0000">
    <title>Duck Camp Dinners</title>
    <sub-title>"In a Camp Down by the River"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Duck Camp Dinners crew leaves the bayous and heads down river to Venice, Louisiana where they prepare for their first duck hunt in the delta.</desc>
    <date>20231006</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716033000 +0000" stop="20250716040000 +0000">
    <title>Goin' Coastal</title>
    <sub-title>"Family Day"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and his wife Anna celebrate the first day of summer by taking their daughters out for a fun-filled day on the water.</desc>
    <date>20250626</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716040000 +0000" stop="20250716041917 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"A Story Of Restoration"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>From time to time you have moments that will change the way think about something. That is what happened for us while hunting the Scimitar Oryx with Republic Outdoors. Hunting is more than harvesting animals, it’s conservation, and in this story, we learn how a species nearly extinct gets another chance to live.</desc>
    <date>20211104</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716041917 +0000" stop="20250716043517 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Fortified Cottonseed"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John Sewell has played a huge part in the development of feeding Fortified Cottonseed 365 days a year. Laramie Barrett of Fortified Cottonseed joins John for a great weekend of hunting at his ranch in Uvalde, Texas. This is a great time for Laramie to get away from the office and see the first hand of how their product is performing.</desc>
    <date>20241021</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716043517 +0000" stop="20250716050000 +0000">
    <title>Storytellers</title>
    <sub-title>"Run-N-Gun Adventures"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Texas Gulf Coast offers an array of opportunities to experience the outdoors. From fishing to waterfowl, we have found that every hunt gives us a chance to experience other people's stories. On this hunt, we learned not only about the incredible adventures that take place at Run-N-Gun, but also about a Texas based organization changing the lives of young people.</desc>
    <date>20211117</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716050000 +0000" stop="20250716054936 +0000">
    <title>Dirt</title>
    <sub-title>DIRT - "Getting a Crash Course in Bull Riding, Tex-Mex Cuisine &amp; the Spirit of Texas | DIRT Texas"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Anyone can be a cowboy—that’s the biggest thing the DIRT crew learned in Texas. From riding bulls in Fort Worth to off-roading in the Chihuahuan desert to forging their own path across this vast state with the help of local trailblazers Liz and Lou Lambert. Lucky for us, they even stopped by Huckberry’s own backyard in Austin for a quick ruck and a couple games of chicken sh*t bingo. When the dust finally settled, we fired up the barbecue for our beefiest feast yet and raised our ranch waters high to 10 DIRT episodes in the can.</desc>
    <date>20240723</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716054936 +0000" stop="20250716060005 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand TIps and Gear</title>
    <sub-title>HuntStand Tips &amp; Gear - "How to Attract Trophy Bucks with Cereal Grains"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>HuntStand Pro Contributor Cody Butler runs us through how he plants cereal grain food plots to attract giants for the fall.</desc>
    <date>20241121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716060005 +0000" stop="20250716063001 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Clowning with Peacocks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ryan Miller targets exotic fish in Lake Ida with local guide Kevin Cannon in Episode 2 of FinQuest. Catching peacock bass and clown knife fish, Ryan also enjoys family fun with a skimboarding session in Jupiter, Florida.</desc>
    <date>20241015</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716063001 +0000" stop="20250716070000 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Ambers &amp; Kings"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 3 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller joins Captain Alex from Supremacy Fishing Charters for an offshore adventure targeting big fish off shore. Starting at the Palm Beach Inlet, the team uses planar fishing techniques to hook wahoo and other catches like kingfish and amberjack. Along the way, firefighter Johnny Bennett shares his journey from fishing to starting a popular fish dip business. The day wraps up with thrilling doubleheader catches and a conservation message, showcasing the importance of sustainable fishing practices.</desc>
    <date>20241125</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716070000 +0000" stop="20250716072959 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Snook On Board"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 4 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller explores Jupiter’s Inner Coastal Waterway, blending fishing, paddleboarding, and community engagement. With the help of Matthew from Jupiter Live Bait, Ryan showcases bait preparation techniques before catching snook in the vibrant ICW. He highlights Jupiter's community spirit by joining a local clean-up initiative with Jeremy from Blue Line Paddleboards. The episode features paddleboarding adventures with Ryan’s family, connecting with nature and marine life, and ends with a conservation message about preserving Jupiter’s pristine environment.</desc>
    <date>20241202</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716072959 +0000" stop="20250716075959 +0000">
    <title>FinQuest</title>
    <sub-title>"Ocean Mixed Bag"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In Episode 5 of FinQuest, Ryan Miller dives into the vibrant world of offshore fishing off the coast of Palm Beach County. Joined by Cabo Mike, they showcase expert bait techniques and strategies, reeling in a variety of catches, including bonita and a stunning mahi mahi. The duo shares insights into their fishing setup, explains the use of daisy chains, and celebrates their exciting day at sea. With breathtaking views of the ocean and a colorful array of fish, Ryan’s passion for saltwater fishing shines through. The episode wraps up with a reflection on the beauty and bounty of Palm Beach County waters.</desc>
    <date>20250117</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716075959 +0000" stop="20250716083001 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Longbeard Mitten Mayhem"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Over a decade after the game changing Longbeard XR was introduced by Winchester, the wait is finally over for their next ground breaking turkey load. After years of perfecting the recipe behind the scenes, Winchester finally unveiled the new Longbeard TSS at a turkey camp in northern Michigan. First watch the jaw dropping Longbeard TSS pattern board testing, then see it go to work on some spring gobblers.</desc>
    <date>20250317</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716083001 +0000" stop="20250716090001 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Remembering A Legend"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Nestled in the hills of Ohio just west of the Appalachians is a very special deer camp ripe with memories from deer season’s past. With the development of the 350 Legend straight-walled cartridge by Winchester in 2019, a world of opportunities now existed in states like Ohio and Michigan. In this episode, with the 350 Legend in hand, three mature whitetails meet their maker, from the same blind, over the course of three seasons.</desc>
    <date>20250317</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716090001 +0000" stop="20250716093000 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Six Decades Of Dominance"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s been 60 years since AA was introduced to the shooting sports world. Since that day, an immeasurable number of AA hulls have hit the ground and countless shooters have stood center stage raising a trophy where millions of dollars have been won. Professional and recreational shooters alike have trusted AA for six decades. In this episode, load up for stories of high school, collegiate competitors and the world’s best as they bust clays with the legendary shot shell. - GUESTS: Zach Keenbaum (Team Winchester) Desi Edmunds (Team Winchester) Kayla Wilgus (Team Winchester) Amy Cawley (Team Winchester) Anthony Matarese (Team Winchester)</desc>
    <date>20250417</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716093000 +0000" stop="20250716095959 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Clays With Purpose"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>For the first time in history, the World English Sporting Clays Championship was held in the United States at the incredible M&amp;M Hunting Preserve owned by the Matarese family in New Jersey. Watch as Winchester’s best shooters vie for Gold as they compete against over 2,500 shooters and 17 countries. We’ll also join the Kids and Clays foundation in Florida as they host an event that will most certainly touch your soul.</desc>
    <date>20250502</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716095959 +0000" stop="20250716103000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Pontoon Deck Upgrade"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team is at  - John’s lake house on Tupper Lake, NY. They are checking out some of the damage done to John’s pontoon decking from freezing weather they received. John and the team are upgrading the material, and adding carpeting to the pontoon decking. We also get some information on SPX-Johnson bilge pumps and the ease of access they provide.</desc>
    <date>20250320</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716103000 +0000" stop="20250716110000 +0000">
    <title>Ship Shape TV</title>
    <sub-title>Essentials - "Painting Aluminum Hulls"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>During this episode of Ship Shape TV Essentials the SSTV team is at  - John’s lake house on Tupper Lake, NY, where they are tackling a new paint Job using Interlux’s paint specifically designed for aluminum hulls. John and the crew take us step by step on what takes to paint on aluminum hulls as well as some other tips from guest hosts.</desc>
    <date>20250414</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716110000 +0000" stop="20250716113013 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Kansas Year 15"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>We are in Kansas again chasing monster whitetails. This season makes 15 years that we have been going to Kansas and this year was special. But first we had to show you this amazing listing in South Louisiana that’s a little different for the Hunting Land Man.</desc>
    <date>20230816</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716113013 +0000" stop="20250716120012 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Home Grown"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode we are not going far, yeah, like 5ooyards from the front porch of my house. From new box stands, good help and maybe even a monster buck. This is all going on now on Hunting Land Man TV.</desc>
    <date>20230911</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716120012 +0000" stop="20250716123013 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Epic Redfish"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Witness a truly epic day on the water when Capt. Justin and Meredith find a secluded slice of beach teeming with redfish biting virtually everything. Topwater plugs, rusty flies and a live well full of bait make for an experience no redfish angler would forget</desc>
    <date>20230125</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716123013 +0000" stop="20250716130013 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Best Go With Plan B"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When your gut tells you to do something different than what’s in front of you, do you listen? - Capt. Justin and Meredith listen, and find that success comes in many forms. And it turns out that success can be really tasty, too!</desc>
    <date>20230130</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716130013 +0000" stop="20250716133020 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Grouper Open"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s opening day of grouper season and, for Capt. Justin Leake and one of his longtime fishing buddies, that means a trip offshore is in order. And what better way to break in a new boat than heading to some reefs and filling the cooler with one of the Gulf of Mexico’s most popular fish?</desc>
    <date>20230526</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716133020 +0000" stop="20250716140006 +0000">
    <title>Chasin' The Sun</title>
    <sub-title>"Foggy Bottom Fishing"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>There’s nothing like a change in weather conditions to wreck a perfectly good fishing plan, and that’s exactly what Capt. Justin Leake and his cousin encounter when December turns unseasonably warm. It’s a grey morning with thick fog so Justin and Capt. Brent Berry won’t be heading offshore right away as planned. Instead, Justin turns to his Humminbird CoastMaster charts to pinpoint a near shore artificial reef just five minutes from the St. Andrews Pass, where the anglers will do a little fishing until the fog burns off. Capt. Leake opts to send a jig to the bottom and he’s not very picky about the one that gets tied on. “When fishing reefs, the specific jig doesn’t matter because it’s all about the presentation,” he says. “When you’re sitting on top of a wreck, break out the ‘junk jigs’ – they get bit just fine.” And that proves to be the case as Justin and Brent enjoy non-stop battles against amberjack, red snapper and bonita. And with a bite this good, there’s no reason to go anywhere else! Also, we take a look at the United States Coast Guard Auxiliary’s new paddle craft safety initiative.</desc>
    <date>20230526</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716140006 +0000" stop="20250716143001 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Nine Lives"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Will Cooper finally trades 3 years of tough times for triumph in his quest to tag an out-of-state buck with a bow.</desc>
    <date>20231031</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716143001 +0000" stop="20250716145709 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Island Time"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh Dahlke grabs a TenPoint crossbow and kicks back on "Island Time," along with the Nashville rockers from Loose Lips.</desc>
    <date>20231106</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716145709 +0000" stop="20250716152959 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Coach"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Join Will Cooper on an unforgettable adventure in the Colorado mountains, where he dedicated three years chasing elusive bull elk without success. Determined to turn the tide, Will enlists the expertise of his good friend Jermaine Hodge, prior World Elk Calling Champion and Wrestling Coach for the United States Army World Class Athlete Program. Together, they face challenges and overcome adversity during a thrilling public land over-the-counter rifle hunt. Experience the highs and lows of their journey against the stunning backdrop of Colorado's wilderness.</desc>
    <date>20231218</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716152959 +0000" stop="20250716160003 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Prize Of The Plan"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In the wide world of western big game, pronghorn antelope hunting in Wyoming is unmatched in its accessibility and excitement. It’s an active pursuit, typically ripe with plenty of opportunities to spot and stalk black-horned bucks. This makes it an ideal forum for riflemen looking to scratch their western itch.</desc>
    <date>20231227</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716160003 +0000" stop="20250716163000 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Reunion In Colorado"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode Slade and the old Trained Assassins (TAT) crew head to Montrose, Colorado where they meet up with Slade’s dad, Bear Cub, TJ, and George for a heck of a week at Elk Camp. This is all going on now on Hunting Land Man TV.</desc>
    <date>20231129</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716163000 +0000" stop="20250716170000 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Opening Week in Mississippi started off with a BANG!!"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Opening day in Mississippi has arrived and Slade is taking full advantage of it! With the weather not cooperating Slade and Zeb stumble into a turkey hunt they won't soon forget. Two days later, the hot streak continues with Slade connecting on another turkey on an 83 acre property he has for sale! Also, Slade gives some tips and his ideas on small acreage hunting, and how it can be just as lucrative as big tracks of land!</desc>
    <date>20250602</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716170000 +0000" stop="20250716173001 +0000">
    <title>Hunting Land Man</title>
    <sub-title>"Two More Turkeys Down in Mississippi!!!"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, Slade and his son take on the turkey woods for an afternoon hunt. Although the woods remained quiet, a tom soon snuck out of the woods and on the end of Bentley's barrel! After that Slade was able to help a client of his harvest his first turkey! And boy was it an action packed hunt! Jakes, hens, and tons of gobbles, This hunt is spectacular! Lastly, Slade introduces a property that we have already made a video on, but with just how amazing the land is, we had to include it! Floweree is the epitome of a sportsman's paradise!</desc>
    <date>20250602</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716173001 +0000" stop="20250716180007 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Mule Deer Dilemma"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting are taking turns filming and hunting Mule Deer in Colorado where they both harvest big mature Colorado bucks with Browning 6.8 Westerns at long range. They leave Colorado and go to Nebraska to hunt with Heritage Outfitters and double up on two great spots and stalk bucks.</desc>
    <date>20250219</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716180007 +0000" stop="20250716183000 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"Western Turkey Tracks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting team up with a crew from Simmons Sporting Goods and head west to chase the Wild Turkey! Good times, Good Friends and Great Hunting make for an awesome Spring hunting trip.</desc>
    <date>20250319</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716183000 +0000" stop="20250716190000 +0000">
    <title>Browning Films</title>
    <sub-title>"2 Limits Of Ducks And 2 Swamp Bucks"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Kyle Barefield and Cole Barthel from All Things Hunting work on moving a duck blind in September before duck season then hunt it later that season for a two man limit in a flooded rice field. After that hunt Kyle heads to the deer stand where he is able to catch up with a big buck a friend had missed a couple days earlier. On the way to look for the buck he shot he comes across some buzzards that lead him to a different dead buck equal in size. Two Limits of ducks and two Swamp bucks is a hard couple of hunts to top.</desc>
    <date>20250619</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716190000 +0000" stop="20250716193001 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Epic Swordfish in the Keys"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon takes outdoorsman Zac Yarbrough to look for blackfin tuna and then out deep for swordfish. They are joined by Styles Haury for some epic offshore action.</desc>
    <date>20250206</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/ltTLmSKQ/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716193001 +0000" stop="20250716200005 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Lighthouses of the Florida Keys"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Renowned Kiteboarder Mike Walsh goes out on a windy day with Brandon to see what they can catch around the iconic lighthouses of the middle Keys.</desc>
    <date>20250303</date>
    <icon src="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/v2/media/6GhsdmQR/poster.jpg?width=720" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716200005 +0000" stop="20250716203001 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Fishing with Garrett Stephens"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Get to know one extraordinary person who works on the show as we go fishing with underwater cameraman and boat captain himself, Garrett Stephens.</desc>
    <date>20250328</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716203001 +0000" stop="20250716210000 +0000">
    <title>Life On The Water</title>
    <sub-title>"Charter Captain Pals"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Jared Dieguz has been fishing all his life and now that he's running his own charter business, finding a day to "scout" the sea is more important than ever.</desc>
    <date>20250407</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716210000 +0000" stop="20250716213007 +0000">
    <title>Captain's Log</title>
    <sub-title>"Havoc In Hypoluxo"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Jonathan Moss heads offshore with Capt. Chris LeMieux ready to face a little havoc!</desc>
    <date>20231115</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716213007 +0000" stop="20250716215959 +0000">
    <title>Operation Healing Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>"Ginger Gilbert-Ravella"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An Honor No One Wants: A Gold Star Family is the immediate family member(s) of a fallen soldier who died while serving in a time of conflict. Ginger Gilbert-Ravella honors the memory her husband…American hero Troy Gilbert.</desc>
    <date>20250228</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716215959 +0000" stop="20250716221601 +0000">
    <title>The Raven Project</title>
    <sub-title>"I-70 and The River Farm"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Randy and Cody are wrapping things up on the Raven before bow season arrives in Missouri. Planting I-70 the plot where Randy killed one of his biggest Missouri bucks ever last year. Then Randy and Cody attempt to setup a new farm they are calling “The River Farm” they attempt to plant a food plot, bush hog, spray the plot, setup a new Titan blind, and setup a Hooyman dual perimeter fence all in one day before the sun goes down.</desc>
    <date>20241014</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716221601 +0000" stop="20250716223001 +0000">
    <title>The Raven Project</title>
    <sub-title>"Pirates Of The Canadian"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The boys are at the Dirty Bird in Oklahoma trying to run some trot lines on the North Canadian river but the water is just a little lower than they expected.</desc>
    <date>20240903</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716223001 +0000" stop="20250716230024 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand Presents</title>
    <sub-title>"Island Time"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh Dahlke grabs a TenPoint crossbow and kicks back on "Island Time," along with the Nashville rockers from Loose Lips.</desc>
    <date>20231106</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716230024 +0000" stop="20250716233021 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"Advanced Food Plots"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S21E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In this in-depth episode of Deer &amp; Deer Hunting TV, the team explores what it truly takes to implement an advanced food plot strategy. We go beyond the basics, walking viewers through soil science, crop rotation, plot placement, and how to integrate food plots into a larger habitat management plan.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250716233021 +0000" stop="20250717000016 +0000">
    <title>Deer and Deer Hunting</title>
    <sub-title>"Patterning Hunters"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E04</episode-num>
    <desc>We explore the sophisticated world of the whitetail deer's senses, exploring how these remarkable creatures have evolved to pattern hunters through their keen sense of smell and heightened sensory awareness.</desc>
    <date>20240808</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250717000016 +0000" stop="20250717002831 +0000">
    <title>Spring  Thunder</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Thunder - "Big Osceola Dreams"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Buckmasters, Honey Brake and Realtree have joined forces with Big Dream Outdoors to get Justin Webb and Brandi Deese a grand slam on video this spring. Justin completes the first leg of the slam with a 2-for-1 Osceola special. Next stop-Texas for the Rio!</desc>
    <date>20250326</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250717002831 +0000" stop="20250717005607 +0000">
    <title>Spring  Thunder</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Thunder - "Big Rio Dreams"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Second leg in the slam is complete! Justin Webb killed his Rio in Texas.  - Next stop - Tennessee for the Eastern.</desc>
    <date>20250403</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250717005607 +0000" stop="20250717010012 +0000">
    <title>HuntStand TIps and Gear</title>
    <sub-title>HuntStand Tips &amp; Gear - "3 Reasons You Need the HuntStand App for Deer Camp"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>From group sharing, to detailed wind forecasts, to the most accurate predictive model for whitetail movement, Will Cooper shares three big reasons you need the HuntStand app in deer camp.</desc>
    <date>20250121</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5fd115b8b7ef8d002dcf1817" start="20250717010012 +0000" stop="20250717013004 +0000">
    <title>Winchester Life</title>
    <sub-title>"Remembering A Legend"</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Nestled in the hills of Ohio just west of the Appalachians is a very special deer camp ripe with memories from deer season’s past. With the development of the 350 Legend straight-walled cartridge by Winchester in 2019, a world of opportunities now existed in states like Ohio and Michigan. In this episode, with the 350 Legend in hand, three mature whitetails meet their maker, from the same blind, over the course of three seasons.</desc>
    <date>20250317</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/arts/waypointtv_artwork_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
