<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59">
    <display-name>Aliwko</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/e20f693c-bf2d-448e-884b-36ec8d382eb7/Aliwko_Plexlogo_1500x1000_-_Ali_Clausen_color.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719225456 +0000" stop="20250719232829 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>26 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>With enough persuasion from Bernard, the court lets Romina file a petition for bail. Daniela, on the other hand, refuses to accept the jury's decision and presses Atty. Cabrera to make sure Romina stays behind bars. Elsewhere, Carlos fails to contain his anger after much provocation from Hector. Meanwhile, Marga grows even more determined to reclaim everything Cassie took from her.</desc>
    <date>20190325</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_26_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250719232829 +0000" stop="20250720000207 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>27 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After giving up her allowance to Marga, Cassie struggles to afford the materials she needs for a school project. Refusing to give up, she finds a way to earn her own money, but Marga pulls another stunt to thwart Cassie's plan. Meanwhile, Daniela orders Cindy to do something to prevent Romina from getting permission to bail. Elsewhere, Kulas gives Hector a piece of his mind for stepping on Carlos’ dignity.</desc>
    <date>20190326</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s6_27_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720000207 +0000" stop="20250720003611 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>15 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to clear his name from the allegations, Jacob enlists Atty. Balmaceda's help to track down his secret enemy. Perturbed by her husband's latest move, Jean relays this new information to Sonya. Unbeknownst to them, their hidden allegiance is on the verge of being discovered. Meanwhile, Anna finds herself in a life-threatening situation and Paco races against time to save her.</desc>
    <date>20180316</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_15_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720003611 +0000" stop="20250720011301 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>16 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Paco falls into police hands upon accidentally ending Dindo's life. With Paco's back against the wall, a trusted ally comes to his aid. Jean, on the other hand, goes to great lengths to earn Jacob's trust. Later, her efforts pay off when Jacob lays some of his cards on the table. Meanwhile, a witness offers to testify against Jacob.</desc>
    <date>20180319</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_16_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720011301 +0000" stop="20250720014903 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jean remains committed to play mind games with Jacob despite his confession on the embezzlements within EduCare. However, she reaches her boiling point upon learning about his hideous plan against Anna. Anna, on the other hand, learns that someone has been protecting her without her knowledge. Meanwhile, Domeng insists on testifying against Jacob. Unfortunately, his post-traumatic condition hinders his request.</desc>
    <date>20180320</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720014903 +0000" stop="20250720022457 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Staying true to his word, Jacob sets up a ploy in order to test Jean's loyalty to him. However, Mrs. Montecillo decides to play along thus, suppressing his skepticism of her. Despite this, Jacob remains adamant to make his wife pay the moment she betrays him. Meanwhile, Letty arrives at a shocking revelation about Jean. This leaves Sonya with no other choice but to spill everything to Letty.</desc>
    <date>20180321</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720022457 +0000" stop="20250720030132 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>For the sake of toppling Jacob, Sonya finally agrees to join forces with his former henchwomen, Katrina and Marjorie. As such, Jean immediately relays to the two to carry out her plan of spying on her husband. However, they only have limited time to get the dirty job done. Domeng, meanwhile, recounts the moments leading to Jacob's attempt to murder him before the fiscal. Unbeknownst to him, a looming danger awaits him and his family once again.</desc>
    <date>20180322</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_19_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720030132 +0000" stop="20250720033535 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Perplexed by his latest discovery, Jacob rushes to his house believing that someone has broken in. Jean, on the other hand, finds a way to distract her husband from searching. Because of this, Katrina, Letty, and Marjorie have time to leave the Montecillo's home. Meanwhile, through the help of Jojo and Rizalina, the Alipios surpass another challenge caused by SPO3 Asuncion and his men. Elsewhere, Anna becomes emotional upon learning that Paco is longing for Georgette.</desc>
    <date>20180323</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720033535 +0000" stop="20250720040534 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob scolds SPO3 Asuncion for his failed mission. The wicked police then comes up with a brilliant idea to locate Domeng. Rizalina, on the other hand, presses Suarez to admit the identity of the mastermind behind the abduction attempt on Domeng. Later, Jojo and Rizalina's suspicion intensifies upon seeing the facial expression of SPO3 Asuncion's henchman. Meanwhile, Jean continues to manipulate Jacob.</desc>
    <date>20180326</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720040534 +0000" stop="20250720043905 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob resolves to abscond from his cases once again, putting Jean in an even more difficult situation. Unfortunately for him, Katrina and Marjorie learn about his wicked plan. They inform Sonya who fears that Jean might not be able to free herself from her husband's hands. Adding to Sonya's worries, SPO3 Asuncion vehemently forbids Jojo and Rizalina from helping her cause. Meanwhile, Atty. Vega's camp receives new information regarding Jacob's embezzlement case.</desc>
    <date>20180327</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720043905 +0000" stop="20250720062945 +0000">
    <title>Mia</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Mia Salazar, a self-destructive, alcoholic doctor who joined the Doctor to the Barrios program to heal from the tragedy of her fiance's death meets the cheerful and nerdy forester Jay Policarpio. Together, the two will embark on a new journey.</desc>
    <date>20200115</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/mia_1200x1600.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720062945 +0000" stop="20250720070000 +0000">
    <title>The General's Daughter</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving an order from Gen. Maximillano, the military carries out a thorough search of an agency believed to be a troll farm. One of its owners tries to escape from the authorities but eventually falls into the hands of Rhian, Franco, and Marcial. Taking advantage of his new discovery, Tiago requests Dante to find any information on Rhian's whereabouts from Isabelle. Elsewhere, Jessie and Ethan seem to have different perspectives on their upcoming marriage.</desc>
    <date>20190805</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/the_generals_daughter_s7_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720070000 +0000" stop="20250720072910 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>17 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Maila, troubled by Rigor’s possible involvement in her assault, turns to Victoria for answers. Victoria rebukes Rigor, but he threatens her in return. Meanwhile, Bianca and Gabriel arrive at the triathlon camp. Carlos, now in control of Tiger Shark, shifts the brand’s campaign focus. Lydia grows suspicious of Rigor.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_17_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720072910 +0000" stop="20250720075706 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While Bianca and Gabriel train in Batangas, Rigor claims his son’s allowance from Tiger Shark and runs into Roman, who confronts him about his past with Victoria. Victoria later faces trouble after learning of their exchange. Meanwhile, Lydia searches for answers, and Maila confronts Rigor about her robbery.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720075706 +0000" stop="20250720082429 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Maila visits the thrift shop where Rigor claimed he bought her wallet. Roman shares his suspicions with Carlos, who warns Victoria to stay away from Rigor. Still doubtful, Roman orders an investigation into Victoria and Rigor’s connection.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_19_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720082429 +0000" stop="20250720085147 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bianca and Gabriel make the most of their remaining days at the triathlon camp but return home to a family issue. After learning of Maila’s suspicions, Gabriel confronts Rigor. Meanwhile, Roman discovers the changes Carlos made to Tiger Shark’s campaign and later receives an incriminating report about Victoria and Rigor.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720085147 +0000" stop="20250720091943 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Maila and Ben dig deeper into Rigor and Victoria's past. Fearing their secret will be exposed, Victoria urges Rigor to keep his distance for now. Rigor tries to dispel suspicions by showing he’s a changed man. Meanwhile, Roman plans Victoria's birthday celebration, and Carlos aims to introduce Bianca and Gabriel as the energy couple.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720091943 +0000" stop="20250720094725 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Unbeknownst to Bianca, Maila and Ben continue investigating Rigor. They meet his former coach and confront Victoria about their discovery. Meanwhile, Roman obtains Gabriel's birth certificate. Bianca and Gabriel are introduced as Tiger Shark’s newest endorsers. To Carlos’ surprise, Roman arrives at the press launch to speak with Gabriel.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720094725 +0000" stop="20250720101557 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Following Roman’s advice, Gabriel asks Rigor about his mother, but Rigor gives a fabricated story. Gabriel shares it with Roman and receives a kind offer in return. Meanwhile, Carlos informs Victoria of Roman’s sudden interest in Gabriel’s mother. Elsewhere, Steph invites Jay-Jay over.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720101557 +0000" stop="20250720104337 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>24 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabriel asks Rigor about his mother, but doubts his father’s honesty. Later, Carlos invites him for a drink. Isabel is hopeful about rekindling her friendship with Carlos, but faces constant disagreement with her mother. Meanwhile, Roman discovers that Maila is investigating Rigor as well.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_24_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720104337 +0000" stop="20250720111138 +0000">
    <title>Ikaw Lang Ang Iibigin</title>
    <sub-title>25 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Carlos comforts Isabel, unknowingly giving her false hope of a reconciliation. Her joy fades when she hears Sandra arguing with Josh. Later, Carlos meets Gabriel for a drink and informs him about Rigor’s attempts to contact Victoria. Meanwhile, Maila gets a call from an unexpected source.</desc>
    <date>20170501</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/ikaw_lang_ang_iibigin_s2_25_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720111138 +0000" stop="20250720114652 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert decides to throw a birthday party once again for Cassie. Daniela disapproves and convinces her father to host a party for Marga instead, insisting that her daughter is the real Mondragon. In order to be fair and equal, Robert chooses to hold a double birthday celebration for the girls. Marga rejects this and becomes jealous of Cassie for taking the spotlight away from her. The tension between Romina and Daniela intensifies.</desc>
    <date>20190129</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720114652 +0000" stop="20250720122245 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>23 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After being reminded by Daniela to show good graces, Marga cannot help but feel jealous of Cassie during their double birthday celebration. Romina, meanwhile, is now determined to reopen her case. Because of this, Daniela worries that she might get in trouble. Kulas, on the other hand, does everything he can to prevent the truth from coming out. Robert conducts an investigation of his own upon learning that Daniela supposedly used her family's savings for the company's projects.</desc>
    <date>20190130</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_23_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720122245 +0000" stop="20250720125716 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>24 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A bunch of comments ridiculing Marga pops up on social media after the party. Afraid to lose her status in school, the young Mondragon takes her anger out on Cassie and humiliates her in front of their classmates. However, karma works fast and bites her in the back. Meanwhile, Romina takes matters into her own hands and looks for evidence to support her case. Daniela, on the other hand, rushes to cover up her tracks.</desc>
    <date>20190131</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_24_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720125716 +0000" stop="20250720133134 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>25 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving an anonymous tip about a vital piece of evidence connected to her rape case, Romina is determined to get it. Kulas, on the other hand, grows anxious as he finds out that the police are now after his accomplice who handled Romina’s case. He then warns Police Officer Presto to lay low. Later on, the Mondragons finally meet one of the men who abducted Marga and Cassie. Having had enough of Marga's bullying, Cassie decides to fight back.</desc>
    <date>20190201</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_25_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720133134 +0000" stop="20250720140559 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>26 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on attaining justice, Romina presses Mark to reveal the mastermind behind Marga and Cassie’s abduction. However, her relentless pursuit of the truth hits a bump in the road when she learns about the suspect’s fate. In an unexpected turn of events, Romina receives an intriguing offer from an anonymous caller. Meanwhile, Marga instigates another fight between her and Cassie. Fed up, the young Mondragon resolves to fight back.</desc>
    <date>20190204</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_26_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720140559 +0000" stop="20250720144112 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>27 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniela and Carlos learn that Marga is at risk of being dismissed from Maxwell because of bullying accusations. They also learn that Marga's actions stem from her problems at home. Daniela and Carlos then agree to make an effort in hopes of helping Marga change her behavior. Meanwhile, Romina agrees to a deal with the mysterious caller holding the evidence she needs. However, Romina receives a stern warning ahead of their negotiation.</desc>
    <date>20190205</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_27_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720144112 +0000" stop="20250720151557 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>28 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Making a promise to her parents, Marga tries to change for the better. However, Marga's friends decide to pull a prank on Cassie, risking her dismissal from Maxwell. Daniela finds out that Romina is getting close to securing the evidence she needs to reopen her rape case. Daniela then tries to find a way to cover up her crime. Meanwhile, Myrna's lies about her illness are catching up on her.</desc>
    <date>20190206</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_28_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720151557 +0000" stop="20250720155027 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>29 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Kulas finds out that Myrna has been using a fake illness to extort money from him. Despite Myrna's desperate appeals, Kulas throws her out without a moment's hesitation. Meanwhile, Romina is desperate to secure the evidence to reopen her rape case. However, Daniela and Alvin remain determined to stop her at all costs. Elsewhere, Carlos rewards Marga upon finding out about his daughter's good deed.</desc>
    <date>20190207</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_29_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720155027 +0000" stop="20250720162522 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>30 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After being driven out by her family, Myrna seeks refuge with Jessa. Much to her disappointment, Myrna learns that Jessa carried out her plan to extort money from Romina. Despite this, Myrna covers up for Jessa and surrenders herself to the police. Meanwhile, Romina becomes more determined to have her assaulter punished after confirming the evidence in her rape case. Elsewhere, Daniela worries that her crimes might soon be revealed.</desc>
    <date>20190208</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_30_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720162522 +0000" stop="20250720165927 +0000">
    <title>Kadenang Ginto</title>
    <sub-title>31 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Kulas ends up as the new prime suspect in Romina's rape case. Later, Daniela confronts her father-in-law for hiding the CD to prevent Carlos from reuniting with Romina. The Bartolome patriarch then gives his daughter-in-law an enticing offer. Meanwhile, Robert acquires vital information about the person who stalked him and Romina. Elsewhere, an unexpected event compels Cassie to spend time with Alvin.</desc>
    <date>20190211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/kadenang_ginto_s5_31_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720165927 +0000" stop="20250720190000 +0000">
    <title>On Vodka, Beers and Regrets</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Jane Pineda is a washed-up actress and former child star whose career hits rock bottom while trying to escape a big scandal.</desc>
    <date>20200205</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/onvodkabeersregrets_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720190000 +0000" stop="20250720193554 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>18 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Staying true to his word, Jacob sets up a ploy in order to test Jean's loyalty to him. However, Mrs. Montecillo decides to play along thus, suppressing his skepticism of her. Despite this, Jacob remains adamant to make his wife pay the moment she betrays him. Meanwhile, Letty arrives at a shocking revelation about Jean. This leaves Sonya with no other choice but to spill everything to Letty.</desc>
    <date>20180321</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_18_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720193554 +0000" stop="20250720201229 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>19 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>For the sake of toppling Jacob, Sonya finally agrees to join forces with his former henchwomen, Katrina and Marjorie. As such, Jean immediately relays to the two to carry out her plan of spying on her husband. However, they only have limited time to get the dirty job done. Domeng, meanwhile, recounts the moments leading to Jacob's attempt to murder him before the fiscal. Unbeknownst to him, a looming danger awaits him and his family once again.</desc>
    <date>20180322</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_19_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720201229 +0000" stop="20250720204632 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>20 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Perplexed by his latest discovery, Jacob rushes to his house believing that someone has broken in. Jean, on the other hand, finds a way to distract her husband from searching. Because of this, Katrina, Letty, and Marjorie have time to leave the Montecillo's home. Meanwhile, through the help of Jojo and Rizalina, the Alipios surpass another challenge caused by SPO3 Asuncion and his men. Elsewhere, Anna becomes emotional upon learning that Paco is longing for Georgette.</desc>
    <date>20180323</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_20_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720204632 +0000" stop="20250720211631 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>21 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob scolds SPO3 Asuncion for his failed mission. The wicked police then comes up with a brilliant idea to locate Domeng. Rizalina, on the other hand, presses Suarez to admit the identity of the mastermind behind the abduction attempt on Domeng. Later, Jojo and Rizalina's suspicion intensifies upon seeing the facial expression of SPO3 Asuncion's henchman. Meanwhile, Jean continues to manipulate Jacob.</desc>
    <date>20180326</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_21_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720211631 +0000" stop="20250720215002 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>22 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Jacob resolves to abscond from his cases once again, putting Jean in an even more difficult situation. Unfortunately for him, Katrina and Marjorie learn about his wicked plan. They inform Sonya who fears that Jean might not be able to free herself from her husband's hands. Adding to Sonya's worries, SPO3 Asuncion vehemently forbids Jojo and Rizalina from helping her cause. Meanwhile, Atty. Vega's camp receives new information regarding Jacob's embezzlement case.</desc>
    <date>20180327</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s4_22_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720215002 +0000" stop="20250720222237 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>01 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Atty. Vega starts off with a plan of her own to stop Jacob from running away from his crimes. The entire camp, however, remains puzzled as to who tipped them of his plan to escape. Eventually, a series of developments points to Jacob as the mastermind behind the information the feisty lawyer received. The entire camp concludes that their enemy is using his wicked ways to their disadvantage.</desc>
    <date>20180328</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s5_01_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720222237 +0000" stop="20250720225624 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>02 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning where she and Jacob are heading to, Jean tries to contact Sonya to inform her of their destination. Jacob, however, finds a way to cut off his and Jean's communication with everyone. Meanwhile, Anna and Paco get help from Atty. Vega in pursuing Jacob. Anna later breathes a sigh of relief as she and Paco accidentally locate Jean and Jacob. Soon, Paco and Anna are shocked upon discovering something about their mothers.</desc>
    <date>20180402</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s5_02_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-64d4ee537b323f6abbd19e59" start="20250720225624 +0000" stop="20250720233035 +0000">
    <title>Hanggang Saan</title>
    <sub-title>03 </sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The police enact an entrapment operation against Jacob before the latter could flee the country with Jean. Worried about her mother, Anna waits with bated breath as the police prepare to attack. Despite Atty. Vega's careful planning, Jacob notices something off as he and Jean arrive at the port. Upon confirming his suspicion, Jacob engages in a shootout with the authorities. In the heat of the commotion, an innocent life is put in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>20180403</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/imd/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/hanggang_saan_s5_03_landscape.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
