<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705000644 +0000" stop="20250705005135 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>17 And Out Of Control</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you struggling to tame your rebellious teen? Chris and Barbara say their 17-year-old daughter, Courtney, is out of control! The teen proudly admits she bullies, steals, drinks and does drugs and is consumed with anger. Can Dr. Phil set her straight? Parents: If you know a teen who’s heading down a dangerous path, this is one show you can't afford to miss!</desc>
    <date>20120125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705005135 +0000" stop="20250705013657 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Double Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E92</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan and Teresa say their 16-year-old identical twins, Dallas and Drew are violent, destructive and dangerous, and they fear someone will end up seriously hurt, or even dead. What’s at the root of the teens’ anger and extreme jealousy that’s driving them apart? Could the parents be contributing to the explosive situation? Broken bones, violent fights, destruction of property -- today’s guests aren’t enemies; they are 16-year-old identical twin brothers. Dr. Phil examines the jealousy and torment that's driving these siblings apart and throwing their home into chaos.</desc>
    <date>20120201</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10092.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705013657 +0000" stop="20250705022334 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Little Miss Attitude!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Renae says her 14-year-old daughter, Amanda, was a model child and a parent's dream, but in the last couple of years has become a rebellious and violent teen. Renae says Amanda's anger is oftentimes directed at her. She says the teen has punched her -- as many as 50 times in the last year -- has knocked her teeth out, called her names and has kicked, bitten and spit on her. Amanda admits that she doesn't respect her mother -- or any authority -- and that she has a violent temper, but says, "Fights find me." Then, Amanda's stepdad, Mike, weighs in. Hear why he calls his stepdaughter Satan and how he feels about her outrageous behavior. Can Dr. Phil help show Amanda more effective ways to channel her aggression -- and her family better ways to cope with her? Then, Courtney, a police officer who works with juveniles, says that despite her training, she can't control her defiant, eye-rolling 16-year-old daughter, Sabby's, bad attitude. She says when Sabby doesn't get her way, she works herself up into a rage and has pushed her grandmother, threatened to kill her younger sister, and was sent to and kicked out of boot camp just recently. Then, meet Sabby, who maintains her defiance with Dr. Phil. What does Courtney believe is at the root of her daughter's anger? Dr. Phil offers his insight and opinion. Can he get through to this tough teen? If you are having a difficult time raising your teen, don't miss this episode.</desc>
    <date>20121023</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11039.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705022334 +0000" stop="20250705031220 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Is There a Predator in the House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>As a parent, you're likely to be concerned about sexual predators who could potentially gain access to your child. But what if you suspected a child molester were living under the same roof as your child or grandchild? Dr. Phil tackles the stories of two concerned moms.</desc>
    <date>20080715</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705031220 +0000" stop="20250705035905 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen writes: Dear Dr. Phil, My husband mentally abuses me. I've never, in my life, had a guy tell me how fat I am, how terrible I look, or criticize how I put my makeup on. He constantly calls me names and makes fat jokes. Sometimes I have to hide in the bathroom when I eat something just so we won't fight about it. Any time I try to get close to him, he literally pushes me away and says, "Don't even touch me until you're under 200 pounds".</desc>
    <date>20250531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705035905 +0000" stop="20250705044535 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>An Obsessed Love Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Sandie says she desperately hopes to win back her ex-husband, Chris, so they can be a family again with their adopted 11-year-old daughter, but Chris’ ex-girlfriend, Aileen, will stop at nothing to keep them apart. Sandie says Aileen is stalking and harassing her, making false reports of abuse and neglect to CPS, and even created a fake profile on Facebook to talk trash about her -- and she wants Aileen prosecuted. Sandie says she and Chris have filed a total of nine peace orders against Aileen, but only the last one filed by Chris was granted, protecting him -- but not Sandie or their daughter. Aileen admits to intentionally causing trouble but says Sandie deserves it, because she destroyed Aileen’s relationship with Chris -- and she also wants him back. Chris says he’s tired of being caught in the middle of his exes and isn’t interested in a relationship with either one, other than co-parenting with Sandie -- but is he sending mixed messages? Can this trio reach a truce and learn to respect boundaries?</desc>
    <date>20140214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705044535 +0000" stop="20250705053108 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Dr. Phil Exclusive: The Boy Under the Stairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E412</episode-num>
    <desc>Exclusive interview with Windy Hall, the biological mother whose 5-year-old malnourished son, Jordan Bleimeyer, was locked in a closet by his father and stepmother.</desc>
    <date>20140424</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12412.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705053108 +0000" stop="20250705060541 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Exclusive: Boy Under The Stairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E406</episode-num>
    <desc>In March 2014, authorities found severely malnourished 5-year-old Jordan Bleimeyer after he allegedly had been locked inside a small closet under the stairs of a Houston-area home. His father, Bradley, and stepmother, Tammi, were arrested and charged with felony child endangerment. In an exclusive interview, Tammi breaks her silence -- why does she say she had no idea what was happening to her stepson?</desc>
    <date>20141118</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13406.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705060541 +0000" stop="20250705065020 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Boy Under Stairs: Hero Siblings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E413</episode-num>
    <desc>The siblings of 5-year-old Jordan Bleimeyer, who was held captive in a tiny cubbyhole under the stairs, starved and abused by his father and stepmother, reveal how they sneaked Jordan food and freed him from his closet prison, saving his life.</desc>
    <date>20190131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17413.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705065020 +0000" stop="20250705073617 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Was Mommy Murdered?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E99</episode-num>
    <desc>The saga of a father's quest for his vanished daughter is discussed.</desc>
    <date>20100303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8099.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705073617 +0000" stop="20250705082035 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>We Survived a Cult</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E402</episode-num>
    <desc>30 years after being forced into a religious sect full of sexual abuse, some of its victims share their stories for the first time.</desc>
    <date>20201026</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19402.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705082035 +0000" stop="20250705090718 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Husband’s Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E98</episode-num>
    <desc>Danielle says that her husband of nearly 10 years, John, has been living a secret life -- reaching out to men on Craigslist for sex and looking at child pornography. John insists that the child porn was accidentally downloaded, and while he admits to exchanging emails with men online, he maintains that he never met up with anyone in person. How does he explain his actions? And, what will the results of a polygraph test reveal?</desc>
    <date>20140221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12098.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705090718 +0000" stop="20250705095343 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Her Baby Be Born Addicted?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E93</episode-num>
    <desc>In a gripping 2-part series, a mother seeks help for her pregnant, drug-using teen.</desc>
    <date>20140127</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12093.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705095343 +0000" stop="20250705103817 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Pregnant and Abusing Drugs!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E318</episode-num>
    <desc>In a gripping 2-part series, Dr. Phil continues a drug intervention with an 18-year-old pregnant teen and her 20-year-sister.</desc>
    <date>20140128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12318.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705103817 +0000" stop="20250705112402 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Mother's Betrayal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E128</episode-num>
    <desc>Sunny was enraged when she learned her mom, Carolyn, was adopting Sunny’s 36-year-old ex-boyfriend, Chris, and begged her to not go through with the process. Now that the adoption is final, she says Carolyn puts more time and energy into her relationship with Chris than into their mother-daughter bond. Carolyn says she always wanted a son and was over-the-moon when she finally adopted Chris. She says no parent has to ask their child for permission to have more children, so why should she need Sunny’s approval to adopt Chris? Carolyn and Sunny see each other for the first time in more than six months on Dr. Phil’s stage. Can Sunny move past her feelings of betrayal, and can Dr. Phil help them mend their broken bond? Then, why did Chris, a married father of three, want to be adopted?</desc>
    <date>20120906</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705112402 +0000" stop="20250705120953 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Twisted Love: The Aftermath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E112</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil follows up with Charles and Tracy. After coming to the conclusion that his dream of being shared by his wife and mistress was never going to happen, did Charles follow through and end his relationship with the other woman?</desc>
    <date>20060227</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705120953 +0000" stop="20250705125822 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>On the Outs With the In-Laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E113</episode-num>
    <desc>Manipulative, violent, controlling, downright diabolical. These are some of the words Anna-Laura uses to describe her mother-in-law, Janice. Anna-Laura says her mother-in-law has threatened to take her children away, calls 12-15 times per day, peeks in their windows, goes through their trash, drives to Anna-Laura’s house and points her finger – from her car- as if she is pulling the trigger of a gun. Morgan says his mother also opens the front door and walks into their home unannounced. Anna-Laura says she got a restraining order against her mother-in-law after Janice hit her, which Janice denies. She says Janice is forcing her husband, Morgan, to choose between his mother and his wife. What can this family do to get along with one another?</desc>
    <date>20060228</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4113.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705125822 +0000" stop="20250705134236 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Tourette’s Made Me Viral</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E106</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman posts Tik Tok videos of her struggle with Tourette syndrome.</desc>
    <date>20220302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L20106.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705134236 +0000" stop="20250705142918 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Fights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you have a relative scheming to get money from a rich aunt, uncle or even parents when they pass away?</desc>
    <date>20071113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705142918 +0000" stop="20250705151517 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>DP Scam - Part One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E55</episode-num>
    <desc>You hear about scams all the time - e-mails and voicemails claiming you have won valuable prizes. Dr. Phil is outraged by what some scammers are doing to him, his family and his viewers. One website offers a Dr. Phil quiz to win $5,000 every hour, another says it has the official Dr. Phil personality test, but even more shocking are 800 numbers that take callers' money for the promise of over the phone therapy with Dr. Phil and Robin. But these 800 numbers connect innocent victims with con artists posing as Dr. Phil staff members. The fake staffers ask anywhere from $375 to $1,000 for consultation time that obviously never takes place.</desc>
    <date>20061109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5055.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705151517 +0000" stop="20250705160117 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>DP Scam Part 2 “The Sting”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E304</episode-num>
    <desc>The drama continues as Dr. Phil goes on the hunt for con artists who cheat viewers out of thousands of dollars by posing as him and Robin.</desc>
    <date>20061110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705160117 +0000" stop="20250705164742 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Living on a Prayer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E65</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents who force their children to live an extreme, harsh existence.</desc>
    <date>20080215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705164742 +0000" stop="20250705173333 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Grandson in a Filthy Death Trap!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents say their daughter's home is unsafe for grandson.</desc>
    <date>20201006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19028.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705173333 +0000" stop="20250705181852 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Rude Relatives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E51</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you know someone who turns your stomach or makes you cringe the minute he or she walks into the room? Dr. Phil talks to guests who say their relative's rude behavior keeps them on edge.</desc>
    <date>20061122</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705181852 +0000" stop="20250705190607 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Want Out!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E79</episode-num>
    <desc>When couples tie the knot, they vow to stay together "'til death do us part," but what happens when a marriage takes a few bad turns, and one partner desperately wants out?</desc>
    <date>20080124</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705190607 +0000" stop="20250705195223 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Broken Family Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sara says her ex-husband, Mark, has brainwashed their three grown children against her, and she just wants to reclaim a place in their lives. Mark and his new wife, Mikel, say they’re afraid of Sara but are willing to face her onstage with Dr. Phil. Can these exes put the past behind them and make peace? And, is Sara’s 22-year-old daughter willing to fix their broken relationship?</desc>
    <date>20131101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705195223 +0000" stop="20250705203823 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Chelsea Refuses to Grow Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Is it asking too much for your 20-something child to make his or her own money and live independently? Barbara says her daughter, Chelsea, needs to grow up! She says she’s given her daughter nothing but the best, and all she has to show for it is a lying child who won’t speak to her. Chelsea says she can’t live up to her mom’s “rich bitch” expectations and just wants to be left alone. Mother and daughter see each other on the Dr. Phil stage for the first time in seven months, and sparks fly! Is Barbara surprised to learn the secret Chelsea reveals? Then, Chelsea’s grandmother isn’t immune to her granddaughter’s conniving ways. Learn why she feels used. And, Barbara says Chelsea has spent thousands of dollars of her family’s money, and anytime she earns her own, she spends it and doesn’t pay her family back. Dr. Phil conducts an experiment to see what the young woman will do with $500. You may be surprised by the results!</desc>
    <date>20101105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705203823 +0000" stop="20250705212421 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E132</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil is launching his parenting boot camp and teaching parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090505</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7132.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705212421 +0000" stop="20250705221115 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E217</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7217.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705221115 +0000" stop="20250705225819 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E218</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7218.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705225819 +0000" stop="20250705234656 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Bootcamp 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E219</episode-num>
    <desc>Have your children gone from little angels to kids gone wild? Are they whiney, tantrum-throwing, feet-stomping, door-slamming, spoiled and entitled? Well, good news, Mom and Dad! Dr. Phil launches his parenting boot camp and teaches parents how to take back control and live in peace for the very first time.</desc>
    <date>20090526</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7219.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250705234656 +0000" stop="20250706003424 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Honeymoon Hangover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E89</episode-num>
    <desc>Couples confront post-honeymoon marriage challenges.</desc>
    <date>20090128</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7089.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
