<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723">
    <display-name>Documentary+</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/3bb2a1fe-7a16-4fa1-9db7-63b7fef3a376/documentaryplus_logo_dark_1_WHT.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250711233633 +0000" stop="20250712012115 +0000">
    <title>The Hobby</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A McDonald’s Happy Meal shortage. A security guard escort. Guns pulled in a Target parking lot. All of these are caused by a common factor: trading cards. In 2020, a new BOOM began. For the first time, large hedge funds, celebrities like Logan Paul and Steve Aoki, nostalgic millennials, entrepreneurs like Josh Luber, and billionaires scrambled to add sports, Pokémon, and other hot item cards to their collections and portfolios. Over the next two years, the hobby exploded — even causing card grading services to shut down due to overwhelming customer service. This documentary is a character-driven feel good deep dive into the high-stakes, eccentric world of card collecting, following buyers, sellers, card shop owners, graders, online streamers, auctioneers, and more, who all participate in the hobby in their own unique ways. Directed by Morgan Jon Fox.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe/original/1r1zwrbofl5ga1hqhhjc4tbxe.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712012115 +0000" stop="20250712023544 +0000">
    <title>Lewis Hamilton: The Winning Formula</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As the only black Formula One driver in history, Lewis' journey to becoming the most decorated Formula One driver in history, is one of dreams, courage, and determination. Directed by Piers Garland.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1/original/s8rtr5p7edhm1ldm9o5kly6y1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712023544 +0000" stop="20250712033456 +0000">
    <title>Kobe Bryant: A Tribute</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The sudden and tragic passing of Kobe Bryant, alongside his young daughter Gianna left the world in a stunned silence. Never before has a sporting star held such high esteem outside of their profession… But Kobe Bryant was a superstar. Unmatched on the basketball court and cherished on the red carpet– Kobe’s dedication to his career, his family and his charity work led to him being adored the world over. Directed by Danielle Winter.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1hnwqz96frnvb149510harw2h/original/1hnwqz96frnvb149510harw2h.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712033456 +0000" stop="20250712043903 +0000">
    <title>The Taylor Swift Story: Dare To Dream</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The incredible journey of Taylor Swift all began with a girl, a guitar and a dream. Taylor Swift is a ten time Grammy winner, and the youngest recipient in history of the music industry’s highest honor, follow the story of an artist who turned a childhood dream into an empire. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/f8g1pm8w4tcv1ovtbgj3ztl9e/original/f8g1pm8w4tcv1ovtbgj3ztl9e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712043903 +0000" stop="20250712054905 +0000">
    <title>Beyonce: Queen B</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>One of the most recognizable figures in contemporary music. Get lost in the ultimate story of modern day superstardom as we take you through the incredible journey of Beyoncé. Directed by Billy Simpson.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1s6q5k9zm2p0z1jkxqauuehch/original/1s6q5k9zm2p0z1jkxqauuehch.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712054905 +0000" stop="20250712070048 +0000">
    <title>The Last 24 Hours: Amy Winehouse</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a very public battle with addiction the world was saddened to hear the shocking news that Amy Winehouse was found dead in her bedroom at the young age of 27. We investigate what really happened during the final 24 hours of the singer’s life, with exclusive interviews and testimonials. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240513</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1rwbqvysjtfeb1emjxae13yua/original/1rwbqvysjtfeb1emjxae13yua.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712070048 +0000" stop="20250712075348 +0000">
    <title>The Diana Story: Part I: The Young Princess</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the summer of 1980, a shy young girl arrives at Balmoral Castle. Two years later that girl became a royal princess. At just 20 years old, Lady Diana Spencer married HRH Prince Charles to become HRH Princess Of Wales. From her first steps into the royal world to the birth of her two sons and heirs, this tells the story of Diana's early years being part of the most famous family in the world. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240430</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/abovorg5cvls1sqc042hcn5t2/original/abovorg5cvls1sqc042hcn5t2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712075348 +0000" stop="20250712084648 +0000">
    <title>The Diana Story: Part II: Broken Hearts</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The marriage of Prince Charles and Princess Diana remains infamous for being one of the most turbulent royal weddings in modern history. As the cracks began to form the world watched. What should have been the fairytale couple could not hold any longer. Discover the truth of what really lead to the split, as the world behind palace gates is uncovered. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/16d6b15pdb87f14ygvjrh8fdp/original/16d6b15pdb87f14ygvjrh8fdp.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712084648 +0000" stop="20250712095850 +0000">
    <title>Adele: Homecoming</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Adele is a Grammy Award-winning artist whose soulful sound has thrust her into the limelight. Her soulful voice, frank personality and chart-topping hits have made her one of the most successful artists of all time. Her authenticity in her work appeals to so many; there are no gimmicks with Adele. What you see is what you get. Through her own words, video and live performances, this documentary takes an incredible look at the life and times of one of the greatest artists of all time. Directed by Billy Simpson.</desc>
    <date>20240502</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/vy7da8kxkn001b4vz74uw7dzq/original/vy7da8kxkn001b4vz74uw7dzq.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712095850 +0000" stop="20250712105923 +0000">
    <title>Meghan Markle: Changing Traditions</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>She's here, she's royal, and she's shaking things up. Meghan Markle has now become very much part of the most famous family in the world, but this strong and powerful woman is not stopping there. After a rollercoaster introduction to royal life, the now-Duchess of Sussex has made the most of her new role to spread a message of empowerment and acceptance across Great Britain and the Commonwealth. From the surprise engagement to the fairytale wedding, to starting a family and beyond, Duchess Meghan has been unstoppable. With Prince Harry by her side the pair have endured their fair share share of adoration and turmoil but they keep calm and carry on. This is Meghan's incredible journey as she redefines everything it means to be a royal. Directed by Jordan Hill.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r8oeebzqwrku1013cckjyhfj/original/1r8oeebzqwrku1013cckjyhfj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712105923 +0000" stop="20250712120931 +0000">
    <title>Taylor Swift: Superstar</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Taylor Swift completed her transition from country star to pop superstar. With exclusive interviews and footage, discover the remarkable story of the most powerful woman in Pop Music. Directed by Billy Simpson</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/13tdu4wen6u5s1sgi1gehei71/original/13tdu4wen6u5s1sgi1gehei71.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712120931 +0000" stop="20250712131519 +0000">
    <title>Selena Gomez: Devotion</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After returning from her five year break from music, Selena Gomez has blown the world away with her third studio album Rare. She has transformed over the years, from Disney pop star to award winning film and tv producer. She is one of the biggest stars in Hollywood and is certain one of the most devoted to her art. This is the life and career of Selena Gomez. Directed by Matt Salmon.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/994f38bje3u21i0sp32xebwrs/original/994f38bje3u21i0sp32xebwrs.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712131519 +0000" stop="20250712142719 +0000">
    <title>Britney Spears: Unbreakable</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Look into the glamorous and tumultuous life of pop sensation Britney Spears. From her incredible skyrocketing ascent into stardom to her personal troubles and downfalls, see the inside of the star's life with exclusive interviews. Directed by Sonia Anderson.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1gfqbszs1z1ns1hggf56nyuyr/original/1gfqbszs1z1ns1hggf56nyuyr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712142719 +0000" stop="20250712151948 +0000">
    <title>The Barbie Story</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barbie is way more than just a 12-inches long piece of plastic, she is way more than a toy. The legendary blond bombshell has grown into a phenomenon and a children's sensation. Wildly revolutionary, Barbie broke barriers, shattered glass ceilings, and has inspired countless dreams, wonder and imagination. The history of the doll is a testament to its enduring appeal and impact. Things have changed for her the same way things changed for women. Whatever we may think about Barbie - love or loathe her - it is impossible to ignore her worldwide impact. Let's step into the beautiful world of Barbie and take a look at her cultural revolution through the decades. Directed by Roxane Schlumberger.</desc>
    <date>20241101</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/6njzqdmspnz11brw5q6s72oy7/original/6njzqdmspnz11brw5q6s72oy7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712151948 +0000" stop="20250712160747 +0000">
    <title>Understory</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>“School of Fish” offers an intimate portrait inside one family's seasonal salmon rituals and their connection to the Bristol Bay Fly Fishing and Guide Academy, where local youth are empowered through fly fishing to serve as guides and conservationists. Can the next generation step up to defend the most prolific salmon run left on earth? Directed by Colin Arisman and Oliver Sutro</desc>
    <date>20250204</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7292680713127408031/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712160747 +0000" stop="20250712181105 +0000">
    <title>After Antarctica</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After Antarctica follows legendary polar explorer Will Steger’s journey as an eyewitness to the greatest changes to the polar regions of our planet. Now, thirty years after his historic expedition across the coldest continent on Earth, Steger heads out on the ice once again, at a time when he is not only known for being the first in history to complete these historic feats - he is also the last. Directed by Tasha Van Zandt.</desc>
    <date>20250103</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7281052154789959068/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712181105 +0000" stop="20250712182846 +0000">
    <title>Groundwork: A Family Journey Into Regenerative Cotton</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a family cotton farm defies the conventions holding them back—they embark on a journey of transformation that radically shifts their farm, their family, and their future. Directed by Lindsey Hagen.</desc>
    <date>20240424</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/k0s2t37gyq7u1fjwl1nsri2iz/original/k0s2t37gyq7u1fjwl1nsri2iz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712182846 +0000" stop="20250712184716 +0000">
    <title>Groundwork: Building Community Through Regenerative Rubber</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Thailand is the world’s largest exporter of rubber, and Chorthip is a key - farmer demonstrating and leading a shift to regenerative agroforestry methods. She’s transformed her land from a rubber monoculture to a diverse rubber forest garden, implementing organic practices that improve the quality of life for both her family and her - community.</desc>
    <date>20240424</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/3vwy7pnvgijr1pbm01m8u1mpg/original/3vwy7pnvgijr1pbm01m8u1mpg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712184716 +0000" stop="20250712190213 +0000">
    <title>Ode To Desolation</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>There used to be thousands of fire lookout posts across the US, but now, because of the advancement of satellite technology, there are about 60 left. Jim Henterly holds his post as the eyes and ears of the historic Desolation Peak Fire Lookout - in an effort to preserve the human narrative. Directed by Lindsey Hagen.</desc>
    <date>20240911</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/qs43dbplzw2w1hyce29vv4f11/original/qs43dbplzw2w1hyce29vv4f11.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712190213 +0000" stop="20250712191030 +0000">
    <title>The Fate Of The Wild</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On the vast, desolate rangeland of Nevada, herds of wild horses still run free. When the Bureau of Land Management determines the herds have grown too large, it sends a helicopter to buzz overhead and corral the animals into pens to be either sold or slaughtered. For years, activist and artist Laura Leigh has been photographing and documenting the abuses these wild horses have suffered. The Fate of the Wild shows that the fate of these majestic, untamed symbols of the American West is intertwined with our own. Directed by Andrew Michael Ellis.</desc>
    <date>20240911</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/10cy4flj1f7da1v9hwl6gaqc8/original/10cy4flj1f7da1v9hwl6gaqc8.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712191030 +0000" stop="20250712192805 +0000">
    <title>Dolphin Lover</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Dolphin Lover is a critically acclaimed, award winning short documentary on the incredible true story of Malcolm Brenner and his summer long love affair with Dolly the dolphin. Directed by Joey Daoud and Kareem Tabsch.</desc>
    <date>20240911</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1dgocat82jqbd1q8l37nblkdu/original/1dgocat82jqbd1q8l37nblkdu.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712192805 +0000" stop="20250712193526 +0000">
    <title>Five Stone Of Lead</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On the west coast of Ireland kids don’t dream about winning the world cup, they dream about being championship jockeys. This is the story of a 12 year old jockey, Dylan, who is tiny even for a jockey. Directed by Jonny Madderson and Jono Stevens.</desc>
    <date>20240911</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1xian6nd6c66m18uivjt4g506/original/1xian6nd6c66m18uivjt4g506.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712193526 +0000" stop="20250712194139 +0000">
    <title>The Thousand Year Journey</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>"Routine is the enemy of time." Jedidiah Jenkins rides his bicycle from Oregon to Patagonia, the southern tip of South America, while expounding upon ideas that made him leave a job he loved for the open road. Directed by Kenny Laubbacher.</desc>
    <date>20240501</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/eyiyf9v46g5t1mggm2ib5svjw/original/eyiyf9v46g5t1mggm2ib5svjw.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712194139 +0000" stop="20250712201705 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Disconnection Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 1 - Disconnection. The start of a 2,193 mile journey on the Appalachian Trail.</desc>
    <date>20250127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7289722565956987576/solid/rectangle/original.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712201705 +0000" stop="20250712205536 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Disintegration Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 2 - Disintegration. Hollywood hikes into potential devastation on the trail.</desc>
    <date>20250127</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7289729112601367656/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712205536 +0000" stop="20250712212745 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Perception Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 3 - Perception. Hollywood is back on trail with something to prove.</desc>
    <date>20240425</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/aab3qnjonzuz1309504sc86cc/original/aab3qnjonzuz1309504sc86cc.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712212745 +0000" stop="20250712220326 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Negotiation Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 4 - Negotiation. Hollywood finds a deeper meaning to the trail.</desc>
    <date>20240424</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/hif0aaaxffhl17qcv6xzdv84j/original/hif0aaaxffhl17qcv6xzdv84j.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712220326 +0000" stop="20250712223723 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Habitation Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 5 - Habitation. Hollywood finds steady footing on trail, carving his name beside all who have come before.</desc>
    <date>20240425</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/10mlgrvxx5u0i1tgzhllwhumw/original/10mlgrvxx5u0i1tgzhllwhumw.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712223723 +0000" stop="20250712230727 +0000">
    <title>Pack &amp; Soul : Revelation Censored</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Episode 6 - Revelation. Hollywood turns inward. Through the lives and stories of others, he finds what's truly needed to get to Maine.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/15i46eex1o2dr1iug3nhoohi8/original/15i46eex1o2dr1iug3nhoohi8.png" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62f42e6cad0081c6ef405723" start="20250712230727 +0000" stop="20250713005510 +0000">
    <title>78/52: Hitchcock's Shower Scene</title>
    <sub-title>Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when you thought it was safe to go back in the shower... Discover how Alfred Hitchcock's Psycho changed film history forever with one shocking scene. Directed by Alexandre O. Philippe.</desc>
    <date>20250306</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/7303212708143552623/solid/rectangle/original.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
