<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250712235810 +0000" stop="20250713004411 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What's Causing Your Symptoms?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Mysterious foot pains? Unexplained nosebleeds? The Doctors reveal what’s really causing your concerning symptoms. Plus, are you over or underspending on your health? Money guru Suze Orman has the answers.</desc>
    <date>20120213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713004411 +0000" stop="20250713013103 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bearded Woman's Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E135</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman with PCOS who was ridiculed for her “beard” has the last laugh with an incredible makeover! Then, it’s Dr. Mike Dow as you’ve never seen him, opening up about the stroke that nearly took his brother’s life and the remarkable recovery that will leave you in tears! A woman undergoes a urinary incontinence procedure that claims to eliminate embarrassing accidents and we put it to the test at a comedy show! The results are no joke! Should opiate dealers face manslaughter charges if their customer overdoses? The secret to finding the perfect nude lipstick may be found on your breast? Find out the surprising ingredient to add to your guacamole to save calories and cash!</desc>
    <date>20170425</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09135.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713013103 +0000" stop="20250713021736 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Toenail Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Why does one woman have a 6th toenail? Watch as THE DOCTORS does a LIVE procedure in studio! Then, the Stool Squad is back to answer your burning questions! Want fast-food faster? A-list nutritionist Keri Glassman shares her kid-approved recipes! Next, would you change your future child’s eye color? Plus, do at-home bunion correctors really work? Then, why some people are turning to drinking vinegar for better gut health! Could it be doing more harm than good?</desc>
    <date>20181016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713021736 +0000" stop="20250713030410 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Most Embarrassing Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E166</episode-num>
    <desc>Reboot your sex drive and learn how to get more connected with your partner! And, get the skinny on going bare down there. Plus, Dr. Travis reveals the best time to have sex!</desc>
    <date>20100517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02166.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713030410 +0000" stop="20250713035150 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>5 Unbelievable Medical Makeovers!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>You have to see it to believe it! Discover cutting edge procedures that have changed people’s lives. See a fascinating surgery that restores movement to paralyzed limbs. And, witness a miraculous mouth makeover that will make your jaw drop.</desc>
    <date>20120926</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05014.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713035150 +0000" stop="20250713043944 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Gross Anatomy: Worst Body Conditions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E508</episode-num>
    <desc>Parasites, freaky feet, piercings gone wrong -- no one is immune to gross anatomy. Witness how modern medicine can solve painful and unsightly problems on a special edition of The Doctors. Relief is possible –change your life today</desc>
    <date>20111121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04508.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713043944 +0000" stop="20250713052556 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman with a 70 Inch Booty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Exclusive: A woman famous for her 70-inch booty visits The Doctors! Is she in for a shocking diagnosis? Then, are you upping your family’s fire risk without even knowing it? We reveal three dangerous household items! Plus, a woman desperate to walk again turns to The Doctors for help!</desc>
    <date>20160922</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09008.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713052556 +0000" stop="20250713061213 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Biggest Makeover Show Ever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>All summer long, teams of plastic surgeons, cosmetic dentists and dozens of stylists worked around the clock. Now, The Doctors presents a makeover show so big, a call had to be made to The Guinness Book of World Records!</desc>
    <date>20090914</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02016.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713061213 +0000" stop="20250713065846 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Emergency: How to Save A Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Could you save someone's life in a dire situation? The Doctors give you must have info for medical emergencies. Learn how to react if someone you love is bleeding from the mouth, nose or ears. Find out what to do when someone is having a seizure, how to decipher an allergy from anaphylactic shock and more.</desc>
    <date>20121025</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bb5e16bf5fd5a0856bde806d78aedd0e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713065846 +0000" stop="20250713074513 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Twin Sisters Get Twin Facelifts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E120</episode-num>
    <desc>We go “inside the O.R.” for an amazing update as two identical twin sisters get the “twinning” facelifts they’ve always wanted! The RefrigerDATEr’s back to help another single bachelorette find a man – by looking through the contents of his refrigerator! Is viral “60 second rule” to a clearer face legit? Is the mental workload of running a house harming moms’ health?</desc>
    <date>20190219</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11120.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713074513 +0000" stop="20250713083142 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Unhealthy Lady-Like Habits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E85</episode-num>
    <desc>Women are taught to always cross their legs, never pass gas in front of anyone, and many never leave the house without makeup. The Doctors reveal why these old-fashioned expectations and other lady-like habits can harm your health!</desc>
    <date>20110121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03085.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713083142 +0000" stop="20250713091829 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Embarrassing Body Questions Answered</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Nothing is off limits as The Doctors address your most embarrassing body problems. Learn why you get tongue-tied at the most inconvenient of times, and how to get rid of back hair. And, what your bowel movements tell you about your health.</desc>
    <date>20091119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713091829 +0000" stop="20250713100532 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing's Off Limits!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E49</episode-num>
    <desc>If it oozes, aches or makes you blush, we’re talking about it today! From one woman’s excruciating pain “down there” to a pill-free fix for erectile dysfunction, The Doctors answers your most embarrassing questions! Could you leak breastmilk years after childbirth? The most embarrassing questions come out of our “Medical Confessional”! A celebrity stylist opens up about an embarrassing secret he’s kept under wraps for years! And, the athlete’s foot fix you can gargle with! Then, an unconventional way to relieve sinus pain that actually could work!</desc>
    <date>20171113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713100532 +0000" stop="20250713105204 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fattest Woman In The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E130</episode-num>
    <desc>She was the heaviest woman in the world, tipping the scales at over 1100 pounds … can a new bariatric surgery save her life? Then, the inspiring story of a Saved by The Bell star who started going blind at age 13 and now thinks it’s the best thing to ever happen to him! A breast cancer survivor turns to The Doctors after her reconstruction goes wrong! Can she be healed? And, one of our most infamous guests - “The Sperminator” – is back with baby news!</desc>
    <date>20170329</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09130.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713105204 +0000" stop="20250713113125 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Bizarre Medical Headlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E42</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS takes on bizarre medical headlines, from blowing your nose for mind-blowing sex … to the health benefits of smelling farts! Author Dr. Jeremy Howick shares his research on how you can heal your body from within without modern medicine. Comedian Ms. Pat opens up on how laughter was her prescription from selling crack … to cracking jokes! Surprising cure for Rheumatoid Arthritis that can be found in your kitchen pantry!</desc>
    <date>20181206</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713113125 +0000" stop="20250713121855 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Your Grossest Body Problems Solved!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when you think you've seen it all, The Doctors make your skin crawl in an all new episode. Meet a woman who survived a 51-pound tumor in her abdomen! And, spiders in your ears, parasites in your eyes, fungus on your face - could it happen to you?</desc>
    <date>20121017</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d0338cd40fb07a72f0bf2ea25f784298.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713121855 +0000" stop="20250713130557 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>50 Ways to Improve Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you want to better your health, but can’t seem to find the time? The Doctors reveal 50 ways to improve your health, and each takes just five minutes or less! And, learn simple housecleaning tips that don’t cost a dime.</desc>
    <date>20090918</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713130557 +0000" stop="20250713135234 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>America's Silent Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E53</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors blow the lid off America’s silent killer: salt. Learn how to take action and join the nationwide movement to Halt The Salt! And, NBA champ Magic Johnson explains the biggest fight of his life.</desc>
    <date>20101124</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03053.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713135234 +0000" stop="20250713144142 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Jersey Shore Star's 6 Pack Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E308</episode-num>
    <desc>Jersey Shore star undergoes 6-pack surgery! Housewives on drug-spiked cheese? The benefits of cow cuddling? DIY facial! Are women happier with younger men? Autistic man’s amazing weight loss. New fitness trend: crawling emotional support alligator. The fruit you need to eat!</desc>
    <date>20190517</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11308.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713144142 +0000" stop="20250713152826 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Skin Infection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E101</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s The Doctors’ “What The Health” show. Can farting thwart flirting at the gym? Can shellfish cause a deadly skin infection? Once considered barbaric, why is electroshock therapy being used in treatment today? Bizarre skincare treatment reportedly used by Meghan Markle. Health risks with DIY eyebrow microblading. How to increase your strength without increasing your workouts!</desc>
    <date>20180220</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10101.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713152826 +0000" stop="20250713161448 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Eye Whitener Scars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A company is accused of pushing opioids on patients for profit! One patient shares her story, and a whistleblower speaks out! A popular TV actress gets a procedure to reverse her scarred eyes, but does it work? Then, our kid taste testers taste favorite foods made healthy! Why some doctors are treating patients with hydrogen peroxide injections! Then, a man has the world’s largest bladder stone removed! And, a secret beauty tip from Molly Sims.</desc>
    <date>20171010</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10025.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713161448 +0000" stop="20250713170025 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Call the Docs Stat!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>THE DOCTORS tackles one of the most difficult interventions yet - a 19-year-old with anorexia and heroin and marijuana addictions. Plus, the crazy story of a married couple with two kids who woke up one early morning to a unique experience – the surprise birth of their third baby! Then, the viral video of two young women who took the “hot pepper challenge” and how it went totally wrong!</desc>
    <date>20161028</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09018.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713170025 +0000" stop="20250713174719 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>How Can I Cure That?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E116</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors share quick fixes for common body problems! Learn how to reduce hair loss, heal bruises faster and get rid of acne – even in embarrassing areas!</desc>
    <date>20100302</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713174719 +0000" stop="20250713183224 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Manic Mom Makeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A stressed out mom has a “manic mom makeover!” Plus, a reality star using coffee enemas to cure his cancer? Then, a paralyzed man walks again by using his brain to move his legs! And one woman’s dramatic reveal after having life changing surgery for her scarred face.</desc>
    <date>20151019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D08033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713183224 +0000" stop="20250713192018 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>A Purse’s Shocking Health Dangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E121</episode-num>
    <desc>Discover the top five dangers lurking in your purse, including a surprising PMS medicine risk. Plus, can ice cream can be addictive? And, top beauty mistakes women make when trying to avoid acne and wrinkles.</desc>
    <date>20120327</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04121.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713192018 +0000" stop="20250713200823 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Become a Medical Statistic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E53</episode-num>
    <desc>Get the facts about women's heart disease with singer and philanthropist Barbra Streisand, founder of the eponymous cardiovascular research program. And, cardiologist Dr. Noel Bairey shares vital tests every woman must take.</desc>
    <date>20091116</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02053.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713200823 +0000" stop="20250713205436 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Treat It Now or Pay Later?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Actress Sally Field joins The Doctors to raise awareness about osteoporosis, a bone-thinning disease that affects four times more women than men. Learn steps to take to preserve the health of your bones.</desc>
    <date>20091109</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713205436 +0000" stop="20250713214146 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>40 Ways to Fight the Flu</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E65</episode-num>
    <desc>Runny noses, stuffy heads and aching bodies can only mean one thing: cold and flu season is in full swing. Find out 40 ways to fight the flu and outsmart a cold! Plus, the latest technology to keep your gadgets germ-free.</desc>
    <date>20101209</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03065.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713214146 +0000" stop="20250713222843 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>140 Pound Tumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E128</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman struggles to lose weight for years, only to learn she has a 140 pound tumor! Why is a young man spending thousands of dollars to become a genderless alien? It’s snake season; hear The poisonous snake warning signs from the experts! Can The Doctors solve a guest’s medical mystery? Find out which nutrition fads are trending up or trending down! Plus, how the color of your outfit could determine the outcome of key life situations! A product promises perfect eyebrows in seconds … we’re putting it to the test!</desc>
    <date>20170503</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713222843 +0000" stop="20250713231634 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Habits That Harm Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E111</episode-num>
    <desc>Are your beauty habits more fashionable than rational? Discover the dangers of carrying heavy handbags, why strutting in stilettos can lead to funky feet and how applying the wrong makeup can actually magnify blemishes.</desc>
    <date>20110301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03111.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250713231634 +0000" stop="20250714000151 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Health Clues: Face, Fingers &amp; Toes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E100</episode-num>
    <desc>They’re the subtle symptoms only a doctor can spot – until now. From head to toe, The Doctors reveal signs, signals and prevention tips for your health. Plus, the latest on actress Demi Moore’s health crisis.</desc>
    <date>20120215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250714000151 +0000" stop="20250714004708 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Surprising Health Dangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrible accidents and life-threatening conditions can happen to anyone at any time, even you! Learn how to prevent a critical head injury, E.coli poisoning, severe dehydration and more. And, spot the hazards in your home!</desc>
    <date>20101011</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03031.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
