<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495">
    <display-name>The Doctors</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/104e6194-484e-4e84-823d-9b1e7936361e/xDoctors_Plex_Channel_Logo_v01_John_LopezRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703100949 +0000" stop="20250703105457 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Preparing for Your First Time!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E84</episode-num>
    <desc>Witness a first for daytime TV; a mother-to-be delivers her first child by c-section Live on The Doctors! Plus, learn your first line of defense against America’s number one killer, and what you need to know before your first time going under the knife.</desc>
    <date>20110207</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03084.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703105457 +0000" stop="20250703113700 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Is Breast Implant Illness Real?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Find out why so many women are removing their breast implants. Could breast implant illness be to blame? Are you your own worst enemy? Do you get in your own way? Psychologist Dr. Judy Ho breaks down how to “Stop Self-Sabotage!” Could your favorite Boba drink put you at risk for intestinal blockage? Who says self-care has to be expensive? Find out how to self-care on a budget!</desc>
    <date>20190930</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D12010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703113700 +0000" stop="20250703122346 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Smile Shame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E124</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman overcomes bulimia, but sees the toll on her teeth. Now she’s so ashamed of her smile, she rarely leaves her home. Can THE DOCTORS help? A domestic violence survivor gets a life-changing surgery! A first date fail leads to a bill? A couple faces charges after using a drone to spy into their neighbors’ homes? The Krazy Coupon Lady reveals money-saving secrets to outsmart retailers! Could yoga be the therapy you need? Find out! Plus, a new app designed to catch distracted drivers in the act!</desc>
    <date>20170320</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09124.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703122346 +0000" stop="20250703131038 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Extreme Measures for Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E60</episode-num>
    <desc>How far would you go for beauty? A controversial surgery alters feet so women can wear heels. And, an acupuncture facelift that claims to take years off a woman's appearance. And, the latest in laser surgery that erases tattoos.</desc>
    <date>20081120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01060.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703131038 +0000" stop="20250703135901 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>When Plastic Surgery Goes Wrong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Considering plastic surgery of any kind? Don't miss Krissy's story and Dr. Ordon's essential do's and don'ts to keep you safe. Watch several controversial potty training techniques in action and see if any of them are right for your child.</desc>
    <date>20081002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D01003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703135901 +0000" stop="20250703144542 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors Investigate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E112</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors investigates lunchboxes! Could dangerous mold, fungus and bacteria be hiding in your child’s lunchbox? You may want to hit the brakes at the drive-thru … could cancer-causing chemicals be hiding in your fast food? An erotic website offers sex-ed for teens with a new “wellness” hub? A judge’s sentence is raising eyebrows: celibacy as punishment? Get your daily dose of gross with a viral earwax video! You might want to think twice before eating chicken with white stripes; find out why! And, how a penny could help you avoid sickness and save wads of cash in an emergency!</desc>
    <date>20121205</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703144542 +0000" stop="20250703153232 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Howie Mandel &amp; OCD</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedian and television personality Howie Mandel confronts his OCD and germ phobia with THE DOCTORS! Our investigation reveals the filth on your hands and the most germ-infested places you’re touching! Restaurant horror stories you must see before you eat out again! Then, a mother’s excruciating jaw condition is destroying her life! Plus, a cure for garlic breath that’s right in your fridge!</desc>
    <date>20161031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09034.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703153232 +0000" stop="20250703161801 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Renew Your Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E160</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling burnt out and run down? The Doctors show you how to renew you life, body, mind and spirit. Learn the advantages to a little R&amp;R and the beauty benefits of steam. And, see what your eyes are saying about your health.</desc>
    <date>20110907</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03160.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703161801 +0000" stop="20250703170442 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hidden Kitchen Germs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E82</episode-num>
    <desc>Go LIVE in the O.R. and watch how surgeons perform a new valve replacement procedure! Are there hidden germs in your kitchen making you sick? The simple swaps to cut down on your sugar! Experts debate if it’s ever okay to yell at your kids!</desc>
    <date>20190218</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11082.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703170442 +0000" stop="20250703174925 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Legends' Top Age-Defying Tips</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E95</episode-num>
    <desc>Look and feel young at any age! Hollywood film stars Diahann Carroll, Dyan Cannon and Jacqueline Bisset reveal the secrets of Their eternal youth. And, see a new non-invasive skin smoothing treatment. Plus, an instant booty lifting procedure.</desc>
    <date>20130129</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703174925 +0000" stop="20250703183621 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Fixes for Common Problems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E165</episode-num>
    <desc>From fighting flab, to stifling sneezes to quieting a crying baby, The Doctors reveals easy fixes for your most common problems! And, Oscar-winning actress Marisa Tomei shares her top secrets to a better body!</desc>
    <date>20100520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02165.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703183621 +0000" stop="20250703192302 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Mom Weighs 6yo Daily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A mom is under fire for weighing her 6-year-old daughter every single day after she’s bullied for her weight! Is this mom doing the right thing the wrong way? Plus, the controversy over using marijuana for pain relief in the NFL continues! Do you think the drug should be allowed for players? Then, kids are so stressed out doing their homework they now need therapists? We discuss the new alarming trend! And, using oregano oil to stop a cold in its tracks – is it a buzz or a bust?</desc>
    <date>20181102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11015.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703192302 +0000" stop="20250703200939 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Large Fibroid Removal Surgery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E95</episode-num>
    <desc>You won’t believe what happens when the show’s cameras go “Inside The O.R.” as a 51-year-old woman has a large fibroid removed, which left her looking 5 months pregnant! Controversial new study claims smart women should marry down if They want to start a family. E-cigarettes and vaping have been sold as a way for smokers to quit – new research on why it doesn’t work? The Doctors’ Court: woman arrested with five different types of drugs hidden…in her vagina?</desc>
    <date>20190123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D11095.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703200939 +0000" stop="20250703205535 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Try This At Home!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E78</episode-num>
    <desc>From kitchen catastrophes to workplace disasters, don’t miss the list of everyday health hazards that may surprise you. Learn when you can do it yourself and when you should call a professional.</desc>
    <date>20100106</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02078.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703205535 +0000" stop="20250703214048 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Secrets to Never Getting Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Runny noses, sore throats, nasty coughs, vomiting: stop dreaded symptoms before they start! The Doctors reveal the top secrets to never getting sick. Find out when you should - and shouldn't - medicate, natural remedies in your kitchen and more!</desc>
    <date>20120217</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703214048 +0000" stop="20250703222740 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Shape of Your Health</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E128</episode-num>
    <desc>Staying in shape isn’t only about muscle tone. From your lungs to your knees, improve your body from the inside out! Plus, flatten your tummy without surgery, and Alicia Silverstone’s secrets for healthy and sweet treats!</desc>
    <date>20110315</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703222740 +0000" stop="20250703231312 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Improve Your Health From A to Z</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E45</episode-num>
    <desc>Get simple solutions for hiccups, nosebleeds, vertigo and 23 other ailments with The Doctors ABCs of medicine! Plus, learn how to how to last longer in bed. And, the number one mistake parents make when their kids get sick.</desc>
    <date>20101112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703231312 +0000" stop="20250703235955 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Top 5 Questions To Ask Your Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E43</episode-num>
    <desc>Learn how to interview potential doctors, which tests you need and how to make the most of your next doctor’s visit. Plus, when you need to go to the emergency room – STAT.</desc>
    <date>20101215</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03043.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250703235955 +0000" stop="20250704004537 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Blame This, Not That!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E152</episode-num>
    <desc>Think you know what’s to blame for what’s ailing you? Bad skin? Must be the chocolate. Acid Reflux? Probably spicy food? Not so fast – The Doctors shed new light on common problems. Plus, how to get your body back after baby!</desc>
    <date>20110422</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03152.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704004537 +0000" stop="20250704013332 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Against All Odds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E111</episode-num>
    <desc>The most inspiring health stories of Season 5! Meet the “Couple of the Year” and see why people compare them to “The Notebook.” Plus, the Lifetime Achievement Award, Best Supporting Spouse, Nurse of the Year, the Viewer’s Choice Award and much more!</desc>
    <date>20130221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D05111.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704013332 +0000" stop="20250704022009 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Medical Mistakes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>People know that smoking causes cancer and continue to puff anyway, but could you be doing something you didn’t know was bad for you? The Doctors reveals some of the health mistakes you never knew you were making.</desc>
    <date>20091002</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02021.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704022009 +0000" stop="20250704030540 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Best and Worst for Your Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Some tenets of good health are undisputable: vegetables are good for you, smoking is not. But some are not as obvious. The Doctors reveal the best and worst things you can do for your body.</desc>
    <date>20091022</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02039.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704030540 +0000" stop="20250704035206 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Cringey Questions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E46</episode-num>
    <desc>Embarrassed by a family member? From Dad’s dancing to your cousin’s crazy clothes, learn how to combat your relative’s kookiest quirks! And, Dancing with the Stars’ Louis Van Amstel’s dance tips.</desc>
    <date>20111101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704035206 +0000" stop="20250704043857 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What The Yuck?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bothered by bad-smelling belches? Problem with pinworms? Get answers to the questions that make you go, “What the yuck?!” And, The Doctors’ Motherhood Survival Club tackles the biggest issues modern moms face.</desc>
    <date>20100924</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D03021.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704043857 +0000" stop="20250704052456 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Fan Favorites Special</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E507</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s The Doctors’ Fans’ Favorites special - from the stories that broke your heart to the stories that broke the internet, we’re delivering ten years of our most memorable moments! A mother loses her hearing and spends fifteen years in silence until cochlear implant surgery. Our cameras were with her in the operating room and The unforgettable moment when she heard her son’s voice for the first time. See how they’re doing now! Remember the 685-pound teen with the voice of angel? Find out if he’s lost weight! Don’t miss the biggest transformations and the most-watched clip in The Doctors history!</desc>
    <date>20170907</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D09507.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704052456 +0000" stop="20250704061036 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>What Every Woman is Afraid to Ask</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E42</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors answer the questions you’re too embarrassed to talk about – even with your best friend! Find out how to improve your love life, eliminate body odor and more!</desc>
    <date>20091105</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704061036 +0000" stop="20250704065732 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ashamed of My Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Are you your own worst critic? From sweaty armpits to thick ankles, see new solutions for your most “embarrassing” body problems. And, get simple, at-home remedies for brittle nails.</desc>
    <date>20091009</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704065732 +0000" stop="20250704074301 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>The Pregnant Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Three years ago, Thomas Beatie made headlines as the first legal man in history to give birth. After years under the radar, The Doctors uncover everything you didn’t know about the controversial pregnancy and delivery.</desc>
    <date>20111031</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704074301 +0000" stop="20250704082936 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>"Teen Mom" Mental Misdiagnosis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E49</episode-num>
    <desc>In a The Doctors exclusive, a Teen Mom star who thinks she was misdiagnosed with a mental health disorder comes to the show for a second opinion! Plus, the shocking story of a baby born with two noses! Then, Dr. Pimple Popper returns to discuss two gross viral videos: the “grandmother of all blackheads” and a popped blister you have to see to believe! And can you be too fat for fitness? A fitness teacher called out for her weight is here to set the record straight!</desc>
    <date>20151125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D08049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704082936 +0000" stop="20250704091537 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Addicted to Exercise Update</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A previous guest who was addicted to exercise and referred to as the “sickest person ever on The show” returns with an unexpected update. Then, can cold medicine be used as a murder defense? The Doctors discusses the much buzzed about court case. Plus, our Stool Squad spins The “Wheel of Poop” and answers all your questions about… “Number Two”! And, The Doctors tackles the new research that points to the root cause of ADHD being sleep issues?</desc>
    <date>20171018</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D10022.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704091537 +0000" stop="20250704100432 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Gross Anatomy: Oozing and Runny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E509</episode-num>
    <desc>The Doctors uncover the best treatments for your worst body conditions. Clear uncontrollable acne and treat embarrassing scars. Plus, a disintegrating teeth disorder and a debilitating problem “down there.” Are you at risk?</desc>
    <date>20120514</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D04509.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-6720271c727d52d7a0e0b495" start="20250704100432 +0000" stop="20250704105004 +0000">
    <title>The Doctors</title>
    <sub-title>Ask Our Docs: Where, When and Why</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E80</episode-num>
    <desc>From when your child should start talking to why hormones affect your mood, The Doctors tackles your biggest who, what, where, when and why questions. And, get the most effective home remedies from around the globe.</desc>
    <date>20100114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/stage_twenty-nine_productions_llc/DRS_D02080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
