<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250706225945 +0000" stop="20250707002705 +0000">
    <title>She's Watching</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Richard and Zoey have recently moved into their dream home, only to find themselves being watched by an obsessed neighbor. Watching them every night isn't enough to satisfy her urges, so she makes an offer they can't refuse.</desc>
    <date>20250429</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707002705 +0000" stop="20250707025207 +0000">
    <title>Sweet Revenge</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Gianna will never forget the day she witnessed her father being killed by a gangster name Curtis as a little girl. Now grown up, fate intervenes, and Gianna finds Curtis back in her life. She meets Detective Corey but he doesn't know her past and gets caught up after his wife dies by the gun from Curtis boys. Now the Detective has to be by Gianna's side and fight!</desc>
    <date>20220710</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/1/gracenote/19397fad61406adad9f2937edd84095a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707025207 +0000" stop="20250707042508 +0000">
    <title>Abandoned at Birth 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>On a quest to learn more about her birth mother. A woman endures societal challenges, heartache, and more obstacles on a journey to find the truth.</desc>
    <date>20240314</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707042508 +0000" stop="20250707062808 +0000">
    <title>Bakerz Union</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Winston, your local hood mailman and his bootlegging friend Greg, can't seem to catch a break. Well their luck is about to change when these two layabouts accidentally intercept a fresh batch of marijuana in the mail, they launch a new edibles empire. However, when the intended recipient notices his missing weed, this new money-making scheme may create more problems than it solves.</desc>
    <date>20200904</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f44f962d93ad017b6e539fe0bf56d4e1.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707062808 +0000" stop="20250707081504 +0000">
    <title>Bad Girl Revelation</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Bora tries to untie herself from her sister's decision while trying to get out of the drug game with her social media profession. Mob boss, Ivan, makes a mistake and sends money electronically for a hit and tries to get his refund</desc>
    <date>20230329</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzRlMWZjMzUtMmE0MS00MDU1LTg5OTAtMzhmZmEyM2NjYmY0XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707081504 +0000" stop="20250707103817 +0000">
    <title>Black Diamond</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Life is all about Give and Take. At some point, we all have to choose a side. The sad thing is it may be friends over family. Black Diamond is a film about a Diamond that was born a Gem but raised a Savage.</desc>
    <date>20191130</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0ac2a2b191dcf42ef2daf07ba7775c5d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707103817 +0000" stop="20250707122852 +0000">
    <title>South Side Hero</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After serving a 10-year sentence on a RICO charge, reformed gangster Tommy ‘Ace’ Crown returns home to find his 15-year old daughter Sierra missing after she ran away with a man she met online. When the police decline to help, Ace is determined to track her down himself.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/e6a68e0e26cf4b153633eca8270319d3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707122852 +0000" stop="20250707140349 +0000">
    <title>Deliveries From Eva</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Disgraced music star Reese is surprised to learn that he still has a fan in the form of delivery driver, Eva. The two form an unlikely friendship that begins to sour due to Eva's growing obsession and her struggles with PTSD.</desc>
    <date>20241004</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/6/gracenote/6dc7eebbd50d79bea9d2b14cb812f75d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707140349 +0000" stop="20250707161714 +0000">
    <title>GRIT</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Three estranged brothers, Jason Jarell, and Josiah, are brought together by their sister Laura’s death. The brothers make a pact to uncover the truth behind her murder, setting off a perilous journey into the dark political world, where they forge unexpected alliances in order to get justice for Laura.</desc>
    <date>20241210</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707161714 +0000" stop="20250707174018 +0000">
    <title>Single Black Female</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Rose is a young college freshman who meets her roommate Max for the first time. The two develop an intense bond, and Max is willing to prove her loyalty to Rose, even if it means someone will have to die if they get in the way.</desc>
    <date>20241203</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707174018 +0000" stop="20250707193825 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707193825 +0000" stop="20250707212414 +0000">
    <title>Priceless: The Score</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After starting their new record label, Donica Blair and Shequell Harris have entered a dangerous arena full of guns, lies, and deceit. Now they are racing against time to right their wrongs and save their own lives before they are next in a string of murders. Meanwhile their partner Seven, has fallen victim to the deadliest of them all; the Black widow.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707212414 +0000" stop="20250707230905 +0000">
    <title>Runway of Shadows</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Sisters Ivy and Zara are separated at a very young age due to their father’s deceit. When Ivy and Zara unexpectedly cross paths at a prestigious runway show, the stage it set for a series of mysterious and unsettling events.</desc>
    <date>20250603</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250707230905 +0000" stop="20250708004335 +0000">
    <title>The Devil Came to Duval</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After surviving a suicide attempt, comedian Eli Thompson faces his past on his birthday, but a night out at the bar spirals into chaos when the Devil arrives. Eli must confront betrayal, revenge, and supernatural terror to survive.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGUyODRhNmItZWQxYi00ZGUyLThjZmQtZGYyZjY0ZDY4ZDY4XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
