<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2">
    <display-name>Journy</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8518d7bc-9f5b-4569-9c06-91a58b9edae6/journy.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250711233000 +0000" stop="20250712003000 +0000">
    <title>Survival of the Species</title>
    <sub-title>Survival of the Species - Hunting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben explores the facts - economic and ethical - behind killing for conservation.</desc>
    <date>20230509</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/eyrxmvyop9nq11kbnu5xemz0r/original/eyrxmvyop9nq11kbnu5xemz0r.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712003000 +0000" stop="20250712013000 +0000">
    <title>Survival of the Species</title>
    <sub-title>Survival of the Species - Human and Wildlife Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode explores the conflict between humans and wildlife. What measures can be put in place to reduce the impact on people and animals alike?</desc>
    <date>20230509</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/ixcm9uzy4q371tg8y6nw8l6k6/original/ixcm9uzy4q371tg8y6nw8l6k6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712013000 +0000" stop="20250712023000 +0000">
    <title>Survival of the Species</title>
    <sub-title>Survival of the Species - Illegal Wildlife Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben explores the plight of endangered animals that are poached and traded.</desc>
    <date>20230509</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/13i5ukw2uga761wxn0ico6g2k/original/13i5ukw2uga761wxn0ico6g2k.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712023000 +0000" stop="20250712033000 +0000">
    <title>Survival of the Species</title>
    <sub-title>Survival of the Species - Poaching</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>How close is the African Rhino to extinction? Ben finds out.</desc>
    <date>20230509</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/4hllk4jm0n6c14ffo1hcgn3c8/original/4hllk4jm0n6c14ffo1hcgn3c8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712033000 +0000" stop="20250712043000 +0000">
    <title>Bear’s Wild Adventure</title>
    <sub-title>Bear’s Wild Adventure - Bear &amp; Jonny Wilkinson’s Wild Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls takes rugby player Jonny Wilkinson on a wild adventure which includes climbing into caves and an ice bath!</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1u683hobl57h116kiwlhvz4nk/original/1u683hobl57h116kiwlhvz4nk.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712043000 +0000" stop="20250712053000 +0000">
    <title>Bear’s Wild Adventure</title>
    <sub-title>Bear’s Wild Adventure - Bear &amp; Nicola Adams’ Wild Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls takes rugby player Jonny Wilkinson on a wild adventure which includes climbing into caves and an ice bath!</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/mepyuv62ujhj1u9m3r0c6zmr7/original/mepyuv62ujhj1u9m3r0c6zmr7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712053000 +0000" stop="20250712063000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls is abandoning 13 ordinary British men on a remote, uninhabited island in the pacific. Can they survive for a month completely alone? When stripped of all the luxuries and conveniences of 21st century living, does modern British man still have the spirit and skills to survive?  The men are dropped off by Bear, and they are left totally alone with the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  In danger of being overwhelmed by the tides they battle through the dense undergrowth and the enormity of the task ahead quickly dawns on them.</desc>
    <date>20190908</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ec987854f67e556ff9958b7d9ce28e91.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712063000 +0000" stop="20250712073000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls abandons 13 ordinary British men on a remote, uninhabited island in the Pacific, where they are utterly alone, filming themselves. Can they survive for a month when stripped of all the luxuries and conveniences of 21st-century living? Does modern British man still have the spirit and skills to survive? In this episode, 48 hours since their last meal and hunger grips the group as the harsh reality of island life is dawning. The race is on to bring food back to camp before they become too weak to hunt.</desc>
    <date>20190915</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/b5d1f208151ee44e2fea981b39c8dca5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712073000 +0000" stop="20250712083000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls has abandoned 13 ordinary British men on a remote, uninhabited island. Can they survive for a month completely alone? Stripped of all the luxuries and conveniences of 21st century living, does modern British man still have the wits and skills to survive? The men are radically losing weight,  existing on a paltry average of just 300 calories a day. With their very survival hanging in the balance,  the castaways lose patience with those they feel are not pulling their weight.</desc>
    <date>20190922</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d30ffefde41b07eb09f69047ba2d200f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712083000 +0000" stop="20250712093000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls has abandoned 13 ordinary British men on a remote, uninhabited island to find out if they can survive for a month completely alone? Stripped of all the luxuries and conveniences of 21st century living, does modern British man still have the wits and skills to survive? Three weeks in and the group is barely getting by on a meagre diet of snails and coconuts.  Willing to take ever-greater risks for food, Mike and Chris battle with trecherous tides in a desperate search for much needed fruit. But as the hunt for food continues tempers fray and it appears not everyone is pulling their weight.</desc>
    <date>20190929</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1s1xbdljbwdf410xe9tm55gnr/original/1s1xbdljbwdf410xe9tm55gnr.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712093000 +0000" stop="20250712103000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls has abandoned 13 ordinary British men on a remote, uninhabited island to find out if they can survive for a month completely alone. Stripped of all the luxuries and conveniences of 21st century living, does modern British man still have the wits and skills to survive? In this final episode the men enter their fourth week of living on the island  and the group is hungry and  divided. And without unity, the men are not gathering enough food to survive. With island life starting to fall apart the men's bodies and minds are beginning to show the strain of the experiment. Even when a stingray arrives in the fishing nets, arguments follow close behind.</desc>
    <date>20191006</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/dacaea973e4be2a9bdb87171eadf1c31.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712103000 +0000" stop="20250712113000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls abandons 14 British men on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  They will be completely alone, filming everything themselves. This time the survival challenge will be harder and longer than before, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. From the very beginning the men face a life and death struggle, as the fierce currents of the Pacific Ocean force Bear to drop them 75 meters off the island.  The men have no choice but to jump ship and make a desperate swim through the violent swells onto a treacherous, rocky coastline.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1jh7igb0wdvox18hn4oxlb2dz/original/1jh7igb0wdvox18hn4oxlb2dz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712113000 +0000" stop="20250712123000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Bear Grylls abandons 14 ordinary British women on a remote, uninhabited pacific island, left with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  They’re given no food and just a day’s supply of drinking water. Like their counterparts on the male island, these women will be utterly alone for six weeks, left to film everything themselves.  So when stripped of the luxuries and conveniences of 21stcentury living will these women have the skills and mental strength to survive and rival the male islanders?</desc>
    <date>20230419</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/ze4xwaoe7pc61lhj1zumm0qjb/original/ze4xwaoe7pc61lhj1zumm0qjb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712123000 +0000" stop="20250712133000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British men on a remote desert island in the pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  This time the survival challenge is harder than before, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. In this film mild mannered paramedic, Barney Strange, comes to the rescue of the group by catching and feeding the men a tasty but unusual supper. Just five days in and the group has reached breaking point.  The island has been battered by a series of torrential storms, and without a decent shelter the men have barely slept. They haven’t had a decent meal since they arrived, and a bitter rivalry between the island’s two builders, Paul and Andy has turned into all out war.  Along with the youngest member, Joe, they are now both hell bent on leaving the island, much to the despair of the others.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/18kehs1w8m2kv1fmdoiljtwo5/original/18kehs1w8m2kv1fmdoiljtwo5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712133000 +0000" stop="20250712143000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British women on a remote desert island in the pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  This time the survival challenge is harder than before, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. The women are desperately dehydrated and separated, after an expedition party crossed the island to find a permanent camp - and got hopelessly lost while returning to the others.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/ahn9tgbpk0pz1kaz74li14c3n/original/ahn9tgbpk0pz1kaz74li14c3n.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712143000 +0000" stop="20250712153000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British men on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  This time the survival challenge is harder than ever before, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. In this episode the men face a life and death struggle with the island's most fearsome predator.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1pqj8ge7vhh1r1gsgdig7c94z/original/1pqj8ge7vhh1r1gsgdig7c94z.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712153000 +0000" stop="20250712163000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>It’s Lauren’s 25th birthday but there’s little to celebrate. Two castaways have already abandoned the women’s island due to the extreme conditions, since being dropped in the Pacific seven days ago. The 12 remaining are desperately dehydrated. The survival mantra goes: You can survive 3 minutes without air, 3 days without water and 3 weeks without food, so finding something to drink is these women’s number one priority.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1fvok3ln658e71bfdv82lq4mh/original/1fvok3ln658e71bfdv82lq4mh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712163000 +0000" stop="20250712173000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British men on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  This time the survival challenge is harder than ever, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. It’s four days since then men trapped and killed a crocodile, and they haven’t been able to repeat their success. Most of the meager meals they are eating are coming from cleaning facilities manager, Vic, who has is the only member of the group to mastered his improvised fishing rod.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/14tfjqayq4u3u1ulmtykuzcs2/original/14tfjqayq4u3u1ulmtykuzcs2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712173000 +0000" stop="20250712183000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 4</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British women on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools. This time the survival challenge is harder than before, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. The extreme conditions on the island are taking their toll on the 11 remaining women and they are now on the brink of starvation. They are living on an extreme low calorie diet, surviving on snails and limpets and scraps of scavenged yucca and coconut.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/b1ac8uvj7u701fluqqxpi7arz/original/b1ac8uvj7u701fluqqxpi7arz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712183000 +0000" stop="20250712193000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British women on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools. As the group approaches the four week mark of the experiment, the 10 remaining women are entering dangerous medical territory. With very little research about how the body copes with extreme survival beyond this point, it’s more important than ever that they keep up their food and water supply otherwise they risk long term damage to their vital organs. Yesterday the women feasted on their first big kill – a large pig. 25 year old Nurse Lauren along with 30 year old potter Beth have stayed up all night to preserve the left-over pork, requisitioning one of the group’s two precious jerrycans – normally reserved for their water purification system.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1gibkn8b22ejo1ghz3vn4k124/original/1gibkn8b22ejo1ghz3vn4k124.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712193000 +0000" stop="20250712203000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 5</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British men on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  The survival challenge is harder than ever, as they attempt to survive entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. In this episode, the emergency evacuation team are called in when 36 year old, Will, falls off a cliff on to rocks, badly injuring himself.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1r9pkfwugtom1mqk9ftzas48a/original/1r9pkfwugtom1mqk9ftzas48a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712203000 +0000" stop="20250712213000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Women: Episode 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In the ultimate survival experiment, Bear Grylls has abandoned 14 British women on a remote desert island in the Pacific with just the clothes they stand up in and a few basic tools.  The survival challenge is harder than ever, as they attempt to live entirely on their own wits for six weeks in the height of the tropical storm season. The women are starving as they enter their sixth and final week on The Island. Having plundered all the resources in the vicinity of their beach, the group are now looking to the ocean to sustain them.  The women are pinning all their hopes on their fishing net catching a major haul but so far it’s eluded them.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/2130ytqy3bkmzffijkkls64a/original/2130ytqy3bkmzffijkkls64a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712213000 +0000" stop="20250712223000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - The Men: Episode 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In this final episode, after five weeks on the island, the men are struggling to find enough to eat as the island's already depleted resources fail to deliver the coconuts and limpets that have become their staple diet. With energy levels at rock bottom, the island's oldest castaway - 58-year-old car salesman Phil - is forgotten when an unsatisfying watery fish broth is served for lunch.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/fu5kwy5rg1ib1pcx1vhhcqdrw/original/fu5kwy5rg1ib1pcx1vhhcqdrw.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712223000 +0000" stop="20250712233000 +0000">
    <title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
    <sub-title>The Island with Bear Grylls - Surviving The Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In this special episode of The Island With Bear Grylls takes an in-depth look at life on the islands. On The Island, Bear conducted the ultimate survival challenge to see if 14 men and 14 women could survive for six weeks on an uninhabited island in the Pacific Ocean. They were completely alone, filming everything themselves, with only a handful of basic tools and the clothes they stood up in. They not only had to survive entirely on their own wits for six gruelling weeks, but had to contend with the vicious tropical storm season.</desc>
    <date>20221116</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1qth25213d7ei1ftm63su0xlu/original/1qth25213d7ei1ftm63su0xlu.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5f5132df62fe160040f26bc2" start="20250712233000 +0000" stop="20250713003000 +0000">
    <title>Travel Guides: New Zealand</title>
    <sub-title>Travel Guides: New Zealand - Northland</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Meet the five families chosen to be New Zealand’s Travel Guides as they take on their first adventure in Northland. But there’s a few unhappy campers when the sleeping arrangements are revealed.</desc>
    <date>20210218</date>
    <icon src="https://images.frequency.com/video/1ebw78tyh4v481j4azurxuemh/original/1ebw78tyh4v481j4azurxuemh.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
