<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724233657 +0000" stop="20250725002158 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Regret Marrying Older Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E59</episode-num>
    <desc>Brenda says she fell in love with and married her husband, Don – despite their 26-year age gap. But soon after, she claims her “Prince Charming” turned “crazy” and “temperamental.” Is their age difference at the root of their issues? Then, Bev says she’s concerned for her sister, Melanie, who married her much younger man, Devar, after meeting him on a Jamaican vacation. Is Devar in it for love, or for a green card and money? And, Dr. Phil catches up with best-selling author Mitch Albom.</desc>
    <date>20151210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725002158 +0000" stop="20250725010856 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Craze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Demi Moore did it. So did Madonna and Halle Berry. This trend of older women dating younger men is called the Cougar Craze, and it’s sweeping the country. Recently, at a New York speed-dating event, "Sugar Mamas and Boy Toys," good-looking 35-year-old men wooed women over 35 who made at least $500,000 a year. Jeremy organized the event and says he was just answering a demand from affluent ladies. Was he sincere in his matchmaking or just out to make a buck? Dr. Phil talks to two women who participated in the event -- Gail, 44 and Nancy, 50. Their experiences might surprise you. Then, 51-year-old Kat says she’s no cougar; she just likes to date younger guys because men her age are set in their ways. She says her 23-year-old ex-boyfriend, Ryon, was loving, passionate and had a much higher libido than older men. Her friend, Nancy, says Kat has a great head for business, but a bad one when it comes to the opposite sex. She says young men just see dollar signs when they see Kat. Is Kat dating down, or should Nancy just butt out? And, Bobbi had an 11-year relationship with a man who was 17 years her junior, but she says once she turned 50, he saw her as too old. She wants to be in a relationship again, but not with an older man. Her son, Nathan, says someone still wet behind the ears can’t appreciate all Bobbi has to offer. Does Nathan have the right to put his foot down with his mother? Do you think it's OK for older women to date younger men? Take our poll!</desc>
    <date>20080502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725010856 +0000" stop="20250725015654 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Love Stories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E317</episode-num>
    <desc>At 36, Lisa fell in love with her sons’ 14-year-old friend, Adrian. By the time he was 15, they were married and Lisa was pregnant with their first child. Seven years and two kids later, they're still together. Will their love last? And, learn how a former Arizona gubernatorial candidate went looking for international love but wound up homeless on the streets of Ukraine.</desc>
    <date>20120402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10317.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725015654 +0000" stop="20250725024440 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Secrets in the Suburbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>How well do you know your neighbors, your friends or even your child's teacher? An estimated four to eight million people in North America are swinging in the suburbs " mostly middle-class folks from all walks of life. Dr. Phil takes you inside the secret world of swingers, a lifestyle where couples swap partners.</desc>
    <date>20080125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6009.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725024440 +0000" stop="20250725033110 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Did She Marry an Imposter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman recounts her marriage to a man, who allegedly concealed his criminal past.</desc>
    <date>20131125</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12033.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725033110 +0000" stop="20250725041903 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Lover, My Abuser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah is a pretty, intelligent, successful woman with everything going for her — so why won't she leave her abusive boyfriend, Robert? She says he punches her, chokes her, spits in her face, and has even threatened to kill her, but she believes he can be rehabilitated. Is she in over her head? If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic violence, don’t miss Dr. Phil's exit action plan for safely leaving an abusive partner</desc>
    <date>20120221</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10029.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725041903 +0000" stop="20250725050622 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Torn Between 2 Lovers Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E123</episode-num>
    <desc>Who will Brad choose: his wife or girlfriend?</desc>
    <date>20050428</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3123.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725050622 +0000" stop="20250725055406 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Torn Between 2 Lovers Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E213</episode-num>
    <desc>Who will Brad choose: his wife or girlfriend?</desc>
    <date>20050523</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3213.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725055406 +0000" stop="20250725064041 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Torn Between 2 Lovers Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E151</episode-num>
    <desc>The intervention continues with a cheating husband.</desc>
    <date>20050429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L3151.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725064041 +0000" stop="20250725072539 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E119</episode-num>
    <desc>The repercussions of revenge are explored featuring a couple whose actions lef to jail time.</desc>
    <date>20100429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8119.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725072539 +0000" stop="20250725081319 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Pursuing the Predator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E94</episode-num>
    <desc>Pedophiles once lurked in parks and around schoolyards, and then they prowled the playground of the World Wide Web. Now these predators have a more sinister method at their fingertips sending explicit text messages directly to your child's cell phone. Dr. Phil examines the latest technological threats to your kids and shows you how to protect them.</desc>
    <date>20090203</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7094.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725081319 +0000" stop="20250725085737 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>We Survived a Cult</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E402</episode-num>
    <desc>30 years after being forced into a religious sect full of sexual abuse, some of its victims share their stories for the first time.</desc>
    <date>20201026</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19402.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725085737 +0000" stop="20250725094010 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Sarah Ever Stop Lying?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E129</episode-num>
    <desc>Three friends confront former friend, Sarah, who faked terminal cancer, miscarriages, and used a wheelchair to pretend she had muscular dystrophy.</desc>
    <date>20190426</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17129.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725094010 +0000" stop="20250725102408 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Liar,Liar: Sarah Faces Her Accusers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E320</episode-num>
    <desc>In part two, will accused liar Sarah, who fibbed about having cancer, miscarriage and muscular dystrophy, change her ways?</desc>
    <date>20190429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17320.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725102408 +0000" stop="20250725111000 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Complicated Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E96</episode-num>
    <desc>Craig and Cherie say the last half of their 16-year marriage has been anything but happily-ever-after. Cherie says Craig is chauvinistic, verbally abusive and demands sex, which she admits she only gives him about three to four times a year. Craig says Cherie withholds sex to control him, and as a result, he has become a slave to his anger. Cherie fears the tension in their household is taking a toll on their 11-year-old daughter, who is often caught in the crossfire of their fighting. Dr. Phil challenges the couple to a communication test. Can they heal their wounds and rekindle their romance? Then, meet the couple who inspired the movie, The Vow. Shortly after Kim and Krickitt Carpenter were married, a terrible car crash changed everything. Krickitt lay in a coma for weeks, and awoke with no recognition of her husband. The couple shares their inspiring, though oftentimes heartbreaking, journey of falling in love all over again. How did they find their way back to each other? And what is it like seeing their lives played out on the big screen? If you’ve ever wondered whether love can survive the toughest of challenges, you won’t want to miss this show! This show contains strong sexual content. Viewer discretion advised.</desc>
    <date>20120306</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10096.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725111000 +0000" stop="20250725115831 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Heroin Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Brandon is a drug addict in recovery who credits Dr. Phil’s intervention with saving his life. Now, he and his mother, Debbie, pay it forward by staging interventions for families and their drug addicted loved ones. Dee saw an episode with Brandon and wrote to Dr. Phil for help with her 23-year-old twin daughters, Brooke and Tiffany, who are addicted to heroin and other prescription drugs. Both women have young children, who are often left to parent each other, as well as take care of their sick mothers. Dee and her husband, Danny, and their two other children, Ashley and Derrick, are united in the goal to save the girls’ lives, but will they be prepared when Dr. Phil makes them all take a hard look at themselves? Find out why Dr. Phil says the whole family is sick. Will the twins agree to treatment? And what will happen to their children? Don’t miss this shocking story!</desc>
    <date>20101103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9020.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725115831 +0000" stop="20250725124553 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Pageant Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E69</episode-num>
    <desc>A pageant mom’s 9 yo beauty queen’s photos ended up on a risque website. Who’s to blame?</desc>
    <date>20131126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12069.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725124553 +0000" stop="20250725133235 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Fights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you have a relative scheming to get money from a rich aunt, uncle or even parents when they pass away?</desc>
    <date>20071113</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725133235 +0000" stop="20250725142051 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Little Mean Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>These parents say their precious daughters have turned into bullies. Dr. Phil spells out how "commando parenting" will reshape the behavior of their "little mean girls."</desc>
    <date>20050920</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4006.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725142051 +0000" stop="20250725150850 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cut 'Em Off!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E97</episode-num>
    <desc>Is there an adult under your roof, eating your food and taking advantage of you financially? If yes, then you live with a moocher! It's time to stop the enabling and start the accountability.</desc>
    <date>20060131</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4097.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725150850 +0000" stop="20250725155541 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Order Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E108</episode-num>
    <desc>Guests share their journeys of seeking love abroad.</desc>
    <date>20110513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9108.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725155541 +0000" stop="20250725164315 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Save My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents, listen up! Your A-student or football champion could be abusing ADD/ADHD medication right under your nose. Dr. Phil alerts you to the latest risky teen trends and gives you advice for knowing what your kids are doing before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>20091103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8023.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725164315 +0000" stop="20250725172846 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Ex Puts Fame Before Our Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple is battling for custody of their 10-year-old daughter.</desc>
    <date>20161024</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L15023.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725172846 +0000" stop="20250725181410 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Ex Falsely Accused Me of Poisoning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E304</episode-num>
    <desc>A heated custody battle discussion continues with accusations of abuse and sabotage.</desc>
    <date>20161025</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L15304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725181410 +0000" stop="20250725190407 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Crazy, Stupid Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E71</episode-num>
    <desc>Amanda says her husband of two years, Jeffrey, was recently caught in an online child sex sting and sentenced to five years in prison, yet she’s not sure if she should leave him. Why does she say she blames herself for what happened? And, hear from Amanda’s parents, Juliet and Timothy, who say they just want their daughter to move on. When Dr. Phil gives Amanda a harsh dose of reality, will she see the situation for what it is? Then, 18-year-old Seri says that two years ago, she fell in love with 26-year-old Hector, who convinced her to quit school and become a prostitute — and give him all the profits. Hector was convicted of sexual assault of a child and is now serving up to 30 years in prison. Seri is raising their daughter and has a new boyfriend, Will, but she admits that she would consider taking Hector back, if given the opportunity. Why does Seri say she still has feelings for her abuser?</desc>
    <date>20130107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725190407 +0000" stop="20250725195140 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Our Dad Left Us for a “Kennedy Heir”!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Trisha and Danielle say they are furious with their father, Ron, who they say abandoned their dying mother -- his wife of 30 years -- to plan a wedding with an alleged Kennedy heiress he met online. The daughters are convinced “Misty Kennedy” is really a catfish, and they want to open their father’s eyes. But Ron says despite never having met “Misty” in person, he believes his fiancée is the real deal and the love of his life. Dr. Phil brings everyone together in search of answers. Who is “Misty Kennedy”?</desc>
    <date>20141006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13009_V2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725195140 +0000" stop="20250725203906 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Controversy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E57</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil explores the controversial trend of older women dating much younger men. Is age really just a number? First, Pie, a 58-year-old self-admitted cougar, has been dating 24-year-old Oleg for four months -- and her best friend, Terese, strongly disapproves. Could Pie be headed for heartbreak? Then, 52-year-old divorcée Bella says her relationship with 32-year-old Eddie is the best she has ever had. Eddie says he loves Bella and doesn’t mind that she’s the same age as his mother. Does this couple see a long-term future together? And, 76-year-old Aalsa -- former Miss Cougar America -- says after 40, men go downhill! After dating younger men for four decades, what advice does she have for fellow cougars? Tune in and decide for yourself: Can a relationship really survive a significant age gap?</desc>
    <date>20141210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13057.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725203906 +0000" stop="20250725212153 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marrying Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E88</episode-num>
    <desc>Sixty-two-year-old Bill and his 23-year-old girlfriend, Bri, are one of the couples featured on Lifetime’s television series Marrying Millions. Bill and Bri say not only do they come from two different worlds, but they have a 39-year age gap and are at different stages of their lives – Bri wants a family and children, and Bill has been divorced twice. Bill’s first ex- wife claims Bill has a history of cheating, as she says he cheated on her and has warned Bri it could happen to her. While Bill and Bri have been together for four years, they say they are at a crossroads: what happens when he turns 70 and she is only 31? Also, they say their families don’t see eye-to-eye, which impacts their daily lives. How “healthy” is their relationship? The couple takes Dr. Phil’s “Relationship Health Profile Test” and learns the results. Plus, Dr. Phil speaks with superfans from across the U.S. and has a special announcement for them. One superfan even gets his own “Dr. Phil” tattoo ... live! You won’t want to miss this episode!</desc>
    <date>20210126</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19088.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725212153 +0000" stop="20250725220120 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Dramas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Imagine your pregnant teen daughter running away to be with the baby's father -- an older man whom she met online. For Heidi, this became reality when her 15-year-old daughter, Brittney, went missing for five weeks. Dr. Phil put private investigator and former FBI Agent Harold Copus on the case to find the missing teen. See the confrontation when Harold finally locates her and her 34-year-old boyfriend. Then, find out why Brittney was even more upset when she found out what was in store for her. It's been two months; has Brittney's relationship with her mother improved? Next, Kim, 15, has run away six times in the last year, most recently making it halfway across the country to be with her married boyfriend. Why didn't her parents look for her, and why does she say she'll do anything to get away from them? Can this family learn to get things back on track? Think your child is being targeted by a sexual predator? Don’t miss Dr. Phil’s warning signs!</desc>
    <date>20061016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725220120 +0000" stop="20250725224626 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cougars And Sugar Daddies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to dating, they say age is just a number. But what happens when the man is more than two decades older than his girlfriend, or the woman is 15 years older than her young lover? Forty-year-old Sanjay is a wealthy cosmetic surgeon who met 18-year-old Jacqueline on the Web site SugarDaddie.com. They’ve only been together for four months and are already talking marriage. Sanjay’s friend, Mike, is convinced that Jacqueline will put him right in the poorhouse! Is there a chance that Sanjay has found true love, or is Jacqueline just in it for the money? Then, 24-year-old Ryan is engaged to Angela, a woman 15 years his senior. Ryan’s friend, Donovan, fears that Angela is alienating Ryan from his buddies. Will Ryan have to choose between his college friends and his soon-to-be wife?</desc>
    <date>20061108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725224626 +0000" stop="20250725233245 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Does Age Matter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Can May-December romances really last? Christopher Knight, famous for his role as Peter on The Brady Bunch, and Adrianne Curry, winner on America's Next Top Model, began their relationship when they starred together on the reality show The Surreal Life 4, and the public watched as they planned their wedding on their own show, My Fair Brady. Now they both say their 24-year age difference is a huge problem in their chaotic marriage. Adrianne says Christopher treats her like an employee, and Christopher says if she worked for him, she would’ve been fired a long time ago. Can these two work out their generational differences? Then, 38-year-old Shelly wants to know if it’s wrong to be in a relationship with an 18-year-old friend of her son. She says he makes her feel beautiful, but wonders if she’s causing him or her children harm. Dr. Phil doesn’t mince words when he tells her his opinion.</desc>
    <date>20070921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6006.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725233245 +0000" stop="20250726001943 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Craze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Demi Moore did it. So did Madonna and Halle Berry. This trend of older women dating younger men is called the Cougar Craze, and it’s sweeping the country. Recently, at a New York speed-dating event, "Sugar Mamas and Boy Toys," good-looking 35-year-old men wooed women over 35 who made at least $500,000 a year. Jeremy organized the event and says he was just answering a demand from affluent ladies. Was he sincere in his matchmaking or just out to make a buck? Dr. Phil talks to two women who participated in the event -- Gail, 44 and Nancy, 50. Their experiences might surprise you. Then, 51-year-old Kat says she’s no cougar; she just likes to date younger guys because men her age are set in their ways. She says her 23-year-old ex-boyfriend, Ryon, was loving, passionate and had a much higher libido than older men. Her friend, Nancy, says Kat has a great head for business, but a bad one when it comes to the opposite sex. She says young men just see dollar signs when they see Kat. Is Kat dating down, or should Nancy just butt out? And, Bobbi had an 11-year relationship with a man who was 17 years her junior, but she says once she turned 50, he saw her as too old. She wants to be in a relationship again, but not with an older man. Her son, Nathan, says someone still wet behind the ears can’t appreciate all Bobbi has to offer. Does Nathan have the right to put his foot down with his mother? Do you think it's OK for older women to date younger men? Take our poll!</desc>
    <date>20080502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250726001943 +0000" stop="20250726010736 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Sugar Baby Students</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil investigates the latest trend in online dating: sugar babies hooking up with sugar daddies. College girls and recent graduates who are struggling with mounting debt and a weak job market are turning to websites, such as SeekingArrangement.com, that introduce them to wealthy men who, in exchange for companionship - and maybe sex - help them pay their bills. Is this the Internet version of the world's oldest profession, or just a niche dating site? Four self-proclaimed sugar babies: Kristen, 21, Jennifer, 28, Janelle, 30, and Tracy, 31, passionately defend why their relationships differ from prostitution. Are their arranged monthly allowances and extravagant gifts the equivalent of being taken to fancy restaurants by a boyfriend or financially supported by a husband? Meet the creator of the website, Brandon, and hear why he says there's nothing wrong with these "mutually beneficial relationships." Former prosecutor and CNN analyst Sunny Hostin has some legal words of warning for Brandon and the ladies. Plus, an outraged father confronts Brandon in defense of his daughter, who he recently learned is on the site, and see why a self-proclaimed proud sugar daddy makes a hasty exit before meeting Dr. Phil!</desc>
    <date>20110916</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
