<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716010905 +0000" stop="20250716015503 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Choose My Husband or My Boyfriend?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman says she can't choose between her husband or boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>20131017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716015503 +0000" stop="20250716024214 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>I Was Acquitted, My Ex Says Guilty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E116</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman confronts accusations of her involvement in her son's accidental overdose.</desc>
    <date>20140512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12116.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716024214 +0000" stop="20250716032909 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Heather Go to Rehab</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E320</episode-num>
    <desc>The conversation continues with Heather, who says she is not at fault for her son's accidental overdose. But- where was she that night?</desc>
    <date>20140513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12320.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716032909 +0000" stop="20250716041407 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E119</episode-num>
    <desc>The repercussions of revenge are explored featuring a couple whose actions lef to jail time.</desc>
    <date>20100429</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8119.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716041407 +0000" stop="20250716050103 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Family Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A family fractured by child sexual abuse sits down with Dr. Phil to put the pieces back together and start the healing process. Michael, now 19, faces his little sister, May, 14, to apologize for molesting her when she was 11. Don't miss this compelling show about the power of forgiveness.</desc>
    <date>20111102</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10016.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716050103 +0000" stop="20250716054845 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Co-Parenting Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Jared says his ex-wife, Chandra, is a deadbeat mom who has failed to pay her court-ordered child support in the last six months. He also accuses Chandra’s current husband, Jason, of physical abuse toward his two children when they’re in his care -- a claim Jason adamantly denies. Chandra accuses Jared of emotionally abusing her since their divorce five years ago, and she claims he’s determined to ruin her life with her new husband. Is Jared a concerned parent, or a bitter ex with an ulterior motive? And, with their children caught in the crossfire, can these exes stop pointing fingers and learn how to peacefully co-parent? Plus, why hasn’t Chandra paid child support? Then, don’t miss Dr. Phil’s tips on how to effectively co-parent with your ex!</desc>
    <date>20130307</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716054845 +0000" stop="20250716063551 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Moms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E138</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil talks to Tiffany Tehan, dubbed the “Runaway Mom” and the family of missing mom, Julie Ann Gonzalez.</desc>
    <date>20100507</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8138.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716063551 +0000" stop="20250716072013 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Moms: The Polygraph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E323</episode-num>
    <desc>In part two, the estranged husband of missing mom, Julie Ann Gonzalez, takes a polygraph test.</desc>
    <date>20100514</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8323.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716072013 +0000" stop="20250716080558 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Mother's Betrayal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E128</episode-num>
    <desc>Sunny was enraged when she learned her mom, Carolyn, was adopting Sunny’s 36-year-old ex-boyfriend, Chris, and begged her to not go through with the process. Now that the adoption is final, she says Carolyn puts more time and energy into her relationship with Chris than into their mother-daughter bond. Carolyn says she always wanted a son and was over-the-moon when she finally adopted Chris. She says no parent has to ask their child for permission to have more children, so why should she need Sunny’s approval to adopt Chris? Carolyn and Sunny see each other for the first time in more than six months on Dr. Phil’s stage. Can Sunny move past her feelings of betrayal, and can Dr. Phil help them mend their broken bond? Then, why did Chris, a married father of three, want to be adopted?</desc>
    <date>20120906</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10128.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716080558 +0000" stop="20250716085258 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s 1000 Lies and Counting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E115</episode-num>
    <desc>Melisa claims her estranged husband, Chris, is a pathological liar. Chris admits he has a problem and insists he wants to change -- but does he really? Should Melisa stay with him or call it quits?</desc>
    <date>20150330</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13115.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716085258 +0000" stop="20250716094005 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>How to Fix a Broken Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E118</episode-num>
    <desc>You've heard people complain, "If I only knew then what I know now, I wouldn't be in this mess," but what about those times when you choose not to see the writing on the wall? Dr. Phil meets couples who say their relationships went from bad to worse after they said, "I do," and now their families are broken.</desc>
    <date>20090520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7118.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716094005 +0000" stop="20250716102718 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Accusations &amp; Polygraphs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrific allegations are tearing a family apart — but who is telling the truth? Todd says he was shocked and appalled when his ex-girlfriend's mother, Diana, accused him of molesting his 4-year-old daughter, Taniya, and turns to Dr. Phil to help clear his name. Diana says that while babysitting Taniya, the toddler detailed ways in which Todd inappropriately touched her, and she's convinced he's done the unthinkable. After learning of the accusations, Taniya's mom, Latia, reported the alleged sexual abuse to a judge who immediately stripped Todd of his parental rights — but was justice served? Latia says that as much as she wants to believe Todd's innocence, as a mother, she needs to take every precaution to protect her child. A year has passed since he's seen his daughter, and Todd says he will go to any length to prove his innocence, including taking another a lie detector test — even though he's already passed one. He's adamant that Diana is lying and says that she coached Taniya to make the accusations. Dr. Phil calls in an expert polygraph examiner. Don't miss the shocking results!</desc>
    <date>20111110</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10039.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716102718 +0000" stop="20250716111421 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Toxic Relationship Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Brittany says her boyfriend, Tim, is evil, abusive and unfaithful. “I sometimes think that he could kill me,” she says. So, why is she still considering marrying him? Tim admits that he can’t control his rage and to choking Brittany while he was holding their 6-month-old daughter -- and he fears he’ll accidentally hurt the baby next. Tim also confesses to cheating on Brittany with both men and women, and even finding male companions online. Can Dr. Phil help Tim reign in his temper before it's too late? And, Tim promises that the violence and infidelity are a thing of the past, and he’s ready to make a change -- but is he? Don’t miss Dr. Phil’s eye-opening advice for this couple and anyone in an abusive relationship.</desc>
    <date>20121114</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11049.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716111421 +0000" stop="20250716120051 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>An Obsessed Love Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E80</episode-num>
    <desc>Sandie says she desperately hopes to win back her ex-husband, Chris, so they can be a family again with their adopted 11-year-old daughter, but Chris’ ex-girlfriend, Aileen, will stop at nothing to keep them apart. Sandie says Aileen is stalking and harassing her, making false reports of abuse and neglect to CPS, and even created a fake profile on Facebook to talk trash about her -- and she wants Aileen prosecuted. Sandie says she and Chris have filed a total of nine peace orders against Aileen, but only the last one filed by Chris was granted, protecting him -- but not Sandie or their daughter. Aileen admits to intentionally causing trouble but says Sandie deserves it, because she destroyed Aileen’s relationship with Chris -- and she also wants him back. Chris says he’s tired of being caught in the middle of his exes and isn’t interested in a relationship with either one, other than co-parenting with Sandie -- but is he sending mixed messages? Can this trio reach a truce and learn to respect boundaries?</desc>
    <date>20140214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716120051 +0000" stop="20250716124407 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>My Teen Can’t Stand Her Stepfather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E104</episode-num>
    <desc>When he last appeared on Dr. Phil, Kip’s brazen and outrageous tirade toward his 17-year-old stepdaughter, Tory, shocked audience members and viewers. But the married father of two refused to back down. When Tory broke down in tears, Kip finally agreed to find a calmer way to express his frustration. Just weeks later, Tory’s mother, Vicky, says the surly relationship has not only gotten worse, the hostility has escalated, and her patience is running thin. She says both Tory and Kip refuse to seek help, and now there is a new bombshell that is making their home life virtually unbearable. What does Kip say is his biggest issue with his stepdaughter? And, will this family finally agree to accept help and repair what’s left of their relationship? Then, Joe, 34, became an instant father to two teenage daughters. One of the girls has run away, and the other feels that he treats her like a slave. Can they resolve their disputes and come together as one? (FOLLOW UP FROM 9093)</desc>
    <date>20110531</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9104.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716124407 +0000" stop="20250716132928 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Mystery of Melissa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who vanished finally faces her family.</desc>
    <date>20201012</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716132928 +0000" stop="20250716141519 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Daughter’s Dark Confession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E304</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who vanished reveals a dark secret.</desc>
    <date>20201013</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19304.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716141519 +0000" stop="20250716150323 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Top 5 Mistakes You’re Making</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E43</episode-num>
    <desc>From marital spats to parenting disagreements, learn the biggest mistakes you're making.</desc>
    <date>20100107</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8043.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716150323 +0000" stop="20250716155057 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Our Dad Left Us for a “Kennedy Heir”!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Trisha and Danielle say they are furious with their father, Ron, who they say abandoned their dying mother -- his wife of 30 years -- to plan a wedding with an alleged Kennedy heiress he met online. The daughters are convinced “Misty Kennedy” is really a catfish, and they want to open their father’s eyes. But Ron says despite never having met “Misty” in person, he believes his fiancée is the real deal and the love of his life. Dr. Phil brings everyone together in search of answers. Who is “Misty Kennedy”?</desc>
    <date>20141006</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13009_V2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716155057 +0000" stop="20250716163847 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cheaters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E109</episode-num>
    <desc>With a dark cloud of lying, deceit and infidelity hanging over your relationship, can you ever trust a cheater again? Some research suggests that 64 percent of marriages stay together after an affair. Will today's guests?</desc>
    <date>20060301</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716163847 +0000" stop="20250716172716 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>On the Outs With the In-Laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E113</episode-num>
    <desc>Manipulative, violent, controlling, downright diabolical. These are some of the words Anna-Laura uses to describe her mother-in-law, Janice. Anna-Laura says her mother-in-law has threatened to take her children away, calls 12-15 times per day, peeks in their windows, goes through their trash, drives to Anna-Laura’s house and points her finger – from her car- as if she is pulling the trigger of a gun. Morgan says his mother also opens the front door and walks into their home unannounced. Anna-Laura says she got a restraining order against her mother-in-law after Janice hit her, which Janice denies. She says Janice is forcing her husband, Morgan, to choose between his mother and his wife. What can this family do to get along with one another?</desc>
    <date>20060228</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4113.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716172716 +0000" stop="20250716181413 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Bully Moms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E111</episode-num>
    <desc>Moms are accused of bullying their own children.</desc>
    <date>20100504</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8111.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716181413 +0000" stop="20250716190121 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Dad Accused of Faking His Own Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's claim of his father's disappearance leads to a shoking decption.</desc>
    <date>20120919</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11016.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716190121 +0000" stop="20250716194919 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Updates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Do you ever wonder how your favorite Dr. Phil guest is faring since being on the show? Dr. Phil follows up with some of his most talked about guests.</desc>
    <date>20081202</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7038.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716194919 +0000" stop="20250716203735 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Heaviest Woman On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E51</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother who is nealty 700 pounds struggles to gets her life on track.</desc>
    <date>20111123</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10051.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716203735 +0000" stop="20250716212413 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Isn’t Enough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E42</episode-num>
    <desc>If you think pretty people are immune to heartache, think again. The headlines are filled with stories of striking women who were devastated by infidelity, despite their outward beauty. Dr. Phil sits down with Joey, a husband and father, who says he can’t pass up a pretty face. His wife, Shannon, says he’s slept with close to 100 women since their wedding day. The personal trainer justifies his actions by saying Shannon is overweight and not hot enough for him. Will he get a wake-up call about his cheating ways? Or will his wife take him back yet again? See the shocking text messages to Joey’s mistress, and hear Dr. Phil’s strong message for the hapless husband when a disturbing secret is revealed. Can Dr. Phil encourage Joey to choose another path and look beyond the physical?</desc>
    <date>20101112</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9042.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716212413 +0000" stop="20250716221028 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Cold Blood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E413</episode-num>
    <desc>Revisiting the 1992 murder of Shanda Sharer, her family reflects on coping and forgiveness.</desc>
    <date>20110520</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9413.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716221028 +0000" stop="20250716225750 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Cold Blood Pt. 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E414</episode-num>
    <desc>The family of Shanda Sharer who was murdered confronts one of the convicted killers.</desc>
    <date>20110523</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9414.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716225750 +0000" stop="20250716234531 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Is This Normal?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Does someone in your life do something so bizarre that you have to ask, "Is this normal?" Dr. Phil's guests confront loved ones about their unusual behavior.</desc>
    <date>20071214</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6030.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250716234531 +0000" stop="20250717003310 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma v. Mom: Custody Battle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E46</episode-num>
    <desc>How do you determine whether someone is fit to be a parent? Should a parent previously ruled unfit by the court system ever be allowed to regain custody? What should you do if your parenting skills are called into question by a family member? Dr. Phil's guests are feuding mother and daughter, Barbara and Nicole, who have been battling for two years over the custody of Nicole's son, Ethan.</desc>
    <date>20081104</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L7046.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250717003310 +0000" stop="20250717012044 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Save My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Parents, listen up! Your A-student or football champion could be abusing ADD/ADHD medication right under your nose. Dr. Phil alerts you to the latest risky teen trends and gives you advice for knowing what your kids are doing before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>20091103</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8023.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
