<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d">
    <display-name>CNN Originals</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/00f41feb-c13e-4a3d-b7ca-c9bb253d19be/CNN_Originals_RDX_color_logo.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719000446 +0000" stop="20250719005449 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Liguria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/30/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits one of the most famous and frequented regions of Italy – the Italian Riviera – which is famous for the glitz and glamour of Portofino and stunning picture-perfect fishing villages of the Cinque Terre. Liguria is a thin strip of mountainous land, sandwiched between the Alps and Apennines, and lined with rugged scenery and stunning coastal views. The capital of Genoa, once a wealthy merchant empire, offers a richness of cuisine fit for a prince from personalized stamped pasta to its most internationally acclaimed export, Genoese pesto. Tucci will discover how Ligurians have learned to adapt to life in this difficult landscape and how they have found ingenious solutions to survive frugally yet thrive.</desc>
    <date>20221030</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/89MgM8OHBURBIhGSzkQC7j2AuML.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719005449 +0000" stop="20250719014453 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Calabria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/9/2022. Calabria is a region of rugged landscapes, dramatic mountain ranges, and some 500 miles of incredible coastline. Connected to Basilicata in the north and separated from Sicily in the south by the narrow Strait of Messina, Calabria is also the homeland of the Tucci family’s ancestors. In this episode, Stanley Tucci travels through the region, discovering the history of this beautiful and troubled place, as well as the history of his own family. Joined by his parents and reunited with Italian relatives, he reflects on the inspiration people draw from Calabria, and why those who leave this region feel compelled to return.</desc>
    <date>20221009</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fG8fsFsm9kMUsTkC7HCifVmagBj.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719014453 +0000" stop="20250719023453 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Just Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/18/2021. Friends, Seinfeld, Living Single – so many of us know the characters in these shows better than most of our real friends. By the 90s, these “hanging out with friends” sitcoms become the vital force driving the genre – and in many ways, pop culture. But it’s earlier shows like The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Laverne and Shirley, What’s Happening!!, The Facts of Life and Golden Girls that set the stage for peak friends sitcom, and it’s iconic follow-ups like Curb Your Enthusiasm, Community, How I Met Your Mother and New Girl that bring that form into the new millennium. Featuring sitcoms such as Friends, Seinfeld, Living Simple, The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Laverne and Shirley, What’s Happening!!, The Facts of Life, Golden Girls, Curb Your Enthusiasm, Community, How I Met Your Mother, and New Girl.</desc>
    <date>20210718</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3SRQMgGOwItxOQDtvLSSCHekBfZ.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719023453 +0000" stop="20250719032453 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Working for Laughs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/25/2021. The workplace is a rich source of comedy as it binds vastly different people together with laughter. From The Mary Tyler Moore Show to Murphy Brown, from WKRP to 30 Rock, from Barney Miller to Brooklyn 99, from Designing Women to Veep, as America’s relationship with their jobs changes - and especially as women break through countless workplace barriers - sitcoms evolve in endlessly humorous ways. Featuring sitcoms such as The Marry Tyler Moore Show, Murphy Brown, WKRP, 30 Rock, Barney Miller, Brooklyn 99, Designing Women, and Veep.</desc>
    <date>20210725</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4bUX7PxQ2oEcQBshbxQRbHBch4C.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719032453 +0000" stop="20250719041458 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Facing Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/1/2021. With cutting-edge humor, pioneering creators and sitcom stars have helped open generations of American minds to the intractable problems of racial injustice and representation. Icons like Norman Lear, Diahann Carroll, Red Foxx and Freddie Prinze smash open doors with All in the Family, Julia, Sanford and Son and Chico and the Man. But with racist roots running as deep as Amos ‘n’ Andy, the sitcom has had a long, hard road to authentic, inclusive 21st century comedies like Black-ish and Fresh off the Boat. Featuring sitcoms such as All in the Family, Julia, Sanford and Son, Chico and the Man, Amon ‘n’ Andy, Black-ish, and Fresh off the Boat.</desc>
    <date>20210801</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zXNH2uTRXO3EUFkNo3nAdIDLgvP.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719041458 +0000" stop="20250719050458 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Movin’ on Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/8/2021. No sitcom finds more endlessly inventive humor in implicit class tensions than Frasier, as a working-class father tries to get along with his sublimely high-brow sons. But though the American Dream of social mobility underpins America’s social contract, that dream is so often beyond reach that it takes sitcom humor to help laugh at the struggles of getting ahead. The Honeymooners, The Beverly Hillbillies, The Andy Griffith Show, Good Times, Alice and Roseanne all offer funny snapshots at class divisions in America, divisions that are even starker in Arrested Development and Schitt’s Creek. But It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia that asks the hardest, perhaps funniest question of all – is this aspirational game we’re all playing really rigged against us? Featuring sitcoms such as The Honeymooners, The Beverly Hillbillies, The Andy Griffith Show, Good Time, Alice, Roseanne, Arrested Development, Schitt’s Creek, and It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>20210808</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8gcFmMG0Ys3t0aapIGw9niZAoGC.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719050458 +0000" stop="20250719055459 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Freaks, Geeks &amp; Outsiders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/15/2021. Though the nerds in Big Bang Theory owned the airwaves in the new millennium, sitcoms have always found humor in fish-out-of-water stories, whether about immigrants, aliens, witches, monsters, nerds, or teens. Bewitched and Sabrina long cast a spell on audiences, while Mork and Mindy and 3rd Rock from the Sun give us fresh, funny alien insights into ourselves. Who can’t help snapping their fingers with The Addams Family theme, or not laugh at Urkel’s “Did I do that?” In one way or another, audiences relate to outsiders, and these iconic characters give license to laugh at our own foibles in ways few other forms of entertainment do. Featuring sitcoms such as Mark and Mindy, Bewitched, 3rd Rock from the Sun, The Addams Family, and Big Bang Theory.</desc>
    <date>20210815</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ph8rgxDSvCmUgaAAkXipXtjb6sW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719055459 +0000" stop="20250719064502 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Sardinia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/16/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits the Italian island of Sardinia. Famous for its harsh, rugged landscape, crystal blue ocean, and passionately preserved traditions, Tucci will learn how Sardinian food culture varies wildly throughout the island. He experiences the culinary delights of its coastal cities influenced by previous civilizations, and ventures inland to discover the rural heart of Sardinia, which remains untouched from outsider influence. This mysterious and mystical island is full of treasures and Sardinians are proud of their heritage and culinary diversity. One thing is certain: whoever steps foot on this island, will never want to leave.</desc>
    <date>20221016</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6NEc6YIycrsCbP94bWzAGC8ViJd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719064502 +0000" stop="20250719073506 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Puglia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/23/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits Puglia, a region famous for its fragrant olive oil, beautiful vegetables, cheeses, and durum wheat. Despite being such a fertile region, Puglia is also one of Italy's poorest and Tucci discovers how today’s spirit of innovation was forged out of hard times. From Bari’s raw seafood to Cisternino’s Fornelli and Foggia’s burnt grain to cheesemaker Vito’s Apulian blue cheeses, it is clear that by reclaiming their past, the Pugliese are taking ownership of their past and embracing the future on their own terms.</desc>
    <date>20220515</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xuXw7L80avbHcUjtc9beOG2PL1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719073506 +0000" stop="20250719082509 +0000">
    <title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy</title>
    <sub-title>Liguria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/30/2022. In this episode, Stanley Tucci visits one of the most famous and frequented regions of Italy – the Italian Riviera – which is famous for the glitz and glamour of Portofino and stunning picture-perfect fishing villages of the Cinque Terre. Liguria is a thin strip of mountainous land, sandwiched between the Alps and Apennines, and lined with rugged scenery and stunning coastal views. The capital of Genoa, once a wealthy merchant empire, offers a richness of cuisine fit for a prince from personalized stamped pasta to its most internationally acclaimed export, Genoese pesto. Tucci will discover how Ligurians have learned to adapt to life in this difficult landscape and how they have found ingenious solutions to survive frugally yet thrive.</desc>
    <date>20221030</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/89MgM8OHBURBIhGSzkQC7j2AuML.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719082509 +0000" stop="20250719091509 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>Escaping Reality</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 8/22/2021. In ever-changing America, sitcoms have offered an escape from the pressures of a turbulent social and media landscape, often through nostalgia and sheer absurdity. From Gilligan’s Island to Get Smart, from The Love Boat to Full House, they are a funny comfort food – an antidote to fear of a fast-changing world. But what sitcoms offer escape from, and what visions they escape to, reveal deep insights into the state of the American psyche and the sitcom form itself. The Simpsons blows up a live-action sitcom mold grown stale to usher in a new era of adult animation, while BoJack Horseman and The Good Place offer deep soul-searching dives to help audiences cope with the 21st century. Featuring sitcoms such as Gilligan’s Island, Get Smart, The Love Boat, Full House, The Simpsons, BoJack Horseman, and The Good Place.</desc>
    <date>20210822</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l1MA7lSMOHtX2EXRLP3nwTL7Enz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719091509 +0000" stop="20250719100509 +0000">
    <title>History of the Sitcom</title>
    <sub-title>A Family Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 7/11/2021. Every sitcom is, at its heart, a reflection of America’s core social “situation” - the family. This episode explores how sitcoms evolve to reflect the changing face of this most fundamental social unit. From I Love Lucy to the blended Brady Bunch, from working class families in All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time and Roseanne to the aspirational The Cosby Show, from the groundbreaking Black-ish to Fresh off the Boat, sitcom humor has helped broaden our horizons and open our minds to what a Modern Family can be. Featuring sitcoms such as Brady Bunch, I Love Lucy, All in the Family, Good Times, One Day at a Time, Roseanne, The Cosby Show, Black-ish, Fresh off the Boat, and Modern Family.</desc>
    <date>20210711</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rjRmsubnWj2RCQj8nY3tCy8qymS.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719100509 +0000" stop="20250719105540 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 04/26/15. Anthony Bourdain returns to Korea after 10 years to experience hyper-modern Seoul, and taste Korean fried chicken, vintage army stew and Kimchi.</desc>
    <date>20150426</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nnVaIdO9lxuXEqLVWmCGmGfZAkE.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719105540 +0000" stop="20250719114610 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Miami</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/03/15. Anthony Bourdain gets a taste of Miami with cow foot soup in Little Haiti and a personal lesson on sights and sounds from musician Questlove.</desc>
    <date>20150503</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nlBexxYfWSfs5XOw34L8OCSK1s2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719114610 +0000" stop="20250719123641 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Scotland</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/10/15. Anthony Bourdain visits one of his favorite cities in Europe — Glasgow— where he makes his first stop at the Old College Bar for a pint.</desc>
    <date>20150510</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bxEQahskwh8rXVsKRn00Uib1OMW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719123641 +0000" stop="20250719132711 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Madagascar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/17/15. Anthony Bourdain explores the island nation of Madagascar, where he visits the capital city of Tana and samples Malagasy cuisine.</desc>
    <date>20150517</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xCrdaoTBgT9JxD2lUIlXgPTbFeA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719132711 +0000" stop="20250719141742 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>New Jersey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/31/15. Anthony Bourdain travels to his childhood home state with his brother Chris, where they rekindle memories at the classic roadside joint, Hiram’s.</desc>
    <date>20150531</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f9HZRKSdby10MtqTAeGfSsZuVXy.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719141742 +0000" stop="20250719150812 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Budapest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/07/15. Bourdain explores the beauty, culture, and food of Budapest, where he samples goulash, fisherman's soup, blood sausage, and chicken liver.</desc>
    <date>20150607</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wUUiBVoQK14OErvlnfVUoLpsFTg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719150812 +0000" stop="20250719155843 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Hawaii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/14/15. There’s another side to Hawaii that many tourists don’t know about. Go with Anthony Bourdain as he explores the unknown area.</desc>
    <date>20150614</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fRqe6sBYlQn3zD0m1K9vMFUe6Cv.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719155843 +0000" stop="20250719164913 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Beirut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/21/15. Anthony Bourdain travels to Beirut, where he discovers a beautiful country known for its vibrant nightlife and legendary cuisine.</desc>
    <date>20150621</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vTtbylD5Ul8jEvMNNELGt9IQGWz.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719164913 +0000" stop="20250719173944 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Ethiopia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 10/25/2015. Anthony Bourdain visits Addis Ababa, to sample dishes like injera bread and soak up Ethiopian melodies with chef Marcus Samuelsson.</desc>
    <date>20151025</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mbXmHZ1jOibkoqCssdratbzfC00.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719173944 +0000" stop="20250719183014 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Borneo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 11/01/2015. Anthony Bourdain returns to Borneo after 10 years to enjoy chicken rendang and pork noodles in the street food paradise of Kuala Lumpur.</desc>
    <date>20151101</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/QX8N9R8NaYLJER5sSB26t8MFWb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719183014 +0000" stop="20250719192049 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Istanbul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 11/08/2015. Anthony Bourdain explores the mixing of food, culture and politics in Istanbul, as he enjoys an authentic Turkish breakfast and watches an oil wrestling match.</desc>
    <date>20151108</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ln621YTUpQ4Gfzw4olUx4IxlEBY.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719192049 +0000" stop="20250719201120 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 04/26/15. Anthony Bourdain returns to Korea after 10 years to experience hyper-modern Seoul, and taste Korean fried chicken, vintage army stew and Kimchi.</desc>
    <date>20150426</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nnVaIdO9lxuXEqLVWmCGmGfZAkE.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719201120 +0000" stop="20250719210150 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Miami</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/03/15. Anthony Bourdain gets a taste of Miami with cow foot soup in Little Haiti and a personal lesson on sights and sounds from musician Questlove.</desc>
    <date>20150503</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nlBexxYfWSfs5XOw34L8OCSK1s2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719210150 +0000" stop="20250719215221 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Scotland</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/10/15. Anthony Bourdain visits one of his favorite cities in Europe — Glasgow— where he makes his first stop at the Old College Bar for a pint.</desc>
    <date>20150510</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bxEQahskwh8rXVsKRn00Uib1OMW.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719215221 +0000" stop="20250719224251 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Madagascar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/17/15. Anthony Bourdain explores the island nation of Madagascar, where he visits the capital city of Tana and samples Malagasy cuisine.</desc>
    <date>20150517</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xCrdaoTBgT9JxD2lUIlXgPTbFeA.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719224251 +0000" stop="20250719233322 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>New Jersey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 05/31/15. Anthony Bourdain travels to his childhood home state with his brother Chris, where they rekindle memories at the classic roadside joint, Hiram’s.</desc>
    <date>20150531</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f9HZRKSdby10MtqTAeGfSsZuVXy.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66ad6025cb5d3b7fb5011c2d" start="20250719233322 +0000" stop="20250720002352 +0000">
    <title>Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <sub-title>Budapest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Aired 06/07/15. Bourdain explores the beauty, culture, and food of Budapest, where he samples goulash, fisherman's soup, blood sausage, and chicken liver.</desc>
    <date>20150607</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wUUiBVoQK14OErvlnfVUoLpsFTg.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
