<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430">
    <display-name>Maverick Black Cinema</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/ott_channels/logos/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703093904 +0000" stop="20250703112016 +0000">
    <title>The Groomer</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Layla is a young and attractive woman who meets Bryce in her teen years, and he is who she claims to be the love of her life. Unbeknownst to her, Bryse is manipulating her and forming her into his own object of desire. Layla is under his spell, until a different side of him that could destroy her.</desc>
    <date>20241217</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7zCkSfQYWGxjRJTMs4WeUwoHpz6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703112016 +0000" stop="20250703131257 +0000">
    <title>The Housekeeper</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After the death of her son, Sharease Smalls loses everything, and is forced to move back in with her sister Elise. Struggling to find steady work, Sharease agrees to become a live-in housekeeper for a local crime boss, Zues. The pairs professional relationship soon turns intimate, but it’s only a veil of secrets and lies. Will Sharease survive the truth?</desc>
    <date>20240703</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0c6dfae8f1b82be8cd0b9985ce70b597.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703131257 +0000" stop="20250703144952 +0000">
    <title>The Only Child</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Twelve-year old Chris has a wonderful and thriving childhood with her loving family. When her mother dies tragically in a car accident, she begins to go down a dark spiral. When Chris’ father starts seeing another woman, she begins a sinister plan, as no woman will ever replace her mother.</desc>
    <date>20240815</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/a/gracenote/ae8af31c5a0994c1a804fee2df4d2b30.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703144952 +0000" stop="20250703164144 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Mother</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Linda, a determined mother, faces the daily struggles of raising her son Ahmad amidst the unpredictable presence of her husband Jeremy. When a series of hardships push her to the edge, Linda's plea for assistance inadvertently leads to Ahmad being taken into CPS custody. Linda rises to the challenge of overcoming adversary to reunite her family and save her son.</desc>
    <date>20241112</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/b/gracenote/bc2e9b15dc6c5dbbb0f69895326e7d91.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703164144 +0000" stop="20250703182131 +0000">
    <title>Who is She</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Megan is a beautiful woman in search of love and acceptance but masks a tormented soul. Beneath the surface lies a volatile woman with multiple personalities and a dangerous capacity for violence.</desc>
    <date>20230530</date>
    <icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2NzI0NWItN2FlNS00N2NhLTgyZmMtYjAwZDJmNWIxZDI2XkEyXkFqcGc@._V1_.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703182131 +0000" stop="20250703194516 +0000">
    <title>Apex</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A special ops team enters the underground bunker "Hades" to rescue missing scientists, only to uncover a terrifying secret far beyond their expectations.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703194516 +0000" stop="20250703212034 +0000">
    <title>The Price of Fame</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the streets of Atlanta, Cassie, a struggling young woman searching for purpose, meets Ryan, a charismatic interviewer who offers her a chance to step into the world of fame and opportunity. With guidance from her cunning best friend, Ledrick, Cassie navigates the glamorous yet cutthroat entertainment industry. But as hidden agendas and betrayals emerge, Cassie finds herself questioning the cost of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/0558d67846acf5282aada1da02655e7f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703212034 +0000" stop="20250703231841 +0000">
    <title>The Wrong Man</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>In the wake of a devastating loss, a widowed mother is left to navigate the complexities of life with her two children. She is determined to provide stability and find love again. New love is sometimes not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250624</date>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/images/thumbnails/maverick_maverick_black_cinema_2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250703231841 +0000" stop="20250704004811 +0000">
    <title>Messy</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>After being sent away to prison for possessing a firearm, Meek Richardson returns home to the DMV to find out his associate Kevin, is killed. Meek seeks to find the truth about his friend’s death, and finds that his enemies are closer than it seems.</desc>
    <date>20250506</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/acyZTZDnhfbliJmKv7n6Y0IbNVO.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704004811 +0000" stop="20250704023259 +0000">
    <title>The Legend of Doc Mays</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Follows the story of Dwayne “Doc” Mays, born in North Carolina and raised in Chicago by his streetwise mother. After the death of his mother when he was 8 years old, he found himself a ward of the foster system, ultimately leading to a life on the streets and of crime. When he meets his future mentor “Street” he would rise to be one of the most notorious gangsters in Chicago’s history of organized crime.</desc>
    <date>20250128</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/9/gracenote/96a81eb7c614536319b831c4906c3f9a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704023259 +0000" stop="20250704041446 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Wife</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A young freelance photographer in Houston meets a beautiful determined teacher from Atlanta. His best friend tries to warn him about her. There is something a little strange about Claudia. Q loves her dearly but she may not be The Perfect Wife.</desc>
    <date>20221122</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/412ca4e25a6d6d4467092f8d652cbdd6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704041446 +0000" stop="20250704060143 +0000">
    <title>The Perfect Wife 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The Styles Girls relocate to a new state to start over after the loss of the only place they knew. Unbeknownst to them, the secrets they left behind surface within the walls of their new residence.</desc>
    <date>20221122</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/412ca4e25a6d6d4467092f8d652cbdd6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704060143 +0000" stop="20250704075515 +0000">
    <title>Till Death Do Us</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Marcus falls in love with Jessica, who has her own house and wants to start a family. Shortly after their honeymoon, Jessica's past life comes back in to the present. When Jessica's long lost husband reappears back in her life, and wants his family back. Marcus and Jessica are not willing to give up their new life, but her ex-husband is determined to win her back, even if it means risking his life.</desc>
    <date>20230905</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f78edcf864d6964bea9e9a5166bd8fca.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704075515 +0000" stop="20250704093308 +0000">
    <title>Till Death Do Us 2</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The fates of Tamara, TJ, and even Marcus himself hang in the balance after the bloody kitchen shooting. Did anyone survive? Will Pastor Marcus's mysterious powers intervene? Meanwhile, Jessica, TJ's ex-wife, faces scrutiny for her past actions and the future of their children. With the threat of child protective services looming, the clock is ticking to find answers and rebuild shattered lives.</desc>
    <date>20240901</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/d/gracenote/d6856f68934d7b0bf393a451cefbcd1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-5ef4e1b40d9ad000423c4430" start="20250704093308 +0000" stop="20250704113604 +0000">
    <title>Toxic Traits</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Eric is a prodigal son, who meets Regina on a dating app and they fall in love. The two seem like a match made in heaven, except for Eric’s suspicious mother. Events begin to unfold and Regina’s true nature comes to light.</desc>
    <date>20240102</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/2/gracenote/25dfe15257df3155b241cc7e95160b16.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
