<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5">
    <display-name>Barney and Friends</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/d1388332-0aee-4da1-9d42-1c2c9c00ab6c/BARNEY_LOGO_COLOR_dylan_canfieldRDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722010015 +0000" stop="20250722013015 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Go For A Ride!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and the children have fun playing with toy cars. They take this opportunity to learn about buses and cars, including all the mechanics inside that make them similar. After learning about different kinds of vehicles they may see on the roads, the kids build a bus to take them to their favorite neighborhood spots.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029565_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722013015 +0000" stop="20250722020019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>That Makes Me Mad!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Nick accidentally gets white paint on Sarahs picture, the children must find a way to deal with their emotions. Barney helps his young friends find good ways to express and deal with angry and negative emotions.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029566_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722020019 +0000" stop="20250722023019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Your Birthday, Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After an abundance of mail arrives at the Caboose for Barney, the kids realize it must be a very special day. Its Barneys birthday! Barneys friends along with Baby Bop and BJ, put together a stupendous party celebration for him in the park, including decorations and cake galore!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029567_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722023019 +0000" stop="20250722030019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>It's Showtime!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney, BJ and the kids spend the day preparing for a very special performance for their friends in the park. They all gather in the caboose to prepare for a stupendous night of singing, dancing, and magical fun.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029568_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722030019 +0000" stop="20250722033018 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>At Home in the Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah and Tony create a beautiful birdhouse to place out in the park. They are happy to learn that the birds will have lots of company; many other animals make their homes in the park too! Barney and the kids travel around the park, noticing and discussing all the various animals that call the park home.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029569_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722033018 +0000" stop="20250722040000 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody's Got Feelings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The children realize its normal to experience all different types of emotions. With Barneys help, the children learn all about how to handle how they are feeling, especially feeling happy, sad, and angry.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029570_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722040000 +0000" stop="20250722043007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbits - Ducks and Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is pretending to be a great detective, and needs a mystery to solve! A case quickly comes his way when something nibbles on one of Baby Bops healthy snacks. BJ, Barney, and Baby Bop uncover several clues along the way and soon realize the culprit is someones pet rabbit. Barney sees Riff protecting a nest full of duck eggs. Together, they leave the eggs to look for food for when the ducklings hatch. When they return, Riff is pleasantly surprised to find the eggs have cracked open and the baby ducklings have hatched!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029604_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722043007 +0000" stop="20250722050008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Goose - Fairy Tales</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in the caboose, BJ is surprised to learn that The Land of Mother Goose truly exists. Several Mother Goose characters have come to ask for help; parts of their rhymes are missing! Mother Goose arrives and fixes the problem, and all of the Mother Goose characters return home. BJ and Baby Bop hope to visit them soon. When Baby Bop catches Barney, BJ, Riff and some children wrapping a mysterious present in the caboose, she just cant wait to see what is in the box. Barney suggests they listen to a story while they wait. Baby Bop finally gets to open her present and realizes that sometimes waiting is a good thing!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029605_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722050008 +0000" stop="20250722053008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Things I Can Do - Differences</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop isnt satisfied with the things she can do. She wants to play the keyboard like Riff and wants to be able to skate like Barney. Nobody can cheer her up, until she unexpectedly gets the whole park dancing and she realizes there are things she can do, too! When a wheelchair-bound child is unintentionally neglected by his friends, Barney steps in to help. He gently reminds the others to include the child by showing them that even Barney feels excluded sometimes. It isnt always easy being a big, purple dinosaur. In the end, everyone is included for a day of fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029606_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722053008 +0000" stop="20250722060005 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing - Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamal has never danced before and is too shy to try. On the day of the big dance party in the park, Barney and his friends introduce Jamal to many kinds of dance. Barney assures Jamal that he can do anything he puts his mind to even dance. With Barneys help, Jamal finally finds his groove and has fun dancing with his friends! Barney tells Baby Bop the story of The Princess Without a Song to Sing. In this original fairytale, Baby Bop imagines herself as the sad little princess trying to find her unique song. Barney, BJ and Riff all become characters in the story, each sharing their songs and revealing an element of song, sound, rhythm and feeling. With their help, the princess finds her song and is delighted to sing it for her friends!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029607_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722060005 +0000" stop="20250722063007 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Neighborhood - Careers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Riff cant find his drumsticks anywhere. He knows he had them when he visited various neighborhood locations with Barney earlier in the day. Barney magically recreates neighborhood spots to help refresh Riffs memory. Happily, Barneys strategy is a success and Riff finds his drumsticks. Along the way, everyone learns that the most important part of a neighborhood is the people who live there! Barney helps Baby Bop explore many different jobs. At the end of the day, Baby Bop has several different careers to consider for when she grows up. But for now, shes happy just being three!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029608_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722063007 +0000" stop="20250722070011 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>China - Kenya</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>BJ is waiting for a very special letter from his pen pal in China. The letter reveals that his pen pal is coming for a visit. With the help of friends in the park, BJ hurries to get the park ready. He wants it decorated so his pen pal feels right at home. BJ soon learns that his pen pal wants to see how BJ really lives! Everyone is anxiously awaiting Mrs. Matumas Harambee Dance Troupe to arrive. They finally arrive and perform a show of African music and dance and everyone pulls together in the true spirit of Harambee!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029609_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722070011 +0000" stop="20250722073008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pistachio - Full Team Ahead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is snacking on pistachios...and just can't seem to stop! His friends try to help. An unexpected avalanche of pistachios convinces Barney that his friends may be right. BJ is looking to find players for his baseball team. When his baseball-impaired cousin Riff asks to play, BJ is faced with a difficult choice. Barney helps BJ discover the meaning of team sports, friendships, and winning.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029610_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722073008 +0000" stop="20250722080010 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Words - Litterbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In her eagerness to play with her friends, Baby Bop forgets to say please and thank you. Barney tells her that these two words can be magic. Baby Bop daydreams she can't say the magic words, no matter how hard she tries! Then Riff invents a robot to clean up the park. When Riff's Litterbot malfunctions, it creates even more trash to clean up.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029611_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722080010 +0000" stop="20250722083008 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bop 'til You Drop - Sleepless Sleepover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop becomes a little bossy playing with her friends, Barney teaches her that being bossy isn't a nice way to treat your friends. Melanie has never been on a campout and is feeling nervous. When Barney tells her all about the fun they will have, Melanie decides to give it a try. What could be better than sharing her very first campout with her friends and Barney?</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029612_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722083008 +0000" stop="20250722090012 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Little Red Rockin Hood - The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop is having a hard time finding a story she hasn't heard before. Barney and the dinos decide to tell her an old story with a new twist...by singing Little Red Riding Hood! A talented young artist is painting a portrait of Barney, but when she steps away, BJ takes credit for it. When the others beg him to teach them to paint, BJ admits the truth and learns that honesty is the best policy!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029613_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722090012 +0000" stop="20250722093009 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Wind and the Sun - The Nature of Things</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop sets up a lemonade stand, but BJ wants to fly his kite in the same spot, leading to a heated debate over sun vs. wind. Barney shares the story of The Wind and the Sun, teaching them that kindness always prevails. Rachel carelessly litters in the park. Later on, she has a dream about animals who talk. With Barney and the animals help, Rachel learns that the park is home to many. Rachel realizes the importance of nature and of keeping our earth clean!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029614_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722093009 +0000" stop="20250722095818 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The New Kid - Grandpa's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After Riff makes friends with new kid Noah, BJ becomes jealous and thinks he is not Riff's friend anymore. Barney teaches him that you can always keep your old friendships and make new ones too. Barney and the kids are excited that they are going to the movies. But Ryan's Grandpa is coming to town, and he wants to spend some time with him. Arriving at the park, Ryan's Grandpa is looking for a very rare bird and he asks everyone to help him find it.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029615_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722095818 +0000" stop="20250722102825 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Garden - Listen!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Baby Bop wants Barney, BJ, and the kids to play with her instead of working in their garden. They promise to play with her as soon as they finish. Baby Bop can't wait, and tries many ways to get them to come play with her now, none of which work. When her friends do come to play, they have a tea party and enjoy some of the fresh things from the garden. When Riff hears a mysterious sound in the park, he plays detective, trying to solve the mystery. Barney and the children join in the fun. Along the way, they explore the sense of sound while identifying sounds of nature and the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029616_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722102825 +0000" stop="20250722105832 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Lost and Found - Pot Full of Sunshine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After BJ loses everyone's tickets to the circus, he sets out to find them and learns a valuable lesson about responsibility. Baby Bop discovers a lonely little flower struggling to grow in a shady spot. She takes it to a sunny spot, nurtures it, and is thrilled when the flower blooms. When the flower dies on a cold day, Barney and friends help her gain hope for the future.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029617_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722105832 +0000" stop="20250722113013 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody's Got Feelings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The children realize its normal to experience all different types of emotions. With Barneys help, the children learn all about how to handle how they are feeling, especially feeling happy, sad, and angry.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029570_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722113013 +0000" stop="20250722120014 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Caring Hearts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After creating a friends and family tree for a school project, the children discuss all the people in their lives they care about. This provides a perfect opportunity for Barney and his friends to learn about love and relationships.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029571_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722120014 +0000" stop="20250722123016 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Make Music!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A fun day in the park with friends involves a musical rhythm clapping game. Barney introduces a new game that helps reinforce learning about music, rhythm, and musical instruments. This new found inspiration causes the kids to make their very own marching band.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029572_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722123016 +0000" stop="20250722130017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movin' Along</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a great day to move around in the park! Barney and his friends have fun with creative movement, while learning new dances, having races, and acting out a story. These activities teach the kids how they can move their bodies while doing different activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029573_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722130017 +0000" stop="20250722133019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let Your Creativity Fly!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious paper airplane flies into the park, inspiring the children to talk about all things Airplanes! The children let their creativity fly when they use their imaginations to build their very own airplane.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029574_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722133019 +0000" stop="20250722140021 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Imagine That!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The possibilities are endless as Barney and the kids use their imagination to bring their drawings to life. Barney and the children have an island adventure by imagining themselves in Lauras picture, transporting them to a sunny island!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029575_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722140021 +0000" stop="20250722143017 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All About Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrate the things that make us special! Barney and his friends discover that trying something new can be fun. Jackson treats everyone to his healthy but unusual snack, while Baby Bop has a special picnic for BJ consisting mostly of her favorite foods.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029576_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722143017 +0000" stop="20250722150019 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Baby Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Oh baby! Oh baby! David has a new baby brother and is now a big brother. But David doesnt know what a big brother is supposed to do and isnt sure hes ready. Barney and his friends help David learn about new babies and how to be a big brother.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029577_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722150019 +0000" stop="20250722153020 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Keep On Truckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends keep on truckin'! BJ enjoys helping with his tow truck, while Barney shows everyone what it's like to be behind the wheel of a real truck. When Jackson's special truck loses a tire, Barney wheels in to the rescue!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029578_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722153020 +0000" stop="20250722160022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>I'm A Builder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing some big construction machines roll by, Barney and his friends are inspired! With a little imagination, they build a castle made out of boxes. By exploring the ways things are built, and the big machines and tools used to build them, Barney builds in the fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029579_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722160022 +0000" stop="20250722162823 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Coming On Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Exercise is good for everybody and every body! From running to touching toes to jumping jacks to some favorite songs and games, Barney and his friends grow strong through various activities and having fun with exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029580_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722162823 +0000" stop="20250722165839 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Play Games!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>It's fun and games with Barney and his friends! BJ's favorite way of getting exercise is by playing sports and games. When Baby Bop is shy about trying new games, Barney and his friends show her how tee-rific trying something new can be.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029581_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722165839 +0000" stop="20250722173022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>You Can Count On Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick shows Barney and the rest of the kids his number cards that he and his mom had put together. He doesn't really think they're fun at first. But Barney helps his friends discover just how fun numbers can be by taking them on a number hunt in the park. With Barney and his friends, you can always count on a fun day!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029582_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722173022 +0000" stop="20250722180023 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Wonderful World of Colors and Shapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Picture this! When Barney shows off his new painting, his friends are inspired to create their own art show. Discovering how to create new colors and draw shapes, Barney and his friends put on a super-dee-duper art show</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029583_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722180023 +0000" stop="20250722182845 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Easy as ABC</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Baby Bop uses the caboose mailbox to deliver a special invitation to her tea party, she discovers that no one can read her handwriting. Barney and his friends find creative ways to help her learn her ABCs so she can spell her name!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029584_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722182845 +0000" stop="20250722185826 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Look What I Can Do!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's friends are playing a fun game of I Can Do where they each share something they can do. When BJ suggests having an I Can Do show, Baby Bop becomes worried. Barney shows Baby Bop that while trying something new can sometimes be scary, with help from family and friends, it can also be fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029585_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722185826 +0000" stop="20250722193022 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Caring Hearts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After creating a friends and family tree for a school project, the children discuss all the people in their lives they care about. This provides a perfect opportunity for Barney and his friends to learn about love and relationships.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029571_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722193022 +0000" stop="20250722200024 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Make Music!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A fun day in the park with friends involves a musical rhythm clapping game. Barney introduces a new game that helps reinforce learning about music, rhythm, and musical instruments. This new found inspiration causes the kids to make their very own marching band.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029572_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722200024 +0000" stop="20250722203026 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movin' Along</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Its a great day to move around in the park! Barney and his friends have fun with creative movement, while learning new dances, having races, and acting out a story. These activities teach the kids how they can move their bodies while doing different activities.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029573_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722203026 +0000" stop="20250722210027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let Your Creativity Fly!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious paper airplane flies into the park, inspiring the children to talk about all things Airplanes! The children let their creativity fly when they use their imaginations to build their very own airplane.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029574_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722210027 +0000" stop="20250722213029 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Imagine That!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The possibilities are endless as Barney and the kids use their imagination to bring their drawings to life. Barney and the children have an island adventure by imagining themselves in Lauras picture, transporting them to a sunny island!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029575_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722213029 +0000" stop="20250722220025 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>All About Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Celebrate the things that make us special! Barney and his friends discover that trying something new can be fun. Jackson treats everyone to his healthy but unusual snack, while Baby Bop has a special picnic for BJ consisting mostly of her favorite foods.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029576_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722220025 +0000" stop="20250722223027 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Baby Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Oh baby! Oh baby! David has a new baby brother and is now a big brother. But David doesnt know what a big brother is supposed to do and isnt sure hes ready. Barney and his friends help David learn about new babies and how to be a big brother.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029577_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722223027 +0000" stop="20250722230028 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Keep On Truckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and his friends keep on truckin'! BJ enjoys helping with his tow truck, while Barney shows everyone what it's like to be behind the wheel of a real truck. When Jackson's special truck loses a tire, Barney wheels in to the rescue!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029578_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722230028 +0000" stop="20250722233030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>I'm A Builder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing some big construction machines roll by, Barney and his friends are inspired! With a little imagination, they build a castle made out of boxes. By exploring the ways things are built, and the big machines and tools used to build them, Barney builds in the fun!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029579_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722233030 +0000" stop="20250722235851 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Coming On Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Exercise is good for everybody and every body! From running to touching toes to jumping jacks to some favorite songs and games, Barney and his friends grow strong through various activities and having fun with exercise.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029580_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250722235851 +0000" stop="20250723002903 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Play Games!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>It's fun and games with Barney and his friends! BJ's favorite way of getting exercise is by playing sports and games. When Baby Bop is shy about trying new games, Barney and his friends show her how tee-rific trying something new can be.</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029581_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250723002903 +0000" stop="20250723010030 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>You Can Count On Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick shows Barney and the rest of the kids his number cards that he and his mom had put together. He doesn't really think they're fun at first. But Barney helps his friends discover just how fun numbers can be by taking them on a number hunt in the park. With Barney and his friends, you can always count on a fun day!</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029582_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-671c1743128bc4121f80aef5" start="20250723010030 +0000" stop="20250723013031 +0000">
    <title>Barney and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Wonderful World of Colors and Shapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Picture this! When Barney shows off his new painting, his friends are inspired to create their own art show. Discovering how to create new colors and draw shapes, Barney and his friends put on a super-dee-duper art show</desc>
    <date>19700101</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/cinedigm_entertainment_corp/1000000029583_1920x1080.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
