<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f">
    <display-name>Western Bound</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/b89e1bed-7f63-46b3-9be4-b72bcf76839a/WesternBound_Plex_channel_logo_light_-_Trish_Boothe.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722010147 +0000" stop="20250722013237 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas and Mark go on a train trip, clouds of swarming grasshoppers force the train to stop. A prisoner takes advantage of the emergency and breaks free, then kills Marshal Dixon. Lucas, with the help of a buffalo hunter, outwits the outlaw.</desc>
    <date>19600301</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72417.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722013237 +0000" stop="20250722020136 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time for Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws kill a preacher and his wife. Two members of the group assume their identity and come to North Fork to rob the bank. However, when Mark finds out who they really are, he is kidnapped and kept quiet. Lucas and Micah set out to stop the gang.</desc>
    <date>19600308</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72418.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722020136 +0000" stop="20250722025910 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Two Trails to Santa Fe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne helps an Apache woman escape torture from her tribe. He transports her to Santa Fe. However, angry Apaches retaliate and attack a settlement. The pair also encounters gold-hungry prospectors along the way.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722025910 +0000" stop="20250722040000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Savage Breed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne is guiding a buffalo hunting party that Marshal Lestrade is leading. Lestrade's daughter Lily and Senator Carr are in the group. Cheyenne finds a herd, but a mysterious gunshot sends the buffalo on a stampede. Cheyenne is suspicious.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722040000 +0000" stop="20250722050000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>These guys can wrangle any bull, but can they tame a wild bulldozer? In this episode of The Cowboy Way, the guys decide to build a new barn for a local rancher but it's man versus machine when Bubba's dozer breaks a pipeline, releasing a torrent of water. Jaclyn admits to her boss she's been looking for a job closer to home, then worries it might get her fired altogether. Will her family have to survive on one income? Cody decides to write a book about the cowboy way of life, but he may have bitten off more than he can chew.   The cowboys struggle to get the barn raised in time to process the first shipment of the herd and might have to call in some favors to do it.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722050000 +0000" stop="20250722060000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <sub-title>Keep on Chuckin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It's The Cowboy Way's first road trip ever! Bubba, Cody and Booger cut loose and head north to enter a big chuck wagon race. But they quickly discover this race is not for amateurs.  Loose wagon wheels, knee-deep mud and professional-grade competition raise both the stakes, and their concerns. Will the guys risk life and limb to race and win? And while the cowboys are away, a surprise shipment of cattle comes in days early and their wives must jump into action.  But this drop off is anything but routine when Kaley and Misty discover one heifer has an infection that could threaten the entire herd.</desc>
    <date>20180915</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/f/gracenote/f3168ccf4b7f860539ca77fa4f9fd0ef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722060000 +0000" stop="20250722063014 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old friends of Lucas', Don Chumera De Lardo and Colonel Black, come to the McCain Ranch. They are there to finish a deed of honor, even insisting on a jousting match. Lucas learns that the feud started over a chess game.</desc>
    <date>19611113</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72471.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722063014 +0000" stop="20250722070000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Honest Abe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor of Lucas' believes he is Abe Lincoln after being mentally injured in the Civil War. Townspeople go along with his impersonation since he is a kind man. However, when a saloon patron makes fun of him, trouble ensues.</desc>
    <date>19611120</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72472.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722070000 +0000" stop="20250722090000 +0000">
    <title>County Line: No Fear</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>When Sheriff Alden Rockwell finally decides to retire, a threat against the father of his friend, Sheriff Jo Porter, may not only ruin his plans for a life of leisure but also bring a dangerous criminal syndicate to both Maksville and York counties.</desc>
    <date>20221206</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/7/gracenote/7ef7b2ecfdcc4de025d343cb3bc2c492.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722090000 +0000" stop="20250722113059 +0000">
    <title>McLintock!</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>A cattle baron awaits the return of his daughter from school and is surprised that his wife has returned to take their daughter away. He tries to keep the peace and do what is best for everyone.</desc>
    <date>19631113</date>
    <icon src="https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rSKUkB28YPbfTh4zt42fdsMbRwR.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722113059 +0000" stop="20250722120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>A Shard of Glass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Haunted by the memory of leaving a man to die, mountain man Jim Bridger is determined not to repeat the mistake. When his trapping party runs out of water while crossing a barren desert, Bridger struggles desperately to keep his companions alive.</desc>
    <date>20240314</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/66e868d10340f39f5e75b08d/08b06d1e-f226-4536-886c-0911f15b73de/thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722120000 +0000" stop="20250722123036 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple move to North Fork and settle down under a false name to keep the town from knowing they are parents of a vicious killer on the loose. However, their plan fails when their son shows up and causes chaos.</desc>
    <date>19600216</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72415.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722123036 +0000" stop="20250722130000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage girl named Heller and her brother are abused by her drunken stepfather. The town becomes aware after Heller is caught stealing from the general store. The children plan the drunk's demise as the cruelty continues. Lucas steps in to help.</desc>
    <date>19600223</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72416.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722130000 +0000" stop="20250722133050 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas and Mark go on a train trip, clouds of swarming grasshoppers force the train to stop. A prisoner takes advantage of the emergency and breaks free, then kills Marshal Dixon. Lucas, with the help of a buffalo hunter, outwits the outlaw.</desc>
    <date>19600301</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72417.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722133050 +0000" stop="20250722140000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time for Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws kill a preacher and his wife. Two members of the group assume their identity and come to North Fork to rob the bank. However, when Mark finds out who they really are, he is kidnapped and kept quiet. Lucas and Micah set out to stop the gang.</desc>
    <date>19600308</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72418.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722140000 +0000" stop="20250722150000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Two Trails to Santa Fe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne helps an Apache woman escape torture from her tribe. He transports her to Santa Fe. However, angry Apaches retaliate and attack a settlement. The pair also encounters gold-hungry prospectors along the way.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722150000 +0000" stop="20250722160000 +0000">
    <title>Cheyenne</title>
    <sub-title>Savage Breed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Cheyenne is guiding a buffalo hunting party that Marshal Lestrade is leading. Lestrade's daughter Lily and Senator Carr are in the group. Cheyenne finds a herd, but a mysterious gunshot sends the buffalo on a stampede. Cheyenne is suspicious.</desc>
    <date>20241211</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-chy101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722160000 +0000" stop="20250722170000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>Booger goes back to school! On this episode of The Cowboy Way, the cowboys visit the Montgomery Stockyard to research cattle prices and Booger gets bitten by the auctioneering bug. Will his auctioneering classes pay off? Back at the ranch, the guys catch heat from a neighbor when their herd escapes into his field, and a rebellious heifer takes them on one heck of a ride. Misty's brother-in-law, Chip, stops by and gives Cody an earful that his feeding pasture has turned to dirt.  And when the cattle stock market takes a nosedive, the cowboys' million-dollar business partner calls the gang into his office for a tough talk.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722170000 +0000" stop="20250722180000 +0000">
    <title>The Cowboy Way</title>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <desc>The cowboys head west to Louisiana in this episode of The Cowboy Way! The boys hit the road to find the perfect bull for their herd, if Booger's backseat antics don't drive them all crazy first. They discover a cowboy candy store where a famous saddle maker fits Bubba's horse for a custom saddle. Cody gets challenged to a roping contest by some teenagers. And when they accidentally find themselves in the fanciest restaurant in town, the guys test their cowboy palate with fine French cuisine. Escargot anyone? Back home Jaclyn and Kaley try hot yoga for their first and maybe last time, and Misty takes a shine to modeling.</desc>
    <date>20240712</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/show/thumbnails/poster/2000x2858/the_cowboy_way_-_s04.poster.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722180000 +0000" stop="20250722182915 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogerty lives in a rundown house with his grandson, Woody. Lucas tries to get the old man to send the boy to school. The ladies of North Fork want Woody removed from the home and ask Lucas to help them.</desc>
    <date>19611127</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72473.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722182915 +0000" stop="20250722190000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Famous writer Mark Twain visits North Fork and Mark, who idolizes him, is hurt by his rudeness. Lucas intervenes and discovers the source of  Twain's bitterness comes from personal tragedy. Later, both Marks become friends.</desc>
    <date>19611204</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72474.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722190000 +0000" stop="20250722192915 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>They Killed Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frontiersman Jim Bridger spins an incredible tale to a group of settlers, claiming he was once killed by Blackfeet warriors yet somehow lived to tell the tale. They think he's joking, but Bridger soon proves that he really did rise from the dead.</desc>
    <date>20240118</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/4/gracenote/49053fbc9fd4e71e781cd495c1e326f2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722192915 +0000" stop="20250722200000 +0000">
    <title>The Tall Tales of Jim Bridger</title>
    <sub-title>Brothers in Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When they are ambushed by a Blackfeet war party, Jim Bridger and a lone Shoshone brave must work together to find a way to defeat their common enemy. If they can't overcome their suspicions and learn to trust each other, they may not survive the day.</desc>
    <date>20240208</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/0/gracenote/026519c3c1e72d4423485f5f99e1d5d4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722200000 +0000" stop="20250722202945 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>The Real Lone Star Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When young Texas Ranger Ira Aten is having trouble hunting down a ruthless outlaw, he enlists the help of John Hughes, an aloof rancher with an uncanny talent for tracking bad guys. The two men form an unlikely and unexpected bond while traversing the dusty path toward justice. With Hughes' guidance, Aten finally catches up to the outlaw and ends his reign of terror. Along the way, Hughes decides to become a Ranger himself and transforms from loner to lawman. Hughes' adventure with Aten is just the first chapter of a storied career that inspires the popular novel, The Lone Star Ranger. Some years later, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews Aten years later to uncover the real story of the Lone Star Ranger and separate the truth from the fiction.</desc>
    <date>20210418</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/wild_west_chronicles_-_s01.backgroundtitle_14.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722202945 +0000" stop="20250722210000 +0000">
    <title>Wild West Chronicles</title>
    <sub-title>Bass Reeves: Trailblazing Lawman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping the bonds of slavery, Bass Reeves takes refuge among the indigenous people of The Indian Territory, where he is welcomed into their culture. When the Civil War ends, his new-found tracking skills and fluency in native languages lead to his appointment as the first Black Deputy U.S. Marshal west of the Mississippi River. Though he faces discrimination from his peers, Reeves earns their respect when he accepts Judge Isaac Parker's daunting order to hunt down one of the most ruthless killers in The Indian Territory and bring him back dead or alive. Some years later, Bat Masterson, legendary gunfighter-turned-newspaperman, interviews Judge Parker to learn more about the amazing career of Bass Reeves, who goes on to arrest 3,000 felons, kill 14 men in self-defense, and complete 32 years of service without being wounded.</desc>
    <date>20210425</date>
    <icon src="https://vod-static.plex.tv/thumbnails/64769c3da2fc3fadb4a20893/12205e3c-98c6-4f6d-ae9e-3adf05f21805thumb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722210000 +0000" stop="20250722220000 +0000">
    <title>Into The Wild Frontier</title>
    <sub-title>John Coffee Hays: A Texas Legend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A Tennessee native, John Coffee Hays heads to the frontier of Texas in the 1830s and signs on as an early member of the Texas Rangers. In 1844, Hays becomes a legend when he leads a small band of rangers in a desperate fight with the Comanche.</desc>
    <date>20240428</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ea75d1d7e1e3b687a3332869615bb8a6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722220000 +0000" stop="20250722230000 +0000">
    <title>Ultimate Cowboy Showdown</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown at the Arena</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Only seven cowboys remain, eager for the chance to prove they can win it all. The immunity challenge examines each cowboy's patience and control in a point system challenge. The contestant with the highest score won't have to sweat the next elimination round. When it looks like it might come down to a tie, the last cowboy to ride prevails. In the two-part elimination challenge, the contestants must gather and load a herd into a trailer before racing off to a neighboring field where they must doctor a few yearlings in open pasture. The green team starts strong, but a few wrong moves have major repercussions. On the blue team, a cowboy takes the lead, curious to see if his teammate will sink or swim under pressure. The elimination comes down to two rivals who don't hold back when it comes to letting Trace know why the other should go home. In the end, Trace sends the cowboy whose heart doesn't seem to be in it to win it, but they don't go quietly.</desc>
    <date>20210331</date>
    <icon src="https://metadata-static.plex.tv/e/gracenote/ee24e0a0312cab5e2e1ea8779fe9e570.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722230000 +0000" stop="20250722235623 +0000">
    <title>The Young Riders</title>
    <sub-title>Pride and Prejudice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Buck guides the cavalry to a Sioux camp to release hostages. They find the Sweetwater store owner's wife, Sally, and daughter, Jennifer, who the Sioux kidnapped years earlier. However, their reunion is not a happy one as complications arise.</desc>
    <date>20241118</date>
    <icon src="https://img.static-ottera.com/prod/ime/video/thumbnails/widescreen/3840x2160/l-yng101_horizontal.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250722235623 +0000" stop="20250723002709 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded Army deserter shows up at the McCain Ranch desperate for a horse. Lucas takes him in just as the Army Cavalry unit appears to take the deserter into custody. In town, the harsh commanding officer demands he be executed for desertion.</desc>
    <date>19600315</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72419.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723002709 +0000" stop="20250723005559 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark drinks some tainted water from a barrel and contracts typhoid fever. Lucas is forced to use an eccentric old doctor. During bouts of a continuous intense fever, Mark becomes delirious and has a vision of his deceased mother, who he never knew.</desc>
    <date>19600322</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-62316e8eb9d292cb4ad7499f" start="20250723005559 +0000" stop="20250723012631 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lariat Jones, an old friend of Lucas', comes to North Fork to open up a new gambling casino. Jones has an excellent reputation as an honest gambler. But when two strangers become his partners, accusations of cheating become deadly for Jones.</desc>
    <date>19600329</date>
    <icon src="https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/72089/72421.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
