<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
<channel id="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90">
    <display-name>Dr. Phil</display-name>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/a07750e7-11a2-4563-a402-40ad1d9e7392/xPlex_DrPhil_Channel_Logo_v01RDX.png" />
  </channel>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724004925 +0000" stop="20250724012852 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Dramas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Imagine your pregnant teen daughter running away to be with the baby's father -- an older man whom she met online. For Heidi, this became reality when her 15-year-old daughter, Brittney, went missing for five weeks. Dr. Phil put private investigator and former FBI Agent Harold Copus on the case to find the missing teen. See the confrontation when Harold finally locates her and her 34-year-old boyfriend. Then, find out why Brittney was even more upset when she found out what was in store for her. It's been two months; has Brittney's relationship with her mother improved? Next, Kim, 15, has run away six times in the last year, most recently making it halfway across the country to be with her married boyfriend. Why didn't her parents look for her, and why does she say she'll do anything to get away from them? Can this family learn to get things back on track? Think your child is being targeted by a sexual predator? Don’t miss Dr. Phil’s warning signs!</desc>
    <date>20061016</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5003.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724012852 +0000" stop="20250724021511 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Does Age Matter?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Can May-December romances really last? Christopher Knight, famous for his role as Peter on The Brady Bunch, and Adrianne Curry, winner on America's Next Top Model, began their relationship when they starred together on the reality show The Surreal Life 4, and the public watched as they planned their wedding on their own show, My Fair Brady. Now they both say their 24-year age difference is a huge problem in their chaotic marriage. Adrianne says Christopher treats her like an employee, and Christopher says if she worked for him, she would’ve been fired a long time ago. Can these two work out their generational differences? Then, 38-year-old Shelly wants to know if it’s wrong to be in a relationship with an 18-year-old friend of her son. She says he makes her feel beautiful, but wonders if she’s causing him or her children harm. Dr. Phil doesn’t mince words when he tells her his opinion.</desc>
    <date>20070921</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6006.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724021511 +0000" stop="20250724030223 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Mom to Blame for Babies' Death?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E136</episode-num>
    <desc>A man accuses his ex-wife and her new husband of killing his children.</desc>
    <date>20140513</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12136.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724030223 +0000" stop="20250724034852 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parents Accused of Murder (Part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E323</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his interview with Tommy, who accuses his ex-wife, Julia, and her new husband, Codey, of killing his 19-month-old son, Darby, and 4-year-old stepdaughter, Kiera -- an allegation the couple vehemently deny. Dr. Phil enlists the help of forensic pathologist Dr. Cyril Wecht to examine the children’s autopsy reports -- what are his findings? And, will Julia and Codey agree to take polygraph tests?</desc>
    <date>20140506</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12323.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724034852 +0000" stop="20250724043450 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Choose My Husband or My Boyfriend?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman says she can't choose between her husband or boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>20131017</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12002.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724043450 +0000" stop="20250724052225 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins (Part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E209</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother faces tough questions from Dr. Phil as they race to get her two daughters off the streets and into rehab.</desc>
    <date>20061120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5209.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724052225 +0000" stop="20250724055726 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins (Part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E210</episode-num>
    <desc>Two sisters struggles to detox and remain clean from drugs. Dr. Phil shows them a scary glimpse of their future.</desc>
    <date>20240605</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5210.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724055726 +0000" stop="20250724064340 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>House: Addicted Twins PT 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E211</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil addresses Cindy's impact on Tecoa's sobriety and reunites Sarah and Tecoa with their estranged father.</desc>
    <date>20061204</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5211.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724064340 +0000" stop="20250724073042 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Lohans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E410</episode-num>
    <desc>In a rare interview, Dina Lohan sets the record straight.</desc>
    <date>20120917</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11410.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724073042 +0000" stop="20250724081748 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Take Your Hands Off My Man!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E101</episode-num>
    <desc>Theresa says her fiancé, Bill’s, ex-girlfriend, Melissa, is jealous and obsessed with trying to ruin their relationship. She claims Melissa is a “psycho stalker” who is making their lives “hell” by sending Bill naked pictures of herself and showing up at his workplace unannounced. Melissa, who has a 3-year-old son with Bill, blames Theresa for destroying their family. She says Bill cheated on her with Theresa when she was pregnant with their son - so for revenge, she claims she has slept with Bill several times since he has been with Theresa. Bill admits he has made mistakes, including cheating on Theresa twice with Melissa but claims she took advantage of him. He says he’s tired of being stuck in the middle of their drama and just wants to peacefully co-parent with Melissa and marry his true love, Theresa but is he sending mixed messages? And, Theresa says she doubts Bill is the father of Melissa’s 3-year-old son. What will the paternity results reveal? And, will everyone heed Dr. Phil’s advice to bring resolution to this drama-filled love triangle?</desc>
    <date>20140502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12101.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724081748 +0000" stop="20250724090215 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Child Kidnapped, Starved and Beaten</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E109</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman endures nearly two decades of severe abuse, allegedly inflicted by her adoptive parents.</desc>
    <date>20190904</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17109.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724090215 +0000" stop="20250724094905 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Lying Husband (Pt 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E45</episode-num>
    <desc>In a three-part series, a man makes a shocking confession to his wife, only after he failed a polygraph test.</desc>
    <date>20071119</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6045.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724094905 +0000" stop="20250724103453 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s Shocking Confession (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E315</episode-num>
    <desc>In part two, Dr. Phil continues working with a couple who are struggling to stay together after the husband’s shocking confession.</desc>
    <date>20071120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6315.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724103453 +0000" stop="20250724112036 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Husband’s Shocking Confession (Pt 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E316</episode-num>
    <desc>In part 3, what started out as a husband’s admitting to a sex addiction turned into a shocking story of murder.</desc>
    <date>20071121</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6316.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724112036 +0000" stop="20250724120810 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Drunk Driving Moms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In the last 10 years, the number of women arrested for driving drunk has risen by 30 percent, and police report that more and more young children are sitting in the back seat when these moms are pulled over.</desc>
    <date>20090930</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L8012.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724120810 +0000" stop="20250724125401 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Twisted Love: The Aftermath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E112</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil follows up with Charles and Tracy. After coming to the conclusion that his dream of being shared by his wife and mistress was never going to happen, did Charles follow through and end his relationship with the other woman?</desc>
    <date>20060227</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L4112.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724125401 +0000" stop="20250724134040 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Stalking Student or Professor?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E94</episode-num>
    <desc>The truth behind a toxic relationship between a student and professor.</desc>
    <date>20150216</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L13094.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724134040 +0000" stop="20250724143013 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Young, Privileged, And In A Gang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E85</episode-num>
    <desc>The family of a 16-year-old self-professed gang member comes together to urge the teen to turn his life around. And, two former gang members have an important message for the teen -- Is he ready to walk away from the gang life for good?</desc>
    <date>20140213</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L12085.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724143013 +0000" stop="20250724151724 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Parenting Dilemmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E79</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple engage in a bitter custoday battle marred by allegations of violence and threats.</desc>
    <date>20070713</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5079.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724151724 +0000" stop="20250724160255 +0000">
    <title>Dr.Phil</title>
    <sub-title>A Stranger Obsessed with Our Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E138</episode-num>
    <desc>April says another woman is electronically stealing photos of her children and posing as their mother online.</desc>
    <date>20160511</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14138.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724160255 +0000" stop="20250724164756 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Will Ashley Confess? (Pt 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E318</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil continues his conversation with husband and wife, Nathan and April, who claim a woman named Ashley is fixated on their beautiful twin daughters.</desc>
    <date>20160512</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14318.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724164756 +0000" stop="20250724173137 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Homeless and “Engaged” to Putin?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman believes she's going to be Vladimir Putin's wife.</desc>
    <date>20191111</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L18035.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724173137 +0000" stop="20250724181831 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Marriage Dilemmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E48</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil's guests say they saw several red flags before they walked down the aisle, but they looked the other way and still said, "I do."</desc>
    <date>20080410</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5048.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724181831 +0000" stop="20250724190306 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>“Is My Nigerian Boyfriend Scamming Me?”</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E66</episode-num>
    <desc>Sixty-four-year-old Josie says she met the love of her life, Victor, on Facebook. Even though he’s Nigerian, 30 years younger, and she’s never physically met him, she insists it’s true love. She’s purchased a ticket to Nigeria and hopes to marry Victor, but her older sister, Carmen, her best friend, Angela, and her 19-year-old son, Anthony, say Josie is acting like a teenage fool. They believe Victor is conning Josie into marrying him for a green card. Dr. Phil took cameras to Nigeria to find Victor to see if he’s telling Josie the truth. Josie’s family says they want Dr. Phil to convince Josie that this relationship will never work. Is Victor who he says he is, and will Josie leave for Nigeria after hearing what Dr. Phil has to say?</desc>
    <date>20190208</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L17066_V2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724190306 +0000" stop="20250724195058 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Angry Women, Scared Husbands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E100</episode-num>
    <desc>You may know that one in four women will become a victim of domestic violence, but did you know that one in nine men will too? Violence against men is rarely talked about and under-reported. Dr. Phil continues his campaign to end the silence on domestic violence with two couples willing to open up about their abusive relationships. Steve says his wife, Monica, punches him and recently pushed him down a flight of stairs. He says he’s not only afraid of her abuse, he’s afraid of how he may retaliate in the heat of anger. The couple has nine children between them – two of whom are severely disabled – and they’re worried about the effect their explosive arguments have on their kids. Then, Charlie worries she’ll get so angry at her new husband, Gary, that she’ll lash out and inadvertently kill him. Gary says that everything he does makes his wife mad, and he just can’t win. Can these women learn to control their tempers and stop the chaos before something tragic happens? Learn more about Dr. Phil’s End the Silence on Domestic Violence campaign and pledge to become a silence breaker!</desc>
    <date>20110527</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L9100.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724195058 +0000" stop="20250724203851 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Sugar Baby Students</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Phil investigates the latest trend in online dating: sugar babies hooking up with sugar daddies. College girls and recent graduates who are struggling with mounting debt and a weak job market are turning to websites, such as SeekingArrangement.com, that introduce them to wealthy men who, in exchange for companionship - and maybe sex - help them pay their bills. Is this the Internet version of the world's oldest profession, or just a niche dating site? Four self-proclaimed sugar babies: Kristen, 21, Jennifer, 28, Janelle, 30, and Tracy, 31, passionately defend why their relationships differ from prostitution. Are their arranged monthly allowances and extravagant gifts the equivalent of being taken to fancy restaurants by a boyfriend or financially supported by a husband? Meet the creator of the website, Brandon, and hear why he says there's nothing wrong with these "mutually beneficial relationships." Former prosecutor and CNN analyst Sunny Hostin has some legal words of warning for Brandon and the ladies. Plus, an outraged father confronts Brandon in defense of his daughter, who he recently learned is on the site, and see why a self-proclaimed proud sugar daddy makes a hasty exit before meeting Dr. Phil!</desc>
    <date>20110916</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10007.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724203851 +0000" stop="20250724211607 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>49-Year-Old Dad Dating Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Joni claims that Gina used to be one of her besties and that they were inseparable, from spending birthday trips out of town to girls’ nights out, often ending in Gina crashing at Joni’s house. Joni says all that changed when 23- year-old Gina began dating Joni’s 49-year-old father, David, behind her back and giving birth to David’s child. Joni says she feels betrayed by Gina and her father, even going as far as sharing her dislike for her former friend and father’s newfound romance on TikTok. Gina says the picture Joni paints of them being best friends is all a lie, but in any event, Joni needs to accept her relationship with Joni’s father. David says despite his daughter’s disapproval, he is going to continue being in a committed relationship with Gina, but that doesn’t mean he can’t also have a relationship with his daughter.</desc>
    <date>20201019</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L19024.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724211607 +0000" stop="20250724220113 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Cougars And Sugar Daddies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When it comes to dating, they say age is just a number. But what happens when the man is more than two decades older than his girlfriend, or the woman is 15 years older than her young lover? Forty-year-old Sanjay is a wealthy cosmetic surgeon who met 18-year-old Jacqueline on the Web site SugarDaddie.com. They’ve only been together for four months and are already talking marriage. Sanjay’s friend, Mike, is convinced that Jacqueline will put him right in the poorhouse! Is there a chance that Sanjay has found true love, or is Jacqueline just in it for the money? Then, 24-year-old Ryan is engaged to Angela, a woman 15 years his senior. Ryan’s friend, Donovan, fears that Angela is alienating Ryan from his buddies. Will Ryan have to choose between his college friends and his soon-to-be wife?</desc>
    <date>20061108</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L5010.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724220113 +0000" stop="20250724224939 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Older Teacher &amp; Younger Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E119</episode-num>
    <desc>Does love really conquer all? James, 41, quit his job and left his wife and three children to pursue a relationship with his 18-year-old former student, Jordan. The couple says they're not breaking any laws, want to set the record straight with Dr. Phil, and want Jordan's mother, Tammie, to stop her Facebook "smear campaign" against them. In a national exclusive, Tammie confronts James for the first time on Dr. Phil’s stage. Find out how the attraction began and why Tammie says James is lying. Were there secret meetings before Jordan turned 18? And, what does Jordan stand to lose? Parents, how would you react if your child started a relationship with his or her former teacher?</desc>
    <date>20120303</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10119.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724224939 +0000" stop="20250724233657 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And Illegal?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E58</episode-num>
    <desc>Thirty-year-old mother of four Melissa Dilan-Hernandez made headlines when she was charged with unlawful sexual activity with certain minors, stemming from her relationship with her fiancé, T.J., who is 17 years old and the father of her 4-month-old child. Melissa is facing up to 15 years in prison and may have to register as a sex offender, yet she says she still doesn’t consider their relationship a crime. How does she justify her love affair with a minor -- and planning a pregnancy with him? T.J. says he wants to spend the rest of his life with Melissa -- but is he willing to wait for her if she goes to jail? And, could their romance stand in the way of his aspirations of becoming a U.S. Marine or police officer? T.J.’s father, Ed, and stepmother, Sea, weigh in with their thoughts on the relationship. Do they approve? Plus, don’t miss Dr. Phil’s stern advice for Melissa and T.J. -- and for any teen who may be blindsided by love.</desc>
    <date>20121120</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L11058.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250724233657 +0000" stop="20250725002158 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Regret Marrying Older Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E59</episode-num>
    <desc>Brenda says she fell in love with and married her husband, Don – despite their 26-year age gap. But soon after, she claims her “Prince Charming” turned “crazy” and “temperamental.” Is their age difference at the root of their issues? Then, Bev says she’s concerned for her sister, Melanie, who married her much younger man, Devar, after meeting him on a Jamaican vacation. Is Devar in it for love, or for a green card and money? And, Dr. Phil catches up with best-selling author Mitch Albom.</desc>
    <date>20151210</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L14059.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725002158 +0000" stop="20250725010856 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>The Cougar Craze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E105</episode-num>
    <desc>Demi Moore did it. So did Madonna and Halle Berry. This trend of older women dating younger men is called the Cougar Craze, and it’s sweeping the country. Recently, at a New York speed-dating event, "Sugar Mamas and Boy Toys," good-looking 35-year-old men wooed women over 35 who made at least $500,000 a year. Jeremy organized the event and says he was just answering a demand from affluent ladies. Was he sincere in his matchmaking or just out to make a buck? Dr. Phil talks to two women who participated in the event -- Gail, 44 and Nancy, 50. Their experiences might surprise you. Then, 51-year-old Kat says she’s no cougar; she just likes to date younger guys because men her age are set in their ways. She says her 23-year-old ex-boyfriend, Ryon, was loving, passionate and had a much higher libido than older men. Her friend, Nancy, says Kat has a great head for business, but a bad one when it comes to the opposite sex. She says young men just see dollar signs when they see Kat. Is Kat dating down, or should Nancy just butt out? And, Bobbi had an 11-year relationship with a man who was 17 years her junior, but she says once she turned 50, he saw her as too old. She wants to be in a relationship again, but not with an older man. Her son, Nathan, says someone still wet behind the ears can’t appreciate all Bobbi has to offer. Does Nathan have the right to put his foot down with his mother? Do you think it's OK for older women to date younger men? Take our poll!</desc>
    <date>20080502</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L6105.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
<programme channel="5e20b730f2f8d5003d739db7-66e4cbef38de9754b6b13e90" start="20250725010856 +0000" stop="20250725015654 +0000">
    <title>Dr. Phil</title>
    <sub-title>Shocking Love Stories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E317</episode-num>
    <desc>At 36, Lisa fell in love with her sons’ 14-year-old friend, Adrian. By the time he was 15, they were married and Lisa was pregnant with their first child. Seven years and two kids later, they're still together. Will their love last? And, learn how a former Arizona gubernatorial candidate went looking for international love but wound up homeless on the streets of Ukraine.</desc>
    <date>20120402</date>
    <icon src="https://partner-upload-assets.wurl.com/peteski_productions_inc/DR_PHIL_L10317.jpg" />
  </programme>
  
</tv>
