<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250726095303 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403490/20250726.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403490&amp;date=20250726&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403490">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726000000 +0000" stop="20250726020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Three Wise Men and a Baby</title>
    <desc>Three brothers get the surprise of their lives when they are forced to work together and care for a baby over the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726020000 +0000" stop="20250726040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Santa Tell Me</title>
    <desc>A design show host finds a letter from Santa promising to meet her true love, a man named Nick, by Christmas Eve. Meeting three Nicks complicates her search.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726040000 +0000" stop="20250726060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Biltmore Christmas</title>
    <desc>A magical hourglass sends modern-day screenwriter Lucy Hardgrove to the set of the 1947 holiday movie classic "His Merry Wife!" However, before she can return to the present, Lucy must make things right or threaten to alter the future forever.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726060000 +0000" stop="20250726080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haul Out the Holly</title>
    <desc>Emily comes home to visit her parents, only to discover they're leaving for a trip of their own. While staying at their house for the holidays, Emily meets members of the community who want her to join in the neighborhood's Christmas festivities.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726080000 +0000" stop="20250726100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">An Unexpected Christmas</title>
    <desc>A speech writer makes a deal with his ex-girlfriend to pretend they are a couple to save his family's Christmas. It's not long before both the ruse and their feelings catch up with them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726100000 +0000" stop="20250726120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas in Evergreen</title>
    <desc>Hoping to spur her longtime beau to action, a small-town veterinarian wishes upon a snow globe that this will be her most romantic Christmas ever.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726120000 +0000" stop="20250726140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Snow Bride</title>
    <desc>A tabloid reporter races to find juicy gossip on a prominent political family. She ends up spending the week before Christmas with the family and falls for one of their sons.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726140000 +0000" stop="20250726160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Veteran's Christmas</title>
    <desc>Capt. Grace Garland, a decorated U.S. veteran, returns home after two tours of search and rescue in Afghanistan. After being separated from her beloved K9 partner, Grace must rediscover the magic of Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726160000 +0000" stop="20250726180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crown for Christmas</title>
    <desc>After getting fired from her job as a maid at a ritzy New York City hotel, a woman accepts a temporary job as governess to a young girl who is part of a powerful European family.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726180000 +0000" stop="20250726200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas by Starlight</title>
    <desc>A lawyer makes a deal with the heir to a development firm to spare her family's restaurant from demolition. However, she must spend the week posing as the legal counsel his father is demanding he hire in the wake of some costly mistakes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726200000 +0000" stop="20250726220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Merry Scottish Christmas</title>
    <desc>When estranged siblings Lindsay and Brad Morgan travel to Scotland at Christmas to reunite with their mother Jo, a big family secret is revealed.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250726220000 +0000" stop="20250727000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Royal Holiday</title>
    <desc>When Anna offers a stranded mother and son shelter from a blizzard, she learns that they are the royal family of Galwick and that they are both in need of a little Christmas magic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727000000 +0000" stop="20250727020100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwrapping Christmas: Olivia's Reunion</title>
    <desc>Desperate to make it back home in time for the Christmas Gala, Olivia gets snowed-in with her ex-boyfriend while delivering gifts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727020100 +0000" stop="20250727040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwrapping Christmas: Mia's Prince</title>
    <desc>Romance novel enthusiast Mia meets Beau, a philanthropist, who is the spitting image of her favorite book hero. As they consider exploring a new romance, Beau's mother has other ideas.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727040100 +0000" stop="20250727060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holiday Crashers</title>
    <desc>Best friends Toni and Bri have worked at the same card shop for more years than they should as both struggle to find their true life's path. Toni and Bri decide to create new identities to crash the Christmas parties.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727060100 +0000" stop="20250727080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas Next Door</title>
    <desc>Eric Randall, an author of bachelor lifestyle books, is left in charge of his young niece and nephew for the holidays. Unsure of himself, Eric turns to his neighbor April, a lover of all things Christmas, for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727080000 +0000" stop="20250727100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holiday Hearts</title>
    <desc>While planning an annual Christmas party, Peyton is forced together with Ben to care for a friend's daughter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727100000 +0000" stop="20250727120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Christmas Train</title>
    <desc>A cynical journalist must get from Washington, D.C., to Los Angeles in time for Christmas, and his only option is to take the train.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727120000 +0000" stop="20250727140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas With Holly</title>
    <desc>The owner (Eloise Mumford) of a toy store falls in love with a man (Sean Faris) who cares for his orphaned niece.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727140000 +0000" stop="20250727160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Nine Kittens of Christmas</title>
    <desc>Cat lovers Zachary and Marilee are thrown back together at Christmastime when they're tasked with finding homes for a litter of adorable kittens.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727160000 +0000" stop="20250727180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cross Country Christmas</title>
    <desc>When a snowstorm disrupts both Lina's and Max's holiday plans, they realize they must work together to find a way home -- without taking it out on each other.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727180000 +0000" stop="20250727200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Following Yonder Star</title>
    <desc>A former television star waits out a scandal in Vermont. She becomes close with the innkeeper and his daughter while she helps him direct the local Christmas pageant.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727200000 +0000" stop="20250727220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Christmas Detour</title>
    <desc>Two travelers become linked when a snowstorm grounds their flight in Buffalo. Paige desperately needs to find a way to New York City to meet her fiance's parents, and it's up to Dylan, a fellow passenger and a guy she can't stand, to get her there.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250727220000 +0000" stop="20250728000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwrapping Christmas: Olivia's Reunion</title>
    <desc>Desperate to make it back home in time for the Christmas Gala, Olivia gets snowed-in with her ex-boyfriend while delivering gifts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250728000000 +0000" stop="20250729000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holidazed</title>
    <desc>In the Manetti-Hanahan family, there's never a silent night at Christmastime; this year, Connie wants peace and asks her husband Chuck to put aside his neighborhood rivalry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-28</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
